You are safe here
with me.
Has a decision been reached
on how far this country
would be willing to go
in helping an anti-Castro
uprising or invasion in Cuba?
Well,
first, I want to say that
there will not be,
under any conditions,
an intervention in Cuba
by United States armed forces.
And this government
will do everything
it possibly can,
and I think it can meet
its responsibilities,
to make sure that there are
no Americans involved
in any actions inside Cuba.
Excuse me, sir.
Do you have change
for a dollar?
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
From our friends
on Wall Street. Miami?
Right away.
Cardinal is interested.
So, the weatherman
says Sunday is a perfect day
for a trip to the beach.
I hope
you can still dance, Edward.
Couple of days,
we'll be doing the cha-cha
in EI Comandante's bedroom.
I'll try to remember
to bring my dancing shoes,
Richard.
Morning, Ray.
Mr. Hayes.
Miami, and our op center
off Guatemala.
Pack a bathing suit,
Mr. Brocco.
We're going for a swim.
What do you make
of our chances for success?
If we get the support
that we've been promised,
I'd say it's fairly certain.
But if there are any doubts,
I can still put out the fire.
It's gone beyond that.
Rocking Chair
is still smiling.
It's the White House.
Everybody's waiting
for the good news.
Godspeed.
When you're back,
come up to the mountains.
We'll go fishing.
Yes, sir.
He's been put on notice.
In Cuba,
sometime before dawn,
the invading forces'
B-26 bombers give air cover
to men landing on the beach.
As the sun rises,
there is a surprise attack
from Castro's air force.
The B-26es are shot down.
Without air cover,
the anti-Castro force's ships
are attacked.
And the men are cut off
from their supplies.
The situation looks dire.
"Where is the air support?
"Where the hell is the Navy?
"Could you throw something
into this vital point
in the battle?
"Enemy in Red...
Trucks coming from Red Beach
"are right now
one kilometer from Blue Beach.
"Two thousand militia
attacking Blue Beach
from east to west.
"We need close air support
immediately.
"Well, I am destroying
all my equipment
and communications.
"I have nothing
with which to fight.
I am going to the woods.
"I cannot wait for you.
I am going to the woods."
They knew
where to find us.
There's a stranger
in our house, sir.
I love you.
People who really love
each other don't have secrets.
You are safe here with me.
I love you.
People who really love
each other don't have secrets.
You are safe here with me.
You have such a...
I love you.
People who really love
each other don't have secrets.
You are safe here with me.
The President's saying
he's going to break the CIA
into a thousand pieces.
Somebody on your desk
gave away the store.
Told the Soviets
where to find you
at the Bay of Pigs.
You got a big problem,
very close to home.
There's gonna be
an extensive house-cleaning
on your side of the street.
Fucking cigarettes.
My ring doesn't even
fit me anymore.
They didn't get it all.
I'm sorry.
Be careful.
Your name is
on a "must worry" list,
right at the very top.
You forgot your hat.
Somebody left
a package on my doorstep
last night.
Have Tech wash them
right away.
I've been trying to reach you.
I haven't been staying
at the Embassy compound.
I've been doing
some outside work.
I heard there was a setback.
Sometimes the best-laid plans
of mice and men...
Be very careful.
I'll be fine.
You worry too much.
Just please be careful.
Everything's fine.
Goodbye, Son.
Goodbye, Father.
We sail the ocean blue
I'm called little Buttercup
Dear little Buttercup
Though I could never tell why
But still I'm called Buttercup
Poor little Buttercup
Sweet little Buttercup, I
I've treacle and toffee
I've tea and I've coffee
But hark ye, my merry friend,
hast ever thought
that beneath this gay
and frivolous
exterior
there may lurk a
cankerworm?
Miss Buttercup.
Skull and Bones.
Accept or reject?
Accept.
Not a word to anyone.
How does it feel
being a woman?
Why do you want to know?
Gentlemen,
I will remind you,
you have all taken
an oath of secrecy.
You have been chosen
to become members of
America's most secret society.
For over 100 years,
Skull and Bones members
have included a President,
Vice Presidents,
Supreme Court justices,
congressmen and senators,
captains of science
and industry.
The very best of America.
I don't think
this is for me.
You can't take it
personally.
Getting pissed on is personal,
Mr. Russell.
I take it very personally.
Edward, we're all
in this together.
Come back inside.
We're brothers for life.
Tell us, Mr. Wilson, brother
to brother, something you've
never told anyone before.
Your most guarded secret.
Something you will need
to trust us with.
It was
the Fourth of July, 1925.
I was six.
I was playing tag
with a friend of mine.
Edward, careful.
And I tried to get away from
him, so I ran up the stairs
into my parents' room
and I hid in the closet.
I looked at my father's
clothes, and hanging there
was his Admiral's jacket.
And then I heard a sound.
And I saw my father.
And I must have made a noise,
because he turned,
and came into the closet
and opened the door.
Have you ever
made up a story, Edward?
Told your friends something
you knew wasn't true,
and you know that if they
found out, they wouldn't
like you anymore?
Why? Because
you lied to them.
Do you understand?
And he asked me
if I knew what trust was.
And I said,
"Trust is when you feel safe
with someone."
Like with my friends.
Like with you and Mother.
And then he said,
"Don't ever lie.
"If you lie to your friends,
they won't trust you.
"And you will have nothing
"and you'll never be safe."
He told me to go downstairs
and watch the fireworks,
because they'd started.
And then he shut the door.
The sound of the gunshot
was very different from
the sound of the fireworks.
And even at six years old,
I knew there was
a big, big difference.
There was a lot of blood.
Father?
And in his left hand,
he held a note
that was sealed.
I don't know why,
but I took the note
and I put it in my pocket.
I always said
it was an accident.
It wasn't an accident.
My father killed himself.
Congratulations, Mr. Wilson.
I'm Richard Hayes,
Master of Secrets and Orders.
What did the note say?
I told you,
I never read the note.
You didn't read the note?
No.
My father said your father
was going to be appointed
Secretary of the Navy
until his loyalty
was brought under question.
We're not gonna have a problem
with your loyalty, are we?
"And yet,
a certain word,
a glance, a guise
"Will mirror never show,
reflecting not my gaze
"But my uncertain question
caught
"Inside a shadow
of our shifting eyes?"
That really is quite elegant,
Mr. Wilson.
Good order. Very precise.
Feeling of the unknown.
Fine poetry is the music
of mathematics.
Numbers singing.
You have to look
behind the words
to understand their meaning.
Right. Well, good night,
gentlemen.
Mr. Wilson?
May I see you in my office
for a few words?
I'm recommending you as editor
of our poetry magazine,
The Poeticus.
I'm honored. Thank you.
I appreciate your faith in me.
Never be ashamed
of your abilities, Edward.
Wasn't there a picture
that used to sit
on the mantel, there?
It was a group of soldiers?
It's my father's
Crimean War regiment.
The glass broke.
I'm having it mended.
I remembered it because
it reminded me of my father.
He was in the war.
I think we're being watched.
Being watched?
What do you mean?
There's a man in a hat.
I don't see anybody.
You know, there's so much
I'd like to share with you,
Edward.
But I hardly know anything
about you at all,
apart from you being
a particularly bright student.
I feel that we have
a kind of kindred spirit.
I really should be going.
Oh, I've started
to write something.
Perhaps you'd like
to hear it.
"A bud has burst
on the upper bough
"The linnet sang
in my heart today
"I know where the pale green
grasses show
"By a tiny runnel,
off the way
"And the earth is wet
"A cuckoo said in my brain,
'Not yet, not yet"'
I haven't finished it.
Excuse me.
Please.
I'm sorry. I can't hear.
What's your name?
Edward.
I'm sorry.
Would you say it again?
I have to read your lips.
Edward.
Hello, Edward.
I'm Laura.
I'm sorry,
would you say that again?
There isn't one person
in a hundred who would walk
by a hat on a bench
without giving it
a second look.
That says a lot about you,
Mr. Wilson.
You don't distract easily.
She's a very pretty girl.
Sam Murach. I'm with
the Federal Bureau
of Investigation.
Mind if I walk along with you?
I had a chance to have a talk
with a fraternity brother
of yours.
John Russell,
the senator's son.
John said you might help us.
You're friendly
with Dr. Fredericks?
He's my thesis advisor,
if that's what you mean.
He's been recruiting faculty
members and students
to join an organization called
the American German
Cultural Committee.
It's a Nazi front.
Has he talked to you
about that?
I'm a poetry student,
Mr. Murach.
I'm not political.
We'd be very interested
in finding out the names of
some of the other organizers
for the Cultural Committee.
Are you asking me to spy
on Dr. Fredericks?
I'm asking you
to be a good citizen.
You blow that thing up,
it'll be fine.
I'll be seeing you.
In Poland, Hitler watches
German regiments
stream across the river San.
This was part
of the river line which
the invading army forced
in its flanking drive
through southern Poland.
The Nazi Führer
makes a quick tour
in the conquered nation
among the soldiers
in captured towns.
Hitler has given the word
of war, and war it is!
Poland has been guaranteed...
Ladies and gentlemen, it is
a great privilege to have with
us here tonight Mr. Haupt,
the Führer's
Education Minister.
Mr. Haupt?
Good evening.
Thank you, Dr. Fredericks
and members of the American
German Cultural Committee,
for giving me the opportunity
to come to Yale.
Germany has always been
a country of...
Yes. Interesting.
It has been
a great pleasure...
...making
new acquaintances...
Excuse me.
Of course.
Someone's in here!
Are you enjoying yourself,
Edward?
Very much so.
I'd like you
to meet Mr. Haupt.
- You know Dr. Manheim?
- Yes, we've met.
I've been asked by the faculty
chairman to relinquish
my post here at Yale.
Now, you'll hear many reasons
for what caused my departure.
Suffice it to say I'm leaving
with my name intact.
Good luck in your endeavors.
Now, Edward,
what did I do
to deserve this?
Have you such little regard
for me that you'd betray me
for my political beliefs?
You know and I know
Trumbull Stickney
wrote that poem in 1902.
You were my teacher.
You betrayed me.
I thought
we were going to a party.
You want to protect me
from them, don't you?
No.
You think they'll make
fun of me.
That's not it.
That's not true.
It's okay.
I'm happy to be with you.
Would you like to dance?
I'm not a very good dancer.
That's all right.
I'm not a good dancer either.
How does this song go?
Blue skies
Smiling on me
Nothing but blue skies
Do I see
Excuse me, everybody,
I have an announcement.
I've just been told
England and France
declared war on Germany.
But please continue dancing
and enjoying our music.
And I'll update you
as information comes in.
Thank you.
Before long,
we'll be at war, too.
Would you like to get
a room for us?
Umm...
Turn down the light.
I can't. I can't.
Good night.
Thank you, Edward.
For what?
For being so nice.
In view of the fact
we're taking a propaganda
lambasting around the world,
why is it not useful, sir,
for us to explore with you
the real facts behind this,
or our motivations?
There's an old saying that
victory has a hundred fathers
and defeat is an orphan.
And I wouldn't be surprised
if information poured
in here regarding...
Hello, Edward.
What are you doing here?
There were only a handful
of us until moment zero
who knew where we were
going to land in Cuba.
One of us
couldn't keep a secret.
I know it wasn't me.
Mr. Allen asked for
the Zapata list of personnel
who participated
in the operation.
I don't have one.
Tell Mr. Allen I'll give him
the list personally.
We're in the same boat
together.
A leaky boat.
Don't ever think
we're in the same boat,
Mr. Hayes.
We're either going to sink
or swim together.
People like us,
we don't let each other drown.
I have said as much as I feel
can be usefully said by me
in regard to the events
of the past few days.
Further statements,
detailed discussions,
are not
to conceal responsibility,
because I'm the responsible
officer of the government...
Mother, Father.
This is Edward Wilson.
Mrs. Russell.
Hello.
Senator.
Yes. It's a pleasure
to finally meet you.
Phillip and Toddy Allen.
Mr. Allen was
President of Bones,
Class of '12.
Welcome to
our little clubhouse.
Thank you.
Where's Clover?
Oh, there she is.
I think so. Yes.
This is my sister, Clover.
Hello, I'm Edward.
Nice to meet you.
Bonesmen!
- All here!
Reverend Collins
will offer grace.
Bonesmen first,
God second.
Dear God,
we thank you for guiding
the Evans Family Trust
in the care
of our beloved island,
so that we may come here
with our families
and our friends
in comfort and in privacy.
He said he was gonna
ask me to dance later.
Here we go.
Don't you dance, Mr. Wilson?
Nobody asked me.
Well,
I think I'll take my chances.
I'm asking.
John is very fond of you.
And I'm very fond of him.
He's talking of going off
to fight with the English.
My father isn't particularly
pleased about it
because he's
one of the organizers
of America First.
Wouldn't look very good
for an isolationist's son
to go off to war, would it?
Your brother John is a man
of great conviction.
I admire him.
And what about you,
Mr. Wilson?
What do you believe in?
Are you in school?
You don't say very much,
do you?
When there's something
worth saying.
Oh! Well.
I think I'm going to like you.
Mr. Hayes.
Gentlemen.
General William Sullivan,
Mr. Edward Wilson.
It's a great honor, sir.
I'd get up and shake
your hand, but my fucking
feet are killing me.
Something about too much sugar
in my blood and my urine.
So when do you boys start
your pissing contest?
I'll excuse myself.
Thank you, Phillip.
Why don't you sit down?
You understand that whatever
we discuss here
doesn't leave this room.
Of course.
We'll eventually
get involved in this war.
Not because we want to,
but because we have to,
and we should.
And the President has asked me
to look into creating a
Foreign Intelligence Service.
And if that happens,
I'll be looking for patriotic,
honorable, bright young men
from the right backgrounds
to manage
the various departments.
In other words,
no Jews or Negroes,
and very few Catholics,
and that's only because
I'm a Catholic.
You'd be trained
and commissioned in the Army
and posted overseas.
If it's something
you're interested in,
you have to be ready to leave
at a moment's notice.
I don't want your answer now.
Just think about it.
But this isn't a bunch of
fraternity boys sitting around
playing with their pricks.
This is for real.
For America.
Have fun.
And behave yourselves.
I'm supposed to be looking
for the perfect husband.
Are you the perfect husband,
Mr. Wilson?
Perfect in every way.
Then is there some reason
that you won't put
your arm around me?
Day and night
Night and day
You are the one
I like this.
Very smart.
And under the sun
...near to me
Do you have a problem
with women, Mr. Bones?
Do you love me?
What?
Tell me you love me.
I love you.
Do you love me?
I do. I love you. I...
I still don't believe you.
I love you.
Say it. Say it.
I think I love you...
Look at me.
Look at me! Stop. Stop.
Tell me!
I love you!
I think I love you.
As soon as the world
comes to its senses,
I'm going to travel.
London. Paris. Rome.
You can come with me.
Is everything all right?
Fine.
We're worlds apart.
What do you mean?
I feel like
I'm just a curiosity to you.
That is not...
That's not true.
I feel like
I'm not real to you.
That is not true.
Edward.
That is not
how I feel about you.
Edward?
John.
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
My sister.
She's pregnant.
I know you'll do
what's expected of you.
Do you,
Edward Bell Wilson,
take Margaret Ann Russell
to be your
lawfully wedded wife?
To love, honor and cherish
in sickness and in health
in good times
and in bad times,
until death do you part?
I do.
I now pronounce you
man and wife.
A man in uniform
wants to see you.
Excuse me, Mother.
Did your mother and I
ever tell you where
we took our honeymoon?
Mr. Edward Wilson?
If we could
speak alone, sir.
Would you like to sit down?
No, thank you, sir.
General Sullivan
sends his regards.
He wanted to ask you, sir,
if you're still interested in
seeing the rest of the world.
Yes, I certainly would be.
Good afternoon, sir.
Thank you.
My orders came through.
I'll be going overseas.
When?
In one week.
What are you going to do,
Edward? Save the world?
You are safe
here with me.
The photograph
is particularly dark.
As we can see,
there is a Caucasian man
and a Negro woman.
The resolution breaks down
pretty quickly.
The film stock
is definitely Russian,
low grade.
One of the areas
we've been focusing on
is the mosquito netting.
Mosquito netting
is predominantly in Africa,
Southeast Asia,
any tropical climate.
The window curtains here
have a distinctive pattern
on them of baobab trees,
also seen in Africa.
Next to the curtains,
we can see
the building's balustrade.
There's a pigeon here.
It's kind of hard to make out.
Pigeons are mostly found
in urban areas, town squares.
If you listen closely,
you'll hear an airplane.
We've washed it out.
By the sound of the thrust
of the jet engines,
we can determine that
it's a plane taking off,
and more than 1,000 feet
off the ground,
which would further suggest
a large urban area.
On this section of the tape,
when you clear out
background noise,
you can hear a female voice.
I love you.
People who really love
each other don't have secrets.
You are safe here with me.
Assuming we're talking about
the same woman,
the linguists tell us
her accent is French.
There's one word here,
we can't make it out yet.
There's an unidentifiable
noise washing her out.
It plays
throughout the recording
at a high frequency,
suggesting an air-raid siren
of some sort.
We're gonna keep
playing with it.
This is a time
for everyone to stand together
and hold firm
as they are doing.
I express my admiration
for the exemplary manner
in which all the air-raid
precaution services of London
are being discharged.
- May I help you?
- Yes.
I'm here to see the tailor
about a fitting
for a new suit.
Certainly. And what
kind of suit would you be
interested in this evening?
A tweed or worsted?
Perhaps a nice gabardine?
Perhaps a worsted
and a tweed.
Both single-breasted?
Yes.
Two or three buttons, sir?
Three buttons.
If you might come this way,
please, sir.
Please. Our senior tailor
will be right with you, sir.
Thank you.
Welcome to London.
You're going to have to learn
as quickly and thoroughly
as possible
the English system
of intelligence.
The black arts.
Particularly
counterintelligence.
The uses of information,
disinformation,
and how their use is,
ultimately, power.
They've agreed to open
their operations to us.
They can't win the war
without us, but they don't
really want us here.
Intelligence is their
mother's milk and they don't
like sharing the royal tit
with people
who don't have titles.
Your London tutor is waiting
to meet you.
This way, sir.
...six-five megacycles
at one, three, five, nine.
Eight point
seven-six-five megacycles
at one, three, five, nine.
Four, two,
zero, seven. Standing by.
...point
seven-six-five megacycles
at one, three, five, nine.
I should have known better
than to use Stickney.
Job well done, Mr. Wilson.
You blew a two-year operation
for me.
I told General Sullivan
to keep an eye on you.
Just as well, really.
I was beginning to long
for the bone-chilling cold
of home.
It isn't personal.
Mr. Carlson? Is this
the American Trade Bureau?
Which product?
Dry goods.
You're late.
Yeah.
That's what my mother said.
Raymond Duca Brocco,
born May 8, 1907,
New York City.
St. Ignatius High School,
Fordham University.
Married Anita Delvecchio,
two children...
Stephanie and David.
Six-foot-two, 182 pounds,
black hair, brown eyes.
Military record,
five years Intelligence.
Anything you'd like to add?
Do you want to
look up my ass, too?
You're working for me,
Sergeant Brocco.
I'm working for the
United States government, sir.
In this office, I am
the United States government.
You're pretty sure of yourself
for somebody who just began.
They wouldn't
tell me your name.
Then how do you know
you're not in the wrong place?
They said you were
a serious SOB that didn't
have any sense of humor.
There can't be two of you.
Are you going to answer it?
Depends if I'm working for you
or if I'm not.
One of your jobs, Sergeant,
is answering the telephone.
Yes, sir.
Use your tradecraft well,
particularly the use
of black propaganda
and the ingredient
known as playback.
Understanding how effectively
your own disinformation
is actually working
on the enemy.
It's almost four.
How do you spell syphilis?
Is it one "L" or two?
Syphilis. One, I think.
I never had it.
It's vital to penetrate
the enemy's
intelligence services.
Push them into
an unreal world, as it were.
Doctors in England today
announced that medical records
taken from Adolf Hitler's
personal physician,
Dr. Theodor Morell,
revealed that Mr. Hitler
had contracted syphilis
while serving
in the German armed forces
during World War I.
The very qualities
that make
a good intelligence officer,
a suspicious mind,
a love of complexity
and detail,
are the very qualities
of someone
you'll be observing.
Good evening, Lord Cooper.
I have some information
that might be of interest
to you.
The mental
facility to detect
conspiracies and betrayal
are the same qualities
most likely to corrode
natural judgment.
Everything that seems clear
is bent. And everything
that seems bent is clear.
Trapped in reflections,
you must learn to recognize
when a lie masquerades
as the truth,
and then deal with it
efficiently, dispassionately.
We know you've
been passing information
to the German High Command.
Never give anyone
time to think.
Now, I'm going to offer you
one of two choices.
You set the tone
of the discussion
and quickly come to the point.
Either you can be executed
for treason,
or you can continue to spy
for the enemy here
and provide them
with the information
we provide you with.
Pass this on
to your German friends. And
if I find out it wasn't done,
there won't be
a second chance.
You'll quite simply
be hanged as a spy.
Do we understand each other?
How do we know
he won't be working
for two masters?
Precisely. We don't.
How do I know
if I can even trust you?
You won't.
I mean, I hope
you're lucky enough
to meet someone you trust.
I regret to say
I haven't.
You must be young Edward.
Dr. Fredericks has told me
so much about you.
Arch Cummings.
Nice to meet you.
I understand we're of
a like mind on many things.
Good schoolboys,
Yale, Cambridge.
Dreamers.
They say to be an exceptional
intelligence officer,
you have to have
a steady mind,
an unwavering sense of belief
in what you're doing,
and be a hopeless romantic.
American Trade Bureau.
It's overseas,
a Senator Russell for you.
Hello?
Yes. Yeah.
Yes, I can hear you.
Thank you for telling me.
Goodbye.
We had a boy.
Would you mind
if we called him Edward? If we
called him Edward Junior?
I love that.
I think it's perfect.
Fit for a king.
That's what I was thinking.
You like Edward?
I think he likes it.
So, how are you? Are you
saving the world
and keeping us safe?
Sometimes.
What color are his eyes?
Hello?
When he's old enough,
you can read it to him.
It's a first edition.
Charles Dickens'
A Christmas Carol.
It was my father's.
He would read it to me
when I was a boy.
Thank you.
I had an unfortunate
discovery today.
A man that works for me,
sat just outside my door.
I found out he had given
a rose to a woman
with a small note.
The rose was quite lovely,
an Abyssinian rose,
its stem neatly wrapped
in silk paper. All quite
beautiful and touching,
save for the fact that the
paper was filled with secret
writing for her German friends
detailing changes
to the American order
of battle here.
Excuse me, sir.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
How did the Irish poet say it?
"A friend for today
is tomorrow's heartbreak."
Do you know
what my deepest fear is?
That I will end up friendless.
Completely alone.
I think you two
know each other.
Richard. I didn't expect
to see you.
Hello, Edward.
Mr. Hayes has come over
to work with us
in Special Operations.
I hope you don't mind,
I've invited him to join
our conversation.
I'm afraid our dear English
teacher has a bad habit
of making easy friendships.
You know, of course,
about his particular
sexual tastes.
I'm afraid he's not been
very discriminating
in his partners.
Some people are extremely
worried about his exposure.
I hope you two can help sort
this rather delicate matter
out for us.
This seems to me
to be a problem
for the British.
Why are we involved?
The British are
a civilized people.
They don't eat their own.
They have somebody
do it for them.
So why are you telling me?
I'm giving you
an opportunity to handle it.
Or somebody else will.
I'm sorry
you've been brought into this.
If the headmaster won't
listen to reason, you might
want to tie your shoe.
I'm sorry
it has to be this way.
It's not something I'm happy
about having to be doing.
Have you thought at all about
maybe going back to teaching
again full-time?
They're concerned about
my personal associations,
aren't they?
Cambridge boys stick together
like glue.
I'm far too democratic
in my tastes for them.
They like pressed trousers
and proper buttons.
No. I've done all the teaching
I intend to do.
I am who I am.
I'll suffer that.
Please. You've given
all the service that you can.
It's time to retire.
The good schoolboy
will be close by.
He'll want to know
my response.
I understand if you want
to tie your shoe.
It's a dirty business, Edward.
I've been part of it
for far too long.
You might want to think
about getting yourself
a new pair of shoes, Edward.
There's a wonderful shop
in St. James'.
Mr. Pettibone's.
He's bootmaker to the King.
But then, I suppose
we all are in our own way,
aren't we?
Bootmakers to kings.
Get out while you still can.
While you still believe.
While you still have a soul.
Hello.
Any of you chaps
got a light?
I'm sorry.
He knew too much.
You understand.
People who really love
each other don't have secrets.
You are safe here with me.
It appears the word
we couldn't make out
had its sound wave
significantly clipped by
whoever made this tape.
We restored it by amplifying
specific frequencies
seen on the oscilloscope.
- Cochinos is Spanish
for "pigs."
- Let me hear it again.
And the siren noise
we couldn't pinpoint before
were hiding church bells.
For some reason,
other noises were added
to distort the bells.
In the makeup table's mirror,
you can actually make out
the reflection
of a church steeple,
whose three belfries
correspond with the bells
you hear.
The volume indicates
that the church
is across the street,
again, possibly
on a town square.
On the nightstand,
we can see a clock radio.
It reads almost 10:00,
which would correspond
with the church bells.
I also have audio
of a ceiling fan.
It's a four-blade,
standard ceiling fan.
We don't know where it's from.
There is something here.
It could be
nothing significant,
maybe a candle, a paperweight.
Or it may be
something personal
that we could identify
the people in the room with.
We're going to wash it again,
maybe see what's there.
How long
until there's some definition
as to exactly where we are?
We're going
as quickly as we can, sir.
- How are Clover
and your little boy?
- Good, thank you.
You know, he's almost five.
You made quite a name
for yourself in London.
The World War is over.
The war for the world
has just begun.
In every liberated country,
there will be a battle between
us and the Russians
for their hearts and minds.
Since we dropped the bomb,
they're feeling a little short
between the legs.
The Russians still live
in the 19th century.
Beets and potatoes.
All that will change
dramatically. Right now,
they're gobbling up territory,
taking home every scientist
they can steal. In 10 years,
they'll have the bomb.
We have to get anyone
that can be useful to us
out of Berlin before they do.
Churchill was right.
We shouldn't have
stopped marching
until we reached Moscow.
They're from Switzerland.
I had them sent
with the pouch to Berlin.
They're a weakness of mine.
When I was a child, my mother
would always reward me
with a chocolate.
It's a dreadful habit.
Chocolates
or seeking approval?
Both.
He was an officer
in the Abwehr,
German Military Intelligence.
He says he knows the location
of certain Nazi V-2
rocket scientists in hiding.
Ask him
where he wants to go.
He wants to go to Chicago.
He has relatives there.
Tell him if he provides us
with the names and locations
of the scientists,
I'll arrange
an exit visa for him.
As soon as he's
served his purpose, turn him
over to the Nazi catchers.
An ex-Waffen-SS Group
Commander would like to speak
with you about asylum.
It's very ugly, isn't it?
It isn't meant to be jewelry.
I lost the sound
in one ear altogether.
I can hear with the help
of the apparatus
out of this ear,
but they say
in one year or so...
You hardly notice it's there.
The Russians
are interested in making
a prisoner swap.
We are prepared to offer you
some Jewish scientists
liberated in the East
for some Nazi scientists
you have here in Berlin.
These are the names
we're willing to discuss.
I understand your cryptonym
for me is Ulysses.
Is that for
the James Joyce book
or the Greek myth?
Do you know
what our code name is for you?
Mother.
I took the first
hot bath yesterday
I've taken in three years,
since the siege of Stalingrad.
I sat for hours,
looking out the window,
soaking.
When I was a soldier,
my fingers were frostbitten.
Since then,
when I get cold,
there is a pain.
Maybe you shouldn't live
in Russia.
We all have our weaknesses.
What is yours?
I had heard you were silent.
"Made of stone," they said.
What is the expression?
"The silence is deafening."
You are going to be
a formidable adversary,
Mother.
I look forward
to our association.
I hope it lasts
for a long time.
I love you.
People who really love
each other don't have secrets.
You are safe here with me.
We were able
to make out the brand
of the fan.
It's called a Froid.
It's Belgian.
The object on the nightstand,
we're still trying to find out
what this is.
We just can't get
any more definition out of it.
Who is this?
Who's this?
Hello, Father.
You have a birthday
coming up.
I'm going to be five soon.
You're a big boy.
I'm bigger than Andrew,
and he's six.
Is your mother there?
What? I can't hear you.
She's getting dressed
to go out with her friend.
He has a new car.
He let me drive with him.
Hello, Mr. Wilson.
This is Edna.
Mrs. Wilson is upstairs.
She's getting ready
for dinner.
I'll tell her
you're on the phone.
I'll call back.
Pardon me.
Do you need me
for anything else?
No, thank you.
Do you ever eat, Mr. Carlson?
I like to cook. Would you like
a home-cooked meal?
Have you ever read Ovid?
Metamorphoses
in the original Latin?
It's quite beautiful.
"I grabbed a pile of dust
and, holding it up,
"foolishly asked for
as many birthdays
as the grains of dust.
"I forgot to ask that
they be years of youth."
Bravo.
I should be going.
Would you like to stay?
Would you like me to?
I would like you to
very much.
Maybe we could go
somewhere together?
The lakes in Bavaria
are still beautiful.
There was an inn there before
the war where they served
breakfast in bed all day.
Hanna?
I hope
you never go home.
Bavaria is really
a beautiful place.
I was born there.
My grandmother lived there.
I really miss her.
Why don't we go?
I let a stranger
into our house.
Mother! Father's here! Mother!
Hello, Edward.
Hello, Clover.
I...
I like to be called
Margaret now.
It's very nice to see you.
It's good to see you, too.
I made something for you.
See? It's a ship.
But it's got
the flag of England.
And then I put
a pirate flag there.
And if you like,
you can count
how many sails there are.
You want to try that?
Fifteen.
That's right.
No, no, it's yours.
I made it for you.
If it's all right with you,
I thought maybe we could sleep
in separate beds for a while,
just until we get
to know each other again.
I made up the spare room.
All right.
What do you hear
from your brother John?
I thought you knew.
He was killed in Burma,
in 1944.
You never mentioned it
in any of your letters.
There wasn't very much to say.
Six years is a long time.
I was lonely
and I was with a man once.
He wasn't very interesting.
Were you with anyone?
It was a mistake.
Thank you for the ship
you made for me.
You're welcome.
I'm glad you like it.
Mother said
you were in the war.
Did you fight?
Did you kill anybody?
No.
Good night.
No! You're it!
Hello, Father.
Hello, Edward. Hello.
Hello, dear.
There's somebody waiting
for you in the den.
General.
Edward.
I'm sorry to barge in on you
like this. Your wife kindly
helped me to a drink.
My feet,
they keep cutting off
pieces of them.
It's not dignified for men
to have to die
from the feet up.
Well, while everybody's been
feeling good about themselves,
the Soviets,
without firing a shot, have
taken over half the world.
They're breathing
down our necks.
They'll be in our backyard
before you know it.
So, I've been telling
the President
about the need to create
a new
Foreign Intelligence Service.
One that would do in peacetime
what OSS did during the war.
Phillip Allen will be heading
the agency. Richard Hayes
will be his exec.
And you'll be taking
Division C,
special operations that report
only to the Director.
It would be limited
to overseas, obviously.
Subversive operations,
intelligence gathering
and analysis.
And I'd be interested
in your thoughts about this.
Particularly in your area
of expertise,
counterintelligence.
I'd be glad to help
in any way I can.
That's all right.
Edward, go outside.
Excuse me, sir. Margaret!
Come on, Edward.
Come. Let's go outside,
all right? Daddy's busy.
Thank you.
I have to tell you,
I have some real problems
with this whole thing,
despite how much we need it.
I'm concerned that
too much power will end up
in the hands of too few.
It's always in somebody's
best interest to promote
enemies, real or imagined.
I see this as America's eyes
and ears. I don't want it to
become its heart and soul.
So I told the President,
for this to work,
there's gonna have to be
some kind of civilian
oversight.
Oversight?
How can you have
a covert organization
if you have people looking
over your shoulder?
You know who gave Hitler
his power? The clerks
and the bookkeepers.
The civil servants.
I have this one weakness.
I believe in a just God.
I always seem to err
on the side of democracy.
This must be a nice place
to raise a family.
I never made the time.
I'll be dead
in less than a year.
I love this country.
We all do, sir. We all do.
No matter what anyone
tells you, there'll be
no one you can really trust.
I'm afraid
when all is said and done,
we're all just clerks, too.
I was under the impression
that Dr. Ibanez
supported a democracy.
I'm afraid
he's changed his mind.
The doctor's started
to believe
his own propaganda.
I mean, you dreamed
this guy up, Edward,
helped get him elected.
Those are the Soviets.
International Department
of Central Committee members
Trubnikov, Kushelnikov,
who have become
overly interested
in their natural resources,
particularly coffee.
Our economic interests
are being compromised,
to say nothing of the dangers
of a Soviet presence
so close to home.
For security, Edward,
we must establish
our own presence there.
Wait, stop. Can you go back?
Go back a little bit.
Run it from there.
I just thought
I saw something.
I want you two
to put your heads together
on this.
Michael will be
going down there
as an agricultural specialist
with the Mayan Coffee Company.
Non-official.
He'll be our eyes and ears.
Congratulations.
Thank you, sir.
Good luck.
Thank you.
I wouldn't wear
my class ring down there.
Yes, sir. Of course.
I want all intelligence
on this sent directly to me
and no one else.
I believe that's
what you're looking for.
That'll do it.
Mr. Wilson?
This came for you through
the Carlson cover address.
There was no card.
There's been
a potential compromise
down south.
Ulysses.
We can't wait
another 24 hours.
If you can guarantee that
all assets are in place and
prepared to move on my order,
I'm prepared to move as well.
Come back to bed.
What were you talking about?
It's grown-up talk.
I had a nightmare.
Everything's fine.
Could you stay with me
another minute?
Try to get some sleep.
Yes?
We haven't got time to be sure
on this. This whole thing
hinges on support.
If we don't have the support,
I can't guarantee the outcome.
Can you guarantee
the support?
That's not a guarantee.
That's not an answer.
Do what you have to do.
These men aren't ideological.
Put more in their
Christmas stockings,
and they'll fall into place.
Call the station chief.
Get him out of bed.
Margaret tells us that
you work with the CIA.
My wife has
a vivid imagination.
I'm a trade advisor.
A civil servant.
Good night.
How dare you speak
to me that way?
You are never to tell anybody
what I do.
How dare you?
Those people are my friends!
I don't have a lot of friends!
You are never to tell anyone
what it is I do. Never.
Do you understand me?
What you do? What you do?
I don't know what you do!
You leave at five,
you're home at ten,
seven days a week.
You don't say
a damn word to me!
I live with a ghost!
I don't know what you do!
Call back.
They're ready.
Launch the operation.
Say something.
I have to go now.
Say something! Talk to me!
Say something!
Look at me. Say something.
Remember what I said.
Don't touch anything.
All right?
Merry Christmas,
Margaret. Edward.
Merry Christmas.
Is this young Edward?
Would you like to come inside
and meet our very
special guest this evening?
Santa Claus.
- Would you like
to meet Santa?
- Yeah.
Come along.
Toddy is wonderful
with children.
Yes, she is.
Come and meet Santa.
Would you like a drink,
Edward?
Thank you.
I believe
congratulations are in order.
The doctor has
no more patients
because of malpractice.
Gentlemen.
Edward.
Phillip.
Bill.
Gentlemen,
you can all be very proud
of what you've started.
Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas, Bill.
- Merry Christmas.
Christmas
is full of surprises.
Do you like surprises
under the tree?
Well, we'll make sure
you have lots of surprises
and things like that. Okay?
I'm sure Mom and Dad
agree that
that would be a good idea.
Surprises are the best part
of Christmas, don't you think?
How about games?
How about ball games?
- Can I get you a towel?
- I'm so sorry.
Are you all right?
All right. It's all right.
Can you take me
home, please?
I think we should go home.
Lower your voice.
You can use our bath
if you'd like.
I might have some dry clothes.
Thank you.
Come with me, Edward.
It's all right. Come with me.
Can I help you up,
Mrs. Wilson?
Did you know that
Phillip is going to be
on the Mayan Coffee Company's
board of directors?
Remember what I said to you
about friends.
You look good, Edward.
How long has it been?
Seven, eight years?
A lot of water
under the bridge.
Carolyn and I,
we just bought
our first house.
And everything's already
broken. I spend my weekends
fixing things.
By the time I get everything
fixed, it'll be time
to sell the fucking house.
Maybe you can give me
a heads-up on somebody.
You're asking me
to give you FBI files
on an American citizen?
You know I can't do that.
It's against the law
to spy on citizens.
Keep it.
Maybe someday
you'll change your mind.
May I come in?
You know, I've never
been in your office.
How was the fishing?
It was a bad year.
The water is too high.
I understand you wanted to
personally give me
the Operation Zapata list
yourself.
There isn't one, is there?
You know it was
a silent operation.
It wasn't silent enough.
I've been asked by
the President to suggest
who we no longer need with us.
Who would you recommend,
Edward?
I serve at the pleasure
of the Director, sir.
I'm just a gatekeeper.
And why is it that
people like us
choose to serve,
for nickels a day,
in a profession that makes us
constantly
look over our shoulder
to see who's watching us?
When will you
make your decision?
Decision?
I serve at the discretion
of the President
of the United States.
I will do what I think
is best for the country.
It's important that
we find out who's responsible.
Good night.
At 2242, call received
on Berlin base chief's
operational line.
Man says he's senior officer,
KGB. Would not give name.
Open up. Thanks.
"KGB officer asks when
Mr. Edward Wilson is coming.
"He wants to know
Mr. Edward Wilson's response."
Tell him
Mr. Edward Wilson is here,
and would like to know
what he intends to
provide us with in return.
He says,
"In return for safe journey,
"he will provide Mr. Wilson
with clear understanding
"of last three losses
in Moscow
"and identities of
Soviet agents in your country,
"penetrations
of Moscow station.
"He will also speak personally
with Mr. Edward Wilson about
"Ulysses.
"Things only he knows
of Ulysses,
"how he thinks,
what he plans to do,
"and what he wants
Mr. Edward Wilson to think
he is doing.
"To establish bonafides,
he will carry with him
"KGB surveillance photographs
of all CIA officers in Moscow
"and would be more than happy
to take polygraph."
Ulysses.
Ask him what his weakness is.
"The cold."
Let's get him over here.
My name is
Valentin Gregorievich Mironov.
My children's names are
Anatoly and Sergei.
My father played the cello.
I play the violin.
But you know this.
I risk my life to come all
the way to tell you this, to
confirm what you already know.
You failed the polygraph,
Mr. Mironov.
You know every Russian
fails polygraph.
Your polygraph
doesn't understand
the Russian soul.
What more do you want?
I've given you my bonafides,
the names of agents,
who has been compromised,
who you need to know about.
I want to speak to
Mr. Edward Wilson.
We were told
Mironov was with these men
the day the photo was taken.
Your immediate superior?
We're not even sure that
any of the circled men
are him.
I told you this
three times already.
Sergei Budanov.
I want to speak to
Mr. Edward Wilson.
I would like some tea.
There isn't any.
I get thirsty
when I say too much.
You going to keep up
this inane questioning
for much longer?
There's nothing you've told us
we don't know, Mr. Mironov.
I think you better try
a little harder.
I didn't come here
to deal with children,
Mr. Edison.
Or is it Mr. Brocco?
We do our homework, too.
Hello, Mr. Mironov.
I'm Mr. Wilson.
Hello, Mother.
Ulysses is obsessed with you.
Night and day,
you are always on his mind.
He trusts nobody.
The only one
whom he lets close
is his aide, Sasha.
He is methodical,
he plans things
years in advance.
For instance, you should know
he has developed a friendship
with a certain
neighbor of yours.
Fidel Castro. A young man
he has high hopes for.
I understand you had
a most interesting
fish swim your way.
Mr. Allen thought
it might be possible
for me to speak with him.
With you as the chaperone,
of course.
I brought him a little gift
I'm sure he'll appreciate.
Send Mironov in immediately.
It'll be nice
to be closely working
with you again.
I expect you to show me
Washington. We can
paint the town red together.
Valentin Mironov,
Arch Cummings.
It is a great pleasure
to meet you.
My pleasure.
Now, please sit down.
It's nice to have someone
like you on our side
of the street.
I thought you may enjoy this.
It's something
you might appreciate.
I hope you haven't read it.
Very clever.
Thank you.
All Russia is our orchard.
The land is great
and beautiful.
There are many
wonderful places in it.
Think, Anya.
Your grandfather,
your great-grandfather...
This is a very bad
translation. It is
much funnier in Russian.
And now,
doesn't something human
look at you
from every cherry
in the orchard?
From every leaf
and every stalk?
Don't you hear their voices?
It's awful.
Your orchard is terrible!
And when in the evening
or at night, when you walk
through the orchard
and the old bark glows
with the dim light
and the old cherry trees seem
to be dreaming of all that was
a hundred, two hundred
years ago, and are repressed
by their heavy visions.
I'm due at a meeting.
We've left those 200 years
behind us, but so far,
we gained nothing at all.
We don't yet know
what the past is to be to us.
We only philosophize.
We complain that we are dull,
or we drink vodka.
For it's so clear
that in order to
begin to live in the present,
we must first redeem the past.
Are you Laura?
What?
Are you Laura? I'm supposed to
offer you a ride.
Hello, Edward.
Hello, Laura.
Why all the mystery?
Do you have children?
I have a boy.
Edward Junior.
Do you have anybody?
A cat.
I've often imagined
what my life would have
been like with you.
And what did you imagine?
I thought you might teach.
Probably poetry.
I saw us living
in a small college town.
You once said to me you were
afraid your life was
already planned out for you.
Are you doing
what you want to do?
My life has been
full of surprises.
You owe me
a day at the beach.
How long do you think
you'll be?
As long as it takes.
I think maybe
I'll go ahead.
All right.
Nothing else
is built the same
Nothing in the world
As the soft
and wavy frame...
Mother?
There was an envelope for you
on the desk.
You look lovely.
Thank you, darling.
It's not enough
that you ignore me
our whole life?
You have to humiliate me?
Margaret, please.
You disgust me!
Calm down, darling.
You're disgusting!
We'll start from the last.
So suppose
the dame ain't right
Or completely
free from flaws
Mother forgot
some of her things.
I'll see you at home.
Are you Laura?
Yes.
I was asked to give you this.
In an
unprecedented effort to
improve U.S.-Soviet ties,
Premier Khrushchev
began his 10-day tour
of the United States today.
The visit
will start with a tour
by President Eisenhower
of our nation's capital,
followed by
a highly anticipated speech
at the United Nations.
All right,
now set it down.
Following that,
the Soviet Premier
will travel across the country
to more casual destinations,
including America's mighty
steel mills, wheat farms,
and, yes, Disneyland.
President Eisenhower greeted
Mr. Khrushchev this morning
at Andrews Air Force Base,
as they prepare to discuss...
It's perfect.
...the ever-threatening
military build-up by the Reds.
Our glee club's
been chosen to compete
in a national competition.
Now, back to
The Classical Hour.
Would you come with me?
Would you like me to?
Yeah, very much.
I'll get your things.
It's good
to have you home.
How was your trip?
Smooth as silk.
My FBI escort
made the trip here
very pleasant.
Which one is your son?
Top row, third from the right.
He's a handsome young man.
My congratulations.
We're particularly concerned
about Cuba.
Your friend,
he's too close to home.
You don't appreciate
him breathing down your neck.
If we continue down this road,
there will be
a Third World War.
I don't think
either of us wants a real war.
What would we do
for a living then?
If he keeps
calling attention to himself,
at some point, we may be
forced to send him a surprise.
Now, I don't want that
to come as a surprise
to your people.
He is very important to us.
We would not like
to be surprised.
Be well.
I am today announcing my
candidacy for the Presidency
of the United States.
The Presidency
is the most powerful office
in the free world.
Through its leadership
can come a more vital life
for all of our people.
In it are centered the hopes
of the globe around us,
for freedom
and a more secure life.
Senator Kennedy,
if you don't win
the Presidential nomination,
will you accept
the Vice Presidency?
I shall not, under
any conditions, be a candidate
for Vice President.
If I fail in this endeavor,
I shall return and serve
in the United States Senate.
We have a secure circuit
with Stockholm station.
Station reports they have
a colonel, Directorate K,
counterintelligence.
Do we have a name?
May I help you, sir?
I'm a colonel with KGB.
I'm requesting asylum.
What is your name?
My name is
Valentin Gregorievich Mironov.
This other man who says
he is Valentin Mironov
is not who he pretends to be.
All right?
His real name is Yuri Modin.
He was
Ulysses' right hand.
He is Ulysses' mole.
Just tell me your real name.
It is just Ulysses
trying to discredit me.
Just tell me your real name.
My real name is
Valentin Gregorievich Mironov.
I was born
in Bobruisk in 1924.
Attended the State Institute
of International Relations.
Served for three years
in Naval Intelligence.
My wife's name is
Tamara Markovskaya.
My children's names are
Anatoly and Sergei.
My father is a cellist.
I play the violin.
All I want is my freedom.
Pick him up.
You all right?
I'm sorry.
You see what you made me do?
Now just tell me the truth.
Because we're going to be here
as long as it takes.
I already told you
the truth.
I want to know the truth.
You know my name.
Tell me your real name.
Mister, please,
I'm not lying.
I'd like to believe you,
but I don't believe you.
Understand?
Now, tell me your name.
My name is Mironov. It's
Valentin Gregorievich Mironov.
That's your name?
Yeah.
That's your real name.
Yes. This is my name.
Tell me your name.
I told you my name.
I told you a hundred times.
We're not going anywhere.
I just want you to know that.
We are not going anywhere.
Today, tomorrow,
next week, next month.
Yuri Modin. He is your mole.
I am not your mole.
You understand?
I cannot tell you
anything else.
I'm gonna be
right in front of you.
The same position.
This is my name.
What is your name?
My name is
Valentin Gregorievich Mironov.
This is my name.
Tell me your name.
I don't have
a different name.
Tell it.
I don't have it.
Tell it to me again.
This is my name.
Valentin Gregorievich Mironov.
Tell it to me again.
Valentin Gregorievich...
Tell me your fucking name!
Mironov!
Valentin Gregorievich
We are gonna be here
a long time.
This is my name!
It's Valentin Mironov!
Shut up! Shut up!
I told you!
I don't have a different...
Tell me your name!
Tell me your fucking name!
Come on, tear it off.
Get it off!
Put him down.
Your name.
What is your name?
Tell me your name.
Sir, this is
lysergic acid diethylamide.
It's called LSD.
We've had
some very favorable results
as a truth serum.
Look, it's him. Papa.
Soviet power is a myth.
A great show,
but there are no spare parts.
Nothing is working.
It's nothing but painted rust.
But you.
You need to keep
the Russian myth alive
to maintain your
military-industrial complex.
Your system depends on Russia
being perceived
as a mortal threat.
It's not a threat.
It was never a threat.
It will never be a threat.
It is
a rotted,
bloated
cow.
I am
Valentin Gregorievich Mironov
and I am free.
Shit. Shit!
If you would like,
I'll be willing to take
the truth serum, Edward.
I've nothing to hide.
I am who I say I am.
I know.
We send
those who are leaving us
to go into the world
with the knowledge,
wherever they go,
whatever they do,
they will never be alone.
They will always be one of us.
And we say,
Bonesmen, all here.
All here.
I didn't know you smoked.
There are a few things
you don't know about me.
I've spoken
to a recruiter here.
I would like very much
to join CIA.
There are a lot of things
you can do, Edward.
I'd like you to think
about this very carefully.
I have thought about it
carefully. It's what
I want to do.
I want to join the Agency.
I want to
make you proud of me.
I am proud of you.
I've made up my mind, Father.
You can stop him.
He doesn't understand
what he's getting into.
You can stop him.
I can't tell him what to do.
Yes, you can.
No, I can't.
Because he's doing it for you.
Because he wants you to
be proud of him. And he wants
to feel closer to you.
You could
have them reject him.
Absolutely not.
I won't do that to him.
Of course you won't.
You wouldn't do anything
for anybody but yourself.
That is unfair.
Unfair?
You abandon the people
when they need you the most.
I don't abandon people!
You abandon people!
I do not abandon people.
It's true.
I have stood by you
for 22 years!
Stood by me?
I have stood by you.
You don't know what it is
to stand by somebody.
I stood by you
and I have stood by him,
I have done everything
to be a good father to him.
You have done no such thing!
I married you because of him!
I know you don't love me,
but you love him.
And no matter what,
you should stand by him
and you should protect him.
I don't need you to tell me
I have to protect my son.
Promise me that
you'll protect him.
I'll protect him.
Today, in Havana,
Fidel Castro
expelled high-profile
crime figures from Cuba.
He's taken control
of their hotels and casinos,
popular vacation destinations
for many Americans.
Castro has nationalized
over $1 billion
from U.S. businesses
in the past six months,
and there's no telling
what the Communist dictator
might do next.
I want to see a man
about a hat.
He had
three casinos down there
until Castro sent him home.
His people know
how to be discreet.
With the right encouragement,
he could help.
And he's very patriotic.
Jimmy. Mr. Carlson.
Tina, the kids.
Come on, kids. Come on,
come on. We're going
to the beach. Let's go.
Mom, please.
Sit down. Want some water,
some coffee, whatever?
Is there someplace else
we could go?
All right, Daddy, we're going
down to the beach.
We'll be back in a while.
Make sure they don't go
into the water unless
somebody's watching them.
No, I'm gonna
let them drown.
Make sure they put
their shoes on.
They'll burn their feet!
We're getting their shoes!
All right, come on. Let's go.
So, what do you want to
talk to me about?
The government's
about to deport you
for certain activities.
I've been in this country
since I'm two months old.
What does that make me,
Italian? I'm American.
And they're trying to
send me back?
I could have the
deportation order reviewed.
Have you classified as
highly sensitive
for national security.
I could take the government
off your back
if you can help us.
Youse are the guys
that scare me.
You're the people
that make big wars.
No, we make sure the wars
are small ones, Mr. Palmi.
Let me ask you something.
We Italians,
we got our families
and we got the Church.
The Irish,
they have their homeland.
The Jews, their tradition.
Even the niggers,
they got their music.
What about you people,
Mr. Carlson? What do you have?
The United States of America.
The rest of you
are just visiting.
The President wants
the noise level
on the operation turned down.
How many men are involved?
Fifteen hundred.
Tell him we're going instead
to Bahía de Cochinos.
The noise level
will be way down.
We'll see you inside.
Could you hear
what we were talking about?
No, I didn't hear anything.
If something was heard,
it has to stay in this room.
Oh, I know that, Father.
Yeah, all right.
Bonesmen!
All here!
Reverend Christiansen
will offer grace.
Agency first, God second.
Thank you, Lord,
for bringing us safely here
to be with our brothers
and loved ones again.
Our prayers are
with our brothers
whom God has seen fit
to take into
his gentle arms this year.
The Honorable Senator
John Russell, Senior.
Mr. Stephen Loomis...
Would you like to dance,
Clover?
I haven't been Clover
for a long time.
I'm going to Phoenix
to live with my mother.
Based on the ringing
of the church bells,
we're going to assume
the recording was made
at the same time
the photograph was taken.
We've checked the schedules
for flights
leaving major airports
at or around 10:00 at night
for a two-week period.
There were flights
leaving nine cities.
Six were places
that also would potentially
have a fan made in Belgium.
Five of those places
were also either tropical
or in their summer seasons.
Three of those were places
where French is spoken.
We think the tape was made
in either Dakar, Abidjan,
or Congo-Leo.
It is all gone.
Hello, Mother.
Let me show you.
As you see, no cameras,
no tape recorders.
There is nothing else to know.
Can I play something for you?
Everything is a secret.
You were brought up
on secrets.
What was such a big secret
that his own son
couldn't know?
When he was
standing outside talking,
I'd heard something
I wasn't supposed to,
and he knew I'd listened
to his conversation.
I heard them
say something in Spanish.
Bahía de Cochinos.
I'm afraid of him.
You are safe
here with me.
People who
really love each other
don't have secrets.
I have something to tell you.
I love you so much.
She's been an active asset
of ours for some time.
Until now.
She loves your son.
Sometimes
even spies fall in love.
We can protect him.
Make him safe.
Nobody would know,
not even him.
All it would require
is for you
to help us
when your help is needed.
I thought
you'd like to see this.
She's a very pretty girl.
It's easy to see
why he fell for her.
I know it's an extremely
difficult situation for you.
But I'm afraid I'm going to
need your answer very soon.
You must decide
what is of more importance
to you.
Your country or...
Or your son.
She's not
who you think she is.
She's not a friendly, Edward.
I don't believe you.
Why should I believe you?
You told me yourself
not to trust anybody.
You're the master
at creating the truth.
I love her.
I've asked her
to marry me.
I will not let you
take that away from me.
I can't protect you anymore,
I can't keep you safe.
Safe?
Safe? I never felt safe.
I was always frightened.
I always lived in fear
that something awful
was going to happen to you.
Or if not,
to Mother or to me.
I was always afraid, because
everything was a secret.
Edward.
Hello, may I come in?
Yes. Of course.
Is everything all right?
I was on my way home
from work
and I had this
overwhelming desire
to hear you play the violin.
Play the violin? But...
Edward, I'm so tired.
Can't this wait
until tomorrow?
I'd appreciate it
if you'd play it now.
Now?
I just wanted to
hear something from you
that was true.
He was careless.
FBI. You're under arrest.
Stand up.
Didn't learn how to
hide in plain sight.
Where are they taking me?
I can't go home! You know
they can't trust me anymore!
You know
what they will do to me!
Sorry, Edward.
I truly did like you.
I mean it. In another world,
we actually would have been
quite good friends.
Are you still there, Mother?
Your worst fear has come true.
Alone and friendless
without a country of your own.
We have a whole new place
to fight over.
The stars.
Your offer.
I have to decline.
You've succeeded
in stopping us
from taking back Cuba.
The damage is done.
There's no need for you
to hurt my son.
Let's just leave it
between you and me.
Very well.
I will wait.
But there will come a time
when I will ask you to help me
with a problem
that wouldn't cost you much
but be of some value to me.
You never know
what the future will bring.
Friends can be enemies,
and enemies friends.
This girl,
neither of us
can be sure about her.
But she's about to be
a part of your family.
I believe in family.
You want her to be
a part of your family,
don't you?
It was good to see you.
We will talk again,
my dear friend.
Sorry to bother.
I want to buy a little
souvenir to my daughter.
They have no change.
What does it cost?
It costs a dollar.
Here. It's a gift.
Regards from
the United States government.
It's a cardinal rule
to be generous in a democracy.
Thank you.
So where is she?
We're gonna meet her
at the church.
I can't wait to meet her.
You'll love her.
You're gonna love her.
Yes, that's good.
Come on in.
Hello, Margaret.
Let's celebrate.
I'll get some champagne.
How was the flight?
It was long.
How do you like
living in Phoenix?
It's the first time
I've slept in years.
Here we go.
To your happiness.
Your wife...
What have you done?
Will you go inside, Mother?
Go inside, Mom.
Please, just go in the church.
She's pregnant.
You couldn't...
You couldn't have.
You couldn't.
No.
I love you.
I love you
so much.
- Mr. Wilson?
- Mr. Hayes.
Have you been here before,
Mother?
No, I haven't.
Whose idea was that?
It's classified.
Mr. Allen has notified
the President he'll resign.
Something about
Swiss bank accounts.
Where did these
come from?
They were in the car.
I thought you had them
sent down, sir.
Seems the greedy
bastard has been
hiding money away for years.
Whoever had the statements
sent them to him
in a box of Swiss chocolates.
It wasn't you, was it?
The President's asked me
to become Director
and do a complete
housecleaning
at my discretion.
I need someone I can trust.
After all,
we're still brothers.
This building
doesn't get built without you.
You're CIA's heart and soul.
Who knows, you might have
a secret about me
in that safe of yours.
This whole wing will be
your part of the world.
Counterintelligence.
Take a look around.
I've got an oversight meeting.
Can you imagine? They think
they can look into our closet.
As if we'll let them.
I remember
a senator once asked me
when we talk about CIA,
why we never use
the word "the" in front of it.
And I asked him,
"Do you put the word 'the'
in front of God?"
"They are right
what they say about me.
"I was weak. A coward.
"I compromised myself.
"My honor. My family.
My country.
"I am ashamed of myself.
"To my wife, I am sorry
I've done this to you.
"To my son,
"I hope you will grow to be
a courageous man.
"A good husband.
A good father.
"I hope
whatever you decide to do,
you lead a good, full life.
"I hope whatever
your dreams may be come true.
"Your loving husband
and father."