So, I'm gonna have
to ask you a question.
Are you a serial killer?
♪ Love hurts
♪ Love scars
♪ Love wounds
♪ And marks
♪ Any heart
♪ Not tough
♪ Or strong enough
♪ To take a lot of pain
♪ Take a lot of pain
♪ Love is like a cloud
♪ Holds a lot of rain
♪ Love hurts
♪ Ooh, ooh love hurts
♪ Some fools think
of happiness
♪ Blissfulness
♪ Togetherness
♪ Some fools fool
themselves I guess
♪ They're not foolin' me
♪ Ooh, ooh love hurts ♪
♪ Strange darling
♪ Stay darling
♪ We will change
and mock and turn
♪ Curiouser and curiouser
♪ Strange darling
♪ Strange... ♪
...the whereabouts
of the Velvet Emerald Cult.
Although skeptics
don't believe it's a real thing,
it is.
But that's
for another broadcast.
Today we're gonna talk about
the chilling uncovering
of a Bigfoot family
in the forest near his property
and what Mitchell
is doing about it.
Pretty serious subject.
Let's jump right in.
Mitchell W. Mahoney, everybody.
- Mitchell, are you there?
- I am. I am.
Listening with both ears.
I ain't taking no goddamn...
Oh! Oh!
I must stop you there, sir.
As you know,
our number-one rule is no bad language.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, that's right. I'm sorry.
- Didn't mean it.
- No harm, no foul.
It's an emotional subject.
I understand. Carry on, sir.
So I take a quick shot
of Old Grand-Dad
and I go out there.
Shotgun cocked.
And the whole time
I hear the dogs
but when I opened the door
to go outside,
it stops.
Real quick like, wild.
Hey. Hey!
Can you help me? Please?
Here, kitty,
kitty, kitty.
Which really upset me
because we were gonna
butcher it next month.
Now the whole thing's
gone away.
I can't hear that.
But the worst
part was,
the grizzly nature
of the whole thing.
Yeah. There you go.
It's nomenclature.
What if it attacked me?
All her innards
were taken out and eaten.
Whatever it was,
it's a loose sack of flesh and fur.
At first I thought
it would be gray.
We've had them
here before too.
Just to clarify
for our listeners,
Mitchell was just referring to
extra-terrestrial entities.
Yeah.
Yeah, thanks, Art.
Here, kitty,
kitty, kitty.
...went
to Nova Scotia in 1972,
down in Breckenridge, Colorado
in 1987.
Yet again, Moran County
back in 2013.
I'm very familiar
with the anatomy of those things.
And even just seeing the outline
in the moonlight,
I knew immediately
what it was.
Of course. Of course.
And was that the extent of it,
or have you continued to be...
pestered, for lack of
a better word?
No. No.
They keep coming.
They've been eating my hens
one by one...
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty!
Fuck!
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
These aren't the same.
Mmm-mmm. Probably better
for you, though.
Mmm... Doubt that.
I even smoked
one of yours tonight.
But first...
A-plus.
- That's a relief.
- Yes, it is.
Do you still want to, um,
get a room?
Can we just, uh,
make out a little bit?
Yeah.
Okay.
Look, we can just...
We can just swap numbers
if you don't wanna...
Well, okay.
You wanna get...
You wanna get digits?
Nobody gets digits anymore.
It's about the Insta.
I guess I'm just getting old.
Well, you are.
I guess that's what I'm into.
This is gonna sound
like bullshit, but, uh...
I don't really do this.
I mean,
I have no problem doing it.
I...
I just have to really want it.
Do you want it?
Or are you, like, about to
tell me to go fuck myself?
No, no, I really want it.
I just... I... I like...
sobered up a little bit
on the ride over
and started judging myself,
I guess.
Look, my groceries
are on one shelf.
Hers are on the other.
You know what I mean?
If I cared, I would've said
something at the bar.
And if she cared,
I wouldn't fucking be here.
Your...
Your business
is not my business.
What this is here,
it's recreation.
And I fucking deserve it.
Hell, yeah.
Okay.
Mmm.
It's garbage.
Yeah.
Ooh.
You know...
The real issue is safety.
Once I'm alone with you
in that room,
it's just us, no witnesses.
Do you have any idea
the kind of risks
a woman like me
takes every time
she agrees to have
a little bit of fun?
It's a goddamn tragedy.
Men think that
we're these prudes
who don't like casual sex.
Most of us
fucking love casual sex.
We just want to know
that murder
isn't gonna be served
on the side.
Jesus.
Never thought about it
that way.
Of course you haven't.
You're not a woman.
Then there's, you know,
plain old risk
of disappointment,
which is the most common, but...
violence...
That's no joke.
That's life or death.
I think I, um...
I think I want one of those now.
Mmm.
You seem like a nice guy.
You do.
But you never really know.
So, I'm gonna have
to ask you a question.
Are you a serial killer?
What?
I'm gonna need you
to look me in the eyes
and give me a serious answer.
No.
- No...
- No.
What?
No, I'm not...
a serial killer.
Okay.
Now can we talk about
all the things
I want you to do to me?
Harder.
Stop.
Can you take these off me?
I don't know
why this isn't working.
It's your idea.
Maybe it's you.
What did you just say?
Maybe I just
don't need it with you.
Well...
Well, look, maybe it's better
that we don't need that
in the beginning.
"The beginning."
If I didn't know any better,
I'd think you were
on the verge of asking for digits.
What are they?
Hmm.
Stop.
- Or social media?
- I'm not on social media.
See...
That makes me
really want that number.
This just got
really fucking complicated.
Well, aren't you eager?
Hmm?
Hmm.
What are you doing?
Do you like that?
Stop.
Okay, baby.
- Can you just wait a minute?
- I don't want to wait.
I said I need a fucking minute!
What are you doing?
Take these off me now.
You don't get to decide.
Yes, I do get to decide.
Just because I asked you
to cuff me at first
doesn't mean that
you don't need my permission.
Wrong.
Get off of me, motherfucker!
You don't fucking hit me!
"Please don't
fucking hit me, sir."
From now on,
you only refer to me as sir.
Do you understand me?
Stop it!
I'm in control.
Now here's what's gonna happen.
Please don't kill me.
First, you're gonna take
my foot in your mouth.
Toes first, all the way
to the fucking heel.
You don't get to make noise!
You just shut the fuck up!
You're a sick woman.
Carrying around shackles
trying to get fucked.
You know
you asked for this, right?
Yes.
Yes, what?
Yes, sir.
I'm gonna take my knife
and I'm gonna cut you.
From one set of lips
to the other.
Watch you bleed to death.
Mr. Snuffleupagus!
I can't believe
that you're into this.
Just relax, okay.
I don't know if I'm into it,
but I'm willing to try.
No, no, no.
I'm gonna have to believe you,
or it's gonna be a huge,
huge fucking turn off.
I mean,
I did do a little bit of acting.
What?
I was in a Holiday Inn Express
commercial once.
What?
So you might actually be
good at this.
Look, hawking
the free hot breakfast
ain't the same
as slapping a woman around,
telling her you're gonna
chop her up into little pieces.
But look, I'm willing to try.
No, no,
I don't want any chopping.
I want something intimate.
Something romantic.
Like a slit throat.
Uh...
You know
you're a little fucked up?
You know you men will do
just about anything to get laid?
- Get the fuck out of here.
- Huh?
Get the fuck out of here
with that.
Don't sell me the car
and then tell me not to drive it.
Okay, okay. But...
Don't tell me when you're gonna turn,
you just do it.
And if I say no, you say yes.
And you push even harder.
If I'm, you know,
scared or angry.
Even fucking crying.
I don't...
I don't like that.
Don't be a fucking pussy.
Are you serious?
I cannot imagine consent being any more clear.
Okay.
All right.
Yes.
Pop quiz.
What's "no" mean?
Yes.
And what is the only word
in the entire English language
that actually means no
once we're alone together
in that room?
Mr. Snuffleupagus.
Mr. Snuffleupagus!
You okay?
Not really.
Shit.
I'm so sorry.
How can you say
those awful things to me?
Fuck! You told...
You told me to say 'em.
I thought...
You were fucking fantastic.
I have never been
so turned on in my life.
Mmm!
Mmm.
Then why Mr. Snuffleupagus?
I just needed a break.
You know, a glass of water,
maybe a cigarette, a drink.
There's no rush, right?
Hmm...
Bon appetit.
Mmm.
Mmm-hmm.
Mmm, mmm.
What do you got?
You're three ahead of me.
Looks like you've got that one
ready to go for the nose.
Stop.
I don't need you
to help me win. Goddamn it.
I want this thing
fair and square.
Now only two.
Oh, my...
Don't get too excited.
I'm still up by one.
Not for long, fucker.
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey! Hey!
That's a crazy lady.
Get the bear spray.
Can you help me? Please?
You sure it wasn't
one of 'em things done this to you?
Shh.
Don't say it out loud.
What things?
It's Squatchy in those woods.
We don't go too deep in 'em.
Squatchy?
- You're sure it was a man did this to you?
- Yes.
- He was chasing me in a truck.
- A pickup truck?
Squatch can't drive
no pickup truck.
You'd be one dead shitass
if Squatch was at it.
Do you have a gun?
We have bear spray.
I thought
mountain people had guns.
We ain't mountain people.
We're just old hippies.
Sweetie, do you want something
for the pain? Aspirin?
How about something
a little bit stronger?
- Percocet?
- Yes.
We only have
a few of those left.
Now, don't be selfish, Mama.
You're right, Papa.
Call the cops.
Better they're on the way.
What's that?
Oh, we ain't into Scott Baio.
They give 'em away free
at the flea market.
- We take whatever they got.
- No. What's that?
- That's our Sunday breakfast.
- Do you mind?
Get in there.
Hold on.
Let me give you a chair.
- Right here. Right here.
- Okay.
Old biker.
Huh?
She said we're old hippies.
I'm more of an old biker.
Got a '59 Indian
sitting in the garage.
Doesn't run anymore,
but doesn't matter.
I couldn't ride it anyway.
Lost it on the bike.
Whole thing? That's heavy.
Just up to the knee.
You ride one of those every day,
doesn't matter how good you are.
It doesn't matter.
Can't find the stronger stuff.
Where is it?
Upstairs bathroom.
Police on the way?
Yes, honey.
No.
Don't you worry one bit.
You're gonna feel
real nice soon.
I meant no police.
No, no. It's better that we call them.
Genevieve's right.
Come on, man.
Just give it a minute, please.
It's best
we let them know.
Please, man, do me this favor.
No fucking cops.
Genevieve. Genevieve.
Genevieve.
Percocet...
Genevieve...
I didn't wanna do that.
I had to.
Can you just...
Can you put your hands up, please?
Just to make us
both feel more relaxed.
This is gonna be a really
tough one for you to believe,
but I'm not gonna kill you.
I promise.
Sure.
I am gonna have to tie you up, though.
All right?
All right.
What do you recommend
that's fastest?
You have some... some cuffs?
Or is there a rope or...
Or is there something
that I can put you in
and lock it from the outside?
Whatever is most comfortable
for you is fine
as long as it's fast.
Well, that's thoughtful of you.
I'm not trying
to fuck up your day
any more than I already have.
There's a storm shelter
outside. There's...
There's some, um, chain
you can use on the handles
once I'm in.
And we even got food and such
that'll last a while.
We aren't just old hippies.
We're...
Doomsdayers.
Okay, let's go.
Fuck!
What?
What? Something on my face?
Like, what?
I was just looking at you
and you are so handsome.
It went straight to my head.
How did I get so lucky tonight?
Do you like to party?
Oh, fuck.
It's going to be light soon.
Mmm. Come on.
Checkout's not until noon
and this stuff
gets me really fucking horny.
It's been a long time
since I touched that stuff.
Me too.
But it's my birthday.
And...
a friend got it for me.
It's, you know,
like a special occasion sort of thing.
Birthday, huh?
Yeah.
All right.
Well, I can't let a lady down
on her birthday now, can I?
Oh, yeah.
Come on.
Shit.
♪ Waking up, getting lost
Making up time
♪ Amber eyes, little lies
Setting up lines
♪ Secret life, only mine
Mirrors and ghosts
♪ Letting go, getting low
God only knows
♪ Where the summer days go
♪ The lake in Montenegro?
♪ The hazy daze of chainsmoke
♪ Like a little grave
in my brain
♪ Life got too heavy
So I got too light
♪ Balancing, manically
♪ Tightropes and wires because
♪ Life got too heavy
So I got too light
♪ Vanishing, magically
♪ I'm disappearing from sight
♪ Into the night ♪
Are we...
Are we gonna fuck?
Okay.
Is that what you were gonna say?
You know what,
I'll tell you what.
If you still can fuck
in five minutes...
Sure.
I thought you said
this stuff made you horny.
Seems like it just
puts you in a bad mood.
Maybe I lied.
What is this, part of your game?
- I'm done.
- You know what?
We're done
when I say we're done,
do you understand that?
No, I don't.
I'm out of here.
Bullshit.
Find your own way home.
Cocaine.
Cocaine. Cocaine.
Huh?
Cocaine.
No. No.
That is cocaine.
This is ketamine.
No.
I'll only use this if I have to,
so don't make me.
I didn't wanna
fucking do this, man.
I was...
just trying to have a good time.
Oh, my God!
I fucking love that song.
♪ Love hurts
♪ Love scars
♪ Love wounds
♪ And marks
♪ Any heart
♪ Not tough
♪ Or strong enough
♪ To take a lot of pain
♪ Take a lot of pain
♪ Love is like a cloud
♪ Holds a lot of rain
♪ Love hurts
♪ Ooh, ooh love hurts
♪ Some fools think
of happiness
♪ Blissfulness
♪ Togetherness
♪ Some fools fool...
Hey!
Shh! Just stop.
♪ They're not foolin' me
♪ I know it isn't true
♪ Love is just a lie
♪ Love hurts
♪ Ooh, ooh love hurts
♪ Oh, oh love hurts ♪
I've never put it there before.
Now sleep.
What the fuck?
He's got a gun!
So do I!
♪ But live a while
and soon you'll find
♪ They turn to caves
in which we hide
♪ The words are the same
♪ The meanings change
♪ The world falls away
♪ And drowns you in a pool
of empty space
♪ Day in, day out
♪ The sun goes down
♪ The tide gets high
♪ Day in, day out
♪ Those sirens cry ♪
- What is wrong with you?
- I'm sorry.
Can... Can you help me, please?
Jesus!
Oh, my God.
How do I lock this door?
Just hold on, darling.
It needs a key,
even from the inside.
Can you unlock the door?
I think I'd better leave.
No, no, don't go out there!
He's gonna fucking kill you!
Do you have a gun?
No, only a baseball bat.
Fuck!
Call 911, will you?
I... I'm not sure
I wanna get involved.
You already are, sweetheart.
Okay.
I know that was fucking awful,
but I had to do it.
Okay?
What's your name?
T... Tanya.
Tanya...
Okay, Tan...
Do you have a bandage big
enough for this in that bag?
Yes.
Okay. I'm gonna need
to borrow your car.
Come on.
- Which fucking key is it?
- It's... It's that one.
- It's that one.
- Okay. What car?
It's the '78 Pinto,
right outside.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Now take off
your fucking clothes.
Hey, Pete.
It's, um... It's RC. Um...
Listen, I'm out here near, uh,
near SR 78
and the old Wilton Bridge.
There's a farmhouse
on the south edge
near the fire road. I, um...
I need you to get out here.
I, uh...
I got myself into
a little bit of trouble.
Got you, you fucking cunt!
I fucking got you.
That's true.
It's like checkmate.
Yeah.
And then some.
There's nothing
more than checkmate.
It either is or it isn't,
you fucking philistine.
Why am I still alive?
You couldn't do it.
After all that.
Oh.
You're gonna be in trouble.
Yeah, well...
I'll take
a little bit of trouble
over a life sentence any day.
You want me
to call your sponsor?
Are you really
The Electric Lady?
I don't care about jail.
I just don't wanna die.
Isn't that fucking funny?
Even when we know we're gonna
spend the rest of our lives
in a tiny little cage,
we will fight to stay alive.
I always used to wonder
why people did that,
when I watched true crime shows.
Thought I'd be
like Gary Gilmore.
Who's Gary Gilmore?
He asked for the firing squad.
I thought I'd...
I'd do that...
if it came to this.
Now I just want
three hots and a cot.
I didn't plan to do it, man.
Love...
doesn't have to be something
that develops.
The purest, most primal kind
can hit you like a wave...
In a moment...
or over the course of one night.
I felt that for you
when you had your hand
around my throat.
Did you feel it for me?
♪ Love hurts
♪ Love scars
♪ Love wounds
♪ And marks ♪
That's our song now.
You'll always think of me
when you hear it.
Maybe.
Not...
maybe.
God! Fuck!
♪ Shut your eyes
♪ Can you hear the waves
♪ And see the world
the way it was
♪ And you stand
with thumbs outstretched
♪ Looking simple,
fine and plain
♪ Still look perfect
and blush
♪ Stop the clock
♪ Give me a smile
♪ They're playing our song
♪ But the beat is so off
♪ And the key is wrong
♪ You and I
weren't made for love
♪ Get it straight
Our time won't come
♪ I was told when I was young
♪ No crying in the rain ♪
RC!
RC, are you in here?
What the fuck happened in here?
Maybe you shouldn't
touch him.
- I know what I'm doing.
- Okay.
It's all right.
- He's dead.
- Yeah, no shit. So is he.
It's okay.
All right? Take it easy.
I'm gonna get these off.
What happened here?
What do you think happened,
Pete? Look at her!
Here we go. Okay. It's okay.
- Here we go.
- Goddamn it!
Take it easy.
Okay, take it easy.
There's a gunshot wound
to the left shoulder.
Just take it easy, honey.
How tender is it?
Can I move it just a little
to get the cuffs off?
Wait. We need to figure out
what's going on here first.
She needs medical attention now.
That's protocol.
Protocol is that we call it in.
Leave her be,
and we wait for the EMTs
and Homicide to show up.
We both know medics won't be here
for at least an hour.
It's okay.
I'm gonna get you out.
Okay.
It was horrible.
He was coked up out of his mind.
I thought he was a nice guy.
Who was coked out of his mind?
His jacket pocket.
It's okay, honey,
you don't need to do this now.
He brought me here.
He thought it was deserted.
And then this guy
stopped him and...
It's okay, honey.
Why is his neck like that?
She was chained to this thing
the whole fucking time, Pete.
She fought for her fucking life!
What else was she
supposed to do?
- Fuck! Fuck you!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Hey, it's okay.
- Okay, okay. All right. Okay.
All right. Hey, calm down, lady.
We're gonna take care of it.
I'm going to the car
and call it in,
and then we'll wait here
for the EMTs.
The victim needs
medical attention.
Our job is to do what we need to do
to keep her alive.
This ain't my first
jar of pickles.
And just because I have
a vagina doesn't mean
you shouldn't listen to
a fucking thing I have to say!
This has nothing to do
with your vagina
and everything to do with
the diapers you were wearing
when I cleared
my first crime scene.
We don't even know
if she's a victim yet.
We need to find that out first.
That's fucking protocol.
You wanna be held
liable for this
or you want to help me move her?
Pete!
Okay, I'll help you move her.
It's all right, honey.
Just breathe.
What the fuck?
A lady came, she killed us.
Calm down, ma'am.
- She killed us!
- Who did what?
Hand over the guns now,
or the chick cop dies.
And trust me, honey,
I don't wanna fucking kill you,
especially after
what you did for me.
God-fucking-damnit.
You dumb bitch.
- I oughta let her...
- Oh, no, you oughtn't,
'cause if she goes,
you go too, motherfucker.
I am in survival mode now.
My rules are out the window.
Honey,
just turn yourself in now...
Just shut up
and give me the guns.
Put it in my lap.
Pete, you keep your hands
on the wheel at all times.
If a fucking finger moves,
I pull the trigger.
You got me?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Okay.
- Get out of the car.
- Honey...
Just turn yourself in now
and stop.
It'll end better for you.
Bitch!
I am The Electric Lady.
Boo!
Get out the fucking car.
Run, honey, into the woods.
Drive, motherfucker.
Why did we stop here?
Just...
Let me think.
Okay?
Are you really
The Electric Lady?
Are you gonna kill me?
I'd rather not.
Why did you kill
all those folks?
Sometimes...
I don't see humans.
I see devils.
Hey.
Hey!
Can you help me, please?
Oh, sweet girl! What happened?
Oh, God!
Here, let me help you get up.
Oh! Oh, yeah?
Yeah, come on.
Here...
Let's get you in the truck.
Easy does it.
You're gonna be fine.
Here, let me help you up.
Okay.
Hello?
I just shot a person.
She pulled a gun on me
and there was
nothing else I could do.
♪ Better the devil you know
♪ Than the devil you don't
I'm bringing her in right now.
♪ Over and over
I keep going under alone
♪ Better the tether
that keeps us together
♪ Than some distant siren
that changes the weather
♪ Oh, better
the devil you know
♪ Than the devil you don't
♪ Never say never
♪ You'll find that
you feel like a fool
♪ Walking and walking
♪ You follow
the light of the moon
♪ Seems like you're moving
But time's standing still
♪ Now it all looks familiar
I've run up that hill
♪ And I'll do it forever
♪ I'll dance with the devil
I will
♪ Those white lights
♪ Those dark nights
♪ You say
♪ I'll never go
♪ Haunting is heavy
and pleasure
♪ It weighs the most
♪ He was the same
when he'd stay up for days
♪ With your ghost
♪ Better the tether
that keeps us together
♪ I've been here before
and I'll stay here forever
♪ Oh, better the devil you know
♪ Than the devil you don't
♪ Than the devil
♪ You don't ♪
♪ Back into the blue
♪ The honeymoon's over
♪ Take the shot
♪ Throw the salt
over your shoulder
♪ Did "no" mean never?
♪ That's what your eyes
appear to say
♪ My indecision is final
♪ I made my bed
That's where I'll stay
♪ Back into the blue
♪ Obey it as it lays
♪ Day for night
It's been night for days
♪ Don't hold my shadow
♪ I'm just the echo
in the leaves
♪ That it will never
come again
♪ Is what makes life so sweet ♪
♪ The daring of despair
♪ Has led me
back to my old home
♪ Paralyzed by patterns
on my wall
♪ You're sitting there
before me
♪ But I'm haunted by your ghost
♪ Were you ever
really mine at all?
♪ Slipping in slow motion now
♪ We're waiting for the drop
♪ Tempo's getting slower
♪ It's too much
to keep this up
♪ I just can't stop
loving you
♪ No matter what I do
or how hard I might try
♪ I can't let go,
I'll die inside
♪ I just can't stop
loving you
♪ No matter what I do
♪ Your shadow's in my way
♪ You follow me into the fire
♪ Captured by the cruelty
of my touch
♪ We're only bones
and bruises now
♪ Sadistic, base and vile
♪ I don't even miss myself
that much
♪ We're toxic
but it feels so good
♪ I'm crying through a smile
♪ We're gutting
all the ones we love
♪ But doing it in style
♪ I just can't stop loving you
♪ No matter what I do
or how hard I might try
♪ I can't let go,
I'll die inside
♪ I just can't stop loving you
♪ No matter what I do
♪ Unending echoes
in a resonating shell
♪ I'll make you sick
to get you up
♪ To make you mine
♪ I just can't stop loving you
♪ No matter what I do
or how hard I might cry
♪ I can't let go,
I'll die inside
♪ I just can't stop loving you
♪ No matter what I do ♪
From the high desert
in the majestic American West,
I bid you all good evening.
Or good morning,
or good afternoon,
wherever you may be
across this great land of ours.
This is the world famous,
Shore to Spooky Shore AM,
dark night in the desert.
And I'm Art Pallone.