(CLOCK TICKING)
(CLOCK CONTINUES TICKING)
WOMAN: Have a good day,
madame.
(DOORBELL BUZZES)
(TICKING CONTINUES)
-Good morning, Professor.
-Good morning.
Not wallowing in myopia.
Kierkegaard said that,
I think...
Yeah, but isn't that,
like, implied?
That it's preferable for one
to focus only on themselves.
Mmm. Busy week, Alma.
Mmm. I'm aware.
PATRICIA He's at Knox's
lecture, sucking up. Ha!
ALMA: See you tonight,
Patricia.
(CLOCK CONTINUES TICKING)
Foucault paints
a picture of public torture
performed in order to
maintain the social contract
of a time
in which displays of power...
(DOOR CLOSES)
Faviola.
-The table looks beautiful.
-Thank you.
(CLOCK STOPS TICKING)
(MELLOW JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
ALMA: I'm not
contesting the...
perceived existence
of a collective morality.
I'm...
saying that...
I'm saying that
pretending that the ethics
of a society
hasn't always started
with the highly biased
stone-throwing court
of public opinion...
Maggie.
(SOFTLY) Uh, yeah.
Is a convenient illusion.
Aimed at what?
Aimed at making us, as people,
feel as though
we once had a plan
for ourselves. We were...
better or more united.
Weren't we?
Would you say
we've always agreed on...
God or sex or race or politics,
or were there just fewer voices,
less easily amassed in dissent?
That reminds me,
what did you say?
What was the thing you said?
What's that thing you said?
-"Performative discontent."
-Discontent.
Ah! Oof!
You read Maggie's
dissertation, right?
Of course.
HANK: She's giving me
little scraps.
That's all I'm getting,
But what I have read is...
-Is barely coherent?
-No.
I'm curious
what you think, Alma.
I think it has potential
to be great.
Truly great.
So why're you hiding it?
Why? Why? You're tight.
Why're you so tight?
All your generation,
everyone in your generation,
you're so tight.
-Fuckin' why. I'm so sorry.
-Look at life. Look at that.
Perfect. Exemplar.
What are you scared of?
Scared of saying
the wrong thing or, uh,
-offending someone.
-I'm sorry about that.
When did offending someone
become the preeminent
cardinal sin?
I mean,
I don't have a date exactly...
That's fine.
...but maybe it's around
the same time your generation
started making sweeping
generalizations about ours.
Are you scared that we're
gonna think less of you
if it isn't perfect?
Whatever shame you have
around your self-expression,
it is...
it's false. It's bullshit.
-It's bullshit.
-Bullshit.
-Bullshit?
HANK: You can't corrupt
your individual purpose,
your clarity of voice. It's...
it's too lucid.
Okay. Um...
That feels like my cue
to use the restroom.
Why?
'Cause you
need the restroom or...
ALMA: Oh, honey, uh,
don't go to the usual one,
'cause Frederik has a...
project in there.
Uh, go to the guest one
down the hall.
'Kay.
And then she said that
all along, you know?
Man, I cannot...
I agree with her
in the beginning...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES)
MAN 1:
Keep it up, okay?
This is exactly the tactic
and it's doing things.
MAN 2: Well, I don't
wanna always be a contrarian.
MAN 1: Why not?
My sense is that the two of you
might feel rather bereft
once you've gotten
the thing you've been
so fixated on
for the past six years, hmm?
Sometimes...
a wish fulfilled...
can be more baffling than the...
longing preceding it.
It's not a sure thing.
Oh... Hey, come on, Alma.
Don't let your modesty
veer into delusion.
It's not a, um...
it's not a mountaintop, Fred.
It's not some egoic...
teleological pursuit
to tenure. It's...
It's a threshold. It's just
a threshold to more freedom...
to freedom,
to follow any impulse,
any desire,
any interest you want
without fear
of systemic reproach.
FREDERIK: Oh, I'm not
questioning its value.
I'm saying that...
(SMACKS LIPS)
Well, it is a significant thing
to work
your whole life for, hmm?
Being above accountability,
uh, consequence.
What happens if, uh,
one of you gets it
and the other doesn't?
(CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES) Oof.
If it's me and not you,
will you be angry?
Yeah, I'll be rageful. Yeah.
-Me too.
-(LAUGHING)
If it's you
and not me. Furious.
FREDERIK: Or will
the strain of it
be too much for your friendship?
Hank, I'm fearing,
doesn't like to lose.
(SNIFFLES)
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(WHISPERING) Shit.
Fuck.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
But seriously, how many
of the people we teach...
Mmm, mmm.
Have private lives that
wouldn't pass today's muster?
Hmm.
-All. Well, most. Plenty.
-Most. Precisely. So...
But we forgive it.
Why? Because...
-we have to figure out...
-Best to forgive it.
...how to forgive it,
because they're canonical.
Nietzsche easily
lends himself to
-Lebensraum propaganda.
-Carl Schmitt...
doesn't just lend himself,
he was a Nazi.
HANK: Sure, sure. Um...
Hegel, uh, couldn't...
-control little Hegel.
-Okay.
-Heidegger.
-Little?
Heidegger treated Arendt
like shit.
Well, that whole dynamic,
fucked up.
So I don't think we can
appropriate blame one way
or the other.
Aristotle, xenophobe.
-Oh, they were all racist.
-HANK: Yeah.
-And Freud was a misogynist.
-HANK: Hmm.
ALMA: Did you
hear that, darling?
HANK: Freud was
a misogynist, darling.
Oh, it was a different time.
(ALMA AND HANK LAUGHING)
ARTHUR: Um,
you know, if you're
-worried about tenure...
-(SOFTLY) You okay?
-ARTHUR: ...you shouldn't be.
-Yeah.
Me? Oh.
-Oh...
-(CLEARS THROAT)
Um...
Well, I mean, you were
gonna get it anyway,
but you'll definitely
get it now.
ALMA: What do you mean?
MAGGIE: Let's not.
ALMA: No, come on,
I'm interested.
-Illuminate us.
-Okay. Okay.
You can't deny it's the culture.
-Mm-hmm.
-The common enemy
has been newly chosen,
and it is the straight,
white, cis man.
MAGGIE: Okay, Arthur,
I'm so sorry,
'cause I just had, like,
I had no idea that you were
going through this...
that you were feeling
so victimized.
ARTHUR: I literally
never said that.
You didn't have to.
But you're still bemoaning
the fact that you're...
white and male and, uh,
straight and,
regrettably, cis...
in a time when the overt culture
is just pretending,
like, you know
it's pretend, right,
pretending to not
prefer these things,
and that makes you, what,
the first man in this room or...
-or in history...
-History.
...to feel fucked over
by society's bad opinion?
(STUTTERING)
-No.
-All I'm saying...
is that it used to be
that a man would edge out
an equally qualified woman
because he was a man.
But now a woman
does just edge out
an equally qualified man
because she's a woman.
(MAGGIE LAUGHS)
So let me get this straight.
What you're saying is...
that even despite...
the many professional
accolades I have accrued
over the years in a...
deeply misogynistic environment,
even despite coming back
after a...
protracted absence,
only to affirm
my singular position
as a woman in the field,
my prospective tenure couldn't
possibly be earned because
its awarding happens to coincide
with higher education's
sudden subservience
-to inclusivity.
-(SCOFFS)
-Did I get that right, Arthur?
-No, I mean, I'm not...
-Did I miss anything?
-I'm not trying to...
-Tart.
-Hey, it's a tart break.
It's a tart break.
Everybody here.
-Hey! You're beautiful.
-ARTHUR: I didn't mean to...
You're beautiful.
You did great.
-You did fine. Oh, yeah.
-You could've backed me up...
a little bit, man.
HANK: It was,
it was fun while it lasted.
I wanted you to see
how you did on your own.
You did okay.
ARTHUR: Okay.
HANK: Have some tart.
ARTHUR: You wanted
to watch the Titanic sink.
HANK: Drop the grandiosity,
eat the fucking tart.
ARTHUR: Uh, no.
I never wanna eat again.
HANK: Tart.
MAGGIE: Don't be
so dramatic, Arthur.
-I mean, it's just a comment.
-(HANK CHUCKLES)
HANK: Maggie, give it to him.
He's, you know,
it takes courage to be
that kind of a moron.
MAGGIE: Yeah,
maybe you shouldn't, Arthur.
Think of that?
A slow death might suit your
new-found martyrdom. Arthur.
-ARTHUR: Tart.
-Don't forget the cream.
(CHUCKLES)
We won't forget the cream.
FREDERIK: Thank you.
ALMA: That will be all.
Don't talk.
-Bye, Fred.
-See you. See you in class.
-Make him stop talking.
-Thank you, sir. Thanks.
-Make him...
-Good night.
Oh, that boy can just
talk and talk and talk and talk.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Hmm.
HANK: I don't think
there's anything wrong...
Don't look at me like that.
Oh, I didn't say anything.
You're the worst
at hiding your feelings.
Well, coming from
the welterweight champion,
I'm flattered.
I'm fine. I haven't had
any pain in weeks.
It was a nice evening.
I'm just capping it off.
I imagine it was nice, hmm,
for you.
Nice to bask
in Hank's continued obsession.
The least he could do
is hide it better.
We're friends. Always will be.
Hank's and Maggie's...
adoration of you.
-Maggie. Just...
-MAGGIE: Stop. (LAUGHS)
Just because Maggie is gay...
it doesn't mean she's
in love with me, Frederik.
I'm saying you tend
to choose people, hmm?
HANK: Maggie.
Elevate people to the status
of your approval
because they worship you
on bended knee, huh?
Not because of any
actual merit on their part.
Maggie is brilliant.
Hmm, is she?
Or does she just think
you're brilliant?
(SNAPS FINGERS) Huh?
-I don't know.
-"I don't know."
-Hi. Oh, sorry. Sorry.
-Oh. Hi.
Oh, did you have a nice night?
-Yeah.
-The pork was too tough.
Oh, well, if you roast it
past 145 degrees,
it is technically kosher.
MAGGIE: You never did that,
but your efforts are duly noted.
Well, I put something together
for you to take to Alex.
Oh, no, they're not
coming back for a minute.
They're still in Boston.
No, it's already done.
Look, it's done, right?
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
-MAGGIE: Thank you.
Thank you.
And thank you both
for a lovely evening, really.
These things are never lovely,
but you're sweet to lie.
-(CHUCKLES)
-Nice, hmm?
-Thank you.
-There you are.
-Thank you so much.
-That enough? Let's see...
Whoa!
-Okay.
-(HANK SPEAKING FRENCH)
-(FREDERIK SPEAKING HEBREW)
-(IN ENGLISH) Okay. Well...
(SIGHS)
-Ciao.
-Hmm.
Freddie, hooyah.
-Cheers, Henry.
-(ALMA CHUCKLES)
-Say that ten times fast.
-That was freakin' phenomenal.
-Peace out...
-Thanks for everything.
...as the students say.
-Phenomenal fifth, Fred.
-MAGGIE: Good night.
FREDERIK: Good night.
MAGGIE: Peace out.
(ALMA EXHALES)
ALMA: Hank,
no smoking in the hall.
No smoking in the...
-Go. Go.
-(CHUCKLES)
HANK: You can have your own,
you know.
You want, you want your own?
MAGGIE: You know it's not
the seventies anymore, right?
-HANK: Narc.
-Stop.
-Teacher's pet.
-Fuck off.
I don't know, I think you're
the teacher's pet, huh?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
-Come on.
-(LAUGHS)
-MAGGIE: Fuck off.
-Fuck off.
(SIGHS) Hugo.
(BOTH SPEAKING FRENCH)
(CLOCK TICKING)
Faviola?
I'm sure we
wore you out tonight.
What do we owe you?
FAVIOLA: It's 350, madam.
(EXHALES)
I don't know
what we'd do without you.
-Thank... (GASPS)
-Thank you.
-(GRUNTING)
-Miss Mendelssohn?
Are you all right?
-(PAINED GRUNTS)
-Take your water.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Ah, thank you. Thank you.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Thank you.
(UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(ALMA VOMITING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(TOILET FLUSHES)
(GARGLES, SPITS)
(EXHALES, SNIFFLES)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(STUDENTS CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY)
Good afternoon.
We were discussing Foucault's
expansion on the Panopticon.
Right?
The Panopticon,
or the police state
in which we all as citizens
are conscripted to observe
and study one another
for missteps,
as opposed to being at the mercy
of an ultimate authority.
This unconscious enlistment...
FREDERIK
Making a cassoulet tonight.
See you later?
HANK Yes to drink
ALMA Meet at Three Sheets
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
ALMA TO MAGGIE
????
-There we go.
-(YELPING)
(LAUGHING)
-Can you behave yourself?
-Nobody, nobody panic.
It's been a long day. Oh!
Wait, wait, wait. No, look.
Did you talk to Micheron
last night?
No.
-I listened to Micheron...
-Oh.
-You're just jealous...
-...last night.
...'cause he's better looking
than you.
Ah! (GASPS, SIGHS)
I was trapped with Find,
and he, oh,
just oozing the desperation
of still being relegated
to adjunct.
-It's awful.
-Yeah. It's a...
-(BOTH CHUCKLING)
-Believe me.
That's the thing
about horse races.
Now tenure is what?
Winning the Kentucky Derby?
This particular
equine metaphor, yeah.
All right, so what's the thing?
Oh.
(WHISPERING)
Only the thoroughbreds
have a chance at winning.
MAN: Here, take these.
Do you think what Frederik
said after dinner...
there's anything to that?
I don't know
what you're referring to...
but almost positive
of my answer. (CHUCKLES)
No, just, what's gonna happen?
You know, when...
when it's won, when it's over.
Everybody talks about, you know,
reaching for the brass ring
but nobody says what you do
when you win it.
Hey, is this mine?
BARTENDER: Sure thing.
I think we celebrate.
BARTENDER: Ladies.
Enjoy those.
And then we just get
right back to work.
Next publication, the next book.
-Opera Completa...
-All right.
The Locke lectures.
All right, all right,
all right. Okay.
(CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTS)
Where is Fred tonight?
Making a cassoulet.
WOMAN 1:
Can I get a beer, please?
BARTENDER: Sure thing.
(SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
It's just a withering thing
to say about a man.
-(CHUCKLES)
-Um...
It's quite a good cassoulet.
He's gonna break eventually,
you know.
No.
He won't.
Yeah. No, he won't.
Mmm.
Talked to Maggie today?
No, she wasn't in class.
No call, no show.
I think I've just extended her
too much rope.
(STUDENTS CHEERING,
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
MALE STUDENT: Hey!
How we doin'? You good?
-Hey. Hey.
-(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
I miss when it was only us
that liked this place.
I can't hear you. (CHUCKLING)
-You okay?
-Yeah. (CHUCKLING)
Uh...
You got this?
-Once a poor kid...
-Always a cheap bastard.
Mmm-hmm.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
-Stop doing that to me.
-What is this?
-Bye.
(KISSES)
That's on me. That's for you.
Keep working on that.
(LAUGHS)
-Check, please.
-BARTENDER: Coming right up.
Here you go.
(ELEVATOR DOOR OPENING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Maggie, what're you doing here?
Um, I came by,
I went to your office,
but you weren't there.
Oh. All right, well,
why don't you come inside?
MAGGIE: Is Frederik home?
Probably.
Um, Jesus, you're soaking.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I... I need...
I need to speak with you.
Okay. Come on,
let's just go inside.
-I'll get you a towel.
-Alone, please.
Um, okay.
Yeah, I guess it's just, um...
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Hank walked me home
like I said he would.
It was friendly.
You know, he's Hank.
Everybody loves Hank. Um...
And, uh, Alex isn't home.
I think I said yesterday,
they're still in Boston, um...
(STUTTERS)
He asked for a nightcap,
which, you know,
fine, whatever, and...
I think, I don't even remember
what I poured us.
It was something
Alex brought home
from a party a few weeks ago.
(SLOW TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Uh...
It was fine.
I don't know. I don't think
I realized how drunk he was
until I saw him, like,
stumble in the kitchen. Um...
Uh... And...
he started asking, like,
inappropriate questions.
I guess first, you know,
it was about my work.
The... My paper.
And then he asked about Alex
and if we had any men
in the relationship, and...
Um...
when he kissed me, I almost,
I thought it was
like a joke or something.
I didn't do anything.
Um, and then
he kept going, and...
I said no...
and he kept going and, um...
When he left, I showered.
(SHUDDERING BREATHS)
What are you saying happened?
MAGGIE: What do you mean?
What are you saying he did?
Isn't it obvious?
He...
He crossed the line.
He kept going after I said no.
ALMA: But what
actually happened?
Why do you need to know?
He assaulted me.
Does it need to get
worse than that?
Do you need to hear a...
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Does anyone else know?
Just you, so far.
And I don't know. I...
Why me?
What?
Uh, I, um...
I don't know. I just...
It's the right thing to do,
isn't it?
To tell someone, and I just...
You know, given your history...
What does that mean, my history?
(STUTTERS) What do you mean?
-I don't know. What...
-Why are you saying that?
-I didn't mean anything.
-What does it mean?
You asked it.
It's gotta mean something.
I just thought your history
supporting women
in the department.
-I don't know, that's...
-Okay.
Why don't you just come inside?
I can get you a towel...
-No. I'm sorry. I'm...
-...and we can talk.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
I'm sorry.
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
(SIGHS)
(KEYS JANGLING)
(UNNERVING MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
FREDERIK: Hmm.
It's late.
Mmm. I'm sorry. The paper.
Of course, the paper.
ALMA: If I don't publish
this month...
Mmm. Your position isn't
as secure, etcetera, etcetera.
Publish or perish.
Mmm-hmm, up or out.
(SIGHS)
I missed the cassoulet.
Oh, I left some in the oven.
-I don't deserve you.
-Hmm.
(SIGHS)
Who did you see today?
What?
No, no, no, it's just,
you never wanna talk
about my work.
-That's not true.
-Oh.
Darling, please.
We're too old and too married
to lie to each other
so blatantly, hmm?
I saw a teenager who hates me...
a woman who's lying to herself
about her husband's cheating...
and another patient. New.
A referral from Tim?
Hmm? Told you about him.
ALMA: I thought
he annoyed you.
-(CHUCKLES)
-ALMA: Interesting?
Uh, remains to be seen.
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS) Have...
Have you ever...
Yes?
Have you ever disagreed
with a patient over...
a sensitive issue?
Course.
You know, most people
don't come to analysis
looking to break old patterns.
They're looking to affirm
that they don't need help.
Did you tell them so?
(FREDERIK CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
My father told me a story once
from when he was first
building his practice.
He, um...
He was working with
a young woman who was...
(CHUCKLES)
So wedded to her own misery,
it drove him mad.
And one day, he told her
she lacked the ability
to overcome repeating
the same patterns
for the rest
of her small, miserable life.
-She never came in again.
-Hmm.
Obviously.
Why?
What's this about?
ALMA: Nothing.
Mmm, I don't know.
I don't know.
I think I'm just starving.
Dinner awaits.
(ALMA CHUCKLES)
-Again, I don't deserve you.
-FREDERIK: Again...
no one is contesting that.
(ALMA SIGHS)
Did something happen?
With a student?
No.
(INHALES)
I wonder if...
I can be cold sometimes.
Cold? You?
ALMA: I mean it.
(SIGHS)
Impenetrable, maybe, hmm?
Aloof, sure. But no, no...
I don't think you're cold...
(UTENSIL CLANKS)
...or unfeeling.
I didn't say unfeeling.
(ALMA CLEARS THROAT)
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
(SIGHS)
Hey, thanks for comin'.
ALMA: I don't have
a lot of time.
What do you want?
Uh... Can we talk inside?
Okay, look.
I don't know what she's told you
or what's already
going around with the faculty.
(SIGHS)
I know I sound like one
of those guys, but there's...
I feel like there's no way
to avoid clichés here.
In fact, everything about this
feels like a fuckin' cliché.
And I know... (CHUCKLES)
I know that by saying that,
I'm making myself out
to be the victim.
Just blameless entity
in this fucking ouroboros
of he-said-she-said.
But see, this is...
(INHALES SHARPLY)
This is what I mean.
I'm damned if I do,
I'm damned if I don't.
Everything I say
has been said before
by someone in my position,
who was probably guilty.
Therefore, I'm guilty
by association. But...
-Hey. Hey.
-Hey. Ready to order?
-Yeah. Please. Thank you.
-Mmm-hmm.
I'm fine.
-Okay.
-I'll have my usual.
-Yeah. You got it.
-Thank you.
Nothing for you?
No.
Okay.
"My usual"?
(UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING)
Yeah.
Okay.
It's not true.
Alma, it's just... It's not.
I swear.
It all happened so quick,
like wildebeest scattering
from an approaching lion.
One minute you're part
of the pack, next minute,
your leg is in the jaws
of some apex predator
and everyone's thinkin',
"All right. Well, damn.
Glad it wasn't me."
I'm not sure that's
what everyone is thinking.
WAITRESS: Okay.
-We got the saag paneer.
-Ooh, yeah.
Yep. And we got
the tandoori chicken.
Tandoori chicken. Oh, yeah.
And then,
we've got the garlic naan.
Garlic naan...
Give me that garlic naan.
-(CHUCKLING) Yeah.
-Goddamn. Thank you.
And the basmati rice.
-Oof.
-And then a plate.
Just in case you wanted it.
Yeah, just in case
I need to... Yeah.
-Sorry.
-Yeah, you can give that
to her. Thank you very much.
I appreciate it.
And then, you guys got cutlery?
-You okay?
-We're all good.
-All right. Great. Okay.
-Appreciate you, Billie.
-Enjoy. Yep.
-Thank you.
ALMA: So, are you gonna
tell me why this is not true?
Or did you just ask me here
to check to see
if I was bearing pitchfork?
Caught Maggie cheating,
a few months ago.
Didn't think much of it, really.
She, um,
you know, I talked to her,
she said she was
under enormous pressure.
I told her...
You know, I gave her a pass,
and she...
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Well, yeah.
But I wasn't convinced.
Not totally.
And then...
Her dissertation?
What about it?
You don't know?
I knew immediately.
She plagiarized it.
She lifted directly
from Agamben's Homo Sacer.
His notion of...
simultaneous subjectification
and de-subjectification,
it's reproduced
almost word for word.
You had to have seen, too.
Didn't you?
So, when you brought it up
at the dinner...
you just wanted
to see what I would say?
Or you were trying
to catch us out?
I wanted to see
how she would react.
-Especially in your company.
-ALMA: Mmm.
HANK: Test my hunch.
ALMA: Test your hunch?
I mean, we did go back
to her apartment that night.
I asked her for a nightcap.
(CHUCKLES) Why? Why?
Yeah, I know. I know.
That was a mistake.
A huge fuckin' mistake.
I just, I thought that
if we were on her turf,
off campus, she would be,
she would be...
more open, less guarded,
you know?
I wanted, perhaps erroneously,
stupidly, to...
ALMA: Definitely stupidly.
To see if what I assumed
was true, was true.
So, we had the drinks. And...
You know, at this point...
(CHUCKLES)
I'm fucking nervous.
I mean, you know
who her parents are.
They donated
half the fuckin' campus, so...
And then, and then,
unprompted, she says to me...
(INHALES SHARPLY)
...that her partner
was out of town.
Truthfully, listen,
I know this sounds
so brutally male, but...
I really did think
she was coming on to me.
(CHUCKLES)
And I'm fuckin' terrified!
'Cause of the climate in
higher education these days.
Then why would you go
to a female student's apartment?
And drink something
she poured you?
Believe me, in retrospect?
(IMITATES SPEECH IMPEDIMENT)
I fuckin' know!
(SPEAKING NORMALLY) But I was
stubbornly stuck on this.
I needed to bring up
my suspicions to her...
to let her know
she would be held accountable.
So, I did. I told her
I suspected she plagiarized,
and she reacted just like...
(IMITATES WHOOSH)
Like, cold, ice calm.
Denied it. And then...
the next day... it's like...
like... (SCOFFING CHUCKLE)
An utter fabrication.
(INHALES)
And now, it's gonna be...
it's gonna be her word...
against a lifetime
of hard work and good deeds,
and advocating
for women in philosophy,
workin' three fuckin' jobs.
You know.
And it took me years
to get through
all that debt and red tape.
And I'm not gonna let it happen.
I can't. I won't.
I'm not gonna allow.
I worked too hard.
Done too much to get here,
to let it all just be
taken away,
just 'cause some lying
little fuckin' bitch
with a shit ton of money,
exploiting this shallow
cultural moment says I should.
(SIGHS)
All right. Please don't ever
fucking say that
-to anyone but me.
-(HANK CHUCKLES)
They're gonna wanna
speak with you.
Why me?
HANK: Since it was
after your party
she's sayin' all this happened.
Now that you know the truth,
my hope
is that you will not allow
what is correct
keep you from doing
what is right.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Professor Imhoff. I don't
believe I was expecting you.
She's not on the schedule, sir.
If you have a minute,
I'd like to speak with you.
Alma, sit.
(GRUNTS)
So...
I imagine you know why I'm here.
A formal inquiry is going
to be conducted, yes,
with all haste and via
the appropriate channels.
Well, I think it's important
I pre-empt those channels.
I believe there is
a conflict of interest
that would preclude me from
speaking either without bias
or without the assumption
of bias should I be asked.
But I believe I will be asked.
I'm just relieved
you're not here about tenure.
It's a minefield, Alma.
A fucking minefield these days.
You keep the fancy stuff
for show?
I hate that Laphroaig shit.
But what looks good,
looks good, and
against all odds,
I've found myself
in the business of optics
rather than substance.
I have to teach later.
Ah, of course. Purpose.
Not just...
Sisyphean administration.
Maybe your secretary
could use some.
Hey, be nice to Wendy.
She still believes
what she does is important.
So, this "conflict of interest,"
do I wanna know?
It's nothing like that.
Good. Thank God.
So then, off the record?
(INHALES)
Off the record.
HANK: (CLEARS THROAT) How many
more times do you think
we're gonna
have to pretend that...
Dr. John Ensler
is capable of anything
remotely close to...
(INHALES DEEPLY)
...illuminating conversation.
You're here.
HANK: Yeah.
Told you I would be.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
You look strange.
(CHUCKLES) You scared me.
I'm eating cheese.
Hmm.
Got a watered down red.
Save you a spot.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
Popular discussion topic.
Who would have thought?
(SIGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
I was surprised the other day.
I reacted poorly.
It's not news
that's easy to hear.
Imagine telling it.
I reacted in a way
that I shouldn't have,
as a teacher and someone
who considers you a friend.
He's in there, Maggie.
-I...
-(SIGHS)
ALMA: I didn't think
he would come,
or I would have warned you.
I have a right to these spaces.
(BREATHES HEAVILY) I have
just as much right as he does.
You don't have to go in there.
Okay?
-I need the lecture credit.
-(CHUCKLES)
I'll sign off on it.
Who cares?
Who cares. Right.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
I'm, um... (SMACKS LIPS)
I've decided to press charges
against Hank.
And I'm hoping...
It would mean a lot to me...
Um...
if I had your support, of me.
More specifically, um,
your testimony.
If we have to go to trial.
You have a lawyer?
-Yeah.
-Hmm.
Sort of. I don't know.
Alex? Isn't she pre-law?
They're in their second year,
and it's more
of a consulting thing.
-I don't know.
-Did you go to a clinic
to collect DNA evidence
and photos?
I don't think we should be
talking about this here.
Yes...
-I did.
-Right. The university one.
That's good.
Uh, no. The one on Whitney.
And I...
I went, but I...
I don't know. I was there.
Um, I was...
I walked, you know.
And I was by myself.
It was late, and, uh,
there was
this group of guys there
and they were just, like,
standing outside
and staring at me.
I don't know. I...
I panicked. And I know
I shouldn't have, but I...
I saw a security camera...
and so,
they'll have me walking up.
And, um, I...
I went to you first.
So, even without, you know,
a certain type
of physical evidence
with the tape
and with your testimony,
it should, you know...
(STUTTERING) ...there could
still be, like, a case.
Right?
Maggie, I didn't see anything.
I don't know
what you want me to say.
I believe you.
You know I believe you.
I told the Dean of Humanities
as much today.
You did?
I did, but I...
I don't know what good
I could do in your case
if it comes to that.
In fact, I might hurt it.
How?
The last thing
you said to me that night
was that he was gonna
walk you home.
And then I saw the two of you
in the hallway, together,
leaving willingly is what
it looked like to me,
if I were to be asked
under oath.
Yeah, but that's not what I'm...
what I'm asking for.
What I'm saying...
Everything okay?
Yes, Professor Angler.
Thank you.
ANNOUNCER: Everyone,
please take your seats.
-They're starting.
-You should hurry.
ANNOUNCER: We'll be
starting momentarily.
(CHUCKLES)
ANNOUNCER: Please join me
in extending...
-Maggie.
-Alma...
ANNOUNCER: ...a warm welcome
to the esteemed researcher,
scholar, and transregional
studies expert...
I can count on you, right?
ANNOUNCER: Dr. Hugo Micheron.
DR. HUGO MICHERON: Thank you!
It's such a pleasure to be here.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
Thank you.
Thank you for having me.
(REGGAE MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS)
(SNIFFS)
(MATCHES RATTLING IN BOX)
(CRACKLING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DOOR OPENS)
Who presented last?
Arthur?
(UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING)
Excuse me.
What are you doing here?
(SIGHS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Who are you?
-How could you?
-What are...
Go to my office.
Just wait for me...
I was fired this morning.
Not suspended. I was fired.
STUDENT: He's gonna see us.
Don't open the door.
ALMA: If you wanna talk,
we can talk,
but not here, and not now.
Not here.
I told you the truth.
You just blatantly ignored it
just to save yourself.
You are being paranoid.
Just go to my office
and wait for me.
Oh, no. Oh.
No, I think I'm right
on top of something.
Something that I just
couldn't see before.
You see, I used to think
that you and me,
we had a mutual fealty
to integrity, to the ethics
that you so glibly teach.
But I'm realizing I gave you
too much fucking credit.
You sound insane right now.
Professor Imhoff?
-Are you okay?
-Oh. Uh...
No, I don't know,
actually, Katie. I'm not sure.
This blood on her hands
may never wash off.
Stop it. Yeah, I'm fine,
Katie. Thank you.
FEMALE STUDENT: Yeah,
we should go. Come on.
KATIE: No. No.
I need to stay here.
(HANK BREATHING HEAVILY)
You know the truth
and you won't say it.
Because it'll make you look bad.
You're lettin' them fuckin'
ruin me, ruin my fucking life
and you could easily stop it.
You give me
too much power, Hank.
I did not do this.
You did this to yourself.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Oh, that's convenient.
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
Yeah, I know.
I fell on my own sword...
but you were the one holding it.
"Let innocence make
false accusation blush..."
"And tyranny tremble
at patience."
Fucking coward!
-Fuck you.
-HANK: Fuck you!
Hey! Fuck you!
-(CHUCKLES)
-Fuck you!
(MAGGIE BREATHING HEAVILY)
Fuck all of you!
Fuck you!
Fuckin' privileged...
coddled hypocrites!
Ugh!
Alma, Alma.
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
-(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
(PANTING)
(MAGGIE SOBBING)
(VOICE BREAKING)
It really happened?
I didn't just make it up,
right? It's real?
If it's real to you, it's real.
(SOBBING)
Everybody keeps looking at me
like I did something horrible.
But he's the one.
He's the one.
-You want my advice?
-Please.
Tell me what to fucking do
and I'll do it, please.
-Please, just help me.
-Okay. Okay.
Tonight, come over,
and we can talk.
Or not talk. You don't
have to have the answers.
I'll cook.
Well, Frederik will cook.
-All right?
-(SNIFFLES)
Okay?
Okay.
(MAGGIE SNIFFLING)
(SIGHS)
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
FREDERIK: It's late.
Why don't we start?
I'm sure she's on her way.
You'd start without me,
if I was late.
Oh, you're being childish.
I wish I had the leeway
to be childish
in this relationship.
Give it 10 minutes, okay?
And even then,
we'll probably still...
be waiting.
Probably, yes.
Why?
Because it's fucking polite.
Because you care more
about kowtowing
to a mediocre student
with rich parents
-than you do about...
-(DOORBELL BUZZES)
Hmm.
(DOOR OPENS)
MAGGIE: Hi.
I wasn't expecting you.
ALMA: Who were you expecting?
Mmm-hmm-hmm.
So, Maggie,
how's the dissertation coming?
Um...
-It's coming along.
-Mmm.
And what is it
that you're exploring?
It's not
particularly interesting.
Well, I'd like to hear.
Please, I'm curious.
Okay. Um...
Well...
it's mainly concerning
the, um, resurgence
of virtue ethics.
Or the outward display
of moral character
as the new model
for personal morality,
as opposed to following, uh,
social duties and rules
or Karmic thought.
Things like that.
Sorry if it's a bit confusing.
It's so boring, I'm sure.
No, no, no.
I like listening to you talk.
How often do you make doro wat?
I'm curious. What drew you
to virtue ethics?
-What drew me...
-Well, I'm...
You're spending, what,
four or five years
of your life on this, right?
Why?
-What, um...
-(CHUCKLES)
What turns you on about it?
Um...
Well, it's become very popular,
-of late.
-Hmm.
And as you might know
or even recall...
it was sort of invented
in the '60s and '70s,
when society was radicalizing
and now that we're
radicalizing again,
I find that interesting.
-Interesting?
-MAGGIE: Yes. Interesting.
-Frederik.
-I'm sorry,
did I say something wrong?
No, no, no. I'm sorry.
I'm intruding.
Forgive me.
I'm sure without me present,
you ladies can talk about
such interesting topics
with much more freedom.
Excuse me.
(BOMBASTIC MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
(ALMA SIGHS)
I'm sorry, Maggie.
He's an asshole.
(CHUCKLES)
Does he want me to feel, like,
stupid or something?
(MUSIC CONTINUES
PLAYING MUFFLED)
(SMACKS LIPS)
(SCOFFS)
Alex didn't want me
to come tonight.
Well, she's also an asshole.
-Yeah, they can sometimes...
-"They."
-...be a little bit...
-(SCOFFING) "They". Right.
-Stop.
-Okay.
They thought it would do
more harm than good
to be back here so soon
with you all.
ALMA: Well, I guess
we didn't prove them wrong.
Yeah, they don't find you
especially trustworthy.
ALMA: What do you think?
(LOUD MUSIC BLARES)
(MUSIC CONTINUES
PLAYING MUFFLED)
You know, I used to think
I could rely on myself,
that I could... (INHALES)
...trust my instincts,
about people, about myself.
Now, (SMACKS LIPS)
I'm not so sure.
I certainly didn't
anticipate this
getting so big so fast,
or being something that would
resonate with so many people.
Like, a lot of women,
you know, DMing me,
stopping me on campus,
with similar stories and...
A reporter approached me.
I declined to comment...
but she gave me her card.
I kept it.
-And...
-And I don't know.
(ALMA CLEARS THROAT)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Don't do it, Maggie.
Don't tell your story to someone
who just wants to turn it
into something they can sell.
I... I am telling you, if you
move forward with this,
if you press charges,
you will become radioactive.
Hmm? I... I...
I know that you want to believe
in the fairness
of the system, but...
(SMACKS LIPS)
Higher education is run
by white men
and you need those white men
to hire you, and they won't
because they will be terrified
you will do
the same thing to them
if they ask you to work late
or touch your shoulder
for too long.
It, not your work, is what
anyone is going to see
when they look at you.
I promise.
(SIGHS)
And what if I don't care to be
a career academic?
(LOUD MUSIC BLARES)
(EXHALES, SMACKS LIPS)
You need to decide
what you care about,
yourself or...
(LOUD MUSIC BLARES)
You need to decide
what you care about,
yourself or what you want
to do for yourself.
And which would you choose?
I think you know.
Sometimes, it's about
taking the long view.
Can we just stop being smart
for, like, one fucking second?
I... I... I feel like you're
completely removing me
from what happened to me.
Like, you're speaking in these
hypothetical riddles
about women writ large
when I'm sitting right here
in front of you.
I just... (SCOFFS)
I thought you wanted my advice.
I do... I did. I do.
I don't know. It's just, um...
(SMACKS LIPS) So...
Because women are penalized
for speaking out, I shouldn't?
That's your logic?
I mean, that's just so...
And then what? He just
gets to get away with it?
And relocate
to another university
and give speeches,
and write books
and sleep with other students
all over again? That is...
Well, I think Hank
is pretty well fucked,
so I wouldn't worry about that.
So you think
I ruined his life? (CHUCKLES)
I didn't say that.
Am I not owed this?
I mean, this happened to me,
and I'm not even allowed
to speak about it?
You can do
whatever you like, Maggie.
(LOUD MUSIC BLARES)
(EXHALES)
(MUSIC BLARES)
(SIGHS)
(SMACKS LIPS)
Just not with your support.
I support whatever you choose,
but I think what you want
is restorative justice
and what you are getting
is vengeance.
And I would be doing
a disservice to you
to let you believe otherwise.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(YAWNS)
(PHONE RINGING AND VIBRATING)
(GROANS)
(RINGING STOPS)
(SIGHS)
(SHOWER RUNNING)
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING
OVER PHONE)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SIGHS)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
(EXHALES)
You free?
(SIGHS, CLEARS THROAT)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYING)
KIM: It's not long now, right?
ALMA: What?
KIM: Tenure.
I keep meaning to check in.
Do you not want
to talk about it?
ALMA: I haven't thought
about it.
I'm always thinking about it.
KIM: Well, I, for one,
have no doubt.
I'm okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You okay?
Hey, Professor.
-KIM: Shall we?
-Hey. Let's go, let's go.
(LOUD INDISTINCT CHATTER)
KIM: Oh, fuck! I have to pee.
ALMA: Hover, don't sit.
They're all genderless now
so we don't even know
who to blame
for all the piss everywhere.
Rich kids are filthy.
(SCOFFS)
Because they've been looked
after their entire lives.
Of course they are.
Hmm?
Good morning.
(GROANS)
Take your drink.
So, are we gonna talk about it?
What?
Maggie Resnick of the Resnicks.
Has she talked to you?
Oh. Doctor-patient
confidentiality.
That is deeply honorable
and fucking boring.
I'm not technically her doctor.
Sometimes. This is between
the two of us, right?
I won't be screwing anything
up between you two?
No.
I believe her.
I think Hank crossed a line.
I think he violated something
she held to be deeply sacred.
The student-teacher
relationship.
And I think one could
make the argument...
that, when a power
differential is involved...
consent and the ability
to give it
is inherently incapacitated
to the point of rendering
the question all but moot.
But I have had a lot of wine.
I know this isn't very
correct of me.
But after all these years,
it's gotten
so fucking hard for me...
to listen to these kids
when they have had
everything, everything
handed to them in their lives,
insist that the world stop
at the first small injustice.
(SIGHS) There's almost
this possessiveness
they have to their pain.
How they nurse every slight,
every bump in the road
every blip of victimization
as if it's the only thing
that can affirm them.
Whatever happened
to stuffing everything down...
and developing
a crippling dependency habit
in your thirties,
like the rest of us?
-(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
-KIM: (CHUCKLING) You know?
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(HEAVEN KNOWS I'M MISERABLE
NOW BY THE SMITHS PLAYING)
They're playing this here?
-(MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
-Bold.
-What?
-KIM: Morrissey.
Oh.
I think this is The Smiths.
Oh, potato, po-tah-toh.
I love this song.
So, what do you think?
About what?
All of it.
The student, the professor.
I think...
it was only a matter of time
and, um, it's hopelessly banal.
Didn't you have to pee?
(CROWD LAUGHS)
You never talk about yourself.
I never hear from you,
about your personal life,
your family.
(CHUCKLES)
All I know
is what I hear from Fred.
Mm.
Well... (SMACKS LIPS)
Misconstruing my need
for privacy
as having something to hide
would be a mistake.
(SMACKS LIPS)
Respectfully, Alma,
I'm not sure that it is.
Look. Maggie and I did talk.
And when we did, she mentioned
a favorite teacher of hers...
a mentor,
the target of her
Electra complex, perhaps.
All right. Let's not bring
Jung into our conversation.
KIM: Fine. Well...
this person
was less than supportive
when she came forward
and this lack of support
made her wonder why this
teacher was unforthcoming,
which made her question
said teacher's deeper motives.
Anyway, without saying too much
I just thought you should know.
And I thought
you should be ready.
Ready for what?
Well, backlash, potentially.
I mean, these are insane times
we're living in.
Now, if you want
anybody to talk,
you can come to me anytime
on the record or off, or I could
put you in touch with some
very excellent people...
Why would I trust a therapist
who violates
her clients' privacy?
Shit. I...
That was uncalled for.
(STAMMERS)
-It's okay. I'm gonna...
-I'm sorry. I'm...
Be right back.
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(INHALES THROUGH TEETH)
Oh.
I, uh...
I'm off. I'm...
I'm sorry. I'm an ass.
I'm buying the wine.
And I mean it.
I... I apologize.
(THE LAST OF THE FAMOUS
INTERNATIONAL PLAYBOYS PLAYS)
Who keeps playing this?
Fuck yeah.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(CONTAINER LID OPENS)
(PILLS RATTLING)
(KISSES)
(ALARM RINGING)
(ALMA GROANS)
-(WATER RUNNING)
-(SIGHS)
Mm.
(GROANS SOFTLY)
(SIGHS)
(AVEC LE TEMPS
BY LÉO FERRÉ OVER RADIO)
Did you see this?
In the Yale Daily?
What?
"Promising young Philosophy
PhD candidate, Maggie Resnick,"
"tells her all-too-familiar
story in her own words."
"Said, 'I was prepared
for hard work,"
"prepared for
the difficulties inherent"
"'in being a Black woman"
"in an elite, white,
male-dominated...'"
Oh, my God.
And Hank.
I almost feel bad for him.
Did you know
anything about this?
No.
She didn't say anything to you?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Campus will be a zoo.
I... I'm gonna go to the wharf
to work. I'll be home late.
But that's it?
What, you're fine?
Guess I'm just
an unfeeling cunt.
(CLOCK TICKING)
(CLOCK CONTINUES TICKING)
-(DOOR SLAMS)
-ALEX: Babe, I'm back.
-Hi!
-ALEX: You're there?
-MAGGIE: Yeah.
-Kiss?
-You're all sweaty.
-Mm.
Is that new?
-MAGGIE: Um...
-Did your mom get it for you?
No, I think she left it, like,
when she was here once. Or...
Mm.
Looks like something
she'd want you to wear.
(GRUNTS)
The reporter called
to, um, congratulate me.
That's great!
I mean, I guess. I don't know.
Yeah. I mean, I guess...
It's just, like,
kinda fucked up,
maybe, to, like,
be congratulated
on being assaulted?
No. I'm sure she congratulated
you for your bravery.
Look, we talked about this.
Fallout is inevitable.
It's your courage that's gonna
inspire other people in pain.
Yeah, I guess...
(INHALES SHARPLY)
It's just, like, amazing
to me, you know. Like,
a young Black woman
can get assaulted
and all these white people
figure out a way
to make it about themselves
or how to process their shit.
Or, like, get a leg up
at their job.
She was like,
"Oh, we might get picked up
by The Times."
And I was like...
"Neat?" (CHUCKLES) Like,
"Congrats on your
fucking Pulitzer or whatever."
Can I?
Come here.
Let me get close to you.
(KISSES)
-She hasn't called.
-Mm.
Your mom?
Alma.
She hasn't said anything.
(SIREN WAILING
IN THE DISTANCE)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(INDISTINCT
SHOUTING IN DISTANCE)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(MAN SHOUTING IN SPANISH)
(UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALMA SIGHS)
(GRUNTS)
(UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(TYPING)
(UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES)
(UNEASY MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(THUDS)
(GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(INHALES THROUGH TEETH)
(GROANING)
(VOMITING)
(GROANS)
(EXHALES)
(WATER RUNNING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PILLS RATTLING)
(GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROANING)
SECRETARY: Uh-huh. Hmm.
Kim's not in.
I'll just...
Okay, go in.
I'll tell her you're here.
SECRETARY:
Yeah, and the other one.
Oh, hi. Alma's in there.
(DRAWER CLOSES)
KIM: Oh, good. You're here.
Sorry I'm late.
I was compelled
to interrogate Donna
on her insistence on eating
and then lying about
eating my Chobani
for the 50th fucking time.
What's up? (SIGHS)
Oh, uh... Nothing. I gotta go.
Well, Alma,
it's not even 7:00.
We said after 6:30.
No, I just...
I thought I had more time.
Well, you asked to see me.
No, it's not important.
I'll see you later.
Night, Kim.
Alma Imhoff, 01-31-68.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
This is a controlled substance.
I'm gonna have to get
the pharmacist to sign off.
Hold on a sec.
Are you okay, ma'am?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WINCES)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Mrs. Imhoff? I just need
to check something.
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(COUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER LAPTOP)
(WOMAN MOANS OVER LAPTOP)
AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICE: Naked
girls want to play with you.
-Download now.
- (WOMAN MOANS OVER LAPTOP)
Naked girls
want to play with you.
-Download now.
- (WOMAN MOANS OVER LAPTOP)
(FREDERIK SNORING)
AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICE: Naked
girls want to play with you.
-Download now.
- (WOMAN MOANS OVER LAPTOP)
Naked girls
want to play with you.
-Download now.
- (WOMAN MOANS OVER LAPTOP)
Naked girls
want to play with you.
-Download now.
- (WOMAN MOANS OVER LAPTOP)
Naked girls
want to play with you.
(ALMA GRUNTS)
(FREDERIK SNORING)
(ALMA GRUNTING)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTING)
(OPERATIC MUSIC BLARING
OVER SPEAKERS)
God.
Frederik, can you
turn the music down?
Frederik!
(MUSIC ENDS)
(SIGHS) Frederik!
(ALMA SIGHS)
Can you please
turn the music down?
(COMPOSITION BY JOHN ADAMS
PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS)
What, you don't like
my beloved Adams?
(SIGHS)
(MUSIC VOLUME REDUCES)
I like coffee.
(LAUGHS)
(ALMA SIGHS)
Last night was nice.
-Oh?
-FREDERIK: Mm-hmm.
Well, we haven't slept
that close together in...
(CHUCKLES)
I don't know how long.
It was nice.
You look so different
when you sleep.
(SCOFFS) Wretched?
FREDERIK: Mm-hmm.
Like you looked
when we first met.
I was 29 when we first met.
(LAUGHING)
(SCOFFS)
(FREDERIK LAUGHING)
Oh, you looked beautiful.
(LAUGHING)
(CHUCKLES)
(FREDERIK GROWLS)
(ALMA GROANS)
-(FREDERIK GRUNTS)
-Frederik...
-(FREDERIK MOANING)
-(GRUNTS)
Frederik.
-What?
-(SIGHS)
What? What? What?
It's been months
since we were intimate.
If it's the beard,
I can lose it.
If it's the belly,
that might take
a little bit longer, mm-hmm.
Or is it because
I'm not
in the Philosophy department?
You're my husband.
I married you.
Won the battle,
but lost the war, have I?
(ALMA SIGHS)
I'm still here, aren't I?
Hmm?
FREDERIK:
How's the paper coming?
ALMA: Uh...
Finished, more or less.
FREDERIK:
(HESITATES) Finished?
Finished-finished. Wow.
MAGGIE Can we talk?
FREDERIK: That's cause
for celebration, hmm?
FREDERIK: Maybe we could,
I don't know...
FREDERIK ...have some
people over, or...
What, go out, huh?
Hmm? Maybe? To the city?
Whatever you like.
Uh...
-Yeah. Sounds good.
-FREDERIK: Hmm? Mm-hmm.
(MUSIC VOLUME INCREASES)
Kim, it's Alma. Call me back.
(SOLEMN MUSIC PLAYING)
(MAN SHOUTING IN SPANISH)
MAGGIE: We could have
done this from my apartment.
I wouldn't want to run
the risk of being deposed.
I thought Alex wasn't
a "real lawyer" yet.
Well, someone
should tell them that.
What did you wanna talk about?
I don't want you to be angry.
(WOMAN SHOUTING IN SPANISH)
I don't know
why I took it. I...
It was a strange,
impulsive thing.
But I can't help
but wonder if...
if something like
what happened to me...
(VOICE SHAKING)
happened to you...
Why didn't you tell me?
ALMA: May I?
You translated it online?
I guess it's impossible
to keep anything
to oneself these days.
You don't know
anything about me.
And whose fault is that?
You are not entitled
to any information
about me in my life.
And yet you have
so much of mine.
I haven't asked you
for anything.
You take it anyway.
Yeah, (STAMMERS)
At first, I thought
it was maybe because
we were close or
you had some sort of interest
in me as a human being.
But now, now I can't help
but wonder if it wasn't
some sort of sick vampiric
kink of yours
to let me bleed myself dry
while you give
nothing in return.
(ALMA SCOFFS)
(WHISPERS) Thank you.
I already have a husband.
That's how you treat people
who care about you?
I told Kim.
I really think you should
talk to someone about this.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
I'm trying to help you.
No.
You...
are trying to convince me
and yourself
that violating my privacy
was moral and good
because it proved you right.
Leave me alone, Maggie.
Go.
Go!
(ALMA SIGHS)
-(VOICEMAIL BEEPS)
-Fuck.
Kim, it's Alma, calling you
for the 15th fucking time!
Fuck!
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Adorno writes
in his Minima Moralia...
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
(IN ENGLISH) "There is no
right life in the wrong one."
What is he really saying?
Okay. What he's saying is
there is no right life
in the wrong world.
We are either of this world
and its conditions
or we are awake to what
is right, and therefore,
cast out of society, alienated.
But then,
why attempt to act morally
if it's truly impossible?
Isn't that just nihilism?
KATIE: I think, um,
Hannah Arendt's explanation
of Ulysses' Paradox
could be relevant.
So, Ulysses is sitting
at the Phaeacians' court,
and, um,
a blind poet...
Aoidos.
Aoidos. Right.
Um, Aoidos starts singing
the story of Troy
and of a hero, Ulysses,
whom he doesn't know
is sitting in front of him.
And suddenly,
Ulysses starts to cry.
And Arendt says,
"Of course,
he never cried before"
"hearing that
what had actually happened."
"Only by listening
to the narration"
"did he fully understand
its true meaning."
And what does that mean to you?
That Ulysses recognizes
himself as a hero
only when his story is
told to him by someone else.
But not just someone else,
"The Other,"
a blind poet who has
no external sight,
only self-sight,
and therefore, more knowledge.
ARTHUR: And so,
such an account
by "The Other" can
mitigate nihilism and give us
a sense of linearity?
Of purpose?
KATIE: When you say
"The Other,"
who exactly
are you referring to?
Stop being so literal.
Trying to
take the philosophical "Other"
and turn him into
a sociopolitical binary
is like a sweaty tourist
at a modern museum of art
who points
at a Pollock and says,
"My kid could do that."
It's immature and regressive
and totally misses
the fucking point.
Okay. In the universal
human condition of...
Of a...
Katie?
Sorry. I don't understand.
What...
What part of the argument
that you helped frame
do you not understand?
It... (SIGHS)
Well, it seems to me, like,
you're condoning literally,
not conceptually,
othering someone
despite seemingly
advocating for the opposite.
(SCOFFS)
(ALMA LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
You do realize this is
a philosophy class, right?
What is it that you think
we are doing here?
What is wrong...
with your question, Katie,
and why I don't care for it
is that you are assuming
when I refer to "The Other,"
I mean something bad.
When, in actuality,
you are the one
who is instinctually
and unconsciously
-making that association.
-I don't think she...
Don't think, Arthur!
You, Katie,
are advocating
for the human rights
of a symbolic poet,
while, in actuality,
refusing to allow "The Other"
to exist at all,
because you think
that acknowledging difference,
naming it, is wrong.
So, what is right? Hmm?
(SIGHS) What could
make you happy?
Shall we build a society
to your exact specifications?
Should I build a world for you
that has all the edges
rounded out?
Pad your chosen cell
with niceties
and fucking
trigger warnings? Hmm?
That's not what I'm here for.
I am here
to fucking teach, okay?
-Okay? Okay.
-Okay.
Good. Great. Good.
Marcus!
Fucking Marcus is here.
You wanna add anything to this?
No, Professor Imhoff.
Okay.
(CLOCK TICKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I wish I didn't have to call
this meeting,
and I'm sure you all wish
you didn't have to be here.
We've experienced
a terrible breach
of Yale's values.
A wake up call for me,
certainly, and for all of us.
As many of you know,
a female PhD student
has brought allegations
against a male professor.
(ALL MURMURING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
DEAN RJ THOMAS:
Professor Imhoff?
Can you stay behind a minute?
-(DOOR CLOSES)
-(CLOCK CONTINUES TICKING)
DEAN RJ THOMAS: Well, no sense
in dragging this out further.
It's come to our attention
that you filled a prescription
under Doctor Sayers' name
that she did not
prescribe to you.
(KIM CLEARS THROAT)
Wait, what?
DEAN RJ THOMAS:
Walgreens on Park
flagged the prescription
for being filed
without an online corollary.
When Doctor Sayers
realized who'd filled it,
she brought it to us.
I... I don't know
what you're talking about.
-(CLEARS THROAT)
-Alma...
there's a pretty
unassailable paper trail here.
Kim has decided
not to press charges,
but we need to decide
collectively,
what disciplinary actions
must be taken.
I think it's safe to say
the tenure conversation is...
paused.
(TICKING STOPS)
(STAMMERS) Paused?
Indefinitely.
Oh.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
FEMALE STUDENT 1:
I just think it's fascist.
FEMALE STUDENT 2:
But it's in the paper, so...
FEMALE STUDENT 3: Yeah.
It's not really
been my thing, but...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Alma, what are you doing here?
ALMA: I'd like to talk.
That's not a good idea.
Maggie?
ALMA: Don't you have
some obscure protest
to go be publicly angry at?
Okay, it's fine.
I'm fine.
ALMA: She's fine.
-Maggie...
-They... go away.
(CHUCKLES)
MAGGIE: (WHISPERS)
It's okay. Promise.
Okay. Okay.
FEMALE STUDENT 1: Did she just
use 'they' as a slur?
MALE STUDENT 1: Yeah.
FEMALE STUDENT 2: Guys.
MALE STUDENT 2: Dude, come on.
FEMALE STUDENT 1: It seems,
like, totally insane.
MALE STUDENT 3: I know.
FEMALE STUDENT 3:
Should we go over?
ALEX: No, it's fine.
You know, Alex is right.
Probably shouldn't be
talking like this.
ALMA: People used to say that
you were like my shadow.
Frederik actually
used to say it all the time.
That you were taking on
my mannerisms,
copying the way I dress.
Okay, you can stop.
MALE STUDENT: So, this is what
we're writing a report on?
Yeah?
FEMALE STUDENT 1: Yeah.
FEMALE STUDENT 2: Yes.
MALE STUDENT: Okay.
FEMALE STUDENT 2:
It's just gonna be like...
What did she say?
(WHISPERS) I know you have
feelings for me.
What is this?
What are you doing?
Alex is right there.
Frederik is wrong
about a lot of things,
but he was always
right about you.
You are the worst
kind of mediocre student
with every availability
to succeed
but no talent
or desire to do so.
Yet so many resources,
so much of other people's time,
is wasted on you.
Not the least of which, mine.
And your paper,
so obviously plagiarized
just reeking of laziness
combined with,
with your desperate hope
that you will be worth
your endowment.
Okay.
I don't know what you think
you think
you're talking about...
Spare me. Please.
Please.
I don't feel comfortable
having this conversation
with you anymore.
(WHISPERS) Not everything
is supposed to make you
comfortable, Maggie.
Not everything
is supposed to be
a lukewarm bath for you
to sink into until you
fall asleep and drown.
And there are no rewards
in death
for suffering as much
as fucking possible in life.
You've constructed
a life that hides
your accidental privilege,
neediness,
desperate desire to impress.
At least I have the self-respect
to be obvious about
what it is that I want.
(WHISPERS) But you?
It's all lies.
Living in an apartment that's
ten times cheaper
than what you can afford?
Dating a person you have
nothing in common with
because you think
their identity makes
you interesting?
Fawning over me
because you think
my affection
offers you credibility,
another adoptive mother
to replace your own
insufferable one.
It's all lies.
Christ, it's no wonder
everyone thinks
you lied about Hank, too.
(ALMA GASPS)
(GASPS) Fuck.
(WHISPERS) You stupid bitch.
You have no idea
what you've just done to me.
Hey, hey, that's enough.
Let's go.
ALEX: You okay?
MAGGIE: Yeah, Alex.
ALEX: You okay, babe?
MAGGIE: I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's all right.
ALEX: Well, what did
she fuckin' say to you?
MAGGIE: I'm fine.
ALEX: Oh, my God. Fuck.
Come on, let's go.
I got you. I got you.
Let's just get out of here.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
(CARD READER BEEPS)
Thank you. Goodbye.
(ICE CLATTERS)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(EXHALES)
(SCOFFS)
(DOOR THUDS)
(HANK EXHALES)
HANK: Hmm.
Oh, yeah, this is embarrassing.
How long have you been here?
(EXHALES) Today?
(INHALES DEEPLY)
I've just been
comin' off and on.
ALMA: How did you get my keys?
Why are you here?
It's my apartment.
HANK: You gave me the keys
last Christmas,
when my sister was visiting.
I never gave 'em back.
I've had a shit day.
You want a drink?
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
HANK: You want?
No, thank you.
-Actually, yes.
-(HANK CHUCKLES)
(LIGHTER CLINKS)
Look at us.
(EXHALING THROUGH TEETH)
(SIGHS) Two Icaruses.
(GLASSES CLINK)
You've heard.
-Word travels fast.
-(ALMA SIGHS)
Last I checked,
we were still living.
What's being alive
when your livelihood
is stolen from you?
(CLICKS TONGUE)
I feel like, deep inside,
I always expected this.
I expected the rottenness
in me to be
seen by other people
right before I managed
to expunge it.
Spoken like a true woman.
Never felt myself
to be rotten at all.
Spoken like a true man.
A man you loved once.
(HANK CHUCKLES)
Yeah.
Knew I was right about that.
(ALMA TUTS, INHALES)
Didn't keep you
from wanting me to say it.
Yeah. Dead right,
I'm a simple man.
Want my feelings
to be reciprocated.
You loved me?
(HANK CHUCKLES)
Come on. Told you.
(SIGHS) Told you.
Countless times.
It never went away.
Not for me.
Why... Why do you think
I'm here?
You're not, you know.
What?
A simple man.
(SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE)
Maggie hit me.
(CHUCKLES) Whoa, whoa.
Uh, what?
Well, she slapped me.
-She slapped you?
-Mmm.
Goddamn.
Okay, well, I do wish it was
the other way around, but...
Well, I mean, I did belittle
all of her life choices
and told her that I knew
about the plagiarizing,
so it wasn't
entirely unwarranted.
You told her what I told you?
No. The dissertation,
I knew before you told me.
It was clear, as you said,
anybody looking at it, so...
You knew?
All this time? You knew?
Why didn't you tell me?
-I didn't think it mattered.
-You didn't think...
(SCOFFS) you didn't think
it mattered?
What would you have done?
Draw a line between
two disparate points
and make a case
against a young woman
who said you abused her?
-It's grasping at straws.
-Yes. Yes. Exactly that.
You sound like a desperate man.
I am a desperate man.
I'm absolutely, positively
fucking desperate!
(HANK PANTING)
You just would have given them
more rope to hang you with.
I wish... I wish they would.
I wish they would.
Rather than let me just
die here in obscurity.
You know how many fuckin' times
I thought about jumpin'
into that fuckin' wharf?
Do you?
Nothing I would have done
could have changed what's...
You don't know that.
You don't know that!
You can't know that.
(HANK EXHALES)
ALMA: Mmm.
Do you think...
Do you think I did it?
-What?
-Do you think I raped her?
You flirted
with all of 'em, Hank.
(SCOFFS) I flirted?
I flirted. Yeah.
So fuckin' what?
All of who?
All of your students.
You could have fucked
any number of them.
So, you're jealous? Is that...
I'm uncertain.
'Cause I didn't.
'Cause I didn't. 'Cause...
'cause, like a fuckin' idiot,
the only person
I ever broke the rules...
(SOFTLY) to fuck was you.
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(HANK SOBS, SNIFFLES)
Shit. (BREATHES DEEPLY)
Fuck!
Fuck.
-Jesus Christ.
-(HANK GROANING)
-HANK: Shit. Fuck!
-You're an idiot. Let me see.
Let me see. Hey.
Jesus!
Hey.
You're an idiot.
ALMA: Okay.
Mm-mm. Hank.
Hank. Stop. Please. Hank...
(ALMA GRUNTING)
ALMA: Stop it!
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
-Get off!
-(HANK GRUNTS)
Jesus. God.
Get out.
This was a mistake. Get out.
Please, get out.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
HANK: (SOFTLY) Oh, shit.
(EXHALES)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(METAL THUDDING)
(GROANS)
-(SIGHS)
-(UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING)
(HORN BLOWING IN DISTANCE)
(CAR LOCK BEEPS)
(KEYS JANGLING)
(MAN 1 CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY)
-(MAN 2 CHUCKLES)
-MAN 1: Shit.
MAN 2: Yeah. Anyway.
-Let's get outta here, man.
-MAN 1: Yeah.
Yeah, man, let's roll, man.
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENGINE TURNS OVER)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
ALEX:
The article came out today.
I know, we just need
a statement from her.
And, honestly,
the administration, too.
That's her!
-FEMALE STUDENT 1: Professor.
-Look, look.
-Oh, shit. Yo. There she is!
-Professor.
ALEX: Everyone, come on!
FEMALE STUDENT 1: Professor!
MALE STUDENT 1: Professor!
FEMALE STUDENT 1:
Professor, we just...
ALEX: Professor Imhoff!
FEMALE STUDENT 1: Are you
gonna hold Yale accountable?
We just wanna have
a conversation with you, okay?
No. Okay. I'm sorry. I...
All we want is accountability.
FEMALE STUDENT 1:
Professor, we just wanna chat.
MALE STUDENT 2:
We want justice.
I'm sorry. I just...
Please. Just...
ALEX: Do you believe
Maggie Resnick?
Are you willing to say
that what he did was wrong?
-You don't understand what...
-We want accountability.
-Will you give us a statement?
-No, I... (GROANS)
They need to hear
the truth, and...
-(STUDENTS GASP, EXCLAIMS)
-(ALMA GROANS)
ALEX: Oh, shit.
FEMALE STUDENT 2: Is she okay?
I don't know. Fuck.
(STUDENTS MURMURING)
ALEX: Guys, give her space.
Give her space.
PROFESSOR: Step back.
Give her some room.
ALEX: We didn't touch her.
I swear. No one touched her.
She just collapsed.
(DOOR OPENS)
(LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS)
(MONITOR BEEPING)
FREDERIK: (SOFTLY) Hey.
How are you feeling?
Like shit.
Well, multiple perforated
ulcers'll do that to you.
Doctor said you must have
been in a lot of pain.
Why didn't you say anything?
You, um...
got a lotta calls.
All from the same number.
And, uh...
It'll blow over, huh?
Some other catastrophe
will break,
and it'll all be forgotten.
Read it to me.
Al, I...
Please.
"It's what Resnik refers to"
"as the 'Feminist
Generation Gap'..."
"Saying, 'Alma had to fight
for everything"
"'she should have been given..."
"'But she can only conceive
of progress in the way"
"'that she achieved it..."
"'By subsuming herself"
"'to the abusive
patriarchal agenda.'"
"'Alma failed me as a teacher,"
"'but beyond that,
she failed me as a woman..."
"'As a mentor. And now,"
"'I'm just another Black woman"
"'who hoped for equal
and fair recognition"
"'from a white woman,"
"'but got nothing
but tokenistic subjugation"
"'in return.'"
We can fight this, yeah?
Do a counter op-ed or something?
I wanna share
something with you.
I told you, when I was a child
that my father's best friend
sexually assaulted me,
abused me.
None of that is true.
(CHUCKLES)
We were in love.
He was so kind.
He was so handsome, and...
I could just stare at him
from across rooms.
I would go...
to work, sometimes,
with my father,
just so I could see him.
I couldn't focus in class.
School, my friends, just,
everything felt so pedestrian.
Except for him.
He was the only thing
that felt real to me.
He kissed me for the first time
the day after my 15th birthday.
And...
-When...
-Six months later, maybe.
He said I was too young,
but I had insisted.
It was the happiest time
of my life.
Then, out of nowhere,
he said he... (CLEARS THROAT)
That he met someone else, and...
someone that was
more appropriate.
He started bringing her
to my parents' parties and...
throwing her in my face
like he was...
trying to prove
how little he cared.
It was so cruel.
So, I made up a story...
that I knew
would hurt him the most.
And three years later
he committed suicide.
I had already retracted
the story by then, but...
it didn't matter.
I'd wanted to hurt him
the way I thought he'd hurt me
and I did.
Alma, you were... you were...
very young.
Young girls want adult things
to happen to them...
sooner than they're
ready for them all the time.
But it's always the adult's job
to protect the innocence
of a child.
No.
I didn't give him a choice.
Hmm.
There's always a choice.
It doesn't matter
if you wanted him,
it doesn't matter if you threw
yourself at him,
he should have
rejected you outright.
No. He did.
He did. He refused me.
He was a good man,
and I destroyed him with a lie.
Alma.
It wasn't a lie.
You keep thinking
he did nothing wrong.
You keep blaming yourself.
Do you think you can
allow yourself to see
the truth in that?
The truth...
is that I love him.
And I love you.
(ALMA EXHALES)
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
MALE STUDENT: Oh, my gosh.
There's so many people in there.
FEMALE STUDENT: I know.
It's, like, 10? What, 12?
(BOTH CONTINUE
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
REPORTER 1: (ON MONITOR)
This is new.
Yeah, we've been watching...
It then spreads,
from these trees...
Look at all these embers just...
I don't know if you can pan up,
but look at all these embers
just flying up.
You see them in the smoke.
All of that.
Those can... Those...
The winds are a little...
Have died down here.
But those can just get
picked up by winds for miles
and they can go for miles
and light down...
-you know...
- (KNOCKING AT DOOR)
REPORTER 1:
...fall on somebody's roof...
and a whole new fire
will pop up.
-So, this house is gone.
-Dean Imhoff?
Your four o'clock.
You said to remind you?
Thank you, Peter. I was
just getting ready to leave.
REPORTER 1: This house
is now underway.
The left side
of this house is ignited.
-Horrible, don't you think?
-REPORTER 1: And also now
-the house nearby it.
- Absolutely.
REPORTER 2: Yeah. This...
REPORTER 1: But liter...
I mean, these embers
are like snowflakes.
They're falling all around us.
The sun, I mean, this,
it looks so crazy. If you...
You can't even see the sun.
It is completely blacked out.
NEWSCASTER: Meta,
the parent company of Facebook
and Instagram, announced Friday
that it's ending
its diversity, equity,
and inclusion programs.
Earlier this week,
Meta announced that it's
ending its third-party
fact-checking programs
in the United States.
It's also changing
its hateful conduct...
(HINDI MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
(MEN SPEAKING PUNJABI)
(DOOR OPENS)
-(MELLOW JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
-(MAGGIE SIGHS)
Sorry I'm late.
-Sorry I ordered without you.
-It's fine.
The wine here
is surprisingly good.
MAGGIE: Oh, I mean,
I don't drink anymore, so...
Nobody does.
-It's good to see you.
-MAGGIE: Yeah.
You look the same.
-You're lying.
-No.
But the people who only live
for one thing never seem to age.
(SMACKS LIPS) You know,
this is where Hank
used to take all of us?
That was his table,
right over there.
Sometimes I still wonder
where he is.
(TAPPING ON TABLE)
Oh, um, making a pile of money
spin doctoring
for some Democrat.
"The death knell
of intellect is politics."
That's what
Frederik always says.
Are you still together?
We're still together.
-(MAGGIE CHUCKLES)
-And Alex?
Uh, (LAUGHS) but I hear
they're doing very well.
On track to make
partner somewhere.
You know, I read your article.
I thought it was very smart.
Your confession, the contrition.
It was well written, though,
didn't you think?
I think it was written
for you to get
everything you wanted.
And how 'bout you? Married?
Engaged.
-Congratulations.
-Yeah.
-Who's the lucky...
-Uh, Nia.
She's great. I mean,
so intelligent and just...
-Do you wanna see?
-Sure.
Wow. She's gorgeous.
How old do you think she is?
Forty-three.
She's the Director
of Curatorial Affairs
at the New Whitney.
You can keep going.
You know,
I think I spent so much time
wishing for you to fail,
I figured it'd make us even
or something.
It probably doesn't matter now,
but I know I hurt you,
Maggie, and I'm sorry.
I don't know if you were
expecting more, I just...
That's nice.
I think I was more confused
than anything at the time.
I wasn't sure if I wanted
to be you or be with you.
And now?
I mean, I always knew
we were different,
but now I know
that that's a good thing.
I like being alive
to what happens to me,
and nothing affects you.
I lost everything.
And look at you now.
You think I'm a bad person?
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
Does that even matter?
I gave up on the idea
of retribution
a long, long time ago.
But I am curious.
After everything, are you...
are you really happy?
Yes, I really am.
Then I'm happy for you.
You did it.
You won.
(DOOR OPENS)
(SOFTLY) Check, please.
(MELLOW JAZZ MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(MELLOW JAZZ MUSIC FADES)
(HINDI MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
Cut!
(UPBEAT
ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING)