Hey, Sonny. Five minutes.
♪ You need coolin' ♪
♪ Baby, I'm not foolin' ♪
♪ I'm gonna send ya
Back to schoolin' ♪
♪ Way down inside
Honey, you need it ♪
♪ I'm gonna give you my love
I'm gonna give you my love ♪
♪ Want a whole lotta love
Want a whole lotta love ♪
Sonny! Hey. BMW guys are over
there bitching about brake trouble.
Thanks, Molly.
You're a superstar.
I'll see you out there.
♪ All the good times Baby,
baby, I've been yearning ♪
♪ Way, way down inside
Honey, you need it ♪
♪ I'm gonna give you my love ♪
♪ Want a whole lotta love ♪
Turn my back for one minute.
It's all gone to shit, Sonny.
Pat had to ease off.
We've dropped down to seventh.
If you can just hold position overnight,
hopeful sunrise catches us a break.
Sonny, watch that high-speed
balance. High-speed balance.
How's the gearbox?
It's holding up, but go easy.
The crowds may have gone home,
but the racing continues.
Sonny Hayes back in the Porsche
for Peak Geico Chip Hart Racing,
the midnight shift.
We all know Hayes
likes to light up the night,
but with the BMW at the head of this
pack, he's got a massive job ahead of him.
Right out of the gate, Hayes
threads the needle into turn three,
moving up to fourth place.
Sonny, wanna maybe
pass on the straights?
Just let me drive, will ya?
Look out. Engine trouble
for the number 12.
That moves Hayes
up another spot.
♪ You've been coolin'
Baby, I've been droolin' ♪
Sweet baby Jesus. We
got ten more hours.
Just let Sonny do his thing.
And if these first few
laps are any indication,
it appears as though Sonny Hayes may
have left his brake pedal at home.
♪ I'm gonna give you
Every inch of my love ♪
Hayes sets his
sights on the BMW.
♪ Yeah, all right, let's go ♪
And he attacks.
♪ Want a whole lotta love
Want a whole lotta love ♪
Here comes Hayes on the outside.
Come on, Sonny.
♪ Want a whole lotta love ♪
♪ Way down inside ♪
♪ Love ♪
♪ My, my, my, my
My, my, my, my ♪
The BMW late on the
brakes. He's in the grass.
Can Hayes hang on?
And he does.
Goddamn!
See that? That's
how you race, boys.
When you get back in that car, you
need to do the same goddamn thing.
♪ Hey, oh, ooh ♪
Sonny Hayes brings it into pit
lane after an epic third stint
that puts Chip Hart
Racing out in front.
Now, it's up to Cale Kelso
to hang on to that lead.
Thanks for the
head start, Chief.
Hey. Lose that
lead, I'll kill ya.
♪ Shake for me, girl I
wanna be your backdoor man ♪
Hayes!
Hey, dirt bag!
-Gonna run me off the track, Hayes?
-It's not worth it.
You think I don't know where
to find you? Screw you!
Let go of me!
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
Hey. Attaboy, Sonny.
Thanks. Don't wake
me if we lose.
♪ Keep it coolin', baby ♪
Sonny Hayes, I believe
you forgot something.
Bag's full, Chip.
Seriously?
Your first win at Daytona.
Don't you even want to touch it?
-Ooh, bad luck.
-Come on.
-Just touch it.
-No. Hey.
I will take that
bonus check though.
Sonny. Sonny! Just hear me out.
Look, I wanna
bring you on board.
You're CHR family now.
Right here, next year,
let's run it back.
We did it, man. Deal's a deal.
I-I know what a deal is.
So that's it? One and done?
I appreciate the seat,
Chip. I really do.
What kind of way
is that to race?
You just spend your whole
life starting over, man.
You take care.
I'll see you down the road.
Hey! Don't you want the watch?
Got one!
WHOG, Ormond-by-the-Sea.
Proud to be locally owned.
A Southern Stone station.
The world's most famous rock...
...from the world's most
famous beach, we are...
...Daytona's rock station...
...ninety-five seven, the Hog.
♪ Out on the streets
That's where we'll meet ♪
♪ You make the night I
always cross the line ♪
♪ Tightened our belts
Abused ourselves ♪
♪ Get in our way We'll
put you on your shelf ♪
Sorry, can I use your
phone for a second, please?
It's not working.
Um, no.
You know, you remind me of
this friend I used to have.
Which friend?
Friend who dressed better.
This is a Gucci suit.
So's this.
Huh. What did your friend do?
Drove cars.
-Was he fast?
-Wasn't slow.
-Did he win?
-Yeah, he did.
Come here, you son of a bitch.
Oh, God.
Are you thinking Baja?
Yeah. New day, new challenge.
That's exactly what I said to
myself when I bought Apex GP.
How deep in the hole are you?
I'll tell you, but you have
to promise not to laugh.
Shoot.
350...
million.
Don't laugh.
Impressive.
Well, been fun?
Oh, yeah. Absolutely.
What's the problem then?
Problem is two seasons
and a half, zero points.
My best driver left
for another team.
He said the car was a shitbox.
The team is in last place.
My number two's a rookie.
And the season's half over.
-How many races left?
-Nine.
And if we don't turn it
around, I lose the team.
-What?
-Mmm.
But you own the team.
No race wins in your first three
seasons, the board can force a sale.
Man, sounds like you
need a new board.
I need a new driver.
You got F2. You got F3.
You got an entire assembly line
of kids raised on the simulator.
No, I don't have time for some kid to
learn how to come in tenth. I don't.
Well, you don't just walk off
the street and pilot a rocket.
Yes, you can if you've done it
before. That's the whole point.
Louis Chiron was 57 years old
when he won the Monaco Grand Prix.
-Louis who?
-Philippe Étancelin, 56 years old.
You just Googled these
names, didn't you?
Some people look at Sonny Hayes,
they see a guy who lives in a van,
a gambling junkie
who missed his shot.
Wow, Ruben, you are
really selling this.
But I see a guy who
makes teams better.
-I see experience. I see know-how.
-Mmm.
You're off your meds.
My rookie's a phenomenal talent.
Phenomenal. But he's young.
You know what he
lacks? Maturity.
You plus him?
Boom. I got a team.
All right. Let's say
I'm the next Louis...
-Chiron. Mm-hmm.
-Him.
The problem is it's not just
the driver, it's the car.
I've followed your
season, Ruben.
"Shitbox" is being kind.
I knew you were watching.
What if I told you we get an
upgrade package this weekend?
-Six months in development...
-Ruben...
No, no, no. Wait.
I just need one of my cars across
the finish line first. One.
I love ya. I'm not going back.
Okay.
What would he want you to do?
Join a boy band?
Seriously. Come on.
Seriously, I'd ask him
what he's smiling about.
Come on.
He's smiling at the possibility.
We both know how that ended.
Yep.
Okay.
-This is a first-class ticket to London.
-Oh, my God.
First class.
I'm offering you an
open seat in Formula 1.
The only place you
could say for one day,
if you win, you are the
absolute best in the world.
-Hey, Ruben.
-Mmm.
-Ever seen a miracle?
-Not yet.
Me neither.
Good to see you, amigo.
-All right, sweetie, here you go.
-Thank you.
-Mm-hmm.
-Hey, let me ask you something.
Close friend of yours made you an
offer that was 100%, positively
too good to be true.
What do you do?
Well, how much are we talking?
Not about the money.
So what is it about?
Hmm.
Tire temps look good.
Eighty-five front, 75 rear.
-You are good to push.
-Copy.
Battery is full. You're
good for strat two.
Going for a lap.
Purple sector one. Best one yet.
Car feels good.
Damn!
Locked it up. Flat
spot, front left.
Bring him in.
Go to strat one.
Uh, box this lap. Box this lap.
Let's go find those gremlins.
Sorry, Joshua.
Jodie, try not to
kill our driver.
What's the verdict?
I don't know what's happening. I
mean, it feels good. I start to push.
Then it understeers in the slow
corners and oversteers the fast.
What? On entries or exits?
Either. Both.
Oh, great. Yeah.
There's 10,000 sensors on this thing
and you can't tell me what's going on.
But I'm not out there, am I?
So, I-I'm gonna need your
help on this. Please.
150 million dollar jungle gym.
So cute.
We should let her drive.
Can't be any worse.
Joshua.
-Hi.
-Lisbeth. PR?
-Oh, yeah.
-Doesn't matter.
For the press conference, we
want to steer around tech issues
and focus on the super strong bond
with your new teammate, Luca Cortez.
Luca?
Who I've known a week.
Who when he was third banana
on the left at Red Bull,
told the press he thought
Joshua Pearce was overrated.
That Luca Cortez?
Yes.
-Can't wait. Yeah.
-All right. Great. Thank you.
-Yo.
-Yep.
That's a yes? Yeah? Yes?
What's up?
Yo, you were right, bro.
Ruben's in big trouble. He
might have to sell the team.
I knew it.
And what does that mean for me?
New buyers, they're
likely to clean house.
Listen.
You need to show these people who
the number one driver really is, man.
Now.
Or you're gonna lose your job.
Yeah. Let that sink in.
Hey.
You good?
Okay, let's take the
first half of the season
and erase it from our minds.
Someone says, "Kaspar,
what happened this year?"
I swear on the lives of my
children, I do not freaking know.
There's only this car.
And there is only our future.
Yes. Our future.
Who is that asshole?
He's with me.
Your man thought I was maintenance.
Sent me to the back gate.
Brother, you have
never let me down.
Well, there's still time.
Apex GP!
Sonny Hayes. He raced
with me back in the day.
-Against you, you mean.
-Yeah.
-Kate McKenna, our technical director.
-Hi.
-Dodge Dauda, our chief mechanic.
And Kaspar Smolinski,
team principal.
You may know him by reputation.
Five-time Constructors
champion with Ferrari.
Huh.
As a rear jack man.
So was my pop. Can't
win without 'em.
-And our talented rookie, Joshua.
-Why has he got a helmet?
Uh, safety?
Joshua, your seat is safe. Okay?
Sonny is here for the audition.
When was the last
time you won a race?
Sunday. Daytona.
Oh, I'm sorry. I-I
meant Formula 1.
Oh, I'm sorry. Then same as you.
Wow.
Never thought I'd say this,
has anyone seen Luca Cortez?
Sidebar bitte, Ruben.
When I interview with you,
many veteran drivers...
Yeah, who all turned you down.
-How many?
-Seven.
-That's a lot.
-I'm number seven?
-Mm-hmm.
-You're eight.
This is a disaster.
Starting to feel
more like a nine.
Technically, there is one
who I've not heard from yet.
So I am a nine?
You know how
numbers work, right?
In business, my most
inspired ideas come late.
Yeah. Best things in life
usually arrive ninth, right?
With respect, Ruben, I cannot
condone we spend our only test day
giving your long-lost
teammate an audition.
Kaspar, you misunderstand.
We're not auditioning
him. He's auditioning us.
That's your new driver.
Good luck.
New wing, new side pods.
Any changes to the floor?
Nothing the eight other drivers
wouldn't have figured out.
That's why they call
me Lucky Number Nine.
Listen, it's been a while since
you've driven here, mate. Yeah?
The balance on these cars are tricky,
so be careful turn one and nine.
Wouldn't want to
see you get hurt.
How about we set a
reasonable target?
Give me the same setup as him. If I can't
post a lap time within a second of JP's,
then I will promptly
see myself out
and you're free to take a
shot at lucky number ten.
-Ten?
-Ten.
Ten.
Who's JP?
Cross round on Brooklands,
easy on Luffield.
Up to Woodcote,
hard out in Copse.
And be careful on the curve.
Default mode, settings
one, to two, back to three.
Differential one through four.
DRS.
♪ I bet you thought You'd
seen the last of me ♪
♪ I can't change the
way I am, you see ♪
♪ I think it's my
responsibility ♪
♪ To tell you I'm just
as bad as I used to be ♪
♪ I'm just as bad
as I used to be ♪
Okay. Let's see what you got.
If he raced with Ruben, he raced
with Schumacher. With Senna.
♪ I tried changing my reality ♪
♪ But I don't think
It's gonna set me free ♪
♪ There's only one
thing I can guarantee ♪
♪ And that's I'm just
as bad as I used to be ♪
♪ I'm just as bad
as I used to be ♪
All right, pull up
Joshua's sector times.
Twenty quid says he stacks it.
Make it a hundred, you're on.
Oh, shit.
Sorry, uh, this is Hugh
Nickleby, your race engineer.
Good morning, Hugh. How
are my tire temps looking?
Yep, almost warm. End of the
lap, you should be good to push.
Right. Man.
-Hugh?
-Yes, sir?
You should've taken that bet.
Copy that.
♪ No one's accusing
me of sanity ♪
♪ I ain't everybody's
cup of tea ♪
♪ But that's the facts
I'm talkin' factually ♪
Going for a lap.
♪ I'm just as bad
as I used to be ♪
♪ Yes, I'm just as
bad as I used to be ♪
♪ Whoa, I'm just as
♪ I'm just as bad
as I used to be ♪
Nope. Shit.
He's dead.
Come on. Don't do that.
And buried.
Wait.
Now.
The car is there, come on.
He's gaining.
Ah, shit.
You okay?
Yep. All good.
Oh!
Come on.
Yeah, she's got something.
Yeah, you mean had something.
But definitely snappy in
the high-speed corners.
Unpredictable in the lows.
Had trouble with the
rears, turns 14, 16...
And the final turn, maybe?
-No, that's on me.
-What was his lap time?
He passed his entirely self-imposed
test by five hundredths of a second.
Huh.
Well...
...it's a start.
Bro, we got nine races to catch
the eye of another team, you know.
And as your manager,
I have to advise you
that we need to start hitting
these social and sponsor events.
You need more engagement,
Josh, more followers.
-All right, deal.
-All right, cool. I'm just saying, innit?
You eaten? I'm starving.
Nah.
Gotta see someone though.
Yeah? Hey, take a
picture, post that shit.
Send it to me, I'll
post that shit.
It's my mum.
Don't you dare post that shit.
I knew you was gonna say that.
Okay, baby?
Yeah. Just tired.
Bad tires or the engine?
Come on, Mum. You don't
know about the cars.
Facety.
All right, I may not know much about
cars, but I know a lot about you.
Go.
I might lose my seat if
the team don't win a race.
Any race.
There are other teams?
Yeah, there's 20 seats,
but they're all filled.
Plus, there's this
new guy, and...
...he's old.
How old?
Like, really old. Like... 80.
He's such an arsehole, Mum.
He's quick, though.
Don't mind that.
Focus on you.
You can spend your whole life
worrying about other people,
but your time is right now.
You still love it?
Course I still love it.
Then remember what your
father used to say.
"Put your head down and drive."
Yes, ma'am.
Come on, then. It's all
good. Come on. Come on, then.
Come on. Come on.
-Come here. Come on, then.
-You're kiddin' me.
Don't park there. It's
just a car. Quieten down.
Come on, eh? Come on.
Thought your job was to build
the fastest car on the planet.
My job is wind.
So, helps to feel it.
Mmm.
Mysterious moves at Apex GP,
who have finally announced the driver
who will take their second seat.
And in a bizarre twist,
it's American Sonny Hayes,
who hasn't raced in Formula
1 for over three decades.
Son of an IndyCar mechanic,
Hayes was considered something
of a reckless young phenomenon,
the greatest who never was.
His former career being
brought to an abrupt halt
by a horrific accident at
the Spanish Grand Prix.
He reappeared a decade later
in racing championships
as diverse as Le Mans,
NASCAR, the Dakar Rally,
and even a stint as a
New York taxi driver.
Oh, no.
But now he's back racing
for a team which has,
in its entire F1 history, never
even finished in the top ten.
None of this will
dampen speculation
that majority shareholder Cervantes
Capital are looking to sell the team.
And if they do, that will
likely also bring an end
to the career of F1
rookie Joshua Pearce.
-Can we go now?
-"Desperate times," they say,
"call for desperate measures,"
but I honestly cannot
recall a driver signing
-quite as desperate as this.
-Let's go.
Boy, look at my son.
-Huh?
-Hey.
-That's the one.
-Huh.
That's the other driver?
Yep. That's him and
his stupid face.
But, wait, you said he
was old. He not that old.
Hey, Josh.
You want a next shot anywhere?
Nine races means nine times
you have to beat Chuck Norris.
For now, start by
winning over the press.
-Yeah? You ready?
-Mm-hmm.
Cool. Let's go.
Mmm.
That's a handsome
man right there.
Joshua. Hey. Um, it's been an
undeniably messy start to your season.
No wins, car problems throughout, and
now you have another new teammate.
How exactly are you finding it?
Messy start doesn't mean you
can't finish neat. All right?
Apex have a fire crew of engineers, so
I'm confident we'll come back fightin'.
In terms of new teammates,
I think it's really wonderful that Apex
are giving second chances to the elderly.
Ah, yes. Next question.
Thank you. Yes, Don. Yeah.
Mr. Hayes. Hi. Don Cavendish.
Um, welcome back to the UK.
It's been a while, mmm?
I mean, last time you
raced at Silverstone,
Bill Clinton was your president, and
we were all dancing the Macarena.
So, uh, it must be
surreal to be back.
Yeah.
And, uh, during that
decade, you gave up racing,
and, uh, gambled professionally?
Uh-huh.
Before declaring yourself
personally bankrupt?
Yep.
You had a marriage annulled
and two more ended in divorce?
Yep.
Anything you wish
you'd done differently?
Yeah.
No more questions. Thank
you. Yes. Thank you.
Yes, Dodge.
What time was he here?
Before me.
And before you.
Okay, here he comes. Apologize.
Apologize? I can't do that.
-How you mean? Why not?
-Because it's a sign of weakness.
It's a sign of strength.
Sign of weakness.
You hard ears, just do it.
Mum, I can't.
You can. You will.
Hey, man.
Other day at the press conference,
stuff I said wasn't cool.
You say sorry.
So, basically what I'm trying
to say is... I'm sorry.
It's all right. You're just worried
I'm quicker than you. Hi, I'm Sonny.
Oh, Bernadette Pearce.
Nice to meet you.
Pleasure. It's all good.
I'll see you out there.
How are you feeling?
-So good.
-Good.
-You good?
Good.
No pressure.
None.
-Great.
Great.
Welcome along to Silverstone,
the circuit where on the 13th of May 1950
the Formula 1 World Championship began.
Today, we kick off the final nine races
of this thrilling championship season
here at the 77th
British Grand Prix.
As always, 11 teams
will take the grid,
fielding two drivers each.
With race order determined by the
qualifying times set yesterday.
Red Bull will start on pole
followed by the two
McLarens and two Ferraris.
Drivers, two minutes
to national anthem.
Sonny!
Ah, Ruben. Don't make
me talk to the money.
Come on, give me a moment.
Just smile and shake hands.
He's an important
member of the board.
Sonny, this is Peter Banning,
-one of my investors.
-Hi.
Hi.
He knows absolutely
nothing about racing...
-Yeah.
-...but he's my eyes and ears on the board.
And, uh, you're
Ruben's Hail Mary.
Now, that is an American
football term, right?
The Hail Mary, the
long shot. The...
I believe it's a religious
term, originally.
That is true. That is true.
I'm praying to them all.
I'm the one guy on the board who
actually wants to keep the team.
The rest are calling it,
you know, Ruben's Inferno.
But, seriously, man, I'm hooked.
I've binged all of
Drive to Survive.
I honestly don't think I've ever known
so much about car tires. It's incredible.
I'm gonna get back
to my day job.
-Okay.
Hey, man. We're counting
on you. Good luck.
What are you doing here, Sonny?
And as the clock ticks then
to the top of the hour,
it's time to get things
going here at Silverstone.
It's formation lap first.
One tour of the track and a chance for the
drivers to warm up their tires and brakes.
Oh, no. There's a
problem for Apex.
That's Hayes in P22.
His car hasn't moved.
Hang on. I got power trouble.
It's start mode, Sonny.
Start mode on.
Yes, a lesson for
everyone at home.
New car? Do read the manual.
It's been a while since he was
out on the track. At this rate...
-Dios mío.
-...he's not even gonna get into the race.
Ay.
I got it.
All good.
And he's away at last.
Thank goodness for that.
If he falls too far behind
on the formation lap...
-Drink?
-...he'll be at risk...
-Eh? No.
-...of having to start in the pit lane.
Where's Sonny?
He's holding us up.
Yeah. Just checking,
Joshua. Just checking.
-What's wrong with his car?
-What? Nothing.
With a clear track ahead,
Hayes has been able to push much
harder on this formation lap.
He'll turn up at the back of the
grid with warm tires, ready to go.
Cheeky shit. It's on purpose.
What is this guy doing?
This is actually now turning into
an advantage for Sonny Hayes.
And he's just made it in
time. Watch out for his start.
Five lights ahead of the drivers.
It's lights out and away we go!
Here comes Sonny Hayes,
ladies and gentlemen.
Using those warm tires to carve his
way through the back of the field.
And if you ever need
confidence in your car,
it's here at Silverstone.
Hayes is just
sailing past people.
He's moved up seven
places since the start.
-Apex GP has struggled with this car...
-Yes!
...but they've brought an
upgrade package this weekend.
Let's see if it makes a difference as
Hayes attacks Perez in the Red Bull.
Car's bouncing around this dirty
air. I can't position to attack.
Hayes complaining about
his car over the radio.
That's not what the
team wants to hear.
Copy. Gap is 0.9 to Perez.
You're within DRS range.
Should be able to take
him on the next straight.
Hayes now using the drag
reduction system to get past.
Yeah!
Won't be able to hold him
off, guys. I got no grip.
-This is trouble now for Apex GP.
-Oh, come on.
The Red Bull's
tires are now warm
and Hayes hasn't got his tire
advantage from the start anymore.
We've seen the attack. Now
it's all about defense.
And Perez on the
attack into Vale.
Hayes is in trouble. This
could be the places reversed.
And it is.
Damn.
Rear end is loose. Tell
me if you see a fix.
Tell him to pull back the
entry to get a better exit.
He-He thinks it's
the setup. It's not.
Twenty laps down.
Verstappen leads but Joshua Pearce is
struggling out there at the moment.
Guys, get me off these
softs. I'm going backwards.
Copy that. Lap 20. Box, box.
Stakes couldn't be higher
for rookie Joshua Pearce.
This is not where you
want to be, in last place.
I'm jammed. Back up!
Hit something. What was that?
Ooh, a seven-second pit stop.
Apex GP won't be
happy with that.
That's double the time
it should've taken.
Lost the rears. Box, box.
Copy. Go to plan B. Box, box.
And here comes Sonny Hayes
for a fresh set of tires.
He'll be hoping these will help him
hold on to his current position of P15.
Front jacks! Front jacks!
The front jack has
not worked properly.
-You're kidding me.
-This is causing absolute pandemonium
in the Apex GP pit lane.
Whatever could go wrong is
going wrong for this team.
And coming out of the pit, Hayes
just ahead of his teammate.
As Pearce and Hayes go battling
it out here at Silverstone.
Coming for you, old man.
Got the pace, man. Tell
him to let me pass.
Yeah. Copy. Hold
position. Stand by. Kate.
Josh is faster. Sonny
is on cold tires.
Yeah, okay, Sonny, no
fighting. Let him through.
Sonny, no fighting.
Who's fighting? I'm racing.
Pearce on the inside,
Hayes on the outside.
Hayes trying to make
him eat concrete
up against the old
pit wall there.
Joshua, you're gonna have
to fight for position.
You are racing Sonny.
A-ffirm.
They're giving
absolutely no quarter.
No benefit to their
teammate at all.
They're pushing as if they're
trying to win a Grand Prix.
But this is the battle
for last place, remember?
And what a brawl it is.
Let's go, kid. Bring it.
What is this guy
doing? Let me through.
Round the final corner.
It's close!
They make contact.
Both Apex GP cars
into the gravel,
and Pearce hits the barrier.
-Ah, no!
-No!
This is mad.
The cardinal sin
of motor racing.
A double DNF.
Just when it couldn't get any
worse for the black and gold.
That's a tough one, man.
We can't corner.
We're bouncing around the place
like we're on the bloody Tube
and now we think it's cool to
leave wheel guns in the pit box.
Who even was that?
-That was me.
-Of course.
Old man.
You losing your
hearing? What was that?
You wanna do this here?
Yeah, I'd love to do this here
in front of the team, right.
The one that you're
apparently a part of.
Okay. You made a
mistake. It happens.
I made a mistake. I
love this guy, man.
-Don't worry about it, Jodie.
-Are you even listening to me?
-Not really.
-No!
Stop.
Joshua is right.
An order is an order.
May I remind you that
you report to me?
Cool.
Just don't ask me
to give up position.
Sorry. Sorry, guys.
Hold up.
You swan into our garage
like some entitled prick.
-"Swan"?
-Calling us piss poor...
-What's "swan"?
-...and then you drive like that. Huh?
You said I "swan."
What's that mean?
You. You're an arsehole. You come
in like an arsehole. You swan.
So swans are assholes?
You're making the mistake of thinking
that I'm just gonna be some grateful kid
who'll bend a knee
to an old-timer.
I climbed a mountain
to get here, bro.
Formula 1.
Back home we call that
a participation trophy.
Joshua, Joshua! Josh!
Yeah.
What the hell are you
smiling about, man?
Did you win something?
There's 20 other drivers
still out on that track
and you're in here
posing for that nonsense.
Do you think any of
them respect us? Do you?
They need to learn that no one
gets past us without a fight.
No one.
You don't like the way I'm
driving? Beat me, swan.
Hell of a race, huh?
Whoo!
Sorry, I didn't see you. Um...
You still beating yourself up?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know that one.
Um, thanks for what
you said out there.
Just don't do it again, okay?
Makes me look like I need help.
Oh, man. You're right. Got it.
Hey, for what it's worth,
don't be shitty to yourself.
There's plenty of people out
there that'll do that for you.
Yeah.
"I'm sorry, Ruben, for demolishing
not one but both of your lovely cars.
For coming back into your
life only to destroy it."
Is this your revenge for Monaco?
Yeah, I waited 30 years
and came all this way to humiliate
myself on global television.
Funny. You think I brought you
in to make my other driver quit?
Listen, he's cocky. He's
arrogant. He's got a lot to learn.
You were cocky, you were arrogant
and you had a lot to learn.
I'm not here to hold anyone's
hand. I'm here to race.
No, you're not, Sonny. You're
here to give me a heart attack.
The board is up my ass
and I have to decide whether
to continue this fiasco
-or pull the plug now.
-You have till the end of the season.
By which time Apex will be
worth less than my shoes!
Sonny! God...
Tell me about Kate.
The car. I wanna talk
to her about the car.
She's the world's first female
tech director of an F1 team.
I mean, that takes balls.
Wow. Is that your line?
She'll see right through it.
It's not a line.
-I'm sorry. Sorry.
-Is she married?
Okay, stay there in that
tub of ice until Budapest.
You don't move.
Hey, Ruben...
We can't get there
with this car.
Hey. Hey.
Yeah, sorry. Hi, hi, hi.
What you working on?
I'm working on a new front wing concept.
Trying to pick us up a tenth or so.
Cool. And you can replicate
turns? Lateral airflow?
No, just straight line drag.
But, I mean, we can
calculate it from there.
Okay, what about turbulent air
from a car we're following?
No, not exactly, but...
Track conditions, surface
quality, weather, ambient temps?
I'm sorry, uh, is there something
that you wanted to discuss?
Kate, you read my mind.
So how does one get to be the first
female technical director of an F1 team?
Must take...
dedication and
lots of hard work.
-That's your urgent question?
-Hmm? Mm-mmm.
Plenty of people think I don't belong
here and I'm happy to add you to the list
if you're implying what I...
I think you're implying.
As a rule I don't imply stuff.
So you like straight talk?
Straight as an arrow. No sugar.
Everyone thinks Ruben's lost it.
That he is clutching at straws.
They're saying
maybe he lost a bet.
Ran over your dog.
They're saying Sonny
Hayes isn't a has-been.
He's a never-was.
Yeah, when I said I like
straight talk I meant me.
From others, I mostly prefer
praise, flattery, hero worship,
at times, straight-up bullshit.
Is that what Ruben's for?
Ruben. I love the guy.
Most solid, steadfast...
Said you asked if I was married.
Disloyal, mean, twisted,
bitter, husk of a man.
Mmm, yeah. And he also told me about a
big string of ex-wives and girlfriends.
He said to avoid
you like the plague.
Okay... let me explain this.
When you're going 200 miles
per hour into Eau Rouge,
it's good to know
who's got your back.
And for the record, in
all my years of racing,
I have never ever hit on
the team technical director.
Well, now that's a huge
weight off my mind.
So what's this urgent question?
Okay.
Red Bull, Ferrari,
Mercedes, Aston, now McLaren
all have us beat on
straight line speed.
Our shot is battling
in the turns.
I need a way to chase
through the dirty air.
You want me to redesign
so you can follow closer?
We need to build
our car for combat.
Uh, how am I supposed
to make that safe?
Who said anything about safe?
That's your question?
Yeah.
And here's the straight talk.
It's urgent.
You know, I bet when
you look in the mirror,
you see this rough-and-tumble,
old school, no bullshit cowboy.
Doesn't take orders.
Goes his own way. Huh?
A lone wolf.
Well, I have news for you.
Formula 1 is a team
sport. It always was.
And maybe that's why
you failed at it?
The only question here is, "Why
did Sonny Hayes come back to F1?"
Now that question is
extremely fucking urgent.
I'll start listening to
you when you finish a race.
♪ Don't let me down ♪
♪ Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah ♪
♪ Don't let me drown ♪
♪ Don't let me down ♪
♪ Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah ♪
♪ Don't let me drown ♪
♪ Don't let me down ♪
♪ Nights like these ♪
♪ There's something mystical
About nights like these ♪
♪ And the concept of
time don't matter ♪
At the Spanish Grand Prix, the
American rookie Sonny Hayes
had just signed a new contract,
and his future looked very bright.
He'd earned a reputation for
his aggressive driving style.
Seen by some as reckless, it
nevertheless served him well
as he climbed up the order
over the course of the season,
relentlessly pursuing
his first F1 victory.
Hayes was running well
in the opening laps,
chasing down race
leader Ayrton Senna.
However when Hayes
made a risky move
and attacked Senna on the outside
of a high-speed right-hand turn,
a frightening scene unfolded
as quick as a flash.
My goodness! I just saw him
plunge off to the right.
There you can see the
debris on the right.
What on earth happened
there, I don't know.
Yes, this looks
very severe indeed.
I must say, it looks like, uh,
he is... he really needs help.
There is nobody coming
to him at the moment.
The race has been stopped.
The red flag is out.
This looks a little
bit like a...
Our models predict all teams are
gonna be targeting a one-stop race.
Plan A is to switch from mediums
to hards, between lap 27 and 33.
Plan B will be medium-hard-medium,
first window 16 to 21, second, 45 to 51.
Plan C for softs
doesn't make sense.
At this temp, the tire
deg will be too high.
Nothing else?
-Yep.
-Yeah, Joshua?
So, we've just got to
drive our race, all right?
Let's not try and be heroes.
Just make it through
those first turns clean.
Can't win at lap one,
starting at the back,
so we just gotta hope for some
lucky breaks later on, all right?
-Yeah.
Create your own breaks.
Um, hello, hi? I just said that.
Hope is not a strategy.
Anything else, Professor?
Um...
Drive fast?
It's lights out, and away we go.
Great start from Hamilton,
Verstappen battling with him.
Piastri, Zhou, Leclerc... and
here come the two Apex GPs.
But Gasly shuts the door,
leaving them with nowhere to go.
Into turn one, and there's
three cars gone off.
Gasly, Ocon, and the
AlphaTauri, Tsunoda.
Hit debris. Check my tires.
Yeah, you've got a puncture.
Right rear. Box. Box this lap.
First goddamn turn.
A ruined race.
Oh, shit, shit, shit. Ah, shit.
He's coming in! Let's go.
Let's go Plan C.
No, Plan C is for soft tires. They
won't last ten laps in this heat. No.
That's a negative,
Sonny. Plan A.
Plan A is called Plan A 'cause it's
when everything is going right.
You see anything going right?
Plan C. Softs.
It's not his call. Tell
him A, as in "asshole."
Okay, let's go! Turn
'em out! Hard tires.
Softs, goddamn it.
-What's wrong with the car?
-The guy sitting in it.
Are you insane? We need hard tires.
Everybody here is at a one-stop race.
We do what everybody
does, we lose.
-Make him go!
-How?
You think I don't know my
tires? I was a mechanic.
Five championship titles
with my bare freaking hands!
Give him his tires.
-Okay, let's go.
-Go, go, change!
Let's go, let's go!
Change quick, now!
Be ready.
Ready for what?
-Where's JP sitting?
-Currently running P14.
All right, here we go now.
Hayes makes his move,
chasing Kevin Magnussen.
It's a late lunge!
He's damaged his front wing.
Any driver knows Magnussen will shut
the door on a clumsy move like that.
Aw, dagnabbit.
Plan C for "chaos."
So that will bring out a safety
car, which always shakes up a race.
Slows down the leaders, leaves
the field bunched up together,
and gives teams the chance
for a quick pit stop,
which only costs
half the usual time.
Safety car. We're boxing, right?
Standby. Kate,
shouldn't we take advantage while
the safety car window is open?
It's early. We gain track
position if we stay out.
Stay out, stay out. Want
you out. Push, push, Joshua.
So, the midfield moves
up for the moment,
including Joshua Pearce to P12.
This guy better not
be messing up my race.
Where's JP now?
Currently running P12.
Okay. Plan C. Be ready.
He's gonna do it again.
Back marker Hayes
is now down a lap.
He has to let Bottas pass, or
face a five-second penalty.
Hayes is making it very
difficult for Bottas.
Under the rules he has to let him
through before passing three blue flags,
or risk a penalty.
Hey, I'm just putting it out there,
but, uh, maybe you should drive.
Sonny, you've gotten the blue
flag. Let Bottas through.
Come on, now. Little closer.
Sonny, do you copy?
I hear ya. Lettin' him through.
Whoops, my bad.
And that's his front wing again!
Oh, that's gonna bring
out another safety car.
Given that each wing
costs more than £200,000,
I think the team might want
Sonny to start chipping in there.
Guys, it's another free stop.
Please tell me we're boxing.
Uh, we're checking.
-Keep him out.
-Stay out. Stay out. You are staying out.
More drivers come in
to take fresh tires,
but still, Joshua Pearce remains
on track. He's moved up to P11.
Look who's back.
I know, I know. Be ready.
What is he doing?
I think he's trying
to score us a point.
Tell JP to save his tires.
Joshua, just take care
of your tires, okay?
You have to make them last.
Last? No shit. I will be.
With four laps to go in
this stop-and-go race,
thanks to Sonny Hayes,
the driver helped most is
his teammate, now in tenth.
With a 12-second
gap ahead of Stroll.
Tell JP to maintain that gap.
Keep pushing.
My tires are gone, man.
What are you waiting for?
Copy that. We have to call it.
He's losing over a
second every lap.
Stand by.
Into turn two. Hayes battles with
the Williams and pushes it wide.
Seriously, what
are we waiting for?
Sonny's off the track.
He's gone too far over.
And that's gonna cause damage.
Plan C.
Oopsie. Sorry, guys.
That's the third safety car
involving the Apex GP driver,
bringing the Hungarian Grand
Prix to an absolute crawl.
A sub three-second stop,
and he'll keep P10.
Box, Joshua. Box, box, box.
Copy. Coming in.
What did you say?
Joshua Pearce
finally gets to pit.
And with a quick stop here,
he could stay in the top ten.
This is critical.
Pearce must beat Stroll to the pit
exit line to maintain tenth place.
And he's done it!
With yellow flags out, all the cars
are forced to hold track position,
-meaning that thanks to Sonny Hayes...
-Let's go!
-...the race ends under a safety car.
-Yeah!
-Vegas!
-What? Whoa!
Hey, yeah. Fuck you.
Yeah!
Yes, baby!
You're crazy, bro.
It's just tenth. What
are you smiling about?
And behind our podium placings,
Hamilton and Piastri
complete the top five,
-and Joshua Pearce in tenth...
-Wow.
-...scoring Expensify Apex GP...
-Yeah, baby.
...their first ever point.
Did you see me? Crazy, right?
-A deal's a deal. I finished.
-Yeah, in last place.
Sounds great when you say it.
I know you have to go
see the stewards later,
what do you think they're
gonna make of your race today?
Well, I have to admit, you
guys got this one right.
-I'm, like... Thank you. Thank you.
-Good job. Yeah.
I'm still a bit rusty and, you
know, finding my way with this car,
but I'm confident
we'll get there.
A rope-a-dope at Silverstone, a
demolition derby here in Hungary...
You've been banned from casinos.
Are you trying to get banned from F1?
Take the whole team down with you?
Tell you what, Don, what
do you say we make a bet?
Your £10 against my 10 grand.
We place at Monza, I win your
10. We don't, you win mine.
Let's do this, man.
Put your money
where your mouth is.
What the hell? I'll take that.
-Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
Hey. No more press.
No, Sonny, you don't wanna
make the media your enemy.
And you'll be fined.
Take it out of my paycheck.
We don't pay you enough.
You know, I have to say.
I kinda like it.
It's very sort of punk
rock for the brand.
Hmm.
Let's run it again.
How long's he been in there?
All day. Playing with different
tire pressures, ride heights.
What were his times?
He found half a second.
Give me the same setup as him.
It must be late.
I'm seeing double.
A deal's a deal. I'm
building her for combat.
At the Dutch Grand Prix,
you'll be entering the Tarzan
Corner at 322 kilometers per hour.
Yeah. Too late to
change my mind?
Yeah.
To answer your question,
I was in aerospace at Lockheed
when Ruben came in and...
He liked my work,
liked my attitude,
and he sold me on the thrill of fighting
to the death for a tenth of a second.
Traveling the world,
the roar of a crowd...
So, I ran the idea
past my husband.
Who swiftly became
my ex-husband.
Good night.
Do you know what time it is?
All right.
Tell me about the kid.
Okay, here's another
one my dad would say.
"Slow is smooth,
smooth is fast."
For what it's worth.
One more time around?
Just one? Come on. Is that all?
I'd never live with myself,
if I can't keep up
with you, Mr. 1990s.
Let's go!
Joining us today, we
have Kaspar Smolinski,
Zak Brown and Fred Vasseur.
Now, Kaspar, can we start with you,
after what was a fantastic result
-for the team in Hungary last time out...
-Thank you.
...but Sonny has got you skirting
the line of penalties and violations.
Is this your only strategy,
and have you got any spare
parts left in the factory?
We compete like everybody else.
Race models change.
We must adapt, huh?
Well, Zak, can we
bring you in on this?
Because you've faced Hayes before, you
know the gray areas in which he works.
Certainly do. Uh, first of
all, he's a lot grayer now.
And, uh, we keep tabs on him,
you know, back there behind us.
And Fred, any
concerns from Ferrari?
What does Ferrari think of Apex?
We don't.
Sonny!
You're the best!
A better qualifying yesterday
gets us in the thick of things.
P10, P15.
So we're gonna go
for a two stop.
Medium-hard-medium, that's plan A.
Final stint, we go hards for plan B.
So, on this, do you
have any track concerns?
Don't look at me. Look at him.
It's good for JP.
Start me on hards.
Nah, the track's cooled down.
You won't have any grip.
That's right.
For three weeks, all the
talk's been how reckless I am.
Everyone's wondering if I'm
gonna drive 'em off track,
which means no one's gonna
be watching out for him.
Today, you win us this race.
Twenty laps down here at Monza,
and the pack have been split.
The leaders are pulling
away, led by Max Verstappen,
with Joshua Pearce back in P10.
Meanwhile, Sonny Hayes is
holding up the rest of the pack,
stuck behind him in a DRS train.
Pearce looks to be in a great
position to finish in the top ten,
and maybe even a
run to the podium.
But there's still a long
way to go in this race,
and with rain potentially
forecast, anything can happen.
Tires are gone. Coming in.
Yeah, copy. Box. Box.
Apex GP is prepping a fresh
set of tires for Hayes.
That's gonna bring in all the
other teams to avoid the undercut.
Uh, changed my mind.
But, no! He's staying out, with
the cars behind him all scrambling
to get on fresh tires that apparently
he doesn't think he needs anymore.
Should we just do the opposite
of what he tells us to do?
Stand by till I lose my tires.
-I thought he had lost his tires.
-I think he means literally.
Puncture, left rear. Coming in.
And there goes Hayes's tires.
That's quite a mess,
gravel on the track.
That will bring out the virtual
safety car for a quick sweep.
So the race gets neutralized.
Everyone slows down to
40% of their racing speed,
and all the race strategies
will get a reset.
And that is why this is the
perfect time to take a pit stop.
While you're in the pit lane,
your opponents are restricted
to a much slower pace
and you're not going to lose as
much track position when you rejoin.
-I take it I'm staying out, right?
-Copy. Joshua, stay out. Stay out.
-We want you out to gain track position.
-Copy.
Up is down, down is up.
Sonny Hayes hesitated
before he left his pit box,
and he's come out just in
front of Max Verstappen.
That was naughty.
Hayes has slowed a
bit in the pit lane,
which will cost the Red Bull and
the two Ferraris precious time.
Push, Joshua. Push.
You are now P4. P4.
Who's coming up from behind?
Here he is, Joshua Pearce.
-Let's see! Let's go!
-Yes!
-This is all playing into his hands...
-Wow.
...at the moment. Could
be a dream afternoon.
But can Hayes hold Verstappen
for a little bit longer?
Verstappen tries into turn
one, nothing doing there.
Gets the better exit. Through
the Curva Grande we go.
-Damn, he's good.
-Verstappen's trying to get past.
Sonny Hayes looking
carefully in his mirrors.
He must let Max
Verstappen through.
Yeah, I deserved that.
And Max shows his disapproval,
and I don't blame him, as they head
down towards the second chicane.
And through goes
Joshua Pearce in P4,
now much closer to
the front of the pack.
Just seven laps to go,
and here comes the rain.
Let's see who plays it safe with
a switch to the intermediate tire,
and who might gamble
to stay out on slicks.
It's getting tricky out
here, guys. What's the plan?
You're running P4. We think P2 and P3
are switching to inters for safety,
and it looks like
P1 is staying out.
-What do you wanna do?
-What's Sonny gonna do?
Take a wild guess.
-I'm staying out.
-Copy that.
And the two Ferraris come
in for intermediate tires.
Let's see who else
decides to play it safe.
And as George Russell pits,
Joshua Pearce moves into P2.
Sonny, Joshua is staying out on slicks.
If he can hold on and find a dry line,
he's gonna finish second.
Second's not enough.
Damn it.
Okay, coming in for inters.
-Inters, inters.
-Let's go! He's coming in!
-How far behind me are they?
-Thirty seconds.
Oh, my God. He's gonna
take out Verstappen.
Let me know when they
hit the main straight.
Don't tell him! They penalize both
cars. They will take the win away.
Just trust me, will ya?
I'm pushing but I
can't catch him.
As the race leaders
approach the main straight,
Sonny Hayes is in another
standoff over team strategy.
-Now.
-No!
Finally, Hayes back
out onto the track,
and just in front of Verstappen.
Now he'll get a blue flag here
so Verstappen can get past,
but until then, the Dutch driver
is caught up in Hayes's dirty air.
With every turn he hangs on,
he slows Verstappen a
fraction of a second,
providing Joshua Pearce one
last chance to catch up.
I can see him. I'm almost there.
Tell JP to follow me.
-Copy. Uh, Joshua, Sonny is your tow.
-I'm right behind him.
Verstappen pulls away then.
But now, onto the rear
wing of his teammate's car
comes Joshua Pearce.
Pearce picks up the
slipstream from Hayes,
gaining time, but driving
blind in the spray.
Come on. Stay with
me. Stay with me now.
Pass. Pass.
-Overtake him. Overtake.
-Copy.
He's been gaining, and boom! Joshua
Pearce slingshots past Sonny Hayes,
and now is in striking
distance of P1.
Tell JP to wait for the
straight into turn one.
Be patient.
-Straight at turn one.
-Copy.
Joshua, Sonny says wait for the
straight. The straight into turn one.
I'm right there.
I've got him.
Pearce is right on the
gearbox of Verstappen,
down the back straight at
over 200 miles an hour.
I see an opening. Going for it.
The rookie attacks in 11.
No, no!
Pearce pulls alongside
the Red Bull,
he's wheels ahead, for
the first time ever...
Apex GP... Oh, no!
No!
For God's sake.
Bernadette, how's he doing?
He's stable.
He's resting now.
Very happy to hear it.
I'm so sorry for what
happened. It was clearly...
Sonny, over here, please.
Um, I just wanna
say I've been...
Joshua says you're an asshole.
Yeah, that tracks.
I think you're a
dangerous asshole.
-Ms. Pearce...
-You're part of the same team, right?
Looking out for each other.
Except you had him doing
something so dangerous
it almost got him killed.
-Okay, listen...
-No, you listen to me.
This is my son.
And if anything... anything
else happens to him,
I'm coming after you.
And you better pray I don't
put you in a bed next to Joshua
for a very, very long time.
Clear?
Sure.
Sonny, Sonny.
Do you think Joshua blames you
for what happened in Monza?
Sonny, come on.
It was clear that you
were running his race.
Look, you kept him out on slick
tires, in dangerous conditions,
that even if you told him not to
pass, wasn't the accident inevitable?
If I may. If I may.
Joshua's back home, recovering.
We are expecting his
return in a few weeks.
Until that moment, our reserve driver,
Luca Cortez right there, will drive and...
-Next man up.
-Answer the question!
A chaotic week for
Expensify Apex GP,
and again, it's Sonny
Hayes at the center.
Many are blaming him for his
teammate's horrific accident at Monza.
His high-stakes, gambling style of
racing has the whole grid on edge,
and while the controversy
continues over who was to blame,
doctors have said that Pearce
will miss the next three races,
due to the burns suffered on his hands
as he begins his road to recovery.
Today, we're going with
our combat upgrade.
The revised shapes will improve
the flow field under the floor,
allowing us to run in dirty air
with minimal loss of performance.
Means we have to keep the
field close at all times,
and as for this week's plan C...
They've docked us to the back of the grid
'cause they don't like the way we drive.
Fine. Fuck 'em.
'Cause if we can pick up a
tenth of a second from you,
and from you, and you, and me...
If everyone in this room can
make one critical contribution,
that's a second every lap.
And after 72 laps, that's the
difference between last and first.
Plan C...
Plan C's for combat.
Combat, combat, combat.
Combat, combat, combat, combat.
♪ I don't wanna lose my mind
I don't wanna lose myself ♪
♪ Tell me if I crossed a line
I ain't trying to hurt myself ♪
♪ Didn't want to call your
name Only got myself to blame ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ In my world, in my mind
Always running out of time ♪
And that's Hayes in
the upgraded Apex.
Now the team were penalized
back to last place after Monza,
but here he is, coming from the cellar,
passing his new teammate, Luca Cortez.
♪ ...still I wait for you ♪
♪ Yeah, it feels... ♪
Round the banking,
Hayes has got past Ocon.
This is brilliant last lap
drama. What a fantastic finish.
♪ Ain't no way to tell
Which way it's gonna go ♪
♪ But it feels ♪
♪ So good I might
just lose my mind ♪
♪ No question if
it's wrong or right ♪
♪ And now it's too late
No way to take it slow ♪
Another fearless
attack from Hayes.
And here's where the Apex
GP has found strength.
Three-tenths gained every
lap, and in the corners alone.
♪ I don't wanna lose my mind
I don't wanna lose myself ♪
Scrapping away on the last lap,
Sonny Hayes gets the inside line,
but he can't quite get past.
George Russell will hang
on here for sixth place,
but this is Apex GP's
best ever finish.
-It's a valiant seventh.
-Combat, I love it!
Every race you miss,
fans just forget you.
Sonny always seems
to be one step ahead.
You never know. Sonny
may be a saboteur, Josh.
He may be a saboteur.
♪ Yeah it feels ♪
♪ So good I might
just lose my mind ♪
♪ No question if
it's wrong or right ♪
...and they go wheel to
wheel, Verstappen and Leclerc.
Verstappen will have the inside.
Perez goes round the outside.
Perez makes contact
with Charles Leclerc
as Sonny Hayes threads that Apex
GP car through the midfield.
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Bounce back When
the bottles is on me ♪
♪ I'm pushin' a new pen
Rewriting the story ♪
♪ Hello to my old ways
Goodbye to the nosebleeds ♪
♪ You fighting to stay
here You probably OD'ing ♪
♪ Ain't finna pop
for no reason ♪
♪ I don't throw
shots, I run legions ♪
♪ I been goin' over the
top Where no queen been ♪
♪ Die with no regrets
This is my season ♪
Talk about leaving it late.
Hayes squeezes through on the inside,
and with a run to the line now,
for their best
position ever, P5.
Give the design team a bonus,
because the upgrade has
completely changed this car.
And if Joshua
Pearce is watching,
well, he must be thinking,
"What might have been?"
♪ Yeah, it feels ♪
♪ So good I might
just lose my mind ♪
He's treating you
like a pawn, Josh.
Be a knight! Be a
knight! Be a knight!
Who would have believed
this weeks ago?
Expensify Apex GP has the
racing world on notice.
Apex! Apex! Apex!
Someone call the 1990s. Sonny
Hayes, if you missed him, he's back.
Last one up buys breakfast.
Look who's back.
Hello.
Good to have you back,
JP. We missed you.
♪ This for the underdogs This
for the underdogs, underdogs ♪
♪ Slide out the garage
I got a hundred cars ♪
♪ This for the underdogs ♪
♪ The teller just ask me
How I want the cashy ♪
Apex! Apex! Apex! Apex!
♪ I told 'em a hundred large ♪
♪ I want them gold wraps
Put it up double R ♪
♪ Tell 'em get out the way
4x4 big Phantom, supe ♪
♪ They thought I was canceled I
piped up and flipped the channel ♪
It's lights out and away we go!
And it's a decent start,
and everyone keeping it clean
as into La Source we go.
Ferrari ahead of Red Bull,
but here the two Apex GP cars
looking to work together as a team.
It's a welcome back to the
track for Joshua Pearce,
and Sonny Hayes glad to see him,
as they slice their way through
positions four and five.
And onto the Kemmel
Straight we go.
Now approaching top speed, Sonny
Hayes ahead of Joshua Pearce.
He's showing no ill effects from
that time off after the crash.
The car's working beautifully.
They're working as a team.
But hang on, Pearce right on
his tail, using the slipstream.
Is he about to try and overtake?
Into the chicane we go
and they touch wheels!
This is disaster for Apex...
...as out goes Sonny
Hayes and into the gravel!
Assholes!
What is happening
with this team?
Their first race back together,
and they've run into each other.
-You did great, Joshua.
-Well done, mate.
Whoo!
You pull that shit again, I
will knock your teeth out.
Oh, no one gets past us
without a fight, right?
Oh, is this funny? You think
you got a seat next year?
'Cause you just cut
your chances in half.
-That's how dumb you are.
-You failed. You failed!
-Why should I listen to you anyway, man?
-Hey.
Look, man. I don't give
two shits about you.
You wanna sabotage your
career, you go right ahead.
I've seen hundreds of guys
with your talent come and go.
No one cares!
But you sabotage Ruben, who
backed you? You sabotage his team?
I won't let you do it.
-Thanks, coach.
-Get your shit together!
So stupid! God...
How would you sum
up your race today?
Ooh. Um, it was good.
You know, the car feels great. I
think the team's done an amazing job.
It's just a shame about
the contact with Sonny.
You hate to see that happen.
-Hey, how are you doing?
-Hi, how are you?
Good. Sensational.
-Where's the team?
-Right this way, gentlemen.
Brilliant, you made
it. Come on. Sit down.
Sonny, you know Joshua.
Joshua, Sonny.
So I'm sure you both
have heard the rumors.
We all lose our jobs if you
can't pull off a miracle,
and that's starting with
staying on the bloody track.
Well, we were doing just
fine while JP was out.
I was out because I
was listening to you.
-Ish.
-And please don't call me JP.
It's a nickname. You
don't get to choose.
And your name doesn't even make
sense. Is it Sonny, is it Hayesie?
We don't know, do we, Kate?
Lads.
Have I not delivered you a car?
So you can do one thing for me.
Cards.
Come on. I know you
have 'em with ya.
It's my team meeting,
we're gonna do it my way.
-We're playing poker.
-Come on.
Yeah. Whoever wins gets to be
our number one driver tomorrow,
and if I win, I get to choose.
-Didn't he gamble for a living?
-Mm-hmm, yeah.
Now he's living in a van.
Texas Hold'em?
So, Sonny here
likes straight talk.
Isn't that right, Sonny?
-Yeah, that's what I hear.
-So, let's talk.
Who wants to go first?
-I'll go first.
No, I'll go first.
What's the difference between
Joshua Pearce and Sonny Hayes?
A lot of decades.
-Hard-won experience.
-Of living in a van?
Total freedom.
Total failure.
Says the guy who still
lives with his mom.
Says the guy with two pair.
-Says the guy with trips.
-Says the guy with a full house.
Girl.
Wait, I don't even
live with my mum.
Okay.
She just cooks for me sometimes.
Mm-hmm.
If you'd any constructive criticism
for each other, what would it be?
-Don't be such an arsehole.
-Don't be such a dickhead.
That was constructive.
You have a deficient
frontal cortex.
-A what?
-You can't analyze risk.
It's not all your fault. It's
not fully formed yet at your age.
But come the day
you learn patience,
-and stop being so immature, thinking...
-Patience.
-Patience is good.
Joshua.
He doesn't care about what anyone
else has to say but himself.
He just comes in and imposes his
will on all of us with no discussion.
He doesn't listen. I'm
trying, but he doesn't listen.
Mmm.
-Sonny?
-What?
Wow.
♪ Why they lie to the people?
Why the world is so evil? ♪
♪ Why can't just cool?
Just let me cool ♪
♪ Walking explosives
Stressing all of the time ♪
Who taught you how to play?
My dad liked to gamble.
-He make big bets too?
-Put a big one on me.
How old were you when
your fathers died?
Sorry.
-Thirteen.
Huh.
Why do you race?
Money... ...fame
and free clothes.
Oh, my God, with the phone.
Put the thing down, will ya?
What do you care what they say?
Easy for you to say.
They all love you.
It's just noise, man.
Drive the car.
You're really good at it.
You might be great.
♪ Hyperbolic catastrophic
scatterbrain ♪
♪ This is one diabolic
catatonic parade ♪
♪ Everyone just go away There's
nothing new to celebrate ♪
♪ There's nowhere
left to run away ♪
♪ They're closing off the open seas
They're locking off the runways ♪
♪ They keep telling me the one
thing So far from everything I see ♪
♪ Just go away ♪
Yeah.
Look at that, huh? Number
one driver tomorrow.
-Bonding?
-Ooh.
Well, this is nice.
We gotta go, mate.
Sponsor party at OMNIA.
Gotta steal ya.
Uh, Uncle Sonny, you're
welcome to come with...
Thank you, I'm good. I
have a race tomorrow.
-Cool. Kate?
-No, thank you.
-Come on.
-Thanks for this, Kate.
Come on, boy. Uh... Uh,
girls, you might have to...
We're gonna go dancing.
Should we go dancing?
Yeah!
Listen,
let's get this straight, okay?
I don't mess around during the season,
and never with a member of my team,
and what I'm attracted
to is winning.
And you just lost
to a pair of fives.
♪ So, baby, let's get messy
Let's get all the way undone ♪
♪ Come over, undress me Just
like I've never been touched ♪
♪ Baby, I'm obsessed with
you And there's no replica ♪
♪ Baby, let's get messy Let's
get all the way undone ♪
♪ I wanna let my hair down While
I'm staring down your face ♪
♪ Wanna go till lights out Take
you right back to my place ♪
♪ You out your mind If you
don't know what this is ♪
Hey.
You're a driver, aren't you?
-Yeah.
-Which team?
Apex GP.
Can you introduce
me to Carlos Sainz?
I'll go get him.
♪ Move from the back ♪
♪ Eyes on me How you like that ♪
♪ Just like this
Here for the night ♪
Oh, hey. Hey.
Oi, why do they say this place
is weird? I like this, bruv.
Glad you're having fun, man.
Be safe. I'm gonna leave, yeah?
-Huh?
-I said I'm gonna cut.
-Oh, wait, no, no, no. You just got here!
-I just... I'm not feeling it.
What do you mean? We just
got here, bruv. Josh!
♪ Just keep watching ♪
Hey.
I shouldn't drink tequila.
Last night was Ruben's idea?
Yeah, the first part.
-Well...
-Not the second!
Come on.
Why are you here, Sonny, huh?
Not much of a story.
Okay.
I'm here to prove
everyone wrong.
My ex, my old boss,
my first-year uni
physics professor...
-That bastard.
-Yeah.
And until we win, I haven't.
So, unfortunately,
I now rely on you.
Mmm.
I was gonna be world champion.
The best there ever was.
I'm just a kid and I'm on
the track with my idols,
Senna, Mansell, Prost.
And I am quick.
I'm fearless.
I was next.
And then...
...it was all taken away.
The crash, huh?
So I lost my seat, my
money, my sanity, my...
myself, really.
Just became this angry,
resentful shithead.
Not someone I'm
particularly proud of.
Till one day, I realized
what I had really lost,
and it wasn't the titles, or
the trophies, or the records.
It was my love for racing.
So I started driving.
Didn't matter the car, the circuit,
didn't need anyone to watch.
Just as long as I was behind
the wheel, I was good.
Sometimes...
What? Come on.
It's rare, but sometimes,
there's this moment in the car
where everything goes quiet,
my heartbeat slows,
it's peaceful,
and I can see
everything, and no one...
no one can touch me.
And I am chasing that moment
every time I get in the car.
I don't know when I'll find
it again, but, man, I want to.
I want to.
'Cause in that
moment, I'm flying.
Kate.
-Ruben.
-Where is he?
Where's who?
What are you talking about?
Ruben, seriously?
One, how dare you?
Two, I respect
professional boundaries.
And three...
Three, yeah, he's on...
he's on the balcony.
-Well, you're up early.
-Get dressed.
-Yeah, what's going on?
-They're coming for our car.
It's my duty to inform you that
we've received an anonymous tip
that your upgraded
floor is in violation.
From who?
-I can't say.
-Ah.
Sir, we submitted the
drawings long ago.
-Right?
-Mm-hmm.
And you approved them all.
It's whether the parts you're racing with
were developed outside of your facility.
What? That's insane.
Based on the paperwork we've
received, there are concerns.
Hang on, where'd you get these?
These are internal documents.
This team doesn't break
any rules, sir. No, no.
-I'll take that with a pinch of salt.
-Someone can fabricate documents.
Your car's under review.
-You know the procedure.
-What?
You cannot race unless you substitute
the previously approved components.
-No!
-Do you mean our old design?
A shit box!
No lo puedo creer.
Where were you the last
two years? Why now?
Because we might actually
win a race? Is that it?
This is not car racing, sir,
this is like corporate espionage!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Come... Come here.
I'm talking to you! Sir!
Without the upgrade,
we're screwed.
Sonny, let it go.
Focus on a clean start.
We'll never win clean.
Can we just not break any rules?
Yeah, the rules are always
against us though, aren't they?
Get them safe through lap one.
Sonny, we just need to
keep it in one piece. Okay?
Sonny?
-Oi, what the hell?
-I don't know!
What's wrong with Sonny?
Joshua, yep. Keep focused.
You're still good.
What's he doing?
He's driving angry.
Not good. It's not good.
Sonny, we need to
make these tires last.
Take it easy.
No, he's put the car
in qualifying mode.
He's gonna run the battery
down. Tell him to put it back.
Sonny, you're in qualifying
mode. What's going on?
Sonny, what's happening?
...blasting along Las Vegas
Boulevard, 210 miles an hour.
Hard on the brakes now,
and into the chicane.
Sergio Perez, ahead of Sonny Hayes,
but that's a mega exit from Hayes.
He's gotta gain on Sergio
Perez, and he's closing.
Meter by meter. Inch by inch.
Is this the place to take a gamble?
Hayes attacks round the outside.
No! No!
Why do we do this?
What's wrong with tennis, huh?
Or golf.
Right?
Christ.
We are totally insane.
"C5 neck fracture."
Spinal contusion.
Compressed thoracic vertebrae.
Further blunt force impact trauma
likely to result in vision loss,
"paralysis, death."
Really lead with the
good news, don't they?
This is a report
from 30 years ago.
Why didn't you tell me?
You never should have
raced again, Sonny.
How... How do you think I'd
feel if you die on the track?
Revenge for Monaco.
It's not a joke!
It's me who's liable, Sonny.
And don't think there's some bullshit
loophole to get you out of this.
-No.
-Ruben, we're drivers.
We are not drivers, not
anymore. I'm sorry. We're not.
We're losers.
We're a pair of dumb,
sentimental,
broke losers.
Okay. You're off the team.
Your van is in the garage with
all your stuff in it, and...
I never should have pulled
you into this, Sonny.
I'm sorry.
Ruben, wait!
I need this.
No one drives forever,
Sonny. Not even you.
Pippa, load up Monza. Just
like it happened. In the rain.
Joshua, Sonny says
wait for the straight,
the straight into turn one.
Run it again, please.
...wait for the straight,
the straight into turn one.
Run it again, please.
The straight into turn one.
Whoo!
Sonny.
Hey. You're not in Abu Dhabi?
I fly out tonight. I, uh...
Yeah, I wanted to catch you.
So, listen.
We both know that the board's wanted
to unload Apex from the start,
but, yeah, then
you rode into town,
raised our whole profile,
and now I've, uh...
Yeah, I've got... I've
got buyers lining up.
-Uh-huh.
-Gotta be honest with you, man,
I thought you were gonna be the...
the final nail in the coffin.
But now I see the play.
And I want you as
part of the package.
What sort of package?
I've set up a sale
where I run the team,
and keep you on for strategy,
maybe even team principal.
With the money from that deal,
I can make you a very rich man.
Here's the thing.
With the... the
changing regulations,
new Mercedes power unit,
Kate's aero, two new drivers...
we've got a real shot at
the championship next year.
What about Ruben?
Don't worry.
You know.
We won't embarrass him.
We'll keep him on with a... with
a title, or brand ambassador...
You know, something.
And I get final say?
Don't change a thing.
Do what you do, man.
And that's the irony here.
You know, the board
originally approved your hire
because we thought
you'd help us lose.
-Sorry to make you sweat.
-Hey.
That's my number.
Talk to your people.
But, uh... right after the race, I,
uh... I wanna lock down the deal, okay?
-So, by Sunday?
-Perfect.
Listen, this thing can
be your legacy, you know?
An F1 champion.
What you always wanted, right?
It was you who forged
those documents, wasn't it?
Huh.
-You're a killer, man, aren't you?
-Hey. I'm a winner.
Aren't you, huh?
Okay.
Oh, hey. How's the back?
Better.
I've got an amazing guy.
I'll, uh... I'll hook you up.
Hail Mary.
You good?
Listen, Mum, I've gotta
tell you something.
In Monza, right before the crash,
it was my decision to make the move.
Sonny actually told me to wait.
Family.
I've been working the
phones with IndyCar,
and I think I can get
you a test drive, bruv.
-Hello, Auntie.
-Hi.
They're trying to pull in a
new demographic, obviously.
And the ladies love that smile.
And we can throw in some
incentives, like flights and cars.
Listen, Cash, you can go.
I don't need you today.
Nah, mate. You got media next.
I don't care. They can fine me.
Besides,
that's not why I'm
doing it, right?
Josh, starting tomorrow,
we're not "doing it" anywhere.
It's all just noise.
Media, engagement, followers.
Listen, I've gotta
focus on the race.
Auntie, please.
Well, you heard the man.
-Deal.
-Yo.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Guys, what's happening?
Parc fermé. Waiting for
FIA to cut the seals.
Oh, good.
-We got time then.
-For what?
For...
No, no, no.
Welcome to the Paddock Club,
for our most valued guests.
Please, uh, grab a drink,
make yourselves at home,
and, uh, enjoy the very best view
there is of, uh... of Formula 1.
Okay? Okay.
Hey, guys, don't
stop! Keep going!
No way.
Jesús, it's like a
morgue around here.
How'd you get here?
Premium economy.
What? What is this?
Well, that's my
bullshit loophole.
Oh, no, forget it. I'm not
even going to read that.
That is a real legal document
from a real Tijuana lawyer...
...waiving all liability to you
and your company vis-à-vis
this race, myself, and me.
And...
...since you owe me my last paycheck,
technically I'm still on this team.
Kate, where's the shitbox?
The FIA confirmed that
the documents were forged,
and they were sent
by someone from Apex.
Huh.
Okay, I don't care about
your loophole. I don't.
That is my car. You
are not racing it.
-Ruben.
-No, Sonny.
Listen,
I can't let you do that.
I can't.
Okay?
If the last thing I do is drive that
car, I will take that life, man.
A thousand times.
We can't win.
We can't if we don't try.
How come you never
look at the card?
What card?
Welcome to the very
final spots on the grid.
And as ever, we'll go from last to
first. And breaking news here in P22,
because we're hearing the
Apex GP team have made...
-Hey, Peter.
-Yeah?
That's your guy. Isn't it?
...being replaced by Sonny Hayes, who
didn't even make the trip to Abu Dhabi...
Uh, will you excuse me for
one second? I'm really sorry.
Now, the rules require that he has
to start at the back of the pack.
Excuse me. What the hell?
What?
You still got my phone?
-Good luck today.
-You too, James.
Excuse me. Hey, Sonny. Sonny!
Hey, look, I know we've
had our differences,
-but look, this is your last F1 race.
-Chaz! This guy.
Any thought...
What's that?
Bloody hell.
Bloody hell!
Elbows out?
Elbows out.
All set for our season finale here
in Abu Dhabi where it's lights out.
And away we go. Good start
there for Joshua Pearce.
Drivers jockeying for position
as we head full-throttle down the
main straight and into turn one.
Tricky first corner, and going wide,
the Aston Martin and the AlphaTauri
as Pearce picks up two places.
Yes, Pearce showing some
real maturity there.
He saw a bad situation before it
happened and he's off to a great start.
Don't even think about it.
Here comes the Alpine
down the inside. Contact!
And three days out of
hospital, Hayes will feel that.
Gained places,
guys. We're alive.
I hope he hasn't
damaged the car,
but despite everything, it's
still a great first lap.
It is! Hayes in P16.
Pearce, his teammate, up to P9.
Red Bull, Mercedes and Ferrari
holding on to the lead.
Apex in the midfield.
Let's see if they can do
anything to shake up this race.
Gap to leader?
Fifteen seconds.
Keep JP plus 20
seconds. Plus 20.
-Length of a pit stop.
-You know why.
It's a busy race
for Sonny Hayes,
and now here comes Kevin
Magnussen looking to make a move.
And this could spell trouble.
There's history
between these two.
Often, the irresistible force
meets the immovable object.
And Magnussen, looking
down the inside,
-locks up and hits Hayes.
-Box, box. Box, box, box.
Copy, coming in for hards.
Damn.
Slow is smooth. Smooth is
fast. Here we go, boys.
Hayes exit the pits.
He had to come in because
of that damage to his tire.
But what of Joshua Pearce?
Where do Apex GP go with him?
Guys, am I boxing?
What's the plan?
Plan C, Plan C.
Stay out. Stay out.
-Chaos.
-Copy that.
Joshua slows down the leaders for
Sonny. Sonny does the same for him.
Pearce stays out.
It's a strategy that Apex
have used before this season.
It helps them with track position for now,
but they gotta keep these tires alive.
It's the only way
we keep this close.
And then we need luck.
I'm way ahead of ya.
Lap 25, and every driver
so far has pitted, bar one.
And he leads the race.
Joshua Pearce controlling
the pace out in front.
And that gives his
teammate, Hayes,
a chance to maintain his
position in the midfield
despite the contact,
puncture and pit stop.
They're working
really well together.
How's JP doing up there?
He's keeping the leaders at bay.
DRS active next straight, Sonny.
Got it.
Onto the back straight. He's
enjoying this new upgrade,
and he's got DRS, and
he's got Pierre Gasly.
Sonny Hayes up into P15.
Sonny, you have got
the pace. Keep pushing.
Pearce has been doing
a great job out front
despite the used tires, but
that moment is nearly over now.
Verstappen up the
inside and he's through.
Fabulous first stint
from Joshua Pearce.
Max has passed, and his
troubles don't end there.
Here comes Charles Leclerc.
It's another overtake. Pearce
lost the lead and drops now to P3.
Sorry, guys. My
rear tires are shot.
Copy that. Box, JP. Box, box.
Pearce stretching those
tires to the limit.
Short-term pain
for long-term gain.
And he exits the pit.
He'll have fresher tires.
He can now attack in the
second half of the race.
Sonny, the three leaders
are still on hards.
They're gonna have to stop
again. This is their pit window.
One of the leaders is gonna undercut.
I need to be there when they do.
P3 Ferrari. Pippa,
can he beat it to one?
Depends on their stop.
Will the undercut
work for Ferrari?
Five point eight. He needs
to pick up half a second.
Sonny, you need half a
second. Go, go, go, go, go.
And Sonny Hayes
is on the charge.
Under the track
goes the Ferrari.
Through the first
corner goes Sonny Hayes.
It's neck and neck.
It's really tight.
Sonny Hayes is just
ahead of Carlos Sainz.
-Yes! Come on!
-It's worked so far for Apex GP.
But their trouble's not over.
Down the inside, there's a chance
for Carlos Sainz, and he takes it.
But he locks up.
The Ferrari goes wide
and Sonny Hayes says,
"Thank you very much indeed."
How are they staying
so close to the lead?
Uh, they're, um...
They're working together.
Two Apex cars in the top 10,
but still a long way to go.
Twenty laps remaining, and Apex
has worked their way up the order.
We're now at the
final pit stop window.
This is our chance for P1.
Make sure JP beats them out.
Hamilton and Leclerc come into
the pits, but Pearce stays out.
-Talk to me. Can I catch 'em?
-Yep. They're just coming out.
Push now. Push now. Push, push.
Copy. Pushing.
Oh, this is gonna be close.
Joshua Pearce inching
ahead. Staying ahead.
For the second time in
this race, he leads.
Let's go!
Yes.
You are P1, Joshua.
But Pearce will have a
hard time holding them off
with Hamilton and
Leclerc on fresh tires.
Four laps to go.
Sonny Hayes is in P4.
He's five seconds
behind his teammate,
but both are on old tires.
There's little chance
they'll gain any places now.
And here's Hamilton attacking
Pearce into turn five.
And he's through.
Nobody has to stop again and
our tires are nine laps older.
And Leclerc attacks and passes.
Pearce's tires are absolutely finished.
There was nothing he could do about that.
I'm sorry, guys. I've
got nothing left.
It's been the Apex GP
story all year long.
Plenty of risks.
A great underdog story,
but we know, Martin, only
talent crowns a champion.
Losing grip. Tires are gone.
Yeah. Sadly, the deck's
been stacked against them
and now they're out
of cards to play.
It ain't over, right?
No, but nothing can change. It's
the worst feeling in the world.
George Russell on the attack.
Hayes looking to defend, through
the left-hander they go...
And there's contact!
Hayes is spun round
and into the barrier.
That's a big one.
-Fucking yes, yes, yes.
-Oh, no.
Yeah, no. Ooh.
There's debris all
over the race track
and substantial damage
to the barriers.
The stewards have no choice
but to red flag this race.
Miracle.
And speaking of damage, Martin,
Hayes will only be allowed
to continue in this race
if he can get his car all
the way around the circuit
and back to the pit lane.
Sonny. Sonny, can
you get it back?
I'll get it back. I'll get it
back if I have to push it back.
Come on, Sonny. Nice and easy.
He's still going.
JP, red flag.
Red flag. Come in.
We are still alive, hermano.
Red flag!
And somehow Sonny Hayes has got
his car back to the pit lane.
-It's a miracle.
-I know! I know.
Never seen one until now.
Home free. Good girl. Let's go.
New softs, both cars.
Raise the tire pressure
for three quick laps.
Team, time to build a car.
Red flag rules then.
The teams can make changes. They
can make repairs to their cars.
But only in that pit lane.
And with only ten minutes to make
repairs, Apex GP has their work cut out.
And all cars can fit
a fresh set of tires
for what will be a
three-lap sprint.
-Dodge! Dodge, are we gonna make it?
-I don't know. I don't know.
That was clean. That
wasn't me. Not this time.
"Not this time"? Tell
that to the stewards.
Check the replay.
I got this. Lift that corner.
I'm good. I'm good,
I'm good. I'm good.
What the stewards
will be looking at
is whether Hayes
went off completely
or kept at least one tire on track
during the contact with Russell.
-Yo, you good?
-Yeah, good.
Listen, you were on track.
Yeah, it was your corner.
P3 and P4. Let's go!
Given Hayes's reputation, they'll be
looking at this really, really closely.
I'm not expecting
a quick decision.
Come on, that's
clearly a penalty.
Like... I mean, not that
that's what we want,
but, like, objectively,
that's the guy.
-Oh, man. It can't end this way.
-It's just a time-out.
Like the last 30 years. It's in
the hands of the racing gods now.
We gotta believe. Gotta believe.
Plenty going on here in the pit.
Oh, look. Here comes the new
wing. This is a massive job.
Yeah, but will the car hold together
for the remaining three laps?
Well, that barrier
looks okay now.
The marshals just sweeping the last
few bits of debris off the track,
and the clock
continues to tick down.
Yeah, it's just over two minutes
until this race gets underway again.
JP, JP!
Three laps.
Three laps is a lifetime.
Go win this thing.
Hey, Sonny. Sonny,
you got a minute?
We got you a car.
Ah, you rock. Thank you.
Because Apex GP didn't make
the top 10 in qualifying,
they have a new set of
soft tires available,
which will give them extra speed
over the cars ahead of them
on the used soft tires.
This red flag is a lifeline.
You'd almost wonder if
Sonny didn't engineer it.
But wait, we're the
only cars on fresh tires
because we sucked in
qualifying yesterday?
Never got the
chance to use them.
Sometimes when
you lose, you win.
-That don't make no sense.
-It's a Sonny thing.
Light at the end of
the pit lane is green.
We're off on our second
formation lap of the evening,
and when this race resumes,
this is gonna be an epic sprint.
Hamilton, Leclerc, Pearce,
Hayes. That's the top four.
Sonny, we just heard
from the stewards.
Goddamn it. Now?
We're debating
whether to tell you.
Kaspar says, "Yes,"
but Kate says, "Don't."
She says you're fast
when you're angry.
Tell her, "Job well done."
And here's news. Stewards
have made their decision.
That Lap 55 collision between Hayes
and Russell is ruled a racing incident.
No further investigation.
Whoa! Sonny.
That was your line, Sonny.
Go finish your race.
Joshua, we still got
two cars in the mix.
Then we've got a team.
Once those red lights go out,
this will be an absolute
sprint to the finish.
Position advantage to
Mercedes and Ferrari.
Tire advantage to Apex GP.
Tell JP to follow my lead.
Joshua, Sonny says
to follow him.
Follow? He's behind me.
-Cheeky bastard.
-That's it. Stay with me.
He's giving you a tow. Take it.
All the way.
Come on, kid. Get it. Come on!
Hayes plays the decoy,
and Pearce rockets past
Leclerc and up into second.
And Leclerc's in danger from Sonny Hayes.
Round the outside, he's up into P3.
Perfect teamwork.
Hayes and Pearce working
together, it's like racing ballet.
It's a beautiful sight,
but now their sights are set on
the race leader, Lewis Hamilton.
Yeah! Remember me?
Come on, boys. Send it!
Why didn't they overtake?
Lewis will defend whichever
car attacks first.
-But they both can't wait.
-Someone has to sacrifice.
Two onto one,
and all the pressure
is on Lewis Hamilton
as Apex work as a pack.
Go win it, kid.
Hayes makes the first move.
-Hamilton defends. Pearce attacks.
-Yeah!
And Pearce has P1.
-Yes!
-Yes, yes!
Toe-to-toe, wheel-to-wheel,
this is epic racing to
finish off the season.
And Sonny Hayes and Lewis
Hamilton aren't done yet.
Hamilton, on Sonny Hayes.
There's contact!
And through goes Hamilton.
-Yes, yes!
-Come on!
Yes!
Guys, talk to me. Where's
Sonny? Can he finish?
One more lap, JP.
Hamilton never backs down.
Can Sonny finish the race, man?
Yes, he's on track. Just
watch Lewis when he fights.
You're P1. No more risks.
No such thing.
The rookie holds his
line. He won't back down.
He's here to fight the
seven-time world champion.
That made contact.
The leader and Lewis Hamilton
are out of this race.
Despite yellow flags flying at
turn one, this race will continue.
Sonny, push, push, push.
You're P1! You're P1!
Apex GP has only one lap to go.
The question is do
they have the car?
We have the driver.
Yeah! Go on, Sonny!
What's happening?
He's flying.
Sonny, you did it!
We won! We won!
Yeah!
Yes!
We won!
Yeah!
-We did it! Whoo!
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
-Come on! Yes!
-Yes!
Means another three
years for Ruben, right?
Yeah.
I guess we'll check
back about that deal.
Presuming you're
still on the board.
Breathtaking!
Breathless! Incredible!
What an Abu Dhabi Grand
Prix this has been!
What a victory as well!
Absolutely. It's a race for
the ages. An absolute thriller.
-And this man wins his first Grand Prix.
-Well done.
-It's been 30 years in the making.
-Well done!
And the team did a brilliant
job from the pit wall.
-And of course we can't forget Pearce...
-Oi! What you smiling about?
-...playing his part in this victory.
-You.
I'm gonna win a million races.
You should at least have one.
We did it.
Yeah, we did.
Whoo!
Sonny!
No, no, no, no. Give it to him.
No, no, no. Give it to him.
Oh, my God. Thank
you. Thank you.
Let's go!
I love you.
Yeah!
Today we get to say...
-"We are the best in the world!"
Joshua.
If you were ever to consider
to drive somewhere else,
you know where to find me.
Thanks, Toto, but
I'm happy where I am.
Congratulations.
Yeah, baby! Let them wait!
Let them wait!
The cup!
Kate, you built a hell of a car.
Another race I don't know about?
Somewhere.
That beats this?
Yeah.
I wanted to say, "See
you down the road,"
but in a way that
was more poetic.
So...
Can I see you down the road?
Yes.
Hang on to that until then.
Okay.
And drive fast.
And where do you
think you're going?
Don't worry about
me. Go celebrate.
But you're off to where?
You know, couple
more dragons to slay.
It's your team now.
It was always my team.
I'll be watching.
See you around, swan.
Hello!
Buenas.
I'm told you're
looking for a driver.
What's your name?
Sonny Hayes.
Have you ever driven Baja?
Nope.
We can't pay much.
Not about the money.
So what is it about?
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Flying through the city
With the speakers up loud ♪
♪ Speeding by with
the top down ♪
♪ Fast lane living Till
they put me in the ground ♪
♪ And I don't wanna stop now ♪
♪ Pull away, wind blowing
Now I'm cruising ♪
♪ Put the past in the
past A new day is coming ♪
♪ Ha-la-lay-la, we can ride ♪
♪ Four wheels, you and I
Gotta get out of here ♪
♪ Ha-la-lay-la, my savior ♪
♪ Ha-la-lay-la, we can fly ♪
♪ Out of this burning fire
Just take me anywhere ♪
♪ Ha-la-lay-la, my savior ♪
♪ Pedal down and drive ♪
♪ Drive ♪
♪ Pedal down and ♪
♪ Just drive ♪
♪ Out of the city Now we're
switching four lanes ♪
♪ Got our eyes on
a fresh start ♪
♪ The world as we knew it
That was caught up in flames ♪
♪ Get ready for the next part ♪
♪ You know I'm good If
I'm back in the gutter ♪
♪ 'Cause this life It was
never about the money ♪
♪ Ha-la-lay-la, we can ride ♪
♪ Four wheels, you and I
Gotta get out of here ♪
♪ Ha-la-lay-la, my savior ♪
♪ Ha-la-lay-la, we can fly ♪
♪ Out of this burning fire
Just take me anywhere ♪
♪ Ha-la-lay-la, my savior ♪
♪ Pedal down and drive ♪
♪ Drive ♪
♪ Pedal down and ♪
♪ Just drive ♪
♪ Drive ♪
♪ Pedal down and drive ♪