(BIRD SCREECHES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(BEE BUZZING)
(BIRD SONG IN DISTANCE)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(HORNS HONKING)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES)
Hey!
Are you single?
I'm a matchmaker at Adore.
Please give me a call if
you want to meet somebody.
We have a lot of
great matches for you.
Talk soon.
James, hi.
Thanks for calling me back.
Um, I just wanted to get some
feedback on your first date
with my client Sophie.
I'm actually on my way
to meet her right now...
but I had a quick chat
with her this morning...
and the headline is,
she had a great time
and would love to see you again.
Hello? James?
JAMES: Yeah, I'd like to
be taken off the service.
May I ask why?
JAMES: I thought you
were going to set me up
with high-quality women.
I said: a fit woman in
her 30s with a nice smile.
She's 40 and fat.
-She's 39.
-39 is not 30s, that's 40.
I would never swipe right
on a woman like that.
-I'm sorry you feel that way.
-(LINE DISCONNECTS)
(LINE BEEPS)
SOPHIE: I'm so happy.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
You did it, Lucy.
When you said that he's 47
and only makes 150K a year...
I almost said no, but I'm
really happy I trusted you.
I know it's only been one date
and I need to manage
my expectations...
but this is probably the best
first date I've ever had!
Uh, Sophie, so I just got
off the phone with him.
And he loved meeting you,
he had a great time...
But he doesn't feel
like the chemistry
is there for him at this time.
So.
Onward and upward.
He doesn't want a second date?
No.
He's balding.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
How fucking dare he?
LUCY: Dating is a risk.
You took a risk. It's brave.
SOPHIE: Why did you set me
up with someone like that?
He checked a lot of our boxes...
and you checked a lot of his.
So, onwards and upwards.
Let's talk about
your next match.
I have an amazing guy for you.
His name is Mark, he's a doctor,
he's very handsome...
he has a full head
of hair, he's 48.
SOPHIE: That's almost 50.
He looks great for 48.
He's very fit. He
looks like he's 40.
-How tall?
-5'11".
Is he actually 5'11" or is he
actually 5'9" and is lying?
What's a couple of inches?
SOPHIE: I don't want
to waste my time.
I am not asking for a miracle.
I'm just asking for
the bare minimum.
I'm trying to settle.
LUCY: Sophie.
I know how it feels right now.
But I promise you...
you're going to marry
the love of your life.
SOPHIE: I don't believe you.
That's okay.
I believe it.
(HORNS HONKING IN DISTANCE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(ALL CHEERING)
Girl of the hour!
Tonight, we're all gathered
to celebrate the
most talented Lucy.
One hell of a matchmaker
with razor-sharp instincts...
and an eagle eye for chemistry
because this weekend...
her client Charlotte
B. Is getting married!
(ALL CHEERING)
Charlotte B. Is
marrying Peter C.
The Prince Charming
Lucy matched her
with 20 months ago.
How many marriages are you
responsible for now, Lucy?
Nine.
(CHANTING) Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!
Lucy, do a speech!
(CHANTING) Speech!
Speech! Speech! Speech!
Okay.
My speech is...
that if the girl asks for
a 6-foot-tall drink of water...
in his 40s with a
salary over 500 grand
and a... good hairline...
(ALL LAUGHING)
You deliver.
(ALL CHEERING)
How did it go with
Sophie L. today?
It took our membership team
an hour to get her to renew.
Hopeless.
I'm afraid there's not a
single man in New York City
that'll date this girl.
What seems to be the issue?
That's the thing. There
is nothing wrong with her.
She's okay attractive...
okay money, okay educated,
okay personality.
There's just not a
standout quality.
She's not competitive in
the mainstream market...
and there is no
niche market for her.
Exactly.
And if there's no
specialty appeal...
then there's no place
for her in any market.
That is tough.
And she's my favorite
client right now.
I mean, she's entitled
like everyone,
but she's sweet...
and she's realistic,
she's not crazy.
She's a nice girl.
There's got to be
a guy out there
who just wants a nice girl.
What about Mark P.?
He's okay.
LUCY: I pitched
him to her already.
She's afraid he's
not actually 5'11".
And I'm like, can
we please not worry
about a couple inches right now?
Because you're
about to die alone.
(CHUCKLES)
You know there's a
surgery for that.
For dying alone?
For getting taller.
Up to six inches.
You break your legs, and...
extend it, let the
bone heal itself.
That's a game changer.
It costs like 200K.
Six inches can double a
man's value in the market.
If you can afford it,
it's definitely
worth the investment.
What's the saying?
"You're not ugly, you
just don't have money."
LUCY: Right.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Do you have a dress picked
out for the wedding?
Yes.
Are you going alone?
Mm-hmm.
Lucy M.: The Eternal
Bachelorette.
A voluntary celibate.
Do you want me to set
you up with someone?
No, I'm gonna die alone.
Or get a rich husband.
Same thing.
(LUCY CHUCKLES)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
HARRY: Hi, Charles.
Good to see you. (KISSES)
You look beautiful.
Oh, my God, look
how big they are.
Mom.
Congratulations.
Nice to see you.
You look beautiful.
Nice to see you again.
Hi, Henry. Hi.
PATRICIA: I have been
saying to everyone
that Peter and Char
are my couple goals...
and I need to find my own Peter
and you're responsible?
Well, I'm how Charlotte
and Peter met, okay?
But it's up to the client
to build a strong
enough relationship...
that leads to marriage.
But how did you know that
Peter would be the
perfect guy for Char?
JAIME: Well, she can't tell,
it's her industry secret.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) There
are no industry secrets.
We can always meet
our life partner
out in the wild or
swiping on apps.
But the happy ending
to a first date...
is not the second date.
It's changing each
other's diapers
and burying each other.
You're looking for a
nursing home partner
and a grave buddy.
Who our partner is...
it determines our whole life...
and how we live.
Not for one, two,
ten years, but...
forever.
Oh, my God. (CHUCKLES)
I need you so badly.
Yeah, I'm desperate.
Can I give you my card?
Of course.
I'm going through a divorce,
but once it's over...
I would really, really
like to give you a call.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
Lucy. She needs you.
Excuse me.
(FOOTSTEPS THUMPING IN UNISON)
I just need five
minutes alone with her.
(DOOR CLOSES)
-Hi, Charlotte.
-Hey, Lucy.
LUCY: How're you holding up?
Not good. (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
What's going on?
(CHARLOTTE SNIFFLES)
What's going on...
is that I am a modern woman.
Like, I could've been anything.
Anything.
But I chose to become...
a bride.
I chose this.
It's not like I'm
getting married
because I need to forge a...
relationship between
two kingdoms.
It's not like my family
needs a cow. (LAUGHS)
I chose this. I
chose to marry a man.
LUCY: Charlotte.
Marriage is a business deal.
And it always has been
since the very first
time two people did it.
You can always walk away
if the deal isn't good.
And as the person who
introduced you to Peter,
I will walk right
out of here with you.
So tell me: do you not
want to get married today?
I have to.
-LUCY: Why?
-Bec... (SCOFFS)
My parents spent so much
money on this wedding.
We spent hundreds of
thousands of dollars...
on this wedding just so that
I could feel like
a fucking woman.
LUCY: Why do you really,
in the darkest, ugliest
part of yourself,
want to marry Peter?
(CHARLOTTE SIGHS)
And I promise you...
I have heard every reason
why a person wants to
get married to someone.
And none of them are shocking
or wrong or crazy to me.
It will be a secret
between you and me.
You promise it'll be a secret?
LUCY: I promise.
You cannot tell anyone.
Not a soul. It is so awful.
LUCY: I will take
it to my grave.
He makes my sister jealous.
She's never said that,
but I know it's true.
She thinks he's better
than her husband.
She thinks he's...
got a better job, that
he's better-looking.
Taller.
And...
that makes me feel...
(SNIFFLES)
...like I've won.
(SOBBING)
So this is about value.
Peter makes you feel valuable.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, he does.
He really does.
Does that make you
want to marry him?
(CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES, SNIFFLES)
(APPLAUSE)
(ALL CHEERING, APPLAUDING)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
Hey.
I'm Harry.
Lucy.
You're the matchmaker.
You're the brother.
What are you doing
at the singles table?
My mother wants me to marry.
I can help you with that.
I saw you recruiting earlier.
A wedding like this
must be a gold mine.
There's a lot of opportunity
here for our company.
Your sales pitch is perfect
because you make it feel
like it's their idea.
It's not like you're telling
people they need you,
nobody wants to hear that.
If they need you,
then something is
wrong with them.
Instead...
you're saying: "You could
do this on your own"
"but if you're lucky enough
to be able to afford me,"
"why not?"
You're a luxury good.
Then they really do feel
like they need you...
just like they need every
other luxury in their lives.
Once you get your
first $400 haircut,
you can't go back to
Supercuts, can you?
It's easy.
No. You're just really good.
What's it like?
What's what like?
Being a matchmaker.
It's like working at the morgue,
or an insurance company.
(CHUCKLES) In what way?
6'2 ", 5'6". Skinny, fit, fat.
White, Black, Asian.
-Doctor, lawyer, banker.
-(CHUCKLES)
100 grand, 200 grand, 300 grand.
Smoker, non-smoker.
But you must know
a lot about love.
I know about dating.
What's the difference?
Dating takes a lot of effort.
A lot of trial and error.
A ton of risk and pain.
Love is easy.
Is it?
I find it to be the most
difficult thing in the world.
That's because we can't help it.
It just walks into
our lives sometimes.
Are you hitting on me?
-Definitely not.
-(CHUCKLES)
But I do think that you would be
a great match for a
lot of our clients.
We need more straight
men in New York City.
You look about six feet tall.
How much money do you make?
Just straight up like that?
I make 80 grand a
year before taxes.
Do you make more
or less than that?
More.
I know.
Finance, right?
Private equity.
Do you want a drink?
-Sure.
-What do you want?
-Coke and beer.
-(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(THUDS)
Hey, buddy.
Hi, John.
Working now, obviously, but
talk after dinner service?
Yeah.
Okay.
HARRY'S FATHER: Love
is the last religion...
the last country, the
last surviving ideology.
So what else really is
there to believe in?
When you get lost...
and I know you'll
be lost at times...
it's life.
When you're lost...
the answer is simple.
Just go where love is.
(APPLAUSE)
ALL: ♪ Touching hands ♪
♪ Reaching out ♪
♪ Touching me, touching you ♪
♪ Sweet Caroline ♪
♪ Bah, bah, bah ♪
♪ Good times never
seemed so good ♪
♪ So good! So good! So good! ♪
(HORNS, SIRENS IN DISTANCE)
Hi.
Hey.
So, what made them
perfect for each other?
LUCY: Similar
economic background.
Politically aligned.
Well-matched in
their attractiveness.
Similar upbringing.
Similar upbringing?
They both come from
big happy families.
(SCOFFS)
"Big happy families."
Yes.
I'll believe it when I see it.
The perception of a
"big happy family"...
is all you need to have
a "big happy family."
That's all it takes
to be soulmates?
Basically.
Poor...
voted for Bernie...
shitty family.
Are we soulmates?
Probably.
How's acting going?
How does it look
like it's going?
Sorry.
No, don't be, I'm
just being a dick.
I'm giving you a hard time
because I'm embarrassed.
LUCY: What are you
embarrassed about?
Having a job?
I'm in a play.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
It's not for a while.
I'm just doing jobs like this
to try and save some cash...
before rehearsal starts.
Definitely didn't expect
to run into you tonight.
I missed you.
JOHN: Yeah.
You don't even remember my face.
LUCY: Got it.
(CHUCKLES) Your turn.
You seeing anyone?
You saw me at the singles table.
(VEHICLE PASSING BY)
I missed you too.
(SIGHS)
Can I give you a ride home
after I'm done finishing up?
I have my car here.
Yeah.
We should catch up.
(SLOW DOO-WOP MUSIC PLAYING)
Mommy, mommy.
Giving me your number?
Recruitment.
Worked for your brother,
so I think it will work for you.
I'll call you if
you dance with me.
I'm going to call you.
But not to hire you.
I'm probably not someone
you want to date.
Why not?
Because the next person
I date, I'm gonna marry.
So what kind of a person
does a matchmaker want to marry?
Well, my non-negotiables
are that they're rich.
My nice-to-have is that
they're mind-numbingly...
absurdly...
achingly...
rich.
-Are you hitting on me?
-(LUCY LAUGHS)
(HARRY CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(SLOW DOO-WOP
MUSIC CONTINUING)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
We have the
penthouse at the Ritz
for the after-party,
if you want to come.
Maybe next time.
Can my driver drop
you somewhere?
I have a ride.
(PUNK ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO)
Remember this one?
Yep.
You still live in
the same place?
JOHN: Yep.
Rent's still $850.
No fucking way.
It's falling apart.
I never get hot water.
LUCY: How are your roommates?
David moved in
with his fiancee...
and I think Logan is developing
a drinking problem.
LUCY: David is engaged?
Yeah.
LUCY: To the TikTok girl?
Yep.
She does OnlyFans now too.
Good for him.
JOHN: Is it?
"He's a 5'7" depressed novelist
who's never been published.
He couldn't do better.
It's that simple, huh?
It's just math.
What are you thinking about?
It smells the same.
JOHN: What, my car?
Mm-hmm.
-Look, there!
-I'm not going to pay $25
to park this piece
of shit for an hour.
That's the cheapest
we'll ever get.
We'll find street parking
on the next block.
John, it's been 20 minutes.
I'll just pay for it.
You're not paying.
-We're going to have to...
-These fucking people...
forfeit the reservation
if we're more than
15 minutes late
and then they charge us
a cancellation fee of
$25 per person.
Wait, are you fucking serious?
I told you this like 10 times.
That's extortion.
Why would you make
a reservation at such
a criminal place?
We agreed to go to
nice restaurants
on our anniversary.
Oh, there's no "nice" places
in New York City that won't...
charge you 50 bucks if
you're a couple minutes late?
Why did we even bring the car?
Yes, it's my fault,
my rehearsal ran long.
-You made your point.
-We could've called a car.
So we could spend $50
to get into the city...
and then another $200
at the restaurant?
Why do you have a car if
you can't pay for it, John?
Look, right there.
$20 for 40 minutes? What
the fuck is this math?
I don't want to
fight about money
with my boyfriend
on our anniversary.
It makes me feel
like my parents.
JOHN: I'm sorry, okay?
We'll park at the
next garage we see.
What are you doing?
Lucy.
Where the fuck are you going?
Hey, I'm sorry, all
right? I'm sorry.
I don't have any
money, and I forgot.
What? What did you
forget? That you love me?
Will you please get
back in the car? Please?
I don't want to hate you
because you're poor...
but right now I do, and
it makes me hate myself.
Do you know how hard it
is to make you happy?
And I want you to be happy.
I'm trying. I really am.
I know. And it's almost
enough to make me happy.
(HORNS BLARING)
I wish that I didn't care if
we ate from a halal cart...
on our five-year
anniversary, but I do.
And however much you hate me,
I promise, I hate myself more.
I don't hate you.
You do.
And it's not because
we're not in love.
It's because we're broke.
(ENGINE IDLING LOUDLY)
(ENGINE SCREECHES)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
You want to come up?
Yes.
But I shouldn't.
Thanks for the ride.
JOHN: Anytime.
Invite me to your play.
I will.
(DOOR CREAKS)
(ENGINE STARTS, SCREECHING)
I'm just giving you feedback
so you can improve
your performance...
and I can start
getting better matches.
I want to meet someone who
is a combination of all
the different awesome parts
of the last four matches.
Sophie's job and
education level,
Emily's body and lifestyle,
Piper's face and
sense of style...
and Jane's hobbies
and taste in TV shows.
Easy, since I'm
Dr. Frankenstein.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
I'm turning 48 in a few months
and I think I need to
meet someone more grown.
Someone I can talk to,
just a proper woman
who knows good music...
has seen old movies,
things like that.
My last couple girlfriends
were 21 and 24...
and they were honestly
kind of immature.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) I
can imagine it might be
a little hard to relate to
girls born in the 2000s.
I have a really special client,
her name is Sophie...
she's a highly accomplished
lawyer, she's 39.
Um...
I wasn't really thinking 30s.
LUCY: So when
you said older...
I meant more like 27, 28.
LUCY: Ah.
It gets really intense
and complicated
with women in their 30s.
They have really
high expectations
and they tend to rush
things because I guess,
their biological
clock's ticking.
I have another really
beautiful client, she's 31...
Uh.
No.
Someone... 27.
Even 29 is pushing it.
Trust me... it's the
best thing for everyone.
I genuinely get
along much better
with girls in their 20s.
I don't care what she's
like or how she lives...
I just care that she's
my type physically.
LUCY: What's your
type physically?
Fit.
LUCY: Just fit?
Fit. Nothing over 20 BMI.
Okay.
Thank you for agreeing to
come on a date with me.
LUCY: Well, I only
said yes to this
so you'd realize you're wrong...
and you're not actually
interested in me.
HARRY: My instincts
are usually right.
You think that you're more right
about this than a professional?
Oh, sure, you're the
expert, but I trust my gut.
LUCY: Okay. We'll see.
You look really good today.
Thanks.
LUCY: How many
drinks per week?
Depends, but like, 8? 10?
Work makes it hard not to.
-Do you do drugs?
-Never.
I do pot at parties.
Me too.
So not never.
Hmm.
What do you think is your
best physical feature?
My eyes aren't bad.
How did you end up
doing what you do?
Both my parents
work in finance...
and so does my brother,
so I just kind of
ended up doing it.
And we all work for the
firm my mother started.
-It's a family business.
-Yeah, it's boring.
Mm.
How did you get into
doing what you do?
It was the... first and
(CHUCKLES) only thing
I was really good at.
HARRY: What else do you
want to know about me?
I bet your parents never raised
their voices at each other.
I think almost never.
Maybe they were
secretly fighting.
Did they ever fight about money?
No.
Makes sense.
I think we emulate the
way our parents fight.
Hmm.
I see couples fighting in
the middle of the street
in New York and I don't get it.
Aren't they embarrassed to
do that in front of people?
I'm the type to fight in
the middle of the street.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Have you ever done that?
-Never.
-(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
SOPHIE: Do you think
he will like me?
I think you will
really like him.
-Are you sure?
-Stay open-minded. (LAUGHS)
-I'm so nervous.
-All right.
Okay, text me after
-and I'll call you tomorrow.
-Okay.
-Okay, talk soon, Sophie. Bye.
-Bye.
-Hi.
-Wow. Thank you.
-(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
You're welcome.
You okay?
Yes. My client is going
on a date right now too.
You seem nervous.
I really want her
to like this guy.
She's had, like, 10
bad dates in a row
and I just need to deliver.
Are you feeling guilty that
you're about to
go on a good date?
(LUCY CHUCKLES)
(FAINT INDISTINCT CHATTER)
LUCY: I don't
know if I like you
or if I just like the
places you take me to.
You like me?
When did that happen?
I think when I saw the
way you pick up the bill.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
HARRY: I do it
really well, don't I?
You do.
Just one swift motion.
No hesitation. No fear.
HARRY: Well, I can afford
it, so why would I be scared?
You're investing
a lot in me, huh?
I just want our
dates to be romantic.
How expensive a meal is
makes the date romantic?
Doesn't it?
When we first met...
you said your job makes
you think like a mortician
or an insurance claims adjuster.
How am I as a corpse?
A good corpse.
How about as a payout?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Couldn't ask for better.
As a nursing home partner?
A grave buddy?
You can do better than me.
Can I?
You know how to do
the math, don't you?
In my line of work...
I meet hundreds of
highly desirable,
high quality men...
but you are what we call
in my industry "a unicorn."
An impossible fantasy.
Your brother was a unicorn, too.
The reason my clients cannot
lower their expectations...
is because, against all odds,
men like you do actually exist.
Well, I'm sure something
is wrong with me.
You're perfect.
You're smart.
You have ideal income,
ideal education...
ideal lifestyle, ideal height...
you're good-looking,
you have a great body,
you're charming.
You were born rich, raised rich,
you're still rich.
You own a penthouse in Tribeca.
You can take a girl to
a restaurant like this
and it's not even (LAUGHS)
like a special occasion.
You don't have a drug habit
or a call girls habit.
You even know how
to cut your hair,
and how to dress.
You have taste.
You are a 10 out of
10 in every category.
A complete package.
So I don't know why you're
trying to throw it all away
on someone like me.
What's someone like you?
Just a girl who works.
I'm older than the women
you could be dating.
Which means my looks
won't last as long.
And I have fewer years
left to get pregnant.
If you marry a 25-year-old,
then in 10 years
she'll look like me.
If you marry me, in 10 years
I'll look like my mother.
What does your mother look like?
I was born poor, raised poor,
and even though I
work, I have debt.
I'm a college dropout
and a failed actress.
I have no dowry.
If anything, I have
a negative dowry.
Do I look like I need a dowry?
At the end of the day,
the math doesn't add up.
Given your position in the
marketplace and given mine,
I'm not a girl you marry.
I'm a girl that you
go home with once,
and then never call again.
So...
what are you doing with me?
You say you think I'm smart,
but you're talking to
me like I'm a caveman.
I wouldn't date you
if I didn't see value.
I'm not like my brother.
I'm not looking for the nicest,
prettiest rich girl
who likes me back.
I'm looking for someone
who understands the game,
how the world works.
I'm looking for
someone I respect.
And trust.
Someone who knows more than me.
I don't want to date you
for your material assets...
though I think you're
underselling them
by a significant margin.
Material assets are cheap,
they don't last.
I want to be with you for
your intangible assets.
Those are good investments.
They don't degrade.
They only get sharper.
And, besides, I have
enough material assets
for the both of us.
I see a lot of potential here.
I think you and I could
make great partners.
I hope you agree.
As for what I can do for you...
I think I'm the
only guy this rich
you can actually stand.
I don't like you
because you're rich.
Then why do you like me?
Because you make
me feel valuable.
You are valuable.
That's what I'm
trying to tell you.
Do you want to see each
other more seriously?
-(SENSUAL INDIE MUSIC PLAYING)
-(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(HARRY MOANS SOFTLY)
(LUCY LAUGHING)
(PHONE VIBRATING)
-(LINE RINGING)
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(LINE RINGING)
VOICEMAIL: Hi, you've reached
Lucy from Adore Matchmaking.
Please leave a message
and I'll call
you back. Thanks.
-(BEEPS)
-Hey, it's John.
Okay. Just give me a
call when you get this.
Just wanted to invite
you to the play.
We start previews
next week, so...
Okay. Bye.
HARRY: What's your
dream vacation?
Iceland.
Hmm.
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
Would you let me
take you to Iceland?
-I don't even have a passport.
-Well, let's get you one.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHING)
(WHISPERING) How much
is this apartment?
Twelve million.
(WHISPERING) Do you like it?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
-(ALARM RINGING)
-(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
(JOHN GROANS, SIGHS)
-(RUBBER SQUELCHES)
-Oh.
What the fuck?
(SIGHS IN EXASPERATION)
Fuck!
(SQUELCHING)
-(THUDS)
-Hey, motherfucker!
You can't leave your used
condoms on the kitchen floor!
It's unacceptable!
I got kind of drunk last night.
I must've missed the trash can.
Why don't you throw it out in
your own fucking trash can?
I don't want it just
sitting there in the room.
Why don't you want your
own cum in the room?
It's fucking gross.
So we have to deal with
it in the fucking kitchen?
I know it doesn't make
sense, man, I was drunk.
RON: Hey, can you
two stop yelling?
I'm teaching an acting
class on Zoom...
and you're making me look
really unprofessional.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(THUDS)
(SIGHS)
Oh, fuck!
(THUDS LIGHTLY, CREAKS)
(THUDS, CREAKS)
(SIGHS)
HARRY: Right.
So he's asking for a
valuation in his dreams.
It's inflated.
He's giving us a DCF
based on pure fiction...
on future revenue streams with
blinders for expense growth.
Yeah, he's a bad analyst...
and he's just making
shit up at this point.
He's just saying numbers that
come to his head. Listen...
it's still a good growth
story for our company...
so we're going to
have to continue
playing ball with this guy.
(LINE RINGING)
VOICEMAIL: Hi, you've
reached Sophie...
(SIGHS)
(LINE RINGING)
MARK: Hello?
Hi, Mark, it's Lucy from Adore.
MARK: Oh, hi.
Hi. So, I just wanted
to get some feedback
on your first date
with my client Sophie.
Actually I haven't gotten
a hold of her yet...
so I don't know how
it went on her end...
but I'm excited to hear
how it went for you.
MARK: It went so
well. She's wonderful.
Like really nice
face, good body,
good job, great energy.
Just all the things I said
I wanted from a match.
Okay.
Okay, I love hearing this.
Um, I'm so glad you
had a good time.
Sophie is really wonderful.
MARK: Yeah, no.
Like the conversation
just flowed.
Uh, we ended up staying
out pretty late.
Cool. So, do you want
to see her again?
MARK: Sure.
Sure. I'm not sure how
serious it's going to be...
but I wouldn't mind seeing
her again, if she's game.
Great. Yeah, of course,
one step at a time.
MARK: All right. Thanks, Lucy.
Great. You have a good day
and I'll reach out
this afternoon...
after I speak with
her. Thanks, Mark.
Thanks, Mark!
(SIGHS)
VOICEMAIL: Hey, it's John.
Okay. Just give me a
call when you get this.
Just wanted to invite
you to the play.
VOICEMAIL: Hi, you've
reached Sophie...
-Hey.
So, uh, Rose was asking
for her client Mia W.
How it's going with Peter
C.'s brother, Harry?
Were you able to recruit him?
Yeah. Uh, actually, um...
I'm dating him.
-You're dating him?
-Yep.
-You know he's a unicorn.
-Mm-hmm.
(CHUCKLES)
You couldn't let him
go on a couple dates
with some of our clients first?
He insisted.
DAISY: (SCOFFS)
I'm sure he did.
Hey, Lucy. Can I speak
to you in my office?
Have you spoken with Sophie L.?
Uh, not yet. Just Mark P.
VIOLET: I just hung up
with Sophie's lawyer.
Her lawyer?
Apparently, she was
assaulted on the date.
What?
By Mark P.?
VIOLET: Yes.
Last night?
Are you serious?
She's bringing charges
to the company, not you.
I have a call with the
legal team in two minutes...
and we're going
to figure it out.
I need to speak with her.
Lucy, no.
-Violet, she's my client.
-VIOLET: She's not anymore.
So if Sophie calls,
you must not pick up.
-I can't do nothing.
-VIOLET: Do nothing.
You made the best
match you could
given the information you have.
This particular match
did not work out
but you've been doing amazing
work for Sophie for months.
The match didn't
"not work out," Vi,
she was assaulted.
A matchmaker can't vouch
for how a person is
in an intimate setting
since she's never
been in one with them.
Has something like
this happened before?
Of course.
This is dating.
This happened to
one of my clients
the third year I worked here.
If you do this long enough,
it happens to all of us.
It's a known risk.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
(CREAKS, CLOSES, LATCHES)
(GASPING)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
Hi, you.
Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
No worries.
Am I dressed nice enough?
You might be dressed too nice.
My mother and father made love.
I was born. I grew up.
I entered this
restaurant. I'm on a date.
A waiter walks up
to me and asks,
"What can I do for you?"
"I don't know. What
can you do for me?"
I order a glass of water.
My mother and father made love.
I was born. I grew up.
I entered this
restaurant. I'm on a date.
The waiter is touching my back.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
I went to school.
I read books.
I wrote book reports.
I went to more school.
I wrote essays.
JOHN: Well, it's
certainly different.
I mean, it's, it's, uh...
It's been a good experience.
I feel really lucky.
Listen, it was great
to meet you guys.
-Thanks for coming.
-MAN: Of course.
-Hey, buddy.
-Hey.
-That was great.
-Was it?
Yes, I loved it.
This is my boyfriend, Harry.
Hey, nice to meet you.
Thanks for coming.
Congratulations. That
was really interesting.
Thanks.
I can't believe you
remembered all those lines.
Yeah. Yeah, it's nuts.
Well, listen, we're going around
the corner to get a drink.
You guys want to come?
-Yes.
-Great.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
JOHN: So, what did
you really think?
I liked it.
Some of it didn't make sense...
but I loved watching
you act, you know that.
Do you ever miss it?
LUCY: Acting? No.
Not even a little bit?
LUCY: I'm not like you.
I was never going
to be an actor.
I didn't know how to
stand or... speak.
You were always good though.
You're even better now.
I'm really proud of you, John.
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
-(PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING)
You met him at the wedding?
LUCY: Yeah.
He's the groom's brother.
You're not gonna
marry him, are you?
Why not?
Because he's good-looking.
And rich.
Has a real job.
Probably doesn't have roommates.
Probably doesn't get angry
at stupid shit all the
time that doesn't matter.
Can we talk about
something else?
You okay?
Why do you ask?
Just... you don't
seem like you're okay.
Is it him?
Is it work?
I just don't think I'm very
good at my job anymore.
(SIGHS)
I'm sure it's gonna be fine.
You're so hard on yourself.
You're not a drone
pilot or a gun lobbyist.
You don't work at
Shell or McKinsey.
It's just dating.
It's not that serious.
Right.
Dating is not serious.
It's just girl shit, right?
That's not what I meant.
You always know exactly
what to say to me.
HARRY: Ready to go?
Yep. I'm gonna wait
for you outside.
HARRY: Uh, I'll
get the drinks.
BETH: (GASPS)
Thank you, Harry.
Thank you.
-(RATTLING IN DISTANCE)
-(SIREN WAILS)
(SIGHS)
I don't want to date a liberal
and they have to go to
church every Sunday.
I don't want someone
who likes cats.
I'm a dog person.
LUCY: Is a moderate
democrat okay?
Only republican.
I want someone who
identifies as a conservative.
LUCY: Audrey,
(SIGHS) I don't know
if there's a cat-hating,
Christian conservative lesbian
in most parts of New York...
who wants to date a closeted
49-year-old with three children.
Would you be willing
to date someone
from Long Island or New Jersey?
I want to prioritize
dating a man
who's white at first
but then if we have no luck,
we can move on to other races.
LUCY: So "whites
only," at first?
I mean, technically, I'm
open to all ethnicities.
Eleanor, "technically,"
you're asking me to set
you up with only white men.
I know the list looks
long but I deserve someone
who fulfills all of my criteria.
I really do.
I mean look at me. I'm
a catch. (CHUCKLES)
Patricia, I know that every year
you go without
having a husband...
raises your expectations
for him exponentially.
But that doesn't mean that
you're due to get one.
And it doesn't mean that
you can customize...
because this is
not a simulation.
If the service I
was providing you
was building you a
man then, of course,
I could build you a man with
everything on this list...
But I can't.
Because this is not
a car or a house.
We're talking about people.
People are people are
people are people.
They come as they are.
And all I can hope
to find for you
is a man that you can tolerate
for the next 50 years
who likes you at all.
And you are not a catch...
because you are not a fish.
I was managing her expectations.
VIOLET: Patricia
canceled her membership
and reviewed us online,
calling us a scam.
We are a scam.
We don't give them what
they pay for, do we?
We promise them love and then...
we just give them bad dates
with morons and criminals.
I know the Sophie L. situation
is still weighing on you.
Burnout is common
for matchmakers.
You need a break.
You should go on a trip
with your boyfriend.
(SCOFFS)
If I take a break right now...
I may never come back.
VIOLET: You will, because
you love your clients.
I hate them. They
are children.
I hate them.
VIOLET: They give us
thousands of dollars.
They're entitled
to some regression.
Do you think that
any one of them
says to their therapist...
"No Blacks, no fatties"?
And if I'm their
actual therapist,
which it feels like I am...
I don't have the
schooling to support that.
And I certainly don't
get paid enough.
VIOLET: Lucy, we're
better than therapists.
We work with the
most intimate...
extremely personal,
unofficial part
of their lives...
that they'd like to see
struck from the record.
We work with their
loneliness and rejection...
the kind that makes someone
get naked for a stranger.
We're the real deal.
That's why they tell you
more than they would
tell their therapists
and why they take
risks with you.
"Risks."
VIOLET: Yes. Risks that
can lead to a situation
like what happened
with Sophie I.
And risks that lead
to lifelong marriages.
You know this is
life-changing work.
And you're born for it.
Take a break starting now.
And I expect you back
in four weeks, renewed.
I insist.
-(CHEERING)
-(KNOCK ON DOOR)
ROSE: Violet! Amazing news!
My client Zoe H. And
Fred A. just got engaged!
(WOMEN CHEERING)
VIOLET: Unbelievable! Oh!
That is so impressive!
What an amazing match!
-Number four?
-(SIGHS)
-ROSE: Yes!
-We have to throw you a party!
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MAN CHATTERING)
LUCY: Sophie.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(PANTING) Sophie.
-Sophie.
-You don't want to talk to me.
Please.
I am so embarrassed.
I thought I could pay some girl
to find me a boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
"An expert"? What
a fucking joke.
-Sophie- -You know
what's even funnier?
I almost felt like
we were friends.
I, I, I, I really... I...
(BREATH TREMBLING)
Can we please just talk?
Talk about what?
What do you have to say?
(SIGHS, WHISPERING) I'm sorry.
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
I'm so sorry.
I trusted you.
I didn't know what
he was capable of.
I see, so...
you knew his height, which
was a lie by the way.
And his job and his salary,
which was also a lie
just for the record.
And his looks, which is
really nothing much...
but you didn't know who he was.
As a person. As a man.
Well, I went on a date
with him and found out.
He's the kind of
guy who gets drunk
and follows you
into the bathroom.
(SIGHS)
Why would you set me up
with someone like that?
He was a strong match
with a lot of potential.
He checked a lot of our boxes.
"Boxes"?
The truth is, you set
me up with that man
because you think I'm worthless.
LUCY: No, I don't...
You didn't know
what to do with me.
That's how I ended
up on that date.
Here I was thinking that
you worked for me...
but the whole time I
was working for you.
Worthless merchandise...
to pawn off to
anyone who'd take it.
But I am not merchandise.
I'm a person.
And I know I deserve
love. (SHUDDERS)
I know you do. I believe it.
Fuck you.
Pimp.
(SOBBING)
(THUDS)
(SNIFFLES)
-(PHONE VIBRATING)
-Thanks.
Can I get a receipt?
-(PHONE VIBRATING)
-(SPANISH CHATTER ON RADIO)
(PHONE CONTINUES VIBRATING)
Thanks, man.
Lucy?
What's going on? You okay?
LUCY: (SHUDDERING) No.
Do you want me to come get you?
LUCY: No, I'm at home.
I shouldn't even be calling you.
You can always
call me. What's up?
LUCY: I fucked up. (SOBS)
Okay.
I'm not supposed to
tell anybody but...
can I tell you?
JOHN: Of course.
Anything.
I set my client up
with a bad person.
I didn't know he was bad,
but I introduced them.
And now
I can't fix it.
I'm the last person
who can fix it.
Do you want me to come over?
LUCY: No.
No. I'm about to
go to Harry's.
Right.
LUCY: Sorry.
No, no. It's... Hey,
nothing to be sorry about.
Keep telling me what happened.
I'm here.
(WATER RUNNING)
(HARRY SIGHS)
Do you know what they are?
I think so.
-It's not a big deal.
-I know.
I made an investment.
A body is like an apartment.
You have to invest to
get the value back.
I understand you.
I invested too.
HARRY: Right. I figured.
Did your brother too?
HARRY: Yeah, we did it
together eight years ago.
Six feet or taller was one of
Charlotte's non-negotiables...
so I'm glad he did.
Was it painful?
I know it sounds stupid,
breaking your legs to
gain a few extra inches.
But we keep saying,
definitely worth it.
It changed our lives.
With women,
completely, of course.
Women just approach
us and talk to us now,
which never happened before.
I haven't struck out since.
But you can also tell
the difference at work
and at restaurants and
airports. You're...
You're just worth more.
Does this change anything?
No.
(SIGHS)
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking that...
that you should go to
Iceland without me.
-Why?
-(SIGHS)
I don't think that you
and I are a good match.
(SIGHS)
Is it because I got the surgery?
No. Knowing that just makes me
feel like I actually know you.
Then what?
It's really hard
for me to feel like
this is not about the legs.
It's not.
When I realized
what you had done,
it made me feel exactly how
I felt about you before.
Which is what?
I'm not in love with you.
And you're not in love with me.
And there's no amount of
money that can fix that.
But we're such a good match.
You're exactly what
I'm looking for...
and I know I can make
your life better.
Harry, you don't
want to marry me.
You want to do business with me,
just like I want to
do business with you.
But isn't marriage
a business deal?
Yes, it is.
But love has to be on the table.
What if I'm not capable of it?
Of love?
It makes me feel like an idiot.
Like I'm...
I'm just a clueless... child.
I feel so... dumb
thinking about it...
or wanting it.
I find it...
so difficult.
You won't, when
you love someone.
(SIGHS)
It'll be easy.
No math.
Should I hire you
for your services?
If you call the office,
they'll assign
someone great for you.
(INHALES, SIGHS)
So this is it?
You want to know
how many inches?
Yeah.
Six.
"You were 5'6" before?
I wouldn't have
had the confidence
to hit on you at 5'6".
I'm sure you would have.
Am I still a unicorn?
You're perfect.
(DRIVER SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
-(WHIRRING)
-(DOORBELL RINGING)
JOHN: Where's my charger?
(CELL PHONE PLAYING)
Hey, is that my charger?
LOGAN: My charger broke.
So you just took mine?
I had an alarm set.
And answer the fucking door
for once in your fucking life!
-(DOORBELL RINGING)
-What?
Hi. It's Lucy.
I'm sorry.
No, no, that's
okay. I was just...
I'll come down there.
Just give me...
Just don't move.
(CELL PHONE PLAYING)
Hey, what the fuck?
Oh...
-(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
-Sh...
Goddamn it.
(WATER RUNNING)
Fuck.
Hi.
LUCY: Hi.
(JOHN SIGHS)
You have a girl up there?
What? No. Why
would you say that?
I don't know. You didn't
want me to come up. (LAUGHS)
Oh. Yeah, no, there's
no girl up there.
Sorry for showing
up without warning.
I tried calling.
Sorry. My phone
wasn't charged.
I'm meant to be on
a plane to Iceland.
Okay.
I sublet my apartment
for the week
that I'm supposed
to be in Iceland...
so I, uh, don't have
a place to stay.
Sorry, I don't know
what I'm doing here.
-It doesn't make any sense.
-No, no.
-I thought it made sense.
-Wait, wait. Don't go. Stay.
This was a bad idea.
No, it's not. It's just...
My apartment is not...
suitable for you.
It was suitable before.
Yeah, well, we're not
in our 20s anymore.
I know what your
apartment is like.
Trust me, it's worse
than you remember.
Want to drive upstate?
And go where?
I don't know.
Just drive around.
Stay at a hotel.
I just got the
stipend from my play,
so... I'm feeling rich.
(SOFT EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING)
JOHN: What are you
thinking about?
You're the same as always.
Really?
LUCY: Mm-hmm.
I was hoping you'd
say I was different.
LUCY: Why?
Because if I'm different,
then I wouldn't be
the guy that lost you.
(CHUCKLES)
LUCY: What?
That's my catering company.
Do you think they'd get us in?
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(ALL APPLAUDING)
(ALL CHEERING)
Oh, he loves her so much.
Yeah.
JOHN: And special
delivery, just for you.
A gift.
LUCY: A white glove
service, handled with care.
JOHN: If you could
just sign here.
LUCY: Initial here.
JOHN: Thank you very
much and have a good day.
(LUCY CHUCKLES)
One day, for no reason
in particular...
you two will start
to hate each other.
You'll resent each other...
you'll take each
other for granted...
You'll stop having sex...
somehow... manage to
make a couple of kids...
and then you'll get
sick of each other...
And one of you will
cheat on the other...
and then you'll fight.
At first, not in front
of the kids, but then...
in front of the kids...
and then you resent the
kids for seeing you fight...
and then you file for divorce...
and you fight about...
who owns what and...
who gets the kids
when until it's...
all over.
(CROWD CHEERING, APPLAUDING)
JOHN: Why does anybody
even get married?
LUCY: Because people
tell them they should.
And because they're lonely.
And because they're hopeful.
They want to do it differently
than their parents.
(SOFT EMOTIONAL
MUSIC CONTINUING)
-(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
-(LIVELY CHATTER)
(BAND PLAYING THAT'S ALL)
WOMAN: ♪ I can only
give you love ♪
♪ That lasts forever ♪
♪ And a promise to be
near Each time you call ♪
♪ And the only heart I own ♪
♪ For you and you alone ♪
♪ That's all ♪
♪ I can only give
you Country walks ♪
♪ In springtime ♪
♪ And a hand to hold When
leaves begin to fall ♪
♪ And a love Whose
burning light ♪
♪ Will warm the winter night ♪
♪ That's all ♪
♪ There are those, I am sure ♪
♪ That have told you ♪
♪ They would give you
The world for a toy ♪
♪ All I have are these
arms To enfold you ♪
♪ And a love time
can Never destroy ♪
♪ If you're wondering what
I'm asking in return, dear ♪
♪ You'll be glad to know
that my demands are small ♪
♪ Say it's me That
you'll adore ♪
♪ For now and ever more ♪
♪ That's all ♪
(THAT'S ALL CONTINUING)
(SIGHS)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
John.
John!
(SIGHS)
-What is this?
-What is what?
Are we getting back together?
Lucy, are we getting
back together?
I don't know.
I really don't.
(SIGHS)
So you thought you'd just
show up at my door...
not have a boyfriend,
agree to get in
my car, kiss me...
fuck me while you try to
get over someone else...
and then leave me
again? Is that it?
-Do you think I'm worthless?
-No, I don't think that.
-Am I disposable?
-Of course not.
Do you feel bad for me?
Poor old John can't
figure his life out?
-Never.
-Then why are you using me?
I'm not.
I'm usually desperate
enough to let you.
I'm a beggar for you.
When I see your face...
I see wrinkles and grey hair...
and children that look like you.
I can't help it.
(SIGHS)
But as your friend...
I would tell you it's a bad idea
to be with a
37-year-old cater waiter
who still has roommates.
I would say...
you definitely
shouldn't marry a guy
that has $2,000 in
his bank account...
in a city he can't afford...
who's only still there...
to keep trying to
be a theatre actor
because someone told him
he was good at it once.
So, where does that leave us?
Here.
At someone else's wedding.
(SCOFFS)
I can't give you the wedding
or the marriage you want.
I couldn't even give you
the relationship you wanted.
It's been years,
and I still can't
afford to be with you.
You're right...
You can't.
But just because
you can't afford it,
doesn't mean it's worth having.
You don't want me.
Of course I want you.
Are you even listening to me?
John, you and I haven't
been together properly...
in so long that
you've forgotten.
You don't want to be with me
because I'm not a good person.
I'm judgmental...
and materialistic, and cold.
I broke up with you
because you're broke.
I've hurt you over and over.
You hate me.
I don't hate you.
LUCY: You do.
And you're right to hate
me, because I'm awful.
Even now...
I'm thinking: If I
choose to marry you...
I'm gonna be sitting
across from you
in cheap shitty restaurants
for the rest of my life.
I'll be riding in
your shitty car,
and living in your
shitty bedroom...
and fighting with you about $25.
I'm weighing being with you...
against these shit tradeoffs.
I'm doing math.
This is what I'm like.
I know what you're like.
LUCY: Then how could
you still love me?
(SIGHS)
(UPBEAT MUSIC
PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
(PHONE VIBRATING FAINTLY)
(SIGHS)
(PHONE VIBRATING)
-Sophie?
-Lucy.
I didn't know who else to call.
I haven't told anyone.
I don't have any
friends in the city
and my lawyers aren't
picking up and...
-What's going on?
-(DOORBELL BUZZING ON PHONE)
SOPHIE: Mark is
outside my building.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
I called the cops but
they said they won't come
unless he's trying to break in.
-And...
-(DOORBELL BUZZING ON PHONE)
He's not trying to break in,
he's just buzzing the doorbell.
That's still harassment,
they should...
He walked me home
after the date.
Which I shouldn't have
let him do, but...
I was scared and... (EXHALES)
-It's my fault.
-JOHN: Lucy.
That's not your fault.
JOHN: Can we finish
talking, please?
SOPHIE: He says he just
wants to talk about it,
but I'm not gonna let him in.
-No.
-(DOORBELL CONTINUES BUZZING)
Bolt your door.
I'm about an hour
outside of Manhattan,
but I'll try to
get there sooner.
SOPHIE: I'm worried
someone's going to open
the building door for him.
LUCY: I'm almost there.
He has to leave. He can't stay
outside all night, can he?
I want you to tell him
someone is on their way.
(DOORBELL BUZZES)
(DOOR BUZZES)
Sophie, it's Lucy.
SOPHIE: Is he gone?
Yes. No one was here
when we got here.
SOPHIE: Oh. He
must've run away
when I said that you're coming.
Can I come in?
(DOOR LATCH CLICKS,
CREAKS OPEN)
-Hi.
How are you holding up?
Uh, not good. (CHUCKLES
NERVOUSLY, SIGHS)
(EXHALES) Mark
sounded really angry.
(SHUDDERING)
Well, he's angry because...
he thought he was going to
get away with something...
but he won't...
because you're not
going to let him.
You are brave.
Can I hug you?
(SOBS)
(CRYING)
You know what I've been
thinking about? (SNIFFLES)
(WHISPERING) What?
I really need to get a boyfriend
so that I have someone to call
that's not my
fucking matchmaker.
(BOTH LAUGH)
I'm going to die alone.
(LAUGHS)
Sophie.
(SIGHS WEARILY)
I promise you, you're going to
marry the love of your life.
You don't expect
me to believe that.
You don't have to believe it.
I believe it.
SOPHIE: Let me guess.
Someone who checks a lot of
my boxes? (CHUCKLES DRYLY)
I'm not asking for a miracle.
I just want to love someone.
Someone who can't
help but love me back.
She's asleep.
Good.
You okay?
Yeah.
You should go home.
I'll take you home first.
I'm gonna sleep on her couch...
and help her get a restraining
order when she wakes up.
Okay.
Thanks for the ride.
Yeah, of course.
You asked how I could love you.
I just do.
It's the easiest thing.
I love you too.
(CHUCKLES) More than you know.
You're the only reason I
know I'm capable of love.
I've been doing some math.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
And I'm ready to
make you an offer.
Okay.
Here's the offer.
I love you now, like
I loved you before...
I'll love you 'til
the day I die.
It's a lifetime guarantee.
And I won't forget it
the way I used to...
even when things are shit.
I'll make a calendar item
every day reminding
myself that I love you.
I'll be your certainty.
It's my final offer.
You can't negotiate because
I don't have anything
else to offer you.
Deal.
(SOFT ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Now I admit, I'm not confident
that I can make
myself less broke.
You don't need to
worry about that.
You know I can take
care of myself.
Yeah, I know.
It's not for you.
It's for me.
For us.
You make me brave enough
to admit that I
want to be happy.
And I want to be happy with you.
And I'm gonna pick up
more catering shifts...
And ask for a raise...
I'll find a serving job
at an actual restaurant...
And I won't say no to
commercial auditions,
even though they're annoying...
I'll make an actual
effort to find a manager.
(MUSIC SWELLS)
And I'm going to move
out of my apartment.
And sell my car.
Don't sell your car.
No?
No, let's just...
Let's just drive around in it...
until it breaks down and
it won't move anymore.
(MUSIC SWELLS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
LUCY: I've been dreaming about
the first people
who got married.
Two cave people...
fell in love...
in between the hunting
and the gathering.
And in my dream...
I keep asking myself...
what made them perfect
for each other?
Similar economic background?
Politically aligned?
Well-matched in
their attractiveness?
Similar upbringing?
Or...
was it something else?
Something like you and me?
(ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUING)
Hey, man.
Can I get two chicken over rice?
MAN: Yeah.
Thanks a lot. Keep that.
I'm sad you're leaving, Vi.
VIOLET: Me too. They really
need me at the London office.
And I'm calling you first
of all the Adore girls...
because the CEOs asked me who
should be asked to step up
and be promoted...
to New York head
and I said it absolutely
has to be you.
-Me?
-Yes.
-You're getting a promotion.
-(LUCY CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(LAUGHS)
VIOLET: What's so funny?
Well, I was going to hand in
my resignation letter tomorrow.
VIOLET: No, you weren't.
Yep. I have it printed
out and everything.
VIOLET: You can't quit.
What would you do instead?
I honestly don't know.
Maybe marry someone poor.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
VIOLET: I don't know
what you're talking about.
Just think about it.
You can negotiate
a crazy salary, too.
Ask for any amount you want,
and I'll support you. Okay?
Okay, I'll think about it.
Vi, I have to go.
My boyfriend's here.
VIOLET: Yeah, before
you go, tell me:
How did Sophie L.'s
date go last night?
She liked him.
VIOLET: Brian A., right?
Yeah.
5'8". 36. Dentist.
200 grand before taxes.
Just... looking
for a nice girl.
VIOLET: Sounds like
a strong match.
(CHUCKLES)
He liked her too.
We are cautiously optimistic.
VIOLET: Good.
You should know Harry C.
Is going on his first date.
Rose made a very strong match.
Gemma N., 30, an art dealer.
Vi, I have to go.
VIOLET: Fine, but
hear the offer first.
I will.
VIOLET: Call me.
Hi.
How would you like to make a
very bad financial decision?
(ROMANTIC INDIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(LIVELY CHATTER)
(MUSIC FADES)
(INDISTINCT
ANNOUNCEMENT ON PA)
(ROMANTIC FOLK MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES)