Back to one.
Let's get it quiet, please.
Everyone, stay off channel one now.
This is a take,
not a rehearsal.
Picture is up.
Camera's set.
Let's roll sound!
Sound speed.
Let's speed cameras.
Camera one speeding.
Camera two speeding.
"B" camera mark.
"C" mark.
Stunts ready?
Ready.
In three, two, one, action.
They're in almost every movie.
You just don't know
that they're there.
'Cause that's the job.
They're the unknown
stunt performers.
And they get paid
to do the cool stuff.
They also get paid
to take it on the chin.
And everywhere else,
if you know what I mean.
Oh, that's... that's me.
Colt Seavers.
Getting blown up and hiding
my face in a muddy puddle.
Which isn't ideal
when you're trying to look cool
in front of Jody.
Who you just so happen
to have a major crush on.
She's a camera operator.
Looking for Tom Ryder's stunt double.
She's definitely gonna achieve her goal
of being a big-time Hollywood
movie director.
- You're so uncoordinated.
- I don't wanna over romanticize it or anything, but,
I think what Jody and I
got's the kind of thing
we can only really find in the movies
- Hey. Jody.
- Thank you.
Hey, Colt. Thanks so
much for the stunt chat.
Stunt chats.
I love 'em. Anytime.
Hey, uh, Tom needs to see you
at the monitor.
- Uh-oh.
- Yeah.
Am I in trouble?
She's talking about Tom Ryder,
who happens to be the biggest
action star on the pl--
Wait, why am I explaining this?
You know who Tom Ryder is.
He's Tom Ryder.
Anyway, I've been his
stunt double for six years now.
Uh...
flying in.
What happened? What's up?
Guess we're going again.
You know Tom and Gail.
There's a lot of grumbling
and a bunch of hand gestures
over at the monitor, so I'm
not sure what's going on there,
- but...
- Let me guess-- too much face.
Okay, guys. Go to one for me.
Um...
- Jody, right?
- What's your name again?
As you can see, that is not my chin.
When you look at my face, look
at my jaw compared to his jaw,
it's like his chin is off.
- It's like...
- Yeah, we can't replace his face.
It's like Mr. Potato Head.
I mean, no offense or anything,
but you know.
Oh, yeah, no. Sorry, I got lost
in your beautiful jawline.
- It's dreamy.
- No, listen,
we're just saying
it's not working for us.
- Let's, uh...
- Okay.
Let's go again.
Oh, yeah, no,
we're gonna have to go again.
Okay.
- Yeah.
- 100%.
I don't know, man.
Do you think, um...
Try and make some magic?
Maybe you could do it
backwards or something?
I don't know.
- It's just... less face.
- Yeah.
The woman freebasing
the Diet Coke
is Tom's producer Gail.
- She's been making him look good for years.
-Thank you.
-And it's not always easy.
- All right. Give me some.
- Oh! I'm gonna...
- I can't complain.
I'm working with my dream girl,
On my dream job.
We got to switch
the pick points to the front.
- I'm living the dream.
- He wants to go again.
Copy that, Colt. We'll flip the rig.
You'll be falling backwards.
Jody, go to two.
Do you have a question for me?
Uh, yeah. It just looked
just now like you wanted
to ask me something.
Oh, I was gonna go for
a spicy margarita after work.
I was wondering
if you drink spicy margaritas.
Um, well,
just to keep it professional,
I can only have
one spicy margarita.
Because if I have two,
I start making bad decisions.
Well, you know,
drinking margaritas
is all about
making bad decisions.
Which reminds me, um,
after this job, I-I got to go
sit on the sand somewhere,
and I was wondering, uh...
I was gonna ask you a question.
Tell me.
Do you have any towels
that I can borrow?
Yeah, I have some towels.
You know, it's so dangerous
to swim alone.
Well, I would ask you to,
you know, be my swim buddy,
but I don't know
if you have a bathing suit.
Wait a second. What do you
call that across the pond?
We call it a swimming costume.
Imagine that.
After this,
you and I could both be
on the beach somewhere
in swimming costumes
drinking spicy margaritas,
- making bad decisions.
- Okay, good to go.
Imagine that.
Okay, let's keep it
locked up all around!
- Let's strap him in.
- Everyone quiet, please!
Speed on "A."
- You all right?
- All right, let's take him to ones.
- Going to ones.
- Go ahead and sit back for me.
Let's go hot on stunts.
- And going out to the edge.
- Stunts is hot.
How we doing up there, stunt?
- Great. He's great. Here we go.
- Position down.
He's at ones.
Ready to drop the line for me?
And three, two, one.
Action, action, action,
action, action!
Call the medic! Medic!
Colt, are you okay?
I need you to step back.
You're not helping.
Break time's over.
You've got a customer.
No. 43.
Yo, bro, I know you
from somewhere.
Where I know you from, bro?
Oh, yeah, you were on
that Tom Ryder movie I was on.
- You're the stunt guy!
- Not anymore.
- Did you, like, break your back or some shit?
- I did, yeah.
How are you even still alive?
Yo, babe.
- Babe, hey, come here.
- I don't know.
I wish I wasn't right now.
Come here.
You got to hear this.
You don't have to hear this.
- It's fine. Hi.
- This dude was on a movie I was on.
Most epic fail I've ever seen.
They let him hanging
up there on these wires
he look like a little piñata.
Action!
This guy falls about 1,000 miles an hour.
I'm like, "this guy's gonna die bro."
"This guy's gonna die."
10 meters above the ground...
Snap!
He cracks into this disgusting pretzel.
It's all pretty foggy, then.
So, like...
stunt man to valet.
How does that happen?
Hell of a fall.
Let me get your car.
Yo, fall guy?
Yo, bring my car back
without a scratch,
I got a crispy fiver
here for you, bro.
No!
Chill! It's a rental!
- Hello?
- Oh! Colt.
it's Gail.
Your favourite producer.
How do you get this number?
Someone said you were working
at the Captain's Cockatoo.
A valet.
Wow! I didn't believe it.
It's actually
El Cacatúa del Capitan.
It's a family-run place.
We pool tips.
Nice change for my whole job.
I'm sure it is.
And to that point you know,
I know things haven't
been easy for you since...
the incident.
And I just hope that you
don't hold it against me
or Tom, yeah?
We were absolutely
devastated.
He sent you a message, right?
The prayer hands emoji?
Right, yeah, he's still an asshole,
but God, he was a force
in Annihilation of Valor.
I'm coming for you, Billy!
He's the best.
Oneself a Globe.
So do one the Oscar.
He is so authentic.
I don't blame either one of you, Gail.
That was my fault.
And when you start making
mistakes like that,
it's time to hang up the pads.
Oh, it was an accident, Colt.
Everybody knows that.
Tom has put me
in a real situation here, Colt.
I just need a little bit
of help from an old friend,
who just happens to be,
you know, the best stuntman
I've ever worked with in my life.
Which is why you are getting
on a plane for me tomorrow
- and coming to Sydney.
- I'm not getting on a plane, Gail.
You know, Colt,
Tom Ryder is the biggest
action brand on the planet,
but that is largely because of you.
Metalstorm will be an epic
stunt extravaganza.
My life is simple now, Gail.
I like simple.
Plus, I get
all the burritos I can eat.
So...
kind of living the dream
if you think about it.
I can't bear that you would
throw away all that talent.
You shouldn't be parking cars, Colt.
You need to be smashing burning
Kawasakis through paint of glass.
I know you've missed it.
Goodbye, Gail.
Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait!
Hold on. Did I...
Did I tell you?
Did I tell you that
the directors asked for you specifically?
Sorry to disappoint him.
Well, then you wanna know who it is?
Nope.
it's Jody.
I'm giving her a big break.
Make sure it's an aisle seat.
Earth, minerals, stone.
A new eau de parfum
by Tom Ryder.
- Is that--
- Yeah.
I didn't realize they were,
uh, scanning doubles now.
Eh, it's new technology.
Basically, we use the
geometry of your face
to retarget Ryder's face,
and we put Ryder's face
back on top of your face.
Like a deepfake situation.
If you get a chance, turn me
into Tom Cruise, would you?
Hey, welcome to Sydney.
Are you Colt Seavers?
Yeah. Hey. Do you know
where I can get some coffee?
This jet lag
is really kicking in.
Yeah, no stress. I got you.
And does the director know
I'm here?
- She asked for me.
- Uh...
Does-does she want
to say hi or...?
I haven't heard.
No, sorry, bro.
Uh, but the stunt coordinator
wants to see you.
- He's just in the jacket there.
- Okay, great.
Will you just tell her
I'm here and...
you know, that coffee
if you get a chance?
Dan Tucker.
Big-time Hollywood
stunt coordinator.
It's about time.
Congratulations.
Thank you. Look at you.
So do I call you "sir" now,
or how does that work?
Oh, feel free
to call me "boss," you know.
Okay, boss.
I don't think I should be
in this Nomex, right?
I mean, it's like, we're not
doing anything crazy, are we?
I was just about
to explain that, actually.
- Just follow me.
- Okay.
- How're you doing?
- I'm good
I'm great. Keeping busy.
Been surfing.
Was growing my hair out
like a few minutes ago.
- Try my hand at bonsai.
- Bonsai.
Sounds like you got a
pretty full schedule there.
Staying busy.
So what made you wanna
come back to work?
What? I was told that
Jody asked for me?
So I knew I had to come, right?
- Oh well...
- What am I gonna do? Not come?
I mean...
She wants me here I gotta be here.
All right.
Everybody huddle up.
Listen up.
First up today is the car roll
we've been rehearsing all week.
Everybody knows their spots,
everybody knows
their responsibilities.
We do this right,
we do the safe and
everybody goes home.
Bad news,
we lost our drive.
So Henry's out.
But good news is,
the cinema gods...
have blessed us
with the greatest stunt man
I've ever worked with,
put your hands together,
for Colt Seavers!
A cannon roll?!
It's time for you to start
rolling cars again
instead of parking them.
You had an accident.
It was a massive
miscalculation of the rig.
I-I almost killed myself
in front of the whole crew.
You know, I'd rather just not
have my first stunt back
be another epic failure,
especially in front of Jody.
I mean, you understand.
"It's not about how hard
of a hit you can give."
"It's about how many times
you can get hit
- Come on.
- and keep moving forward."
That's messed up. You can't
quote Rocky on me like that.
So it's a laser gun
with a dagger?
- Yes, like a bayonet.
- Right.
Do we need the bayonet?
Wouldn't the laser achieve...
On the battlefield, yes.
Hundred percent.
It just gives it
a quite a strange shape.
- Oh, this guitar bit at the end?
- Yeah.
Yeah, well, you said
you wanted metal,
so it's, like, heavy metal.
How many
have you done like this?
- Uh, two.
- Okay.
- Hundred.
- Ooh. Okay. Yeah, fantastic.
- Thanks, boss.
- Okay. It looks like a guitar
- Yes.
- Nigel, how we doing on the pyrotechnics?
- What's going on?
- I think we only have enough for one take.
- No. Come on.
- Boss, listen.
Yes.
We could create something that
looks way
- more realistic with VFX.
- No, no, no.
- Venti, Venti, Venti.
- Come on.
- Give it to me.
- I don't want real.
This is a sci-fi epic,
cosmic love story.
Okay?
Of cosmic proportions.
It's got to mirror
that otherworldly thing
when you fall in love.
You know, it's imperfect.
It's beautiful.
I want it that way, okay?
Let's go big with
our one take, okay?
Holy shit.
Was that it?
Was that my one take?
Uh, I'm sure we have--
Oh, my God!
Well, I got to say, though,
looks absolutely fantastic.
Look at that.
You sure you want
to use real pyros?
- Yeah.
- But we definitely don't need this.
- No, no, no, no. Yeah.
- We don't.
Well, we're just gonna
have to loop the actors.
- That's all.
- That's okay, Ray.
It's a stuntman in a car
with a helmet on, okay?
- No looping. No monologuing.
- What the hell is going on over there, Rush?
We did not call for pyro.
I will seriously track down your family
and kill every last one of them!
This is why they're doing it.
'Cause they feel you don't
respect them, Nigel, okay?
Your tone,
your words, all of it, just...
Darla, yes? Okay. Yeah.
Sorry, I... I couldn't get my printer
working last night...
...but I sort of synthesized
our conversation
that we had on the third act,
and what if
one of the characters in the
film acknowledges in the film
that we're having a problem
with the third act?
- Yeah?
- No. No.
But I appreciate you thinking
outside the box, Darla.
I really really do.
Nigel you've got to stop them.
I will gut you like the pigs
that you are! Stop testing!
-Boss!
- Yep?
- Test went well.
- Fantastic.
Okay, so, guys, simmer down.
Eyes on me.
Here's what's gonna happen. No VFX, Venti.
It looks absolutely fabulous.
Nigel, we need to shoot now.
The tide's coming in.
Let's go.
The shot's gonna be epic.
Shot's up in five, people.
Thank you.
Colt? Brother?
What's happening, man?
- Bad sand.
Yeah.
I think we got to postpone.
Hate to say it.
Dan, what's the delay, please?
Uh, we're just doing
a little safety check.
It's the density.
It's bad density.
We're looking at
the density of the sand.
- There's a new driver.
- Who is it?
Where's Henry?
Nigel, this is the biggest
shot of the film,
and I have a newbie.
- Dan says we can do it.
- Okay.
Seriously, we're gonna drift
all over the place.
What is that, a king tide?
Here's what you do.
You wait till it comes in.
It compacts the sand,
then we shoot sunset for sun up.
You're stalling.
- Maybe.
- You're stalling.
- Two things can be true.
- Brother, I've got
a tent full of
rookie Australians out here.
I'm gonna be sick.
You got this. You're the one.
- Why you got to say that?
- Okay?
You've done this
a million times.
And so have you.
You know, you just jinxed it.
You just jinxed it!
Hey, Dan, I need the driver
in the car now, please.
- Okay, the tide's coming up.
- Okay.
Thank you so much.
Appreciate you.
- Is that Jody?
- Yes, it's Jody.
She say something about me?
Stop with-- your face.
Stop it.
She didn't say
anything about you.
Get in the car!
This is really important to her.
Yes, it's important to her.
- Is this Comic-Con or something?
- Hall H.
"This is one of those times,
whether it's an inch or a mile,
a win is a win."
That's easy.
Fast and the Furious.
Let's go.
- You got this.
- Did you see the coffee lady?
She was wearing, like, a hat.
- I see you in the car.
- Okay.
This is the hero set.
I got five more after that.
Are you ready, Dan?
- Yeah?
- Rock and roll.
Lock it up!
Thank you.
Okay, folks. he's buckled in.
Stunts are ready.
Godspeed, Colt.
All right, FX...
go high.
FX, please go hot on the cannon.
Okay, engaging the cannon now.
Charging the cannon.
2,000 PSI in the cannon.
- Stunts is good.
- Cannon is hot.
Cameras, where are we at?
Are you rolling? Camera one?
- Speed on one.
- Camera two?
And three, two, one.
Action, action, action!
- All right, guys, stay frosty.
- Three, two, one!
Dan, I need him close to the
camera now.
Copy that!
Look,
I don't want to be that guy,
but the sand's a little loose.
I can't get any traction.
When I do, it jumps, so...
if you get any closer,
you're gonna lose the camera.
I know, I know,
but get in there.
You got this, baby!
Move up, move up.
No, no, not that close.
Oh. What the--
Keep rolling.
We have seven more cameras.
- Keep rolling!
- Okay!
Ready in
three, two, one!
You alright?
Quickly, get him.
Come on, get out.
Are you good?
Colt, you did it!
Eight and a half rolls!
Come on, you okay? You good?
You good?
- Jody's coming. Hold on.
- Okay.
So good, Dan. Is he good?
- Yeah, of course.
- So good, so good.
Loved it, loved it.
- Incredible.
- Okay.
Whose idea was this?
I think it was Gail's idea.
I thought it was your idea.
I just found out
about this yesterday.
Dan, come on.
I didn't approve him.
I would never have approved him.
She didn't approve me.
Can I talk to you for a second?
I'm not approved.
Interesting move.
Really, really interesting.
Just very casual.
Here you are, you show up,
and, "I'm your new stuntman."
- Don't do that. You can't do that.
- What?
- I'm directing a movie.
- Your hat's coming off.
Why are you here?
I think there's been
a misunderstanding.
Clearly.
Because I was under
the impression that...
...you did want me here.
That's a delusional thought.
We haven't spoken in a year.
- Let's not get into it.
- Gail, Gail-- But Gail
- told me that you
- Okay. Whatever.
- wanted me here.
I don't even care about it,
but you clipped the camera.
I'm a little rusty.
- Comic-Con shot ruined.
- I'm sor-- I know.
- Hall H.
- Yeah.
- It's a big deal.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
I'm happy for you.
This whole director thing
looks good on you.
Even the gardening hat, somehow.
Everyone wears them.
It's like a set thing.
- Okay?
- Yeah, I see it. It's--
They're not making it look
as good as you are, that's all.
And I'm not trying to be fla--
I'm just saying the facts.
But you look good in everything.
You look good in nothing.
Whatever.
- No, I don't mean it like that.
- Really?
- But you do look good in nothing.
- This isn't... This isn't work--
- This isn't gonna work.
- I mean, you do.
But it's not what I...
- I'll take anyone. Anyone else.
- Yeah.
- Anyone but him.
- Can I be honest with you?
We literally have no one else.
What's next?
The fire burn.
It's your call.
- Okay.
- Can we get a nurse on standby, please?
We're gonna set
this man on fire.
Cut, cut, cut.
Cutting there, please.
How you feeling, Colt Seavers?
- He's good.
- We're gonna go again.
Thumbs-up, okay?
Technical issue.
Little bump on the dolly.
- Huh?
- Can you fix that, Jimmy?
- Back to ones, please.
- Thank you.
Colt, do you feel a bit
flung into the deep end here?
I'm just wondering, 'cause
you haven't read the script,
if you'd like some backstory,
some context?
Would that be good?
- Just go with it.
- Yeah, helpful?
Okay. Here we go.
So, sci-fi love story,
two characters,
one of them's an alien--
Aliena-- and you're Space Cowboy.
They shared what's called
a moon season.
In real life,
you might call it a fling.
Um, brief but very intense.
And... hopeful.
Now, neither of them
had ever been in a relationship
that deep before.
And they told each other that
over and over and over again.
Him more than her,
you know, to the point
where sometimes she was like,
"Chill out," you know.
But anyway,
in a tragic turn of events,
Space Cowboy is wounded,
and he just disappears.
Without a trace.
- I can keep going.
- I can hit the rock better now, thanks.
We're going again!
Sound speed.
And action!
That's a cut!
Cutting there, please.
- Everything okay?
- You good?
For a little more context, Colt,
Eliana sort of devastated.
And she starts sort of
replaying everything
in her head over and over again.
Did she misread the vibe?
Was it just a fling?
Did she let her imagination
run wild again?
Or did he lie to her?
Was he full of shit?
But let me be clear, eventually,
Eliana did move on.
All right?
And she started doing Pilates.
Got herself
a banging revenge body,
and then she started dating
other humans.
One after another.
And she had
so many mind-blowing,
far superior experiences,
you wouldn't even believe it.
Right, girls?
You know what I mean?
Yeah, it was like a sushi train.
I'm gonna be sick.
And do you know what?
We're gonna go again, Colt,
'cause there was
a little buzz on that one.
Okay, light him up.
Last one, everybody. Action!
It-It's just feeling
so withheld,
so how 'bout some dialogue?
Yeah, that's all right, Darla.
I'm gonna go
straight to the source.
Hey, Colt, if Space Cowboy
had to say something,
if he was forced to say something
what would he say?
How would he justify
this year she's spent
spinning out over this?
What could he say?
It's a puzzler, isn't it?
- But have you got any thoughts?
- Uh, maybe he could talk...
Nigel, can you, can you
get him a bullhorn?
I can't hear him.
Traveling.
Come again, Colt.
What was that?
It's already on.
In this movie,
do the aliens and
the humans ever talk...
in private?
- No, not really.
- No private conversations?
No, they don't like
doing private.
Like, they like to keep it very public.
Very open.
Well...
maybe I'll just, uh,
open it up to the group here.
Have you ever been in one of
those situations where...
...you want to say something
and it's so important
that you can't mess it up?
So...
you think
long and hard about it,
and then you realize...
you've already messed it up?
'Cause you've thought too long
and too hard about it?
You're...
What's that?
You want...
I had a similar situation
when I fell in love
with my wife's sister.
- Okay. All right. What...
- No.
Okay.
And again, this
is hard because...
you know, I haven't
read the script.
But...
...he'd probably say...
...that he's been living...
...in total regret since then.
You know, afraid...
that he'll never get
an opportunity to make it up to her...
...because he waited too long.
And...
...she's probably moved on.
Uh, sorry, Jody,
speaking of moving on,
we, uh...
One more?
I'd love another chance.
- Roll it, Nigel.
- Let's turn over, please!
- All cameras are rolling.
- Shot's up, sound speeding.
Okay, light him up!
Action! Thank you!
Gail.
Coffee.
Mm! You're here.
Oh, no, don't use that.
It's broken.
Eight and a half rolls?
That is a world record!
Thank you so much.
It's better than parking cars,
isn't it?
Would you cut the shit, Gail?
What? It was amazing.
What are you talking about?
She doesn't want me here, Gail.
Yes, she does.
- Oh, of course she does.
- You lied.
You lied.
- Colt.
- Do you know how that feels?
Come on.
Sit down chill your beans.
How many memories
have we got doing this?
You and me back here...
all of those movies?
14, 15 movies...
we've done together now was like...
a decade of our lives.
- You do Last Time for Murder.
- Yeah.
But, you know, Ryder
he can be a bit of a kind of...
methody...
twat face.
But you know what, people change.
You know my mom's version
of a good night kiss?
I'm not kidding. Smacking the chops.
Knock me out cold. I forgave her.
We can all change, Colt. We can evolve-
- Look what you did to Jody.
- Huh?
You run out, you disappear.
You're not in contact with her.
- I mean...
- Honestly.
- I was in the hospital.
- She was...
I appreciate that.
But it was brutal.
- Horrendous.
- It wasn't magic trick...
- She was devastated.
- I didn't disappear.
Yes, you should feel bad
but you can make it right.
It's, like, the message
in all my movies.
You know that, right?
What's the message
in all my movies?
Nihilism's a viable worldview?
No, that's just
the entertainment.
That's like the...
like the sexy bacon.
- What is this?
- You know? It's like dogs.
You got to wrap the message...
in some sexy bacon.
I mean, all those movies,
people fall down.
They're rolling
in their own shit.
They don't think they can cope,
but they can. They get back up.
Do you mind if I lay down?
With the multiple fire burns
and the cannon rolls
- and the jet lag, I just...
- Yep, yep.
...could use a little shut-eye.
Yep.
Okay, let me get this straight.
Nihilism is the sexy bacon?
- Yeah
- The audience...
are dogs?
There we go.
And when you fall down,
you get back up.
- Thank you.
- I'm glad we did this.
Now,
what am I really
doing here, Gail?
Ryder's missing.
He has fallen in with some shady,
shitty, shitty people.
Well, Gail...
...call the cops.
I can't call the cops.
Well, why not?
The studio will know
that I am way over budget.
They will pull the plug on this.
You know that
Please go and find him.
Why me?
You're a stuntman,
for God's sake.
No one's gonna notice
whether you're here or not.
- No offense.
- I mean, some taken.
You know him intimately.
It can be so simple.
You pick him up,
you dust him off, you
you bring him back here.
I know I can trust you.
And you know who can
trust you more than anyone,
she just doesn't
realize it yet, is Jody.
This is her big chance.
Do you want her first movie
to be her last?
You've got to help me out, man.
It's been a long couple days.
I'm gonna go to the hotel,
I'm gonna--
What is it?
It's my...
yesterday, it's your tomor--
I'm gonna call you
- your tomorrow.
- Right, no.
- Today.
- My today.
That is the door code
of Ryder's loft.
The patio door.
Took it from his trailer.
He's still doing
this Post-it note thing?
Let's not even get into that.
At this point,
it's like Memento level.
I can only keep this from Jody
and the studio 48 hours max.
Save Jody's movie,
and maybe you get
the love of your life back.
Did you just turn Jody
into the sexy bacon?
She's been
the sexy bacon all along.
You're good.
It's the only left-hand drive I have.
Please don't wreck it.
It's product placement.
There's only two of them.
I know how you stunties drive.
You seek to destroy
all I hold dear.
What are you doing?
Uh, just, uh, chilling down.
Were you "chilling down"
to Taylor Swift?
Yep.
It's just something
Australians say.
Really? I've been here for six
months, I've never heard it.
Yeah, "chilling down under,"
you know,
- but it's shorter to say "chilling down."
- Have you been crying?
- Not at all.
- You look like you've been crying.
Jet lag.
That was so dangerous,
and I'm very sorry.
Lighting you up like that.
It was very cathartic.
- I feel better.
- I deserved it.
I'm gonna make the camera
up to you, by the way.
Can I get in the car with you?
Clean your face. You're a mess.
So how have you been?
Oh, you know.
Yeah? Thumbs-up?
God, I hate that bullshit,
that stunt guy bullshit.
And that's fine.
You don't have to explain anything.
It's all good. It was a fling.
Less than a fling. It was
a flingette, and that's fine.
I don't even want to know.
And the problem with
forcing something is you get nowhere.
You know, one time my mom
forced my dad to exercise.
Do you know what happened?
Snapped his ankle first time
he stepped on the treadmill.
She forced it, now he has
a piece of metal in his foot.
Moral of the story is
you should just be you.
Well, look, I've thought
a lot about this, actually,
and I, uh...
It's not like
I didn't want to apologize
a million times.
Yeah.
Uh, it's just, every time I...
You know, when I think of
something to say...
...doesn't seem like enough.
Okay.
No problem.
Boundaries. Boundaries.
That's important.
Because I have a lot of pressure on me.
You have no idea how hard it was
for me to make this movie, okay?
I just need to focus,
so if you're gonna stay here,
we need to keep it...
like, super profesh.
"Professional"
is my middle name.
I thought your middle name
was "Danger."
That's a stage name.
Colt Profesh Seavers.
Promise me you're not
gonna derail this, okay?
Promise.
Want to do some doughnuts?
Do you want to drive me
to my car?
Yeah.
Okay, goodbye.
Okay.
"Tom, long time no see.
Gail asked me to check
and make sure you're okay."
"Colt, thought you were dead.
Why you got to be
such a pussy bitch?"
"Tom, I'm gonna have to ask you
not to refer to me
as a pussy or a bitch."
"Okay, but you got hurt
like a pussy
and you're acting like a bitch."
Tom?
Colt Seavers.
Just checking in on you.
Jody needs you back on set, pal.
And I-I don't want
to be a part of any...
breaking in, role-play games.
Well, all right.
Coffee.
What the...!
Why do you look so familiar?
Where do I know you from?
I'm Iggy Starr,
lead actress on Metalstorm.
- I'm Ryder's girlfriend.
- Oh.
- You're in Metalstorm.
- Yeah.
Hey, were you
in that movie Carjacked
where that guy named Jack
steals your car
and then you shoot him
in the hand and you say,
"I hope you know
how to drive stick"?
And it doesn't make sense
'cause it's like,
should be "automatic,"
but the way you say it...
That's Natalie Portman!
Oh. She's great.
- Is there anything else I'd know you from?
- Storm Chaser.
- No.
- Ice Warrior 1..
Ice Warrior 2.
I didn't see one.
- Back in Manners.
- No.
I got a 17 minutes
standing ovation at Cons.
Is it Con?
'Cause it's just like
I thought it was Cans.
I'd love to see you film.
Where is it streaming?
Streaming?
I'm just a stunt guy.
I'm working on
Metalstorm,, too.
You lie!
We're only on Metalstorm 1.
I meant also, though!
Is this a prop sword?
Mm-hmm.
I'm a good actress.
Hey, if you are
really working on Metalstorm,
why are you
sneaking around here?
Just trying to find Ryder.
He's, like, really drugged up
and paranoid right now.
He thinks someone's
trying to kill him.
And I'm like, "If you don't
finish Metalstorm,
I'm gonna kill you myself."
I can think of a million reasons why,
but why does Tom think
someone's trying to kill him?
I don't know.
I mean, all I know there is
some dark shit going on.
And the sooner I can
get out of here the better.
It is killing my high vibes
way of being.
I am a light worker.
I am a person of positivity.
I am a giver.
Did you know that there are
actually people in
the world going through hard things?
Like flood and crime
and there are povos.
- What's a povo?
- A poor person like you.
Cool.
Any idea where I could find him?
Uh, you could try this club
he hangs out at.
He's there with his drug
dealer friend, Doone,
Who has leopard print
tats on his head.
Okay, well...
It's been real.
I'll see you on Saturday.
Do you know the call time, by the way?
6:00am for the Povos.
- Hey, stuntman.
- Yeah?
You never gonna get in looking like that.
- What's with the bird?
- That's Tom Sober, the cockatoo.
They're like sensitive to energy and shit
so if you get high around one of them,
they're like freak out
and they attack you.
So what kind of shit is Tom into now?
He's into this new crazy
Australian shit called Dundee.
Dundee?
Yeah, like Crocodile Dundee?
It's like you see unicorns and shit
you go like get guided on this tour
and then the unicorns
there, like,
"hello, follow me."
it's like, a little bit weird
but I'm kind of into it.
It's very specific.
What's with your
Miami Vice Stunt Team jacket?
Is it second-hand?
It's first show I ever did.
50 stunts in 15 minutes.
I had to jump a boat
through a ring of fire.
I got so good I could do with my
hands tied behind my back, actually.
No one's ever done a stunt like that.
So the poster said.
So...
You're very into yourself, aren't you?
I mean you know,
you did ask.
Alright, so security is super tight
at the club.
You're gonna look the part,
but your best bet at getting in
is acting like Tom.
You know how to do that, don't you?
Yeah, just act like I own everything
and everyone
and there's no repercussions
for my actions.
what time we slow together Tom
I do like that yeah
I do like that
you doing
Stuntman! Yeah, yeah, Iggy said
you were gonna come see me.
Sit down, get a drink.
Hey, hey, get him a drink, get him a drink
What do you want?
Oh, no, no, I'm good.
I'm just looking for Ryder.
Get him a Shirley Temple.
Sit down.
No offense, I just want to find Ryder.
How come no one ever wants
to chat with the drug dealer?
Sorry. I, uh...
I mean no...
no disrespect.
Just had a long day.
Ryder hasn't shown up to work.
That was fast.
You do a stunt today?
I just, uhh, yeah, car roll.
Just a car roll?
Hear how he said that?
"Just a car roll!"
What a stuntman! My man!
It's what I do.
Hey, that's why I like you.
'Cause you do all the hard shit.
They give Oscars for that?
For stunts?
No.
Nope.
Hey, to the unsung heroes.
- I'll drink to that.
- Yeah.
No offense,
but I prefer cartoons.
See, movies are always trying
to make things real.
But it's not real.
It's a movie.
It's not meant to be real.
That's why I like cartoons.
See, 'cause cartoons
don't pretend to be real.
That's what I like about them.
You seen Dumbo?
- Dumbo?
- Yeah, Dumbo.
Dumbo changed my life.
You know that scene when Dumbo
gets into the bad champagne,
then he starts seeing
the pink elephants
on parade and shit?
I was like, "Yes, please.
"I'll have what he's having!
Make it a double!"
Hey, stuntman?
Why don't you come with us?
We'll get you nice and
comfortable at the hotel, huh?
Get out the way!
Move! C'mon!
Where's Ryder?
Yo, speak louder!
I'm too high for this shit!
Hey, over here!
Yeah! Follow me!
Don't give up, Colt.
Come on.
I know where I am.
Hei!
Where is he?
Where's Ryder!
Where's Ryder?!
Speak louder!
- Where is he?
- Huh?
I'm crazy, but...
I think I wanna be...
I think I wanna be a unicorn.
Look at that shiny white coat.
Look at that dreamy metal horn.
Now be your unicorn.
What are you doing, Colt?
You know what I'm doing.
I'm gonna stop this car.
Done 100 times to keep
my hips by the hood.
Should be fine.
You're just doing it
because the unicorn told you to.
You're just jealous the unicorn
didn't talk to you.
You know what?
You're clearly high, Colt.
And you're clearly checkingshit!
We don't have time for this.
Talk about this later.
Yeah, okay.
Driver, what are you doing?
Drive!
Drive, bro!
Hey, you need to chill.
Just relax. Just re--
Hey, just relax! I'm a lover,
not a fighter, okay? Just...
Where's Ryder?!
I just drugged you 'cause they paid me to.
Who's "they"?
The guy that runs
Ryder's security.
He's into some real shady shit.
What kind of shady shit?
- You know...
- What kind of shady shit?
Shady shit, you know...
You said shady thing.
Did not tell me what it is.
Tell me what shady shit is!
- Different types of shady shit.
- Like what?
I deliver drugs to him at
the Pennelton Hotel sometimes, okay?
What room?
I don't know what room.
You know, it changes.
Just ask Kevin for the--
- for the fruit plate. He'll give you the key.
- Kevin?
- Kevin! K-E-V-I-N.
- I know Kevin!
You know Kevin?
- I don't know Kevin.
- Well, you're gonna get to know Kevin.
Okay, he's in love-
I don't wanna get to know Kevin!
Ask him for a fruit plate.
Look, I'm not lying to you.
It's a fruit plate.
It's a fruit plate, are you serious?
Yeah, you know, mango strawberry
or fruit plate.
I know what a fruit plate is, sir.
Then ask Kevin for a fruit plate,
and he'll give you keys.
How long does this last?
- What?
- How long is this gonna last?
- Bro, what are you even saying?
- How...
long does this last?
Oh. When you stop
seeing unicorns.
This is a Dundadully Dundoo trip Colt.
I'd like to speak to Kevin.
Kevin's, uh, on a break.
Okay, maybe you can help me.
Can I order the "fruit plate"?
Okay. Do you want me to call...
"room service"?
I don't know.
Is that what happens?
- D-Do you have a room? Should I just...
- Do I need one?
To order the fr...
- The fruit plate.
- Hey, Colt.
The fruit plate.
- Hi. Hey.
- That's a look.
What happened to your face?
- Hi.
Okay.
Are you good?
What's wrong with you?
- It's good to see you.
- Wow, you look terrible.
You look amazing.
Did you fall?
What happened to you?
Wow. You're so pretty.
Okay. Your face is bleeding.
- What?
- What happened to you?
Oh. No, I was running.
Just-- I was running.
Very unusual athleisure wear
for a run.
- This?
- Yeah.
Yeah, they gave me
the wrong bags at the airport,
but, you know, it's-- it works.
I can sweat.
If I'm gonna play Ryder,
I thought I should just,
like, cut weight a little,
you know...
You seem kind of tweaky.
I'm a little... spotty.
Like, when I--
my glucose levels get low.
I get a little...
Okay, is that a new thing?
Is that a new thing?
- What's that?
- Is that a new thing?
- Is your hair new?
- Yes, I cut it.
I changed my hair.
You changed your number.
We're even.
I thought we'd sort of
even the score.
Yeah. I have a lot of new s--
You know, I've learned
a lot about myself
since-since we last
seen each other.
A lot of doctors.
A lot of therapy.
A lot of work.
And I realized that, I'm a mess.
And you dodged a bullet.
You have some vault, aren't you?
Spill the beans.
Heavy how,
and wanted to be there for you.
Yeah you say that because
you're such a wonderful person
that you would say that but trust me
it’s that heavy and we were...
you know, we were so new so I just...
I figured that...
you know, spare you for all the stuff.
A lot of things you can't do.
- It's a lot of stuff.
- Like what?
We could-- it could have gone
in the bathroom stuff.
- For instance.
- I mean...
I would have been really good
at bathroom stuff.
What?
Yeah, I think I would have been
really helpful and gentle with you
and sweet and discreet,
I would have closed my eyes.
Held my breath.
Give you a sponge bath.
- Excuse me?
- I give a great sponge bath.
- Very thorough.
- What?
Okay.
So thrilled about your new
relationship with fruit.
And I hope you'll be very happy.
It's just a fling.
It's not serious.
Trust me. I'm still...
hung up on my ex.
Yeah, but how she's supposed
to do quality work
if you keep harassing
her all the time.
Okay.
Can you go and grab your things?
We have ready...
Okay.
- Got a zip.
- Yup.
- What's going on?
- Seriously.
Colt, you're...
You look like
you've been busy.
Yeah. real busy, Gail.
Yeah. Good.
A lot of running around.
We'll get a drink and discuss that
but right now the studio...
so far up my ass
I can taste them.
We need your third act.
Okay. Yep.
You having problems
with the third act?
We're gonna, we're gonna go
and do things right now.
I need to write it.
I'm gonna go write it. I just--
It's like the studio are wanting me
to contort the love story
so that it all ends happily
and everything's rosy and...
- Jody, Jody, Jody.
- But I feel like if I...
lean into reality,
then...
maybe that's the way to go.
And most love stories
don't end well.
Usually.
- Know what I mean?
- I strongly disagree with that,
so, we should keep
chopping it up.
Yeah? Should we?
It's important.
It's the ending.
Okay.
Sir?
Huh?
Hi.
- Yeah.
- Hi.
Um, I hear that you're interested
in a-a fruit platter.
-  Kevin?
-  Yes.
Yes. Okay, so...
It's-it's on...
it's on ice.
Yep. There we go. Sorry.
Hello?
What do you think
about split screen?
Jody?
Yeah.
Is this okay I'm calling?
You said to call and...
- Yeah, it's fine.
- Yeah?
We could chop it up?
Let's chop it up.
It's good time.
Not doing anything.
Okay. Great.
Uh, so, split screen.
Right. Do you think that
it's like, nostalgic
super cool or do you think it's a gimmick?
I think
it could be super cool.
Yeah, how do you,
uh, want to use it?
I mean...
you know, tell me.
Tell me everything.
Tell me, you know,
about your vision.
So, I like that
they're on-screen together.
But they are in
separate worlds...
...you know,
visually and emotionally.
So you've got
this very prominent divide
between the lovers.
And I want that.
- You want the divide?
- I want the divide, yes.
It's funny 'cause I-I didn't
get the impression
that there was that much
keeping them apart.
Well, you haven't
read the script.
All I know so far is that
the alien lady and the cowboy
are having what seem to be
pretty manageable problems.
Jody? Jod-- How's this?
Manageable problems?
The aliens invaded Earth,
and they left it in tatters.
So this whole thing the studio are pushing
for the "love conquers all" thing...
I'm not buying it.
Well, I have to admit that I'm
surprised to hear you say that.
Why?
Well, I'm just
a boy in a neon suit
standing in front of a girl,
reminding her that Notting Hill
is her favourite movie
and she watches Love Actually
every year at Christmas.
Well, you know
I watched it again this year
and I didn't love it, actually.
- Wow. It's worse than I thought.
- Yeah. I'm ruined.
Yeah. It's a really sad day for
Notting Hill as well.
The happily ever after stuff.
- Unsubscribe me.
- I didn't get happily ever after
- from Notting Hill.
- What are you talking about?
- Of course you did.
- Did you?
Yes, of course.
they're like they're on the park bench.
She's got a head in his knee.
- She's a "regular girl."
Maybe, but we don't know
for sure
she's not gonna go back
to working the street.
All we know is that
in the beginning,
she's pretty much up for
anything but kissing,
and in the end,
she's open to kissing him.
And it gives us hope.
- You have got your Julia Roberts movies
- And that's all we want.
- so twisted...
- A little hope.
No, that is Pretty Woman.
where she is
a lady of the night,
and this is Notting Hill,
where she's a very famous actress.
Well, don't listen to me.
What do I know?
Look, you're the director.
You're gonna make
the right choice.
I'm just saying,
for people like me,
who may not necessarily get the
metaphor...
- of the split screen.
- You may not get the deeper metaphor,
but you're gonna see it.
You're gonna see
this bright line between them
that we're gonna ache
to see blur.
You know, but maybe it can't.
Maybe it doesn't.
Right. Right. Yeah.
But what do we know, right?
'Cause all we know at this point
is that the cowboy
likes the alien.
Does the alien like the cowboy?
She's on the fence.
Right
Because they got problems.
Because she's an alien and he's
a cowboy, and that's a problem.
But is it a problem
they can't overcome?
Here's a question.
Are they even gonna try?
What do you think?
Do you think they're gonna try?
I think...
I think this was
a great brainstorm.
So...
what'd you decide
about the split screen?
I have a better idea.
I don't think you need it.
I think the connection between
these characters is so strong
that nothing can
come between them.
Jod?
Jody?
- Hello?
- Dead guy on ice.
What?
There's a dead guy on ice
at the hotel, Gail.
Wait. Sorry.
What are you talking about?
Well, if you think
that doesn't make sense,
don't order the fruit plate.
Hold on, You're seriously telling me
you've just seen a dead body?
Yes, Gail.
On the rocks. In the hotel.
What hotel?
The one I just saw you in, Gail!
So, whose room is it in?
It wasn't Kevin Kevin per se,
but he definitely had
something to do with it.
Who is Kevin?
It was in Kevin's room?
Gail, you asked me
to do this.
So, please try and keep up.
I know. I'm sticking.
I went to Ryder's apartment
just like you told me.
That's where Iggy with the sword
and the silver cockatoo
put me in the neon suit
and they sent me
the man with the leopard print head.
Now...
He goes by the name of Doone.
It was Doone's goons who dirtied my Shirley,
and gave me the Dundee
and not in a fun way, Gail.
I think they were
trying to kill me, Gail!
So you can understand why
I chased him with my scooter
but when the unicorn
showed up I had no choice.
I had to hit their car with my body.
The point is that's how
I got the Kevin's fruit plate
and the dead guy on ice.
Do you understand now?
Does it make sense?
It's absolutely clear as mud.
Listen...
Don't-- just step away.
Step away and calm down.
I am gonna handle everything.
No more handling!
- I want the police!
- You're very aggressive.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry to yell.
- I want the police.
- You're not gonna talk to the police.
You don't talk to anyone
about this, okay?
- I'm calling the police.
- You are not talking to the police.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Wait, who's there?
It's the police.
I'm gonna talk to them.
No, no, no, no, no!
Don't talk...
No parking at any time.
Sorry.
Just making sure
we're both here.
I'm-I'm here, mate.
I want to report a crime.
- Okay.
- An ice crime.
Yeah. You're still
getting a ticket, mate.
I got to tell Jody. about the dead guy
About the dead guy.
How do you know he was dead?
He could've just been
knocked out.
- On ice?
- Yeah.
Ice baths are very good
for inflammation.
And are you forgetting
that you were high?
How can I if you keep fixating
- on that one point?
- Okay, you know what,
let me just stop you
right there.
- I don't know what I said.
- has got her all fired up.
I don't know I got her all
fired up about one
About what?
And now I have to build a truck
for a 250-foot jump.
- In a day and a half!
- Sounds pretty cool, actually.
And on top of that,
the fight scene today,
And Jody has decided that she wants
to do it all in one take.
A oner.
Dan, did you tell
him about the oner?
- Yes.
- So cool.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- So good. He's into it.
- Hi.
- Yeah, can I talk to you for a second?
- Okay,
about this sequence today,
Ryder's a no-show. Again, he's probably
on a bender or something.
Well, it's interesting you say that,
because that's...
...that's what I want to
talk to you about.
Me, too. Me, too.
Because we don't even
we don't even need him.
We don't need him.
I had an epiphany last night.
- Let me just tell you.
- Last night?
I was so excited.
After we spoke,
it all came to me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
The third act, this sequence,
all of it. I've been s...
After talking to me?
Yeah. You know, I was shocked
when you showed up.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- Well, it was...
- But...
shocking.
But I just started to wonder
if maybe you showed up
just at the right time, and...
I've been going for this thing
in the action,
and I've never been able
to get it.
Like this, feeling
of the pursuit of love.
And how far would you go for
the one that you love and...
You know?
And then...
You know, I realize it's not
very far with Ryder, 'cause he's a drip.
- Right.
- And he runs weird.
- Right
- And he can't do action,
- Well, it's...
- you can.
You can.
I'm unlimited with you.
I can do everything
and everything with you,
and it just made my brain just...
So cool. I don't need cuts,
I don't need gimmicks.
I don't need anything.
I just need you.
To finish this movie.
You know, maybe even make it
a great movie.
You know?
- Wow. Okay.
- What do you think?
Do you want to work together?
Shoot the shit out of Sydney
Opera House in four hours?
- Three hours and 52 minutes.
- Three hours and 52 minutes?
What are we waiting for?
Good! Okay!
Venti, Venti, come on.
I'm gonna get some dots
on your face, 'cause I need you
- but not your face.
- oh God.
Get-- Yeah, just get rid of it.
I'm gonna stick right his head on okay
- Okay. Cool. Okay, okay.
- Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
Ready for a take?
Make it rain, please!
- Oh.
- Thank you.
How'd we do, boss?
Yeah, it was good.
I mean, it was amazing.
It was so amazing,
we're gonna go do some karaoke,
- if you...
- Oh.
If you like karaoke,
you know, you could--
you could come.
Like, I'd--
I would like you to.
I'll be there.
Okay.
I don't know what that was.
That was just so awful and...
- Really?
- Yeah, who's she?
- Yeah.
- Holster that.
- It's holstered.
It's done. Forget.
You-you never saw it.
Jody, do you like
Christina or Britney?
I saw that.
- You saw the finger guns?
- Oh, I saw the finger guns.
She started it.
Hi.
I didn't ha--
I didn't have breakfast.
Yeah, you did.
- I disagree.
-I gave you a brekky wrap this morning.
Technically,
this is all meal penalty,
- if you want the...
- It's fine. Just-just sign.
- Thanks.
- I'm just saying,
not everyone's gonna be
as cool about it as I am.
- You know?
- No, I get it.
What is this?
I've got you on a 5:55 flight
out of here.
Okay? I have a car waiting for you.
- Now?
- Engine's on.
Yeah.
Colt...
there is some serious shit
going down, okay?
I just told Jody I was gonna
meet her for karaoke.
And I'm actually embarrassed
that I got you here
and got you all tangled up.
I just want to get you out
of here before it escalates.
Get your stuff together.
We're going.
You're gonna miss the flight.
Thank you.
- Sorry.
- Okay, but I'm late,
and I got to get Ryder's dogs
to daycare.
Fluffy needs her oatmeal bath.
She gets hives.
Hey, should I be
looking for another job, Alma?
You're Ryder's assistant.
You must know.
All I can tell you is that
if Ryder is a no-show tomorrow,
the studio will shut us down.
Ugh. Poor Jody.
Say hello to directors' jail.
Am I crazy or is Nigel hot?
He-- Wow, he's got
some great qualities.
He really does. Yeah, you
should go for it, Venti.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Jean-Claude.
Good day, sir
Good day.
How are you doing?
You're such a good boy.
Sorry, his commands
are in French...
French. I know.
I worked with him on a movie,
you know.
Can't believe he kept him.
Well, it's more for
a party trick, really.
This one's got a command
where he'll bite people in the balls.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. We-we know.
- No, no, don't.
- Attaque...
- Alma, right? I'm Colt...
- Colt Seavers.
I know who you are.
You know...
Of course you know.
I'm not surprised
What is that supposed to mean?
'Cause you're an assistant.
You guys secretly rule the world.
- You're not wrong.
- Look,
I had a really rough,
24 hours.
Maybe 48.
I don't know.
It's yesterday in LA,
I've already had a terrible tomorrow.
so if you could just tell me
what you know.
That would be amazing.
You grew up in Florida
until your parents divorced.
You were raised by a single mother.
You were an overactive child.
So she put you into martial arts.
You got four belts in one year.
You got hired in the stunt industry
when a local stuntman saw you
jumping off a buddy's roof.
And you used to double for Ryder.
until you broke your back.
Rough.
6'1 185 and your favourite colour is blue
Okay.
Well...
after that...
...oddly specific and...
sad summary of my life,
can we move on to Ryder?
Help me walk these guys
to doggy daycare?
Can I walk him?
So, the last time I saw Tom,
everything was pretty normal.
He and Henry were
in some kind of drug-induced,
shirtless shit-show
grappling match.
That's pretty normal.
Yeah, typical.
But then Gail called me early
the next morning in a panic.
Drop whatever you're doing.
Tom has lost his phone again.
so I headed to the apartment
expecting the usual,
you know, naked debauchery
piles of drugs, people passed out.
But this time it was different.
There was nobody there.
It was spotless.
Bu I did found the phone,
the one that Dressler,
Ryder's creepy security goon,
just called me about.
Metalstorm crew,
we have a call time of
6:00 a.m. tomorrow. Don't
be late.
Hey. Two shots of tequila, please.
- Hey.
- Wow.
I didn't think you liked
coming to these things.
What are you talking about?
I love listening to people
murder my favourite songs.
Thank you.
I got to get to karaoke.
Thanks, Amy.
Au revoir, Jean-Claude.
You got to get rid
of that thing.
Why don't you just give it
to Gail?
Whatever's on this phone
is a goddamn bazooka
that'll blow
a movie star-sized hole
through somebody's career.
I'm happy to get this
into the hands of a good guy.
- Okay...
- For the right price.
What do you want for it?
A producer credit.
On Metalstorm?
Winner winner chiken dinner.
Are you out of you mind?
Look, I need
career protection, okay?
I'm burning myself with this.
I mean I want Megadeth
to come out with a new record
and we have to accept that
some things are not gonna happen.
it's not like I'm asking
for points on the back end here, okay?
I know there's a lot of
producers pissing in that pool.
I'm a stunt guy.
What am I supposed to do
about it?
You're a stunt guy
who used to date the director
and seems to be getting close
to rekindling
some sort of short but
legendary, torrid love affair.
Drop it into the pillow talk.
I don’t know.
Do you think
we're close to rekindling, though?
I mean, I feel like we are
it feels like it.
But I'm saying from your perspective,
Do you...
truly...
What do I know?
Well, you seems to know a lot.
- You did say...
- Is it a deal or not?
It can help you find Ryder.
I'll do what I can.
I don't have the passcode.
Just figure it out,
okay, stuntman?
Just find Ryder.
I'm gonna need you
to sign an NDA.
As you know,
- I don't have time for an NDA. I got to--
- nothing in this industry...
I'm late for karaoke.
Jean-Claude!
Ryder's phone. Where is it?
What am I doing?
You sad that he left town?
Who?
Colt.
No, he didn't.
He's coming here. He's swinging
by to sing some karaoke.
No... I...
I gave him the tickets.
I see it! I see it!
Engage your core.
I need him to finish the movie.
Why would-- why wouldn't you
talk to me about it?
What?
Oh, chicken?
Really?
Transfer will kill me.
Okay?
It's product placement!
Give me that.
Fine.
Call me chicken.
All right. Okay, tough guy.
Okay, Jean-Claude.
I'll buy you a drink
when this is over.
Attaque!
Get away! Help! Help!
You've been so distracted.
You should have spoken to me.
This crossed wires-- Excuse me.
Can I get another, please?
Thank you.
God!
-  Get me out!
Stay back! Stay back!
I thought you wanted me
to get rid of him.
And he just left?
Still got it, man!
I'm working with you.
Who are you working for?!
Where's Ryder?!
- I don't know! I don't know!
- Tell me where he is!
Where's the phone, stuntman?
I need that video!
Wow, he didn't tell you.
Jean-Claude!
Can I get another one, please?
Thank you.
I really thought
I was doing my job.
It's fine.
But you know what?
He can do whatever he wants.
He's an adult human male,
and he should do as he pleases.
He should just...
...you know, go his own way,
you know?
But that means
y-you can focus up now.
- Yeah.
- You know, you have a massive--
Do you know you have a big, fat hit
- on your hands?
- I know. Yeah.
- It's High Noon at...
- High Noon.
- ...the edge of the universe.
- Edge of the universe.
Yes. Hear it yourself.
Forget about him. Just...
All right, uh, next up,
uh, we got a Jody.
- Is there a Jody in the house?
- Yes!
- Right here, right here!
- Ah. There she is.
Big round of applause for Jody!
I actually want
to change my song.
That one.
Jean-Claude.
Go help!
I love this song.
Come on, everyone. Let's do it.
- Brake!
- I can't!
There's something stuck!
Jean-Claude,
what are you doing?!
What are you just
sitting there for?!
Get the bootle.
You okay?
You?
I gotta get to karaoke.
Colt?
Where's Jody?
She left.
Where were you?
At a rave?
In a sewer?
What's with the dog?
It's a long story.
Give me a sunset on ice
and a water back.
Coming right up.
What's this?
It's Ryder's phone.
Why do you have Ryder's phone?
All I know is some really bad guys
are trying to get it.
Are you serious? What?
I just got to figure out
what's on there.
Then find Ryder and get him
to finish Jody's movie.
Okay.
Well, shit, yeah.
Venti, she's like a tech genius
at this stuff.
Thank you!
Hey, Venti!
- Ventilicious.
- Hey.
What's poppin' on, boys?
- Yeah, Ventinator.
You know how
to get into this thing?
Oh, I've seen
some of these guys.
This thing is a vault.
It'll take me like two or three days
- to crack this thing.
- Yeah, but you're like,
a tech genius you know?
What if you don't have
three days?
You need the password.
I'm telling you that.
You're next.
Nigel.
Nigel!
Knowing Ryder, it's...
written on a Post-it note
in his apartment somewhere.
Okay.
Okay, next up, we've got Dan.
Come on, buddy. Come on, Dan.
Don't be shy, mate.
Come on, buddy.
Let's go.
You owe me!
Finish your drink.
It's got to be around here
somewhere.
Let's just split up.
Jean-Claude...
Guard the cockatoo.
You know what? I deserve this.
Idiot.
Colt?
Colt!
I got it! Colt!
To finishing the movie.
I think I got it.
All right.
That guy mentioned a video.
Oh, baby, I'm here at work,
but I got a little something
for you, a little surprise.
It's just above my ass.
Oh, my God. Cover your eyes.
I think I've seen Tom's ass
more than my own.
Now is the winter
of our discontent
Made glorious summer
- by this sun of York...
- He's such a dick.
But, God, he's good.
Yeah.
What about this?
Look at him.
He's jacked to the tits.
So much for that silver cockatoo.
Oh, here's that party his
assistant was talking about.
Iggy.
Wait a second. Who's that?
That's Henry.
That's Ryder's stunt double.
He looks a lot like the guy
I saw at the hotel.
When you were high?
And you were seeing unicorns?
And a dead guy on ice.
Hell yeah! Come on!
What?! What?!
Do I do my own stunts?
I think I do.
I think I freakin' do.
Yeah, baby.
Uh, gimme, gimme,
gimme, gimme...
Gimme the phone.
- Oh, shit.
- Did they just kill Henry?
They just killed Henry.
- Oh, it's Venti.
- Hey, uh...
- Dan.
- Hello?
- Turn on the news right now.
I can't believe this!
The dead body discovered this
morning at the Pendleton Hotel
has been identified
as Henry Herrera,
an American stuntman known for
doubling superstar Tom Ryder.
Authorities are investigating
his death as a murder.
Their prime suspect
is another stuntman,
Colt Seavers, who was
last seen in the hotel room
where Herrera's body
was discovered.
Police have released
this security footage
showing Seavers leaving
the scene of the crime.
If you have any information,
please do us a favour,
reach out to Crime Stoppers
by the number on your screen.
And we'll have more on that
later. In the meantime...
I got to call Jody.
It's high noon
at the edge of
the universe, folks.
Which one was that?
- That was take four.
- Goddamn it, Jody.
I mean. It looks like
frickin' Burning Man.
My balls are drenched.
I need a towel.
This dude always forgets
that he's mic'd.
- I know.
- He says the craziest shit.
Craziest shit. I know, I know.
What, is it on airplane mode?
If this was The Fugitive
and you were Harrison Ford...
the bad guys would be
closing in.
I call tomahawk.
- Damn it.
- You stay alive.
Stay alive.
No matter how long it takes.
No matter how far, I will
find you!
- Last of the Mohicans.
- Ah,
boy! Stunts!
Damn it.
Shit, is this rubber? Oh, God.
Daniel Day-Lewis!
Jason Bourne!
Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson!
- Give me the phone!
Where's the phone, stuntman?
We got to get this phone
to the cops.
-Okay.
-It's the only thing--
Hey, man bun!
Where's the phone, stuntman?
Jean-Claude, attaque!
I'm gonna take that.
Be careful of that, big fella.
Shut up!
I'm gonna go out the front
and make sure no one's there.
- Okay.
- All right.
Hey, take Jean-Claude,
would you?
- Okay. Allons-y!
Just you and me, stuntman.
Shit.
Colt's down.
Big fella got away, though.
You can make it. You can
make it. You can make it!
No! It's too dangerous!
Got to be stairs.
Okay, okay, okay, okay!
Colt.
Hey, man.
Look at that.
Yeah, makin' a movie here.
Could you leave us, please?
Ooh, Gail. So tense.
You remember old Dressy, right?
Stuntman.
I never forget a fist.
Listen, I'm gonna
need the phone.
Where is it?
It's a matter of urgency.
I need to know.
Right. The one that proves
that you killed Henry, not me.
That phone.
- Well...
- Yeah.
I'm gonna hold on to that.
Seems like it's the only thing
keeping me alive right now.
Okay.
You hold on to it.
Okay, sure.
What happened, Colt?
You know...
all those movies...
we had some laughs, right?
Remember Prague?
Yeah?
I made you carry me?
All around the city?
That was a very dark time.
Plan paraplegic.
Remember? Right?
Yeah.
- That was fun.
- Yeah.
What's wrong?
What's happen?
Police has found Henry's body
in his hotel room,
murdered.
What?
Colt's gone MIA.
But he's on a plane.
They said he never got on a plane.
What do you saying to me?
He's the prime suspect, Jody.
Gail, come on.
Are you kidding me?
- I know.
- Colt?
- Yeah.
- There's no way.
- That's what I said.
- There's no way!
What went wrong?
Well, as I look at it,
you know, you're--
you're torturing me
right outside your superyacht
like a Bond villain.
Dipshit!
What went wrong?
What went right?!
You changed.
Yeah.
We used to be like brothers,
you and I.
Entered into the sacred bond
of actor and stuntman, man.
Oh, God.
You think Colt could murder
a human being?
- No, I don't.
- Did you tell them that?
- I said that.
- This is a man--
This is a man
who spent 23 minutes
ushering a cockroach
out of my room once,
and I was like, "Just stomp
on it," and he was like,
"No, let it live."
I mean, it's Colt.
I told them all of that.
I told him who he is--
who I thought he was.
Did you, emphatically?
- Yes, I did.
- Yeah, because he
was at the airport
where you sent him.
He would've been in karaoke with me.
I thought he was on the plane.
Don't do that.
He lied to both of us.
- How many movies have we done?
- Oh, I don't know.
Yeah, too many
to count, that's right.
'Cause I put you
in the contract, didn't I?
I put you there, right there.
Yeah? That's right,
I had the assistant,
the makeup and hair...
- Right.
- ...uh, trainer, and then boom,
Ryder's number one stuntman,
Colt Seavers.
That was me, I did that.
I did that for you.
What are you gonna
do for me? Huh?
Die, I guess?
Right? Die?
Is that the plan?
- Oh, my God.
- It's nothing personal.
Well, I'm taking it personal.
- Yeah, I can see that.
- The torture.
You know what?
It's just business.
- The drugging, the Taser.
- You know, it's just business.
I mean, Tom Ryder's
a global brand.
- I'm taking it personal.
- I literally move markets.
If I go down...
the freakin' Dow goes down.
If you break your back,
I replace you like this. Boom.
Look, I can see how you can
get so easily confused, you know?
You put on my clothes, all right?
You walk a mile in my shoes
you start to get some attention
and you get your little article in Variety
or whatever it is.
- 10 top stunts man or whatever the shit.
- Oh my God, Variety article.
- Are you serious?
- Doesn't really matter.
- Nobody read it.
- The Variety article?
But you start to feel like
you're something special.
I didn't even do the interview!
This is what's happened, right?
And muddy's up the waters,
and that's what I got
to nip it in the bud.
I got to protect the asset.
Come on.
You know, if you'd just
stuck to your job
instead of trying to
hog the spotlight,
this wouldn't have happened.
I mean, Henry wouldn't be
on the scene, his accident
wouldn't have happened,
your accident...
freaky little fall.
'Cause you just
push my buttons, man.
Wait a second. What?
What?
What did you say
about my accident?
Well, you know,
you pushed me over the edge.
You literally pushed a button.
I mean, you didn't--
I mean, I pushed the button.
I had to crank it up a notch.
That was you?
Yeah.
Had to teach you
a little lesson, didn't I?
Got a little
too big for your boots,
ain't you?
Henry's no different, you know.
Hey. You do your own stunts?
Do I do my own stunts?
In front of all those people,
that's humiliating.
And yeah, I'm gonna
kick you into next week.
But then Gail, you know...
- Remember Gail, right?
- I've known her for 15 years.
Oh, yeah. I forget, 'cause
you've been out of the game
- so long, you know?
- I introduced the two of you.
Calls me up and says,
"It doesn't look good."
Bad for marketing and renting,
and blah, blah, blah,
and murder and...
I know, I-I-I d--
I real-- I really
don't need this right now.
Fucking Henry!
Don't worry about it.
You lay low...
and I will handle everything.
But maybe we don't know people
as well as we think we do.
- Oh, my God.
- You know?
Oh, my God, it's Colt.
- Give me the...
- No.
- What are you doing?
- Gail, get off the pho--
- Oh! What are you doing?
- Oh, my-- Jesus Christ, Gail!
- Oh, my-- Oh, I'm so sorry.
- Oh, my God.
- Let me help you.
- No, stop it.
- Let me take it up to--
- Do you know what?
- Just give me a minute.
- Yep.
Just give me a minute.
This plan was so simple.
Yeah, we were gonna put
Henry's body on ice
so it doesn't decompose.
We could pull you out from
that rock you crawled under.
- My life, yep.
- You know, scan your face.
Stick you
on the murder video.
Drug you, drive you
and Henry's body
off the Sydney Harbour Bridge,
in your car-- boom.
You got murder, suicide.
So simple. Boom.
Cut. Check the gate.
Move on. Beautiful.
We have different ideas of what simple is.
Y-You just didn't
stay down, did you?
You had to, like, uh,
create a big scene,
like Colt Seavers does.
Dipshit Doone sends you where?
To the freaking crime scene
back to the hotel.
Oh, brilliant.
That's nice. Great.
Good job.
Now I got a witness.
Now you leave me with no options, Colt.
Now I'm- I'm now gonna improvise.
So say goodbye to Doone.
What?
He's gotta die.
Whaddaya mean i gotta di-
No, no!
Don't do this. Listen to me.
Shit.
God damn.
You're killing Doone.
This is insane.
Well, this is on you. man.
- This is all you.
- Insane.
This is insane.
But no, then you got Kevin.
Uuh... Kevin,
spoiler alert Kevin, run!
No, he had a good idea
he ain't gonna run.
- Kevin, I'd run.
- Don't run, Kev.
You were good, right?
Quick wits.
If it wasn't for him, the cops
would have found Henry's body.
Think about this.
- I am.
- Sleep on it.
If killing Kevin is a good idea,
it'll still be a good idea in the morning.
Colt, now he's a witness.
Now he's gotta go.
What?
What, no!
Hang on! What-
Oh, my God. You killing--
You killing Kevin.
He's killing Kevin.
- He's killing Kevin.
- She's gotta kill that sound.
I don't know when it stops.
Just adding up one by one.
All on your plate.
It's like pancake...
Still kind of works.
Sort of writes itself, actually.
- It's not writing itself.
- Yeah.
You're writing it.
Crippled stuntman,
falls from Grace.
Flies to Australia in a bitter rage,
because...
Tom Ryder,
two times Oscar nominees
working with his ex-girlfriend.
- This is terrible!
- Dresses up as the movie star
and goes to the club
to fill once in his life.
Relevant.
Gets high as balls goes to the
- This is your idea?
- Pennelton Hotel
and kick them and
- Tom, you should not write.
- find the new stunt double's door.
lands on both the tragic doubles
at the bottom of the Sidney Harbour.
The plot is heavy.
Or getting tangled in exposition.
The murder caught on tape.
Loose the last part of the suicide.
You lose the audience if it’s too much.
I can think of a few
other people who can't.
We could bring Dan up here,
maybe Jody, perhaps.
I mean, I like Jody,
but you know.
There's no phone.
Okay? That's the twist.
No phone.
He shot it out of my hand.
Up there, go check.
You, too, all of you.
I'll wait.
-  He shot it.
- You didn't know you did that?
It's crazy. I've been wanting
to tell you this whole time.
No, he didn't.
- I was by the door frame.
- No.
And he shoots it
out of my hands!
- No.
- Take the ties off.
- Oh, my God, what a relief.
- That's crazy.
You were right about one thing,
that was the only thing
keeping you alive.
I really wish you could see
what Jody's gonna do
with Metalstorm.
It's gonna be awesome.
And honestly...
it's gonna be a banger.
Kills him,
and an empathetic last stunt
No, I don’t think they give a shit.
Actually, Colt...
Tom, you need carbs!
Where's the phone?
You need carbs.
I need the phone.
Your brain runs on glucose.
Get your chef to make grilled cheese.
Okay?
It'll change your life right now.
Colt, you're the fall guy.
You the fall guy.
Where is the phone?
I mean... you can taking hits all night.
But, you know what?
Wish you didn't
break that bond, bro.
Wish you didn't break that bond.
Time for a drink, mate. Eh?
There we go.
Help!
- Help!
- Shut up.
Shut up, mate.
There.
This fire gag's real.
Come on, guys, start the boat.
He's gone the wrong way.
Shit!
Oh, Colt.
Colt?
- Hey.
- What's going on?
What'd you sing?
- What?
- At karaoke.
- I'm sorry I didn't make it.
- It doesn't matter.
Listen. Everyone's saying
you killed Henry.
- Oh, that's not true.
- What's happening?
You're gonna hear a lot
of things that aren't true.
I just wanted to say that,
when I first got here,
when you asked how I was doing
and I gave you the thumbs-up,
when you were like,
"That's stunt guy bullshit,"
and you're right,
it's total cliché,
but,
you know, there's a
reason you don't see
the thumbs-down stunt guy.
You know,
it's kind of part
of our training.
Right? You know,
you get hit by a car,
you get thrown out of a window,
you get set on fire,
you give the thumbs-up.
But, uh, after my accident--
turns out was not an accident,
by the way--
I, uh...
I wasn't okay.
And not because I broke my back,
because I just felt
like a huge...
failure.
And I realized that, uh...
you know, I'm not invincible.
Huge shocker.
And I thought maybe
I wasn't so special
or something, so I, uh...
just figured that
the thumbs-down version of me
wasn't what you got
into it for, so I disappeared.
But, you know, I didn't
just disappear after you, uh...
just disappeared on,
on, uh, myself... too.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
You deserved more than that.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted you to be honest.
You know, honestly,
it, uh, all hurts.
Getting hit by a car hurts.
Getting thrown out
of a window hurts.
Getting set on fire
really hurts.
But, uh...
...none of it ever hurt as much
as not being with you.
Where are you?
Is that from a movie
or did I just make that up?
It's pretty good.
- There he is!
- You can use it if you want.
No, please...
For what it's worth,
I'm still in love with you.
And I don't think you should
give up on that happy ending.
Colt.
I got to go.
Wait, Colt.
That's a wrap on Colt Seavers.
Gail?
Jody.
Colt's...
Colt's dead.
Police are investigating
an explosion on Sydney Harbour
just outside the Opera House,
where it appears a boat
has collided with...
...an alleged suicide
of Colt Seavers,
the man responsible for the
recent murder of Henry Herrera.
Hey. Hey.
Looking for Stunt Coordinator
Dan Tucker.
- You seen him?
- No.
Hey! You two.
Helmets off. Looking for
Stunt Coordinator Dan Tucker.
Following
a dramatic boat explosion
on Sydney Harbour, police are
currently investigating
the suicide of
American stuntman Colt Seavers.
Jody, you need
to be quiet. Don't say a word.
Wait, wait. No.
Jody...
You think you can come
to my set and sneak up on me?
Wait!
It's me. It's me.
Remember?
Jesus Christ.
I knew it.
- I knew it.
I knew you were alive.
Three shows a day,
six days a week for three years.
The Miami Vice stunt show.
You remembered.
Yes.
I'm happy you're alive, Colt.
Colt, I'm so happy you're alive.
- I knew it.
- Oh, my God.
- What were you doing...
- Nice work with the pen.
- So sorry.
- No, it was great.
You got it out just in time.
I think the ink poisoning didn't set in.
-  Chef's kiss.
- What's going on?
- Huh?
- Everyone's saying that you killed Henry.
Ryder killed Henry.
He framed me.
There's footage of you.
Well, he deepfaked me.
What?
They do it all the time
on the Internet.
They take Tom Cruise's face,
and they put it on yours.
And you can't tell
the difference.
No. Okay, so where's
the real footage
of Ryder killing Henry?
How do we get it?
It was on Ryder's phone, and
then it got destroyed because
Dan's Last of the Mohicans
plan didn't work out.
What?
It's not his fault, you know?
He called tomahawk first, okay.
I got "blanks only."
And it was going
pretty well, actually,
and then Dressler showed up.
So he, you know, he does this, like,
Jason Bourne shit.
I have so many questions.
Okay.
Who else knows you're alive?
No one.
Great.
No, that's the point.
I mean, I figure
we can't finish the movie
unless they think I'm dead.
What movie?
Metalstorm.
What about Metalstorm?
If they think I'm dead,
they'll come back and finish.
- Who?
- Ryder.
- Finish what?
- The movie.
- Metalstorm?
- Exactly.
- Are you insane? You are insane.
- What?
You need to be
burning your fingerprints off,
and you need to be
getting across the border
as fast as possible.
We're gonna hide you
until we can clear your name.
None of it matters anymore.
It's just a stupid movie.
- What?
- It's a stupid movie.
Don't say that.
That's Metalstorm
you're talking about.
That's the movie you spent
your whole life trying to make.
Who knows?
You might inspire a whole
generation of little Jodys
to pick up cameras
and make their own movies.
You're just-- you're special.
And all of us get to be
a part of something special
because it comes from you.
I obviously failed
at getting us our happy ending,
but I'll be damned
if I'm gonna let
Space Cowboy and Aliena
not have theirs.
Jody, my love!
- One sec!
- I'm coming...
Stop it.
Gail.
She's in on it.
- What?
- Yes.
- Okay, come on.
- Let's just kiss a little bit first.
No, come on, we g-- got to get
you in the bathroom, please.
Come on.
Christ!
Got to work.
You all right in there,
my darling?
Here, this-- Take this soap
and rub it on my belly.
Get in the bedroom.
- Okay. Colt. Are you good? Okay.
- Okay. Yeah.
- Be quiet. Don't make a sound.
- Jod?
- My head. The head.
- What?
- Hi!
- Hey.
Hello, you.
Aw, come here.
Aw, how's my favourite director?
- Uh, a bit emotional, you know.
- Oh, no--
Jesus.
Like Johnny and Amber
have just been here.
I just need to vent,
'cause it's been...
- it's just been so much.
- I know. I know.
- I'm so sorry about Colt.
- Thank you.
You know, it's such a shame, but,
what a mess.
- Right.
- Who knew?
- Yeah.
- I mean, I tried to help him.
I hope you know that, but
sometimes you can't help people
who don't want to be saved.
- Right.
- But...
silver lining
to this very dark cloud.
I've got Ryder to come back.
- And I have a plan.
- Really?
But we're not
gonna be able to do
your big third act set piece,
the car jump.
It is an impossible jump,
especially now with Colt gone.
Dead.
He's gone.
- He's so dead.
- Stay with me.
I spoke to Venti.
She says that she can do it
in VFX.
The car jump.
All we need to focus on
is Ryder's new,
final, bombastic monologue.
I've read the pages.
God, you smashed it.
I knew you would.
- We're gonna get him covered.
- Yeah.
You, meanwhile...
please go and rest up in Fiji,
on me.
You know?
Plop yourself on a beach.
And I'm gonna take care
of all of it...
...for you.
Gail.
You've got so much to process.
- No.
- I can take care of all of it.
This is my movie.
Now, listen to me.
I've learned so much from you.
- I know. Thank you.
- And I'm very grateful.
But the lesson I stand by now,
- that you've taught me...
- Yeah. Yeah.
You fall down,
you get right back up.
I am directing this movie, yeah.
Oh, my God, that's my girl.
- It went in. I'm so proud of you.
- Good. Okay.
Thank you. All right,
- let's get you out of here.
- One last thing.
Have you seen Dan?
Nope. I think he's
by the taco truck.
He's probably over there somewhere.
Thank you so much.
- I'm proud of you.
- Thank you.
Thanks for the pep talk.
Okay, buh-bye.
- Love you, darling.
- Love you, too. Bye!
You're gonna finish the movie.
No, I'm gonna clear your name.
Why can't we do both?
I think we can.
We're gonna bring him to set,
in a controlled environment,
and then we surround him...
And we beat the shit out of him.
No.
We're gonna force
a confession out of him
by putting him in a scene.
- Right.
- You know, he always forgets he's mic'd.
That's better.
I just don't know
how to do it yet.
I know how to do that.
Make him do his own stunt.
The impossible jump.
Then we beat the shit
out of him.
It's high noon
at the edge of
the universe, folks.
Now, we're facing
a powerful enemy.
An alien species born of
the worst of humanity's traits.
Well, what our enemy doesn't see
is that their demise
is imminent.
And the most powerful weapon
in all galaxy?
Love.
Inside each and every
one of you is a spark, baby.
An ember.
A goddamn fire!
Love is how we will win.
And even if we lose,
we're gonna die
fighting for a happy...
Goddamn Jody, what in the crap am I saying.
- Cut, cut!
- Cutting that, please.
I mean...
Panties in a twist.
it is if someone took the last few pages,
wipe your ass but then said hmm, yeah sure,
give that a try. I mean...
What's the problem Tom?
- Do you not like the new pages?
- No.
Jody, you promised me real.
You promised me grit, art...
- I mean...
- Happy endings can be real.
I know.
I get it.
I see what you're trying to do
This Colt things hit
you pretty hard, okay?
It has me as well.
- You know.
- Yeah.
Look, he let us down.
Come here.
I think what you're having
is a little nervous breakdown.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
And that's okay.
We all get one of those.
I have those quite frequently, actually.
Habitually, hoping you say.
I just, I feel pretty...
I feel pretty focused.
And I want you to know something.
I'm okay.
He was dead to me, anyway.
Do you know what I care about?
Not anymore.
Finishing this movie.
Our movie.
Makes me so....
happy to hear you say that because...
Our movie.
Metalstorm.
A Jody Morano film.
Starring Tom Ryder.
Metalstorm, baby, here we come.
We gonna put the Metalstorm
- to the past storm.
- Make me believe.
Okay?
Okay.
- You got this.
- Okay.
You got this.
- Make me believe, Tom Ryder.
- Give me some.
What do you want?
What do you want from this next one?
- What do you want.
- Dazzle me.
- Okay.
- Dazzle and surprise me.
Inspire me.
I just got my motivation.
Of course you did.
Right there, Jody.
Okay.
That is...
my trip out of here to
Saint Barris with Drake.
One take is all I need
and then I'm out of here.
I love it.
Sounds amazing.
- All right. Let's do it.
- Off we go, all right?
- One and done.
- Yep.
Let's do it.
- Let's... Let's go again!
- It's gonna be mad.
Resetting, please!
Oh, you again!
One take wonder, Jody.
You know it.
- Yeah.
- Very tense.
You know what, Gail?
It's the vibe on this set, okay?
You got bulletproof vested security.
Right. I know but, look,
think about it.
Everything that's happened is bit of
extra protection for all of us, okay?
Gotta be safe.
It just... if they can just
clear out of it, that would be...
- Yeah.
- Okay.
You heard her, back it up!
Guys, back it up.
Thank you.
Lock it up, guys.
The pumpkin heads goes to two.
Amazing.
- Where's she gonna...
- she's just, um...
I think she's...
we all got playback.
Listen, I got more
take out of him,
and then you need to be ready.
Okay?
It's game on.
174, Alpha, take two.
- And, action!
- Whoa, whoa, one second, one second.
Action!
It's high noon at the edge of
the universe, folks.
Zero notice here.
We're moving as fast
as we can, all right?
Light the pyro!
We need enough charges to blow
this canyon sky-high, people.
McCabe, where are we?
Going as fast as I can, Nige.
And even if we lose, we're gonna die
fighting for a happy ending!
Hell yeah!
Let's go get it, man!
Go on out there, here we go!
Who's with me?
Who is with me!
Cut!
Yes!
Soo good!
Soo good.
Thank you.
- Is that it?
- God, yeah.
- Did we get it?
- It was so good.
- We got it?
- Magic. Yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
- I really felt that one.
- Gail was in floods.
- Of course you did.
'Cause I had tears.
Yeah, I know. I can see them.
Yeah, it was fantastic.
So, listen, all we have left
is the alien truck coverage.
- All right? That's it.
- No.
Yep. We're gonna do
the car jump.
No.
- No one told me about another setup.
- We said-- No.
- There's another setup?
- Venti's gonna do that in VFX,
- so we're out of here.
-I know, but we need his close-up.
All right? I need his close-up
right here for the coverage.
All right? 15 minutes tops.
That's all I need.
This is the bit,
do you remember,
where Space Cowboy steals
the alien vehicle?
-Come on. This is his moment.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm not gonna do any driving, right?
Because I'm gonna feel
really nauseous.
It's a blue screen setup.
I need this. I need this, okay?
Everyone, double the pace, yes?!
Use those muscles!
Everyone in position!
We're as ready as we can be.
Okay. Hey, get Ray to come in
- and check the mic before we go, okay?
- Copy.
Sound, can you come down here
and check Ryder's mic, please?
All right, Tom. You ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Remember this bit?
You're gonna be in
the alien vehicle.
- Okay? Okay.
- Yep.
And with nowhere to go,
you're gonna jump the car
over the ravine.
So I just need
a quick pop on you...
Space Cowboy
ain't scared of no ravine.
- Of course he's not.
- So I'm thinking maybe just
a couple of reaction shots
of me gritting my teeth.
Like, "Goddamn."
Something like that.
Stoic.
- Yeah, yeah. I like it.
- All right?
- What do you think?
- I like it. Okay.
I think it's gonna be great.
Yeah, I love the choice.
All right, let's pop these on.
- Okay. What's this?
- There you go.
No, this is because
you've escaped the aliens.
Is this necessary?
It's a bit much, no?
Raise the stakes.
It's kind of cool.
- Yeah. It's cool. Okay.
- Raise the stakes.
- Let's do it.
- 'Cause you know, Space Cowboy.
Nobody can get at
the Space Cowboy.
- No way. Even when he's cuffed.
- Excuse me. Tom, sorry.
Jesus, Ray. I told you
to do it before I got on set.
Appreciate you, Tom.
Thank you. Sound good.
- Okay.
- Okay, great.
- So...
You got this guy
coming on your left.
- Hey, bro.
- All right, take him out.
Someone else is gonna
crash down on the bonnet.
You're gonna take him out.
No, no, no. See, what I'm
thinking is maybe I come down,
I take him out first,
and I'm like "pow, pow, pow."
- I slide over and go "pow."
- Yeah. Yeah.
And then maybe I say
a little line like,
"I was shooting aliens
way before I was paid to."
Fantastic.
All right, let's lock it up.
- Let's shoot, Nigel.
- Standing by, please.
All right.
Take one. Marker.
In three, two, one, action.
Not your lucky day, alien.
You got to go.
You can't outrun me.
I'm Space Cowboy!
You are approaching the ravine.
There's nowhere else to go.
Turn right. Go on.
You have no choice.
You're gonna
have to make the jump.
In three, two, one.
Who is that in the car with him?
We're-we're in the middle
of a take right now, asshole.
What are you doing?
He's just buckling you in.
Safety first. That's it.
It's really tight.
Is this necessary?
Hey, we are filming right now.
Keep rolling, keep rolling.
Sell it, Tom. It looks amazing.
- Take a deep breath.
- It does not look--
Get out of the car.
Howdy.
No, no, wait. Stop. No.
Wait, what's happening?
Oh, my God!
Get to the cars!
Jody, what the hell
are you doing?!
I'm trying to get something
real out of him, Gail.
There's no cameras on him!
Hey, Dan? They're approaching
Ambush Alley right now.
We're ready.
Let me out right now!
What are you gonna do, huh?
You gonna kill me? Again?!
- Can you untie me?
- No.
McCabe!
Smoke screen in three, two, one!
This does not seem safe, man!
Dan, where are they?
Do you have eyes on them?
I see 'em.
Everything's going to plan.
I'll block the road.
They shall not pass!
I see them.
They're entering Ambush Alley.
I can't see shit!
McCabe, one!
McCabe, two!
McCabe! Now!
I love my job.
Whoa, mama!
Oh, goddamn!
I can't think straight when
you drive like this.
You're supposed to be dead.
You blew up
in-in a thousand pieces.
You went kaboom.
Maybe you confusing me with someone
else you murdered?
Like, Henry or Doone or
Kevin?!
I like Kevin, okay?
- Like him or not, you murdered him!
- I was roleplaying!
I was playing a character.
Playing freaking Tommy
I said a few things,
i ordered their death,
I didn't think they gonna kill them.
- Okay.
- Okay?
I can’t help it if no one
can't tell the difference
when I'm acting,
and I'm being so goddamn natural.
- I was there, Tom Ryder.
- What's your problem?
Some might say i was an eyewitness,
- And how did I do?
- Tom Ryder.
- How good was that performance?
- You ordered their death.
Right.
It was very convincing,
Tom Ryder.
Why are you saying my name
like that?
- That is your name, isn't it, Tom Ryder?
- Yes, yes.
A blind man could see
that you're
- Tom Ryder.
- You're saying that like...
- "Tom Ryder, Tom Ryder."
- Okay. That's me.
- You're saying it like some obsessed fangirl.
- That's me, Colt Seavers, saying that.
Roll the cameras.
We're heading for the jump.
Tom Ryder's
doing his own stunts!
Everyone, roll. Arm car?
Check.
- Heli.
-Check.
I'm done taking the falls
for you.
You're gonna do your own stunts
from now on.
I don't want to do my own
- stunts, Colt!
- Relax.
It's just a 250-foot jump
that'll probably kill us.
It's never been done before.
It's for Comic-Con.
- It's Hall H. It's a big deal.
- What are you doing, man?
I thought it'd be fitting.
Me and you, Tom Ryder,
one last stunt.
You know,
like Thelma and Louise.
- Thelma and Louise?
- Yeah.
- They die at the end.
- Exactly!
Murder-suicide.
Can you just pull over
and let me out right now?
You're not getting
out of this car until you,
Tom Ryder, tell me,
Colt Seavers, the truth!
All right, all right,
all right, all right!
It was all Gail.
When I killed Henry,
she wanted to cover it up
because, to be honest,
Space Cowboy's one of
my best roles yet, Colt,
and I don't want
this movie to fail.
So you're saying that Gail Meyer
was responsible for framing me
for your murder of Henry?
Yes! Yes!
But what's your real name?
Tom Ryder.
Did you get that, Jody?
We got it! He confessed.
You wearing a wire?
Bro, you recording this?
This is entrapment.
You can't do that.
- What are you doing?
- No, it's not entrapment,
because you're wearing
the wire, dipshit!
He's going for it. Go. Go now.
I'm just an actor!
Wait.
He has a mouth guard.
I don't have a mouth guard.
- Oh, good.
- Colt!
- You're alive.
- Are you okay?
Are you okay?
I told you
I'd make the camera up to you.
Oh, it was fantastic.
Dressler, come in! -Ah!
Oy, can you hear me?
We've got to get out of here!
This is all Gail's fault, man.
This is all Gail's idea.
- Give me that confession!
- No.
Give me all the media!
Are you deaf?!
Dressler, bring
the helicopter to the trench.
- What about Ryder?
- Now!
Now, about this date.
Put it in the case, you numpty!
Can we call it a date?
I mean,
that's what it is, right?
Such a moron!
- Hurry up! God!
- Take it.
Gail, Gail, Gail.
- Listen...
- Give me the recording, Gail.
Darling, calm down.
Just come with me.
We don't need
all this toxic masculinity,
because we're the same,
you and me.
You know, we're survivors.
No, no, no, no.
I'm nothing like you.
I don't want to be
presumptuous, I mean,
but let's call a spade a spade.
That's why I gave you the job.
- Okay.
- Well, that and because
you're so easily mouldable,
you know?
We put up with worse than this.
We've survived more than Ryder
I mean, you know what?
My mom's version of
a good night kiss...
- Oh!
- Gail, just give me the case!
This is a Gail Meyer production!
Not yours!
Rendezvous with the boss
in the canyon.
Extraction to the spaceship set.
Spaceship set?
Oh, no, Big Red.
I don't think
you're gonna make that one.
- Stunts set!
Go!
Trust me, I will not
be taking the fall for this,
because I deliver hits
for all you little people.
You're welcome.
Jody?
That's for me! That's for me!
That's my helicopter!
This crazy stuntman's
lost his mind!
I'm on vacation!
Get this dog off me!
Not again, dog.
Just stay there!
Night-night, dog! You're dead.
This design is growing on me.
Get in! Let's get out of here!
Yeah, copy that.
Taking off now.
Drake said no plus 1.
Look, they know everything!
Wait, what-what is this?
It's the evidence!
Why didn't you just
stop talking?!
Jody!
Blow the pyros. Blow the pyros!
They're getting away!
Holy shit!
- Lower the arm! I'm gonna jump.
- Okay.
Okay, lower the arm.
Lower the arm.
I have a plan!
What is it?
What's-what's the plan?
Get me to the helicopter.
I'm gonna jump onto the skids,
and then I'm gonna
beat the shit out of him.
No, just-just get the recording.
Go!
Ah, shit.
Get me down!
We're losing hydraulics here.
I can't get it under control.
Just wondering,
you know, after this movie,
and if I don't go to prison
and, you know, you're not busy,
maybe we could go
to a beach somewhere.
Wear a couple of
swimming costumes.
Just drink a spicy margarita
or something.
Make some bad decisions.
Okay, sure. Yes.
- Sound like a plan?
- It's a better plan than this.
Okay, please be careful.
Okay, swing him around. Go!
God, get it under control!
Get us out of here!
What are you doing?!
Ryder, the confession!
No!
- No! No, Gail, no!
- No, Gail!
Stunts!
Mobilize that airbag now!
No!
Get out of the way, Ryder!
87North to the rescue!
- Go, go, go, go!
- Go!
Move, move, move!
Get it!
Just keep it steady!
You moron!
Yes!
Nice!
Go, go, go!
Yes!
- Oh, God!
- Oh, shit!
No!
Grab it!
Oh, my God! My nose!
Ryder, the gun!
Shoot him!
He's a stupid stuntman!
No one gives a shit!
He's one of the best
stunt doubles I've ever had!
Oh, shut up!
Give me the confession!
Come on, come on, come on!
Quick!
Give it back to me
or I will blow your head off!
It's empty, Gail.
No!
From visionary
director Jody Moreno
and Universal Pictures
comes a cosmic love story...
...of epic proportion.
Starring MTV Best Kiss
award nominee
Jason Momoa.
It's high noon
at the edge of the universe.
I know these creatures.
I fought them.
I've loved them.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
We are facing a powerful enemy.
But what our enemy does not know
is that inside
each and every one of you
is a goddamn fire!
Oh, shit.
Justice is on the horizon.
Metalstorm.
Metalstorm was a huge hit.
Aliena and Space Cowboy
finally got the happy ending.
As for Jody and I,
we got something even better.
We got a new beginning.
Filled with spicy margaritas and
bad decisions.
And look, I don't want
to over-romanticize it
or anything, but I think
what Jody and I got,
it's even better than
what you find in the movies.
Previously on
THE FALL GUY.
Wait.
You just-- Calm down.
You know who I am, right?
I mean...
I can make you massive star, you,
handsome beast!
and you...
you have the right
to remain silent.
So shut the hell up.
Well, somebody cuff this bitch.
- Let's go.
- This like from
the prop department, is it?
This ain't cop, man?
Back up, man!
Call my agent!
Get my agent involved!
- Let him-- let him go.
- Tom!
No signal.
Gotta get....
3 bars!
Actor.
Get me Jason Momoa's agent
on the phone.