[heavy breathing]
[haunting solo female
voice sings single note]
[waves lapping]
- [female voice sings]
- [heavy breathing]
Woman: Mia?
Mia! Mia, come back!
- [ominous music playing]
- [breathes heavily]
[ominous music continues]
[Mia pants]
Woman: Mia? Mia, come back!
Come back!
[pants]
Mummy!
[yelps]
[suspenseful music playing]
[pants]
[intriguing music playing]
- [rumbling]
- [dark music playing]
Synthetic female voice:
Atmospheric dome disturbances
within normal range.
[exhales]
Synthetic voice: This
morning, you swam 1409 meters
- at a stroke rate of...
- What's wrong with your voice?
Synthetic voice:
Aaryan changed it.
[chuckles] Oh.
Synthetic voice:
Do you like it?
Mia: I can live with it.
Synthetic voice: Suggested
Senoxidine dosage, one tab.
[machine whirrs]
[beeps]
Synthetic voice:
Atmospheric pressure
within the dome, one ATM.
Radioactivity levels,
within safe range.
[Mia sighs]
[door whooshes open]
- [she sighs]
- [electricity buzzing]
- [inhales sharply]
- [buzzing stops]
Aaryan: Reduce
coefficient 2.04 to 2.019.
[soft whooshing]
[cat purrs]
[Aaryan echoing] Why is
your texture so fuzzy?
[echoing] Why does Sjøhus
sound like your mother?
Aaryan: Are you serious?
I'm changing it back.
- I'm teasing. I like it.
- [cat purrs]
Why don't we have
something nice tonight?
I cultivated a new algae.
Maybe you can use it?
Sounds good.
[wind rushing]
[ominous choral music playing]
- [water running]
- [choral music playing]
Sjøhus, how's pressure
in feed pipe four?
Sjøhus: Lower than usual.
Shall I run diagnostics?
No, that's all right.
[choral singing continues]
[water running]
Sjøhus: Pressure
back to usual levels.
Hello.
[electronic beeping]
You're not feeling too good?
[choral music continues]
[door lock clicks]
[choral music concludes]
I don't think I'm
gonna get much sleep.
Me either.
You want to go to bed anyway?
Hmm.
- [grunts softly]
- Is that too much?
No, that's great.
[sighs]
- Mm.
- Yeah. It's really much better.
Mm-hmm.
What if we're not good enough?
If we're not, who is?
It just makes me nervous.
It's all so secretive.
We'll be fine.
- Hey.
- Hmm.
I love you.
That's right.
[smooches]
[Mia moans softly]
[breathes heavily]
[smooches]
[moans softly]
[sighs]
- [waves lapping]
- Mia!
[pants]
[crackling and rumbling]
- [choral music playing]
- [electronic chirping]
[door whooshes open]
[door shuts]
[choral music continues]
[low thrumming]
[choral music concludes]
- [electronic chime]
- Sjøhus: It's 6:00 a.m.
Sjøhus: Your
visitor has arrived.
Are you ready? Okay.
[quivers]
I'm Virginia. Your Assessor.
[electronic chime]
- [chuckles softly]
- Your supporting material,
as previously reported,
places you in the top 0.1
percentile of citizens.
I'm therefore happy to
confirm that under Article 96,
you qualify for
in-person Assessment.
- Over the next seven days...
- Can I just ask someth...
Virginia: There's a
lot to get through.
Sorry, I just...
Virginia: Over the
next seven days,
you'll undergo close
observation and formal testing
to ascertain suitability
for parenting.
In the event of a
pass, your material
will be passed on for
ex-utero gestation.
All other methods
of reproduction
still remain forbidden.
In the event of a fail,
candidates will be
notified immediately.
Candidates have the right
to withdraw from Assessment
at any point up to and including
the in-person questionnaire.
After which they waive
any and all right
to future applications.
Assessor's decision
is final. Clear?
- Yes.
- Absolutely.
Finally, you are reminded:
Everything that takes place
over the next seven days
is highly confidential.
And what are we being
assessed on exactly?
It's just a little... opaque.
Opaque?
Not opaque... I just
mean, not clear.
- That is what opaque means.
- What Mia's trying to say is...
We couldn't find any
specific criteria,
that's what I'm trying to say.
Virginia: The less you know
in advance, the better.
I want to get to
know the real you.
- Is that a good idea?
- Virginia: Yes.
I was joking.
Hmm. [chuckles]
Good. [chuckles]
Humor is important.
I'm sure that
everyone says this...
but I...
We would be really
great parents.
Everyone does say
that. [chuckles softly]
So, who's first?
On a scale of one to ten,
how would you rate
your current levels
of satisfaction with
the relationship?
Nine, at least.
Describe Mia with three words.
Funny. Smart.
Sharp. She can be
a little sharp.
But I like that.
Keeps me on my toes.
We were in a lab
and he was absorbed
in some code.
And I don't know why I took
this moment to tell him,
but I said "I love you", it
just popped out and he said,
"That's right." [chuckles]
How often do you have sex?
- Once or twice a week.
- How are we defining sex?
Virginia: Oral,
manual, anal or full.
[low thrum]
Do you achieve regular climax?
Yes.
Virginia: Every time?
Would you like some water?
Is that part of the test?
- No, just water.
- I'm fine. Thank you.
Tell me about your mother.
She expected a lot
from me, but...
it was good.
She was sent to the Old World
when my sister
and I were little,
so I only have a few memories.
- She was a dissident?
- Yes.
Do you have any
differences with the State?
No. Does it not say
this in my file?
Virginia: Why do
you want a child?
We know how lucky
we are. We feel...
We feel fulfilled...
...professionally and personally
and want to share that.
Every child deserves
the best possible start.
That sounds a little prepared.
[chuckles softly] It's
our duty to help nurture
the future of this society.
It's a big thing, so,
yes, we're prepared.
Mia: I want to give a
child what I never had.
[soft choral music playing]
And what was that?
A sense of belonging.
You don't feel you belong?
Now, yeah. No, I
meant as a child.
[choral music continues]
Everything's as per
the instructions.
We thought that we
could use this...
Not that we're
presuming, but we...
- [wind whistles]
- [sighs]
Do you hear that?
Loose springs.
But there's no springs
in that mattress.
Do you have somewhere else?
Yes, but there's
actually no springs...
You take our room.
We'll sleep in here.
Virginia: Don't
go to any trouble.
- It's no trouble.
- Yeah, yeah.
It's no trouble at all.
Better.
[low thrumming]
[soft whooshing]
[Mia echoing] I call it
Aaryan's thinking cave.
[Aaryan echoing] Sjøhus,
open Cooper slate.
I'm working on
the cat's texture.
This is all virtually generated.
[softly echoing] This is where
you designed the virtual pets?
Not the prototypes, they
were at the university,
but, yes, the second generation.
It's funny, I was in this seat
right here when it struck me...
Virginia: And what about you?
Do you have a work space?
Yes. Sure.
[chuckles softly]
[mysterious music playing]
[wind whistles]
The airflow system allows
different micro-climates
to coexist,
that's what allows
for the variety.
[water dripping]
It's very, er...
- colorful.
- Colorful?
This is a template
for sustainable food
production everywhere,
- it's a laboratory.
- Colorful's right.
Nature wants to be noticed,
but she's deceptive.
Underneath her beautiful façade,
she provides energy and shelter.
And this greenhouse alone
contains over 1000
different species
- of plants and algae able to...
- What's this one?
Oh... paphiopedilum.
It's also known as
the Venus Orchid.
It's the oldest of its
kind. Some live to be 100.
My mother gave it to me.
It's the only thing
I have of hers.
Your mother?
Sorry, can you be careful?
- Virginia: [scoffs]
- Sorry, she's sensitive.
I'll need full
access to all areas.
- But you don't mean...
- Full access.
It's already done.
I programmed Sjøhus
to recognize your voice. Sjøhus?
- Sjøhus: Welcome, Virginia.
- [chuckles softly]
I'll also need samples
of urine, saliva,
blood, hair, vaginal
mucus and semen.
[mysterious music playing]
I thought we already gave these.
[Aaryan pants, grunts softly]
[sighs]
Virginia: You'd be surprised
how many people cheat.
[she clears her throat]
It'll do.
[mysterious music concludes]
Mia synthesizes all
the nutrients herself.
We can produce
crops all year round
without depleting the soil.
May I? A little wine?
She's found a way of harnessing
the soil microbials into energy
that powers all our work.
[munches]
How did you get your scar?
The pet cull hadn't
happened long before
and some people thought I was
somehow responsible, so...
some activists
decided to intervene.
Which is insane because
Aaryan developed
virtual pets as a
solution to the cull,
he wasn't responsible for it.
The pet cull was part of
the disease prevention
and resource
conservation program.
The problem was the
State underestimated
the psychological
importance of companionship
when they exterminated
all the pets.
Especially during a
time of upheaval, so...
I was tasked with creating
an alternative. I did.
Just, not everybody
saw it that way.
These people firebombed
the university research lab
that Aaryan was working in.
I... I jumped out of
a third floor window.
Broke my shoulder,
my collar bone,
three vertebrae and
these burn scars.
That must've been terrifying.
Mia: He's still
traumatized by fire.
What happened to the
people responsible?
They were sent to the Old World.
They got what they deserved.
Your mother was sent
to the Old World.
Did she get what she deserved?
All that stuff about my mother.
She's just pushing
buttons, okay?
It's obviously how it works.
We just need to stay
cool, not react.
She likes you.
[chuckles] You jealous?
Yeah, embarrassingly so. I am.
Maybe I can make
you not jealous.
Light, Sjøhus.
[grunts softly]
[chuckles] Being in a single bed
makes me feel like
a teenager again.
Pervert.
[chuckles softly]
Get on your back.
Ow! You just kneed
me in the balls.
Sorry, do you want to complain,
or do you want your
cock in my mouth?
- What was the first option?
- [laughs] Yeah.
[smooches]
- You gonna fold those?
- [Mia chuckles]
Don't make me laugh. I'm being
very, very serious right now.
Aaryan: Okay.
[moans]
[Mia moans]
Oh. Oh, fuck!
Virginia! Virginia!
Mia: Oh, my God.
[pants]
I need to assess all aspects
of your relationship.
It's fine.
Seriously?
Virginia: Just
imagine I'm not here.
[Mia whispers] What? No.
[Mia clears throat]
- Aaryan?
- Yeah?
I... Fuck.
[mysterious music playing]
[moans]
[grunts softly]
[pants]
[groans, pants]
[electronic chime]
[dish clangs]
Oh, hey.
Erm, these all came. Do
you know what they are?
You sleep okay?
[spoon crunching]
[mysterious music playing]
- [grunts softly]
- [mysterious music concludes]
[breathes deeply]
You gonna eat?
Virginia: [chuckles]
[both] Mm.
[chuckles]
Why don't you try?
Yeah? You wanna try?
Yeah, that's, that's...
That's really good.
It's really yummy.
Whoa! What the f...
- You shouted at me.
- Mia: I did not. I did not...
- You did, you shouted.
- It was not. No, I...
- I raised my voice.
- Did.
- Mia: I raised my voice.
Mia: It's just not
the same thing.
- Did. [chuckles]
- Mia: No, I didn't.
- Did!
- It was a little loud.
- Ha! No, it was not!
- Did. Did. Did. Did.
- Mia: Okay, Virginia.
That's very cute, very charming.
- Did.
- Mia: Okay.
- [stomps] Did. Did. Did.
- Mia: Virginia.
- [bangs]
- Virginia, could you stop?
- Virginia, please stop.
- Did.
- Mia: Virginia.
- [chuckles] Did.
- Yeah. [chuckles]
- Mia: Virginia.
- Did! Did! Did!
Mia: Virginia!
Okay, that was... that
was a shout, yeah?
Why don't we start again, hmm?
[stomps]
Aaryan: Hey! Why
don't we try a game?
It's a train.
Oh, it's a bullet train.
[imitates a train]
Oh, it's going really fast.
Oh, is it gonna crash?
Oh... Or it could
go in the tunnel.
You don't want it to
crash now. Come on.
Come on.
Pew! There it is!
All right.
- Spoon.
- Spoon?
You wanna feed yourself?
Okay, all right.
- Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- [chuckles]
- Aaryan: Mm. [chuckles]
All right.
[both chuckle]
Sorry. It's kind of funny.
- Ooh...
- Virginia: [giggles]
- Ow, fuck. [grunts]
- Fuck.
- Aaryan: Oh, my God.
- Are you okay?
[grunts] I got shit in my eye.
- Yeah. [chuckles]
- Aaryan: Oh, that's not good.
- Shit.
- Shit!
Aaryan: Oh, it hurts.
- [groans] Fuck, I can't see.
- Fuck!
- What?
- Fuck! Shit!
Aaryan: It's fine.
I just can't see.
What do you mean you can't see?
- Mia: Aaryan, are you okay?
- Fuck!
Fuck. Shit. Shit. Fuck. Fuck.
- [water running]
- Mia: Is it better?
Aaryan: I can see now.
It just hurts like hell.
Sorry.
[Virginia shouting indistinctly]
- Wanna get some drops?
- [grunts softly]
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
- One. Okay, a second.
- [grunts]
- Yeah, okay.
- [grunts, whimpers]
Let me get this
out of your face.
Virginia: [in the
distance] Shit! Fuck!
Hey, can I see it? Lemme see.
Oh, my God.
- It's really red.
- Ow.
Do you think this is normal?
I mean, it has to be, right?
Why don't we just...
Let's set some rules.
Because children respond
to boundaries, right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Okay.
Okay. We're gonna...
I'm gonna apologize.
- So just let me...
- Yeah.
- Can you let me...
- Yeah, okay, okay.
Hey, Virginia, sweetie...
We...
[rhythmic panting]
Mia: You gotta be kidding me.
Aaryan: She's having fun with
us. We can clear this up.
Mia: It's everywhere.
Oh, my God.
[both] Virginia!
[rhythmic panting intensifies]
- Aaryan: Okay.
- Can you?
- Mia: Virginia!
Aaryan: Virginia!
You're not serious.
- Virginia!
Aaryan: Oh, shit.
No, no, no, no.
Mia: This is crazy.
[metallic clanking]
[high-pitched thrumming]
[intense music playing]
[metallic clanking]
Stop! [pants]
[quivers]
[sighs]
This is not a toy!
End of test.
Are you sure that we can't get
you any dessert or a drink?
[chuckles] Please,
treat me normally.
No airs or graces. Mia: Oh...
- [electronic chime]
- Sjøhus: A delivery.
Sjøhus: A delivery has arrived.
[wind whistles]
- Aaryan: Can you?
- Mia: Yeah.
- Aaryan: It's really heavy.
- Mia: Okay.
Aaryan: [grunts]
- There.
- Mia: Okay.
[clanks]
This could be your child's.
If you pass, of course.
You have until morning.
Aaryan: Okay. There's eight
different types of those?
- Mia: Yeah.
- Aaryan: So...
Do we know which one's
which, or just...
Mia: No, I don't know yet,
but we will figure it out.
Aaryan: Well, if we check the...
Does this say which orange piece
we're supposed to use for
the bottom with the greens?
The grey pieces are the pieces
- that actually link it.
- These connect...
Aaryan: They're the connectors.
...the orange.
No. The orange pieces
just sit on top.
They're not doing
any connecting.
- You use it to...
- My God.
The grey bit connects the pipes.
- Mia: Okay. Okay! Put the grey.
- Aaryan: That's it.
Then use them on
top. Put that on top.
Aaryan: And then you
just put that on top.
Well, you know the instructions
don't necessarily have to
tell us the right thing.
You don't necessarily think
the instructions have
to say the right thing?
Yes, that's what I said.
Okay.
[sighs] Okay, wait.
Now, after this, I'm
gonna need that wrench.
- Is it nearby?
- Aaryan: The wrench?
- Mia: The little tool? Shit.
- Aaryan: Okay, it's over there.
Gimme a second. Oh,
my finger. Shit.
Okay, wait, wait...
- Mia: Yeah. Sorry. Got it.
- Aaryan: I'll loose the head.
- Yeah, got it. I got it.
- Aaryan: Okay. Wait.
Yeah. Oh, my God.
- I can't...
- Mia: You are my savior.
Okay, okay.
[clattering]
[tense music playing]
But that's...
We've got that, so
if you want that...
[electronic chime]
Mm-mm.
"Warning: For safety purposes,
all parts must be used."
What are we gonna do with it?
[mysterious music playing]
[grunts, pants]
[mysterious music continues]
[mysterious music concludes]
I like it. You've done well.
Thank you. It was
a team effort.
Virginia: Would you get my bag?
I slept terribly.
Yeah.
[sighs]
- Sjøhus, open Hawkeye slate.
- [soft whooshing]
[choral music playing]
[chuckles softly]
- One over 9.172 constant.
- [soft whooshing]
Rotate 0.3 to 0.41.
Maintain vert...
- Hi.
Aaryan: Are you "you" now or...
Virginia: [chuckles]
It's always me.
Hmm.
When I was younger,
I had the stupidest
looking cocker-poodle.
When it was time to hand
over the pets for the cull,
the idea of him dying in a room
with some stranger
was too much, so...
I got hold of some pentobarbital
and I did it myself.
I remember him
looking at me with...
his big, trusting eyes.
I cried for days.
A grown woman, can
you believe it?
Did you ever get a virtual pet?
[scoffs] I know some
people found it a comfort,
but I couldn't bear the
thought of not touching him.
I mean, they were there
to be held, not admired.
- Go ahead.
- Virginia: What?
Go ahead.
[chuckles softly]
[chuckles]
[soft whooshing]
- [chuckles softly]
- [gasps]
- [chuckles]
- [rumbles]
[chuckles] How do you do that?
Aaryan: Magic. Science.
He feels all funny.
It's the fur. I
can make it solid,
but I can't get
the texture right.
Same with skin,
it's even harder...
I'm bored.
You wanna play a game?
- [low thrumming]
- [animals growl and snarl]
- [birds twitter]
- [insects chirp]
[growling]
[birds chirping]
- Virginia: [snarls]
- Mia: Sjøhus, lights!
[both laugh]
We were playing tigers.
Sure.
- So is your back okay now?
- Yeah, it's fine.
Okay.
[electronic chime]
[choral music playing]
[wind whistles]
[choral music continues]
[all chuckle]
Virginia: Here. Here. Come on.
[shrieks]
- Wait. You're so quick.
- Wait.
Be careful now. Oh, nice.
Virginia: Er... one,
two, three, four,
five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten!
Hello?
Daddy?
- [grunts]
- Virginia: [shrieks]
[both laugh]
- Okay. Okay, yeah...
- Virginia: You go.
Aaryan: All right. One,
two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Virginia?
♪ Virginia? ♪
♪ Where are you? ♪
- [grunts]
- Virginia: [shrieks]
[both laugh]
Aaryan: I got you!
Where's Mummy?
I thought you were
looking for me.
Aaryan: I thought
you were hiding.
- I was hiding.
- Aaryan: Okay.
Okay. Hey! Let's build a fort!
All right, nice.
Here?
Daddy, can I make
another one over there?
Sure.
It's "Daddy?"
Don't let her get to you.
Are we doing the right thing?
Of course.
What if I can't do this?
What if I'm not cut out for it?
- You're not your mother.
- What if I am, though?
She left you.
You would never do that.
Where's Virginia?
Aaryan: She can't have gone far.
Virginia?
Virginia!
[ominous music playing]
- Virginia!
Virginia!
- What are those?
- Where?
There!
Are those her shoes?
Oh, God! Oh...
Check there! Over there!
Mia: Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
- Virginia: [grunts]
- Can you breathe?
Are you okay?
- [coughs]
- Are you okay?
- I've got you.
- Get off me.
Get off! [coughs]
No! No!
- Get off.
- I got you.
- What were you doing?
- I was being a starfish.
I thought you were dead.
[both pant]
I said I was being a
starfish, you idiot.
Mia: Oh, great.
So next time, I'll just
let you drown then, huh?
- Nice.
- Virginia, I didn't...
Virginia.
Aaryan: You cannot behave
like this if you want a child.
I want a real child, Aaryan.
Not... this.
This is how we get a real child!
[suspenseful music playing]
Virginia: Daddy?
Carry.
[sighs]
- Aaryan: One, two, three.
- [chuckles]
Mia: You're indulging her.
All right. Off we go.
- Oh.
- [giggles]
Sjøhus: Unexpected atmospheric
pressure change within the dome.
Imminent rainfall.
[rain patters]
[thunder rumbles]
Virginia: Faster,
Daddy. Come on, faster!
Why do you stop?
I can't. My back. I can't.
Mia: Here. Get on my back.
- Just give me a minute, okay?
- Come on, I'll carry you.
I don't want you. I want Daddy.
Well, I'm all you've got.
Virginia: I want Daddy.
This is silly.
[panting]
All that is happening right now
is you're getting cold and wet.
It doesn't mean you hate me
any less if you come inside,
but at least you'll be warm.
All right?
- Arms up. Arms up. Okay, okay.
- Virginia: [shivers]
- Okay, okay.
- [whimpers]
- Mia: Okay, okay. Almost there.
Mia: There you go, come on.
Mm.
Virginia: [giggles]
Me. Me.
[giggles]
- Mia: It's okay. That's okay.
- Not the eyes.
Mia: I won't get
the eyes. I'll try.
There you go.
Let's take it all off.
- Virginia: Done!
- Mia: Done? Okay. Done.
Virginia: [whimpers]
I got you. Here you go.
My mother used to
do this for me.
- What was she like?
- She was beautiful.
Fearless. And infuriating.
I wanted to be her.
- You have beautiful hair.
- [chuckles softly]
[kisses]
[smacks lips]
[chuckles softly]
Can I wear some of your clothes?
- Mia: Yeah. Sure. Yeah.
- Yeah? [chuckles softly]
[electronic chime]
Sjøhus: A delivery
has arrived.
Aaryan: Mia!
In here.
Aaryan: It's a...
a dinner invite for tonight.
Mia: Someplace nice, I hope.
Er... It's here.
We're the hosts.
Mia: What are you
talking about?
[chuckles softly]
[metal clanging]
[choral music playing]
[low rumbling]
[electronic chime]
Sjøhus: Your first
guests have arrived.
- Hi.
- Hi. Come on in.
[choral music concludes]
Mia: Hello.
- Hey.
- Hi, Aaryan.
Hi. Hi. Er, Mia,
this is Serena.
Oh. Yeah, the Serena. Hi, um...
I've heard a lot of
great things. I'm Mia.
- It's really nice to meet you.
- Mia: Likewise.
- This is Holly and Amelia.
- Holly, hi. And Amelia?
It is... it's really such
a pleasure to meet you.
Are we going in?
- [chuckles]
- Sorry. Kids... Amelia!
I'm gonna go make
sure that everyone...
- Sure.
- Okay.
[footsteps recede]
Mia: Can I get you
something to drink?
- We have wine, juice.
- Holly: Thanks. Amelia...
How's Assessment going so far?
[indistinct chatter
in background]
[sighs] It's a
fucking nightmare.
[chuckles] We thought
we were a disaster
and then we got Amelia.
You'll be fine.
[indistinct chatter continues]
Holly: Serena, you
have to come see this.
Serena: I should...
Sjøhus: More guests
have arrived.
Aaryan: Hi. I'm Aaryan.
I'm Walter. And this is...
Oh, don't bother with all
that. We shan't meet again.
Amelia: They always stare.
Serena: They haven't
seen a child in a while.
- Walter: You seen that girl?
- Evie: Stealing our oxygen.
Amelia: There's never
anyone to play with.
[crash]
- Welcome!
- Evie: Oh, Jesus!
This is Virginia, our Assessor.
Mia. It's been too long.
Evie: Any chance of
a drink over here?
[electronic chime]
- Serena: How do you two...
- I was Walter's lab assistant.
- Serena: Oh, that makes sense.
- Walter: Mia was the most
brilliant and dedicated
assistant I ever had.
- Holly: High Praise.
- Regrettably,
she abandoned me for a
more exciting scientist.
Holly: Don't stare, sweetie.
I wanted to pursue my own work.
I still bear the scars
from your departure.
[she scoffs] Scratches, darling.
All down your back, if I recall.
- Can I get anyone anything?
- Is there alcohol in this?
- Yes, a bit, is that all right?
- No.
I'm gonna need
something stronger.
So, um, about Walter...
It's okay. You don't
have to explain.
When I was his student,
we had an affair
that I think Evie knows about.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
she knows about it.
It was completely inappropriate
and he probably exploited me,
but, you know, he was actually
a pretty good professor.
[quivers]
- Look at me, I'm shaking.
- Aaryan: Mia...
These people are
here to throw us off.
That's the game.
- We just have to stay calm.
- [inhales deeply] Okay.
Evie: Can't believe I
have to endure this.
Mia: So, Amelia, do
you go to school?
- Amelia self-educates.
- No schools in our district.
It's better, though. You get
to follow your own interests.
- Holly: Amelia's an artist.
- Mia: Oh!
Abstracts, mainly.
I would love to see
your work some time.
Do you show your art
at any exhibitions?
Amelia: Not really.
But I want to.
- Aaryan: Virginia?
- [grunts]
- Mia: Virginia. That's okay.
- Aaryan: Virginia, could you...
- Amelia: Is she okay?
- [Virginia chokes]
- Serena: I'm sure she's fine.
- Evie: Oh, God.
- Mia: Okay, sweetie.
- Amelia: She doesn't look fine.
- [chime]
- Sjøhus: Aaryan...
your mother has arrived.
[Aaryan sighs deeply]
Don't start. First thing
I knew about this...
- What the hell is that?
- Mom.
No, you stop calling me that.
You're not a child, anymore.
It's Ambika, not Mom.
You know, I was having
a perfectly nice time
in the gym when I got the call.
But as we all know, an
invitation from the State
isn't really an
invitation at all.
Okay. Can you just
promise me one thing?
Don't say anything
stupid or embarrassing?
You're so like your father.
Oh, Ambika, hi!
How was your trip?
Nice to see you too, Mom.
- Mia: How's work, Ambika?
- I'm not allowed to say.
Walter: Why? Is
it very secret?
Ambika: Ah, no.
Aaryan asked me not to talk
in case I embarrass him.
Aaryan: I was joking.
Serena: I'm sure he
was just teasing.
Evie: Virginia, stop it!
I design the modular estates.
- Virginia!
- I hear they're fantastic.
[screams]
How old is she supposed to be?
- Okay, I'm gonna clear plates.
- Mia: I'll help.
Thank you.
Evie: Are we pretending
this is okay?
Assessment is everybody's right,
whether we agree with it or not.
- It's an indulgence.
- How?
'Cause we don't
have the resources.
Serena: That's for the
state to decide, not you.
They reengineered Senoxidine
to prevent reproduction,
- as well as aging and disease.
- What about you, Holly?
Amelia: She's sliding
under the table.
What keeps you occupied?
Holly monitors border activity.
- Walter: That's fascinating.
- Mia: What is?
Serena: Holly works
by the border.
Honestly, I'm nowhere near.
I just see the reports.
What's to report? I thought
they were just dying.
Well, there are indications
that limited tracts of
land may be survivable.
- Are you serious?
- How long are they surviving?
Holly: The data's limited.
Ambika: How long
do people think?
- Years.
- Holly: We don't know for sure.
So, they're reproducing?
Once the Senoxidine
wears off, in theory.
Virginia: [squeals]
I mean that's what we're
trying to find out.
How would they have babies
without the Assessment?
- From their own wombs.
- Evie: Like in the Dark Ages.
Amelia: You mean it's
not forbidden there?
Virginia, I'm asking
nicely... Come back to me.
- Think of the pain.
- Yeah.
They must live such
short and unhappy lives.
Holly: I'm really not supposed
to talk about any of this.
We should be reducing the
population, not increasing it.
I'm not sure this
is the occasion
to talk about
population control.
This is the exact occasion
to talk about
population control!
- Mia: Okay, Virginia...
- Virginia: [cries out]
- Walter: Oh, shit.
- Evie: Control that brat.
Ambika: It was not
like this in my day.
Aaryan: Sorry about this.
[Mia whispers] It's okay.
It's okay, I'm not mad.
I'd like to propose a toast.
Ambika: A toast!
To Mia.
And Aaryan. The future.
- Oh, my God!
- All: The future!
Second time lucky, then?
Sorry, what do you
mean second time?
Well, you must know that
Aaryan and Serena applied?
- Mia: Oh...
- Obviously, it didn't work out.
Walter: [chuckles softly]
I guess things just
got interesting.
- Evie: She didn't know that?
- No, I didn't know.
We didn't get far at all.
I pulled out before the
end of the questionnaire.
So Aaryan wanted to continue?
It didn't mean anything.
I don't mean...
It's fine. He's right. It didn't
mean anything. It was a mistake.
- I'm gonna make space.
- Aaryan: Mia, this...
Oh, wow. Yeah, the future!
- Amelia: The future!
- Evie: Hooray.
- Serena: Ah, Jesus.
- Evie: Well done, Ambika.
[Walter chuckles]
[indistinct chatter]
[footsteps approach]
I didn't want to upset you.
Can we talk about this later?
Mia?
Holly: If you're
concerned about resources,
stop taking Senoxidine.
- Serena: Good idea.
- Walter: Great idea.
Let's grow old and die.
Why not throw ourselves
into the abyss?
But maybe finish dessert first.
Hands up. Who wants to die to
make room for the new people?
- Yeah.
- Oh, come on.
- What about madam over there?
- Amelia: Me?
Why not? Last one
in, first out.
- [Amelia gasps]
- God, you're a witch!
I think you'll find the
witches are in the Old World
along with the other
enemies of progress.
Enough! Mia's mother was
sent to the Old World.
Oh, I know. I know exactly
what happened to her.
She was exiled for spreading
lies and misinformation.
She deserved exactly
what she had coming...
Hey!
- Don't talk to her like that.
- Oh, spare me your outrage.
You're all too young to
remember the border, aren't you?
Amelia: You were alive
before the border?
How old are you?
I'm 153.
- What was it like?
- You don't want to know.
You really do not want to know.
I do.
Aaryan: Virginia, will
you sit down please?
- Evie: Oh, God, what now?
- Virginia: I wanna know.
Holly: It's okay.
Stay there, Amelia.
Evie: Oh, well...
- Aaryan: Virginia!
- Evie: I can tell you from...
- Oh, God. Ow.
- Holly: Don't worry, it's fine.
- Evie: You comfortable? Right.
- Virginia: Hm.
In the beginning, all
anyone could talk about
was how nice it was to
finally have decent summers.
And then the summers
never stopped.
Unbearable heat,
endless storms...
No crops, no shelter.
Nothing habitable.
[melancholic music playing]
Famine. Disease.
Countless species extinct.
Did you know we tore each
other apart over scraps?
We'd finally done it.
Destroyed ourselves.
All for greed and indifference.
And then one day, those
of us who were left,
we found a solution.
A new world.
We had to be smarter
than we were before,
because there wasn't
room for everyone.
Choices had to be made.
It wasn't kind or nice,
but it was necessary
for survival.
You think because we're
able to drink wine and...
grow crops in greenhouses,
and breed brats in bags,
you've somehow conquered nature.
You're wrong. It's borrowed.
And anything you
take from nature...
sooner or later,
she'll want it back.
So, forgive me if I
don't smile politely
and go along with this
whole fucking charade,
while you risk
everything we have
just to scratch some
vain and vestigial itch.
Fucking hubris will
be the death of us.
All of us. I want
no part of that.
There we are. That's
the story. Was it fun?
- [liquid trickles]
- [chuckles softly]
- Oh, my God. Get off!
- Ambika: What happened?
- Get off me!
- Mia: Hey...
Evie: She pissed all over
me, the fucking little bitch!
- Oh, my God.
- Ambika: Here. Take this.
Holly: I'm sure you'll
feel just awful.
Evie: Oh, my Gosh.
Serena: Can I get
something to clean up?
Evie: Well, at least we
know it runs in the family.
- Walter: Evie, please.
- What does?
Evie: Being a bad
fucking mother.
- [yells]
- Aaryan: Mia!
Amelia: Is Assessment
always like this?
Holly: Oh, my God.
- Evie: Fucking barbarians!
- Aaryan: Hey...
[melancholic music playing]
[sighs loudly]
[door opens]
Mia: It's late.
It's time for bed.
Evie was mean to me.
[kisses]
Thank you, Mummy.
- Mia: Hm.
- [chuckles softly]
- [smooches] Hm, no, I...
- [smooches]
- I...
- [chuckles]
Aren't you a silly? [chuckles]
I didn't realize I had
to tell you every detail
about my life before we met.
- Assessment's not a detail.
- [sighs loudly]
Mia, it didn't mean
anything, okay?
Serena said it herself,
it meant nothing.
- It is not nothing.
- Okay, maybe it's not nothing.
But it's not as big
a deal as you...
Stop! Stop. Stop. Stop.
Everything we went through.
The check-ups, the
protocols, the application,
just imagining the life
that we would have, and...
you never thought to mention
that you did that with her, too.
Yeah, I'm sorry. I
should've told you.
This can't just be another thing
for you to be good at, Aaryan.
You need to want this with me.
- I guess I was scared.
- Of what?
That you'd think I
wasn't good enough
to raise a child with.
That if you knew Serena
felt I wasn't good enough,
you'd feel the same.
What are you talking about?
I love you.
I want to have a child with you.
I thought that was obvious.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
This is really fucking hard.
Just two more days with
her, then she's gone.
[unsettling music playing]
[low indistinct muttering]
[mutters indistinctly]
[music fades]
Aaryan: Virginia?
I think you're having
a bad dream, okay?
I think you need
to go back to bed.
[breathes shakily] Yeah. [pants]
No, Virginia. Your
own bed. Not here.
That's okay. It's okay.
Just let her sleep here.
[electronic chime]
7.19 reinstate.
- [monkey chatters]
- 7.06 comma maintain.
- [soft whooshing]
- [dripping sound]
How do you think
Aaryan's coping?
I'd say that we're
both doing very well.
- [dripping fades]
- [chuckles]
Virginia: [hums softly]
Sjøhus: Mia, incoming call
from State Hospital West.
The doctor said that
she had an embolism
and lost her speech and sound.
Aaryan: For good?
Mia: They don't know,
they're running tests
They just said to get
there as soon as I could.
Did you tell them
you got Assessment?
What? No.
- Do you think you should?
- Why?
I just don't know if
it's okay for you to go.
She's my sister.
Aaryan: But Mia, you
hardly ever see her.
I'm the only family she has.
I'm just saying we should
check with Virginia.
- Virginia: Check what?
- Aaryan: Jesus!
Mia: My sister is
in intensive care.
So I just need to make
sure that she's okay.
- Virginia: You have to see her?
- Yes.
- Well then you must.
- Thank you.
Will it affect Assessment?
Virginia: Assessment
will be terminated, yes.
[stutters] There must be
exemptions for an emergency.
Parents are exempt
from emergencies?
- Aaryan is here.
- I'll be fine.
You're assessed jointly,
not as individuals.
- I have to see her.
- This is a choice.
Parenthood is full of
them. [chuckles softly]
You are assessing on whether
we are fit to bring up a child.
This is expressly
against regulations.
Mia: What kind of a person
would I be if I didn't go?
This is a demonstration of
my commitment to family.
[smacks lips]
You have until 6:00 a.m.
Not a moment later.
[footsteps receding]
[unsettling rhythmic percussion]
[sighs]
- Sjøhus, two degrees cooler.
- Sjøhus: Temperature adjusted.
[groans]
[ominous swooshing sound]
[breathes raggedly]
Were you having a nightmare?
Did you dream about the fire?
In mine, I was drowning.
I don't think this
is a good idea.
Virginia: Hold me.
Hold me. I'm scared.
Is this you now or...
- What's your hand doing there?
- Nothing. Hey.
- How does it feel?
- Aaryan: Okay, no, stop.
- Squeeze it.
- What?
Squeeze it. Harder.
- [Aaryan groans]
- Harder.
Aaryan: Am I being
assessed on this?
Okay. Oh, no, no, no.
[grunts] I can't. I can't.
- It appears that you can.
- It's an involuntary reaction.
- [groans]
- Assessor: So's this.
[groans] No, stop. [moans]
[moans, pants]
Faster or slower?
No, no, no, no. Stop, stop.
I can't do this to Mia.
All elements of Assessment
are subject to the discretion
of the individual Assessor.
[moans]
What do you mean? You're
saying Mia wouldn't know?
- Don't move.
- [groans]
Aaryan: No, no, no,
stop. I can't...
I'm giving you a
rare opportunity.
Aaryan: You're saying
I have to do this?
- I think I make myself clear.
- No.
- [moans, groans]
- [moans]
- [breathes shakily]
- [Aaryan groans]
- [breathes shakily, grunts]
Assessor: You're a
magician, Aaryan.
One of the architects
of our time.
- [grunts]
- Assessor: A prodigy.
You've built things
no other man could.
And now you're a prisoner
of your own success, a
captive of your talent.
[moans]
No one can touch
your achievements.
[pants] You're a genius.
- [moaning intensifies]
- [Virginia pants]
[Aaryan moans]
[moans softly]
[sighs loudly]
[soft choral vocalizing]
[electronic chime]
[intermittent
metallic drum beats]
[drum beats speed up]
[drum beats slow]
[drum beats stop]
- How was your sister?
- It was a false alarm.
There was a... mix-up,
someone with the same name.
I must've gone to
every department
before they figured it out.
It was very frustrating,
but, you know, a relief.
Caffeine. Triple shot.
- [toys tap on table]
- [liquid pours]
[intermittent drum beats]
[drum beats stop]
Well, I'm glad
your sister's okay.
- Thank you.
- Me too, Mummy.
[imitates airplane engine]
[low thrumming]
[thrumming stops]
Can you keep an eye on Virginia?
I'm gonna go for a swim.
- Can we talk?
- No, I need to clear my head.
Then we can talk.
[ominous vocalizing]
[door opens, closes]
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[vocalizing fades]
Wanna go play outside?
I just need to
finish this thought.
Then we can go and play outside.
Okay.
[steady metallic clanging]
[sighs deeply]
[wind whistles]
[metallic clanging stops]
Mummy! Mummy!
[waves crashing]
[fast, steady beats]
- Sjøhus, open Hawkeye slate.
- [soft whooshing]
[Virginia hums]
Okay, er... 2.9,
reinstate profile 368.
[chatters]
Sjøhus, disable protocols.
[locks click]
[female voice panting]
Rescale 419 to 412.
♪ Once upon a time ♪
♪ There was a pretty fly ♪
♪ Then one day she flew away ♪
♪ She flew away ♪
Maintain all other variables
and reduce 4.19 to 4.12.
[rhythmic vocal music]
[glass shatters]
[rhythmic vocal
music intensifies]
Maintain density.
[soft whooshing]
[gasps]
[rapid electronic beeping]
[steam hisses]
[chuckles]
[rapid electronic
beeping continues]
[rhythmic vocal music fades
into choral vocalizing]
[Aaryan gasps]
[Virginia sings] ♪
Once upon a time ♪
♪ There was a pretty fly ♪
♪ She had a pretty life ♪
♪ This pretty fly ♪
♪ But one day she flew away ♪
♪ Flew away ♪
♪ And she had ♪
♪ This one pretty child ♪
♪ But one day ♪
♪ This... ♪
- [chuckles]
- ♪ This pretty child ♪
♪ Flew away ♪
♪ Into the sky ♪
♪ Into the sea ♪
- [vocalizing fades]
- [explosion]
[flames roar]
[pants, whimpers]
- [pants]
- [glass shatters]
Mummy!
- [fire roars]
- [glass shatters]
Daddy!
[pants, whimpers]
[shrieks] Mummy!
[coughs]
Mummy. [whimpers]
[Virginia sings] ♪ Then
one day she flew away ♪
♪ Flew away ♪
[coughs, splutters]
[rapid drum beats]
Aaryan!
Sjøhus: Emergency
in greenhouse.
Emergency in greenhouse.
[Mia bangs on windows] Virginia!
Virginia! Virginia!
Shit. [grunts] Sjøhus, open!
[grunts] Sjøhus, open!
- Aaryan: Mia, get away!
- Aaryan, Virginia's inside.
[pants] Aaryan, please.
Please.
Aaryan!
- Come on. Come on!
- [grunts]
Mia: Come on!
- Aaryan!
- I am trying!
I can't fucking move! [grunts]
I can't move.
[she groans] Mia!
[coughs]
[whispers] Come on. Okay.
[whispers] Come on!
- [glass shattering]
- [Mia mumbles]
Okay. Okay. One, two! [grunts]
- Yeah, yeah, it's okay.
- [Virginia coughs]
- Aaryan: Mia!
- Mia: Aaryan. Aaryan, I can't.
- Aaryan: Hey. [coughs]
- [coughs]
[groans]
[explosion]
[breathes shakily]
Virginia, please eat.
Come on.
- Virginia.
- Just let her go.
You could've died.
Yeah. What about her?
I tried. I couldn't
because of the fire.
Yeah, I know.
Do you?
I'm gonna be right back.
Mia...
[exhales sharply]
- [waves crashing]
- [wind howling]
You know all my work
was in that greenhouse.
My orchid...
my entire life.
Do you have any idea
how long it takes
to build something like that?
'Cause it doesn't just happen.
Are you listening?
Do you care? I...
Do you even know what
you're doing anymore?
[whimpers lightly]
[soft choral vocalizing]
[receding footsteps]
[vocalizing continues]
[vocalizing fades]
Virginia: Assessment
is a rigorous process
with a high threshold
for success.
You've marked yourselves
out as serious
and impressive candidates,
demonstrating high
levels of competency.
So, it's therefore with...
regret that I must inform you
that your application
has not been successful.
You can't do that.
We've done everything you asked.
- My decision is final.
- Aaryan: No.
We did everything you asked.
I did everything.
Everything!
You can't fail me
'cause of that.
You told me I had to do
it to pass Assessment!
I never said that.
You fucked her?
I did it for us.
- You fucked our child.
- She's not our child.
Of course she is,
that's the entire point.
She was not our child
when she fucked me!
You said if Assessment was
over, you'd let us know.
Why didn't you fail
us at the time?
You can't do this.
It's not right.
- Step aside.
- Why did you not do that?
[chuckles softly]
Aaryan: You can't do this,
okay? It's not right.
- Assessor: Please.
- Aaryan: No, it's not right.
You can't. It's... Do you
know the things I've done
for this society?
The people I know?
- Listen to me. Listen to me!
- [Mia laughs hysterically]
[Mia continues laughing]
[gulps, breathes shakily]
- [munches]
- [cutlery clatters]
[somber music playing]
[rattling]
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
[grunts]
Fuck! [sobs]
[grunting intensifies]
[breathes shakily, grunts]
[sobs]
Aaryan: Hey. Hey.
[sobs, whimpers]
Aaryan: There's something
I want to show you.
[baby gurgles]
[whispers] Hi.
Hi. [shushes]
[whispers] Oh, my gosh.
- [whispers] Hi. Hi.
- [baby coos]
- [whispers] Hi.
- [coos]
- Mia: You okay?
- [baby gurgles]
Mia: Yes.
- [baby coos]
- I haven't named her yet.
[baby gurgles and coos]
Mia: Hey. Hey.
[baby coos]
- [baby gurgles]
- [Mia chuckles softly]
[whispers] Yes. Yes.
[sniffs]
What? What's wrong?
- [baby cries]
- Mia! What is it?
Mia: Her smell.
Aaryan: Her smell? What
do you mean? I don't...
[shakily] She... She doesn't
smell of anything. She...
- She has no smell.
- I'm gonna work on that, okay?
I'm gonna get it
right, I promise.
No, I don't want right,
I just want human.
So do I, but we can't
have that. We tried.
I called in every
possible favor.
They all said the same thing.
Assessor's decision is final.
These are the rules we live by.
Mia: I... I can't
do this anymore.
It's the price we pay
to drink clean water,
to live, to breathe.
[shakily] Then why does it
feel like I'm suffocating?
[baby coos]
We'll go back
to how it was before.
- I need to know why we failed.
- Why?
What's the point?
'Cause I have to understand.
How is that going to help us?
Mia.
We love each other.
- [baby cries]
- That's right.
Mia: That's right.
[baby continues whining]
[baby cries]
[haunting music playing]
[indistinct voice over PA]
[low, rhythmic rumbling]
[music fades]
[sighs]
[door closes]
Virginia: You
have five minutes.
It wasn't easy to find
you. Grace, right?
They think it helps
you keep less involved,
if you use a different name.
[water trickling]
Look, if you're here to tell
me what a monster I am...
Why did we fail?
- Because you...
- [Grace sighs]
- ...you tricked Aaryan.
- Aaryan made a choice.
You trusted him.
Children lie, Mia.
No, we're not these
kinds of people.
'Cause people like you couldn't
possibly be not good enough.
What does that mean,
people like me?
Do you even know how serious
an offense it is
you even being here?
I could have you arrested.
I could have you exiled.
I'm not going anywhere until
you tell me why we failed.
I've told you why you failed.
You're lying. I know you are.
'Cause I saved
your fucking life.
I...
We...
- connected.
- It's... It's common,
for candidates to feel a
bond with their Assessor,
- it doesn't mean...
- Why are you being like this?
What are you afraid of?
That you might actually
feel something?
I've had to learn
how to not feel.
What I'm...
What I'm trying to do
here, Mia, is to help you.
You need to leave.
I actually thought there was
a person behind the uniform,
that it couldn't
all just be an act,
but there isn't, is there?
- You're a lonely bitter husk.
- Yes. I'm a monster.
So it's normal for you to
fuck someone's partner?
To nearly die? That's
just what you do?
'Cause I have to say it sounds
a little unprofessional.
Don't you think people
ought to know that this is
- what Assessment is?
- Everything that I did
is within the protocols.
But you failed for
the same reason
that everyone fails, Mia.
You just weren't
good enough. [sighs]
What do you mean,
everyone fails?
[scoffs]
What do you mean,
everyone fails?
That's... That's a turn of
phrase. I didn't mean...
How many people passed
Assessment this year?
Grace: That's
confidential information.
What about the last two years?
The last three? The
last five? How many?
A 100? Ten? One? What? Do
you think we can't find out?
That Aaryan and I
don't know who to ask?
Six years.
That's the last
time anyone passed.
[breathes shakily]
[whispers] So...
So, we never had a chance.
Then what is the
point of any of it?
Stopping it would
be bad for morale.
You could've just failed us.
You didn't have to humiliate us.
No, I had to prove you
weren't good enough.
What is wrong with you?
- How can you even do this?
- Most can't.
Assessors usually burn out
within a few months,
they find it too intense.
But if you can do it,
there are rewards.
- And what was yours?
- A child.
[laughs softly]
Grace: They're gonna
give me a child.
- Okay.
- Grace: In the future.
If the numbers drop.
And you think that
you would be ahead
of people like Aaryan and me?
We've made things
for this society.
And what have you done? Just
victimized innocent people?
I've done everything
that they asked of me!
And I've been spat on.
I've been demeaned,
I've been debased.
I've sacrificed every
single part of me
that is left to...
to help the society to function,
and you fucking dare
to look down on me.
There's no list.
You must know that.
Of course, there's a list.
- Mia: Why would there be?
- Because there has to be!
Because this
society needs people
who know what it is...
to love a child.
You have no idea...
what it's like...
to hold...
to hold your child
in your arms...
telling her that
everything's gonna be okay...
even though she's dying.
That's when you really
know what love is.
My daughter is not alive,
but she's here, you know?
She's... she's present.
She's a part of me for
every single second.
And you can't...
You can't, you
can't possibly know
what that's like.
Not the way that I
do. [breathes shakily]
[softly] I'm sorry
about your daughter.
It's her birthday next week.
She drowned when she was eight.
[quietly] So stupid.
[sighs deeply]
Is it true what
Holly said, that...
that people are surviving?
Grace: It's not much of a life.
But yes.
Would you go?
[sighs]
I'm old, Mia.
Without the Senoxidine,
I won't last long.
And the Old World is
not a nice place to be.
And this is?
[soft music playing]
[indistinct chatter
in background]
[Grace] Your supporting
material places you
in the top 0.1
percentile of citizens.
Over the next seven days,
you will undergo
close observation
and formal testing
to ascertain suitability
for parenting.
In the event of a pass,
your material will be passed
on for ex-utero gestation.
In the event of a fail,
candidates will be
notified immediately.
Assessor's decision is final.
Is that clear?
I'm sure everyone
says this, but...
we'd make really great parents.
Catherine: Let me
show you the room.
It's got everything
you asked for.
Adequate.
I'll... I'll let you unpack.
Do you...
Do you ever keep in
touch with the children
as they grow?
No. I don't.
Catherine: I'll leave you to it.
[somber music playing]
Sorry, what time
did you say you'd...
[woman speaking distantly]
- [baby coos]
- [shushes]
[indistinct chatter]
Border guard 1: Next, please.
Announcer: Please prepare your
belongings and Senoxidine.
Border guard 2: Name, please?
Mia Grey.
Officer 2: Please move along.
Announcer: Please prepare your
belongings and Senoxidine.
Border guard 3: Name, please.
Announcer: Please prepare your
belongings and Senoxidine.
Border guard 4: Next.
Border guard 5: Name, please.
Officer 1: Let's go.
Come on, hey, get up.
Eight, nine, ten.
Ready or not, here I come!
[Chrissie giggles]
Synthetic voice: Chamber
before Old World.
Approaching final
chamber before Old World.
- Male guard: Let's go.
- Female guard: No talking.
- Male guard: Ready?
- Female guard: Stay in line.
Synthetic voice:
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five, four,
three, two, one.
[door whooshes open]
[muffled breathing]
[low rumbling]
[Mia breathes heavily]
[soaring music continues]
- [breathes deeply]
- [music fades]