You have three new voice
messages. First message.
Edie, where the hell are you?
It's 1:00 a.m. and your mother is
making an ass of herself. So you need...
-Hey. Where you going? I said we're not...
-I need five minutes. No.
-Kat, we're leaving. Fuck.
-Oh, come on. Five minutes.
Edie, move your ass.
Next message.
No. What are you d... No, don't
serve her. Don't serve her another...
Jesus Christ, man. She's
shit-hammered already.
-Oh, shut up.
-What the fuck?
Edie, seriously. Get down here.
Next message.
If you fell asleep with
your goddamn headphones on,
I swear to God, I'm
gonna lose my shit.
Pick up the phone.
What the hell is...
What the fuck are you looking
at? Was I talking to you?
-Yeah, boy. Keep walking.
-Nobody's hitting on your girl.
Nice shirt, you fucking Ricky
Martin wannabe motherfucker.
-You see me going anywhere?
- Who you think you talking to?
-I'm right here.
-You want trouble, you found it.
Mark, don't... God. Oh, my...
I worked last week.
It's my money.
Oh, great, yeah. One week. You
worked one week. Oh, you know what?
How is it that you get to spend all
your work money on your bullshit,
when I give everything I make
to you and Edie?
I'm not taking you
back to that shithole.
-Who the fuck was that guy in there?
-It was Chico.
-Chico? Who's Chico?
-No, uh, Rich, or...
-Ri... Rich? Rich Pacheco?
-Whatever.
That was Rich Pache... The jagoff that
robbed the Sevs with a butter knife?
-He's harmless.
-No, he tried to kill a cashier.
But he didn't.
Because he used a fucking butter
knife. Which makes him an idiot.
-Stop socializing with stupid junkies.
-Okay.
-That's crazy.
-"Junkies."
Thought he was in jail.
You know, I didn't
ask you to police me.
-Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Fine.
-Jesus Christ already.
Thank you for filling
in for my dead dad.
'Cause I was really missing
having someone up my ass 24-7.
Well, obviously it didn't
work the first time.
And what makes you think
it's gonna work now, hmm?
Are you even... What
a pain in the ass.
-Guys.
-What?
Fuck!
-What do I do? What do I do?
-No, no, no. No. It's fine, honey.
-Just calm down.
-It's not fucking fine.
No, we'll just... let's just tell
him that we've been drinking.
-She's 14.
-Yeah, he'll think we're being smart.
Shut it, Kat. Hey, Edie,
Edie, do not pull over.
I'm pulling over.
Edie! Do not fucking
pull over. Oh, my God.
Okay, you know what? I'm gonna
hide it. That's what I'm gonna do.
-Shut it, Kat. Edie. Look at me.
-I'm just gonna...
Look at me.
Your mom has a shit
ton of coke on her.
She bought a bunch of coke
from Rich fucking Pacheco,
and if you don't get us
out of here right now...
Okay, you know what?
You're overreact...
You... You don't think he's gonna
pull us out of the car? Huh?
When he finds out
that she's fucking 14?
Edie, if you don't get us the fuck out of
here right now, your ma is going to jail.
-Mark.
-It's your third strike, babe.
Edie. Look at me.
It's okay.
Now.
Just like I taught ya.
Punch it.
Hey!
I gotta go!
-What? No, no, no, no, no. Fifteen.
-Come on!
-Fifteen more minutes.
-I've got work in, like seven hours.
So? It's my birthday.
Yo ass used to be fun.
Oh, come on. I still have to study.
Tori's gonna stay. She's fun.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
Tori is too fun.
Look, I got a 2:00 a.m. last
call with that crazy-ass bitch.
So, no, I'm good. Yeah.
Okay, yes. Stay away from her.
-Yeah. I'm good.
-Thank you.
No, no, no. You don't have to do... I
know how tight your shit is right now.
Oh, no. It's your birthday. You're
not paying on your birthday. Come on.
-Declined.
-Shit!
It's fine. It's fine.
My tuition probably
went through.
-I got you.
-Uh.
No, no, no. Thank you,
thank you, but we're good.
You gonna let your friend
pay on her birthday?
-Oh...
-You can pay me back with your number.
She said we're good.
Why you stoppin' me from
blessin' your girl's life?
Yo breath. Oh, my God. You
done cleared my damn sinuses.
Mmm, yeah, okay.
Wow. He's still here.
He has confidence.
He doesn't have a mint.
I'm sorry. She's
really mean. I'm sorry.
You don't look sorry.
-I-I'll try. I'll try. I'll try.
-Get you a mint. Get you a mint, boo.
Bye, Doug.
-You doing too much.
-Yeah.
School, work, studyin' in
the middle of the night.
-Definitely feels like too much.
-Yeah.
Well, I'm proud of you.
And you still ain't called that bum-ass,
broke-ass motherfucker in, what now?
-Hey. You promised. Come on.
-I ain't promise shit on my birthday.
I could talk shit about
that bum-ass on my birthday.
It's been seven-and-a-half
months now, so...
That's good. For real.
That's a long-ass time to be
with somebody and then walk away.
I know how hard that shit is.
Ooh, this motherfucker.
Yo, call me.
Oh.
-Well, well, well.
-Ain't you got work?
Standing outside a
dealership, floppin' around.
I'm sorry about her.
You still don't look sorry.
Well, you're not making
it very easy, man.
Looking like Jack
Skellington and shit.
Goddamn!
You gon' fuck him
'cause of that car.
Huh?
Well...
Ugh.
No, no.
Fuck. Fuck.
No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck.
Goddamn. Shit. Fuck. Fuck.
Come on. Come on. Go, go, go!
Okay. Okay.
Uh-uh.
Uh-uh. Fuck!
Fuck!
Sorry, Lisa.
-Morning, Rick.
-Dale told me to shoot if you came in.
-I might ask you to anyway...
-I have to be able to count on you.
I know, I'm sorry. My
car shit the bed again.
Well, then you should consider
purchasing a car that you can count on.
And if that car is unreliable, may
I suggest, once again, a bus pass.
You're absolutely right, Dale.
Sure, Dale's the uncool
guy with the bus pass.
-But, uh, you wanna know what is cool?
-Mmm.
Low carbon emissions. Yeah,
no monthly insurance payments.
Getting to work on time.
Uh, excuse me. What is
the ETA on that filter?
I think your fish is sick, Dale.
Next.
But you reversed
the fee last time.
Yeah. Yeah, we did. We offered
you that one-time reversal.
-Do you understand what a fixed budget is?
-I do. I'm on one.
Hands up, motherfuckers.
Everybody, on the
ground. Phones out, now!
Hands up! Back that ass up!
-Phones out!
-You! Gimme your phone! Gimme your phone!
Open it!
-Okay, okay, okay, okay.
-Now!
Open it!
Get over here now!
Get your ass down.
-On the ground.
-Ah, not you.
-Get up. Open the drawer.
-On the floor.
Get your ass on the ground.
Uh-uh. Stay down!
Hey! Get your ass down!
-Let's go. Nice and easy.
-Okay. Okay.
-You idiot! Pick it up!
-I'm sorry.
Get it all in there. I'm not
fucking with you! Pick it up!
Motherfucker!
-Goddamn it! Look what you did.
-That was not supposed to happen!
-You did that shit on purpose!
-Oh, God.
-Look at my face! Dumb bitch!
-I swear! It must've been broken!
Look what you did to me!
Look what you did to my face!
You're fucking lying
to me, you bitch.
-Goddamn it!
-That's not supposed to happen.
Look what you did! You
did this shit on purpose!
No fractures, no concussion.
Everyone okay at the bank?
Far as I know. Security guard broke
an orbital bone, but, otherwise...
Oh, and they got
caught. The robbers.
Yeah, I figured. They made, like, five
mistakes before they even hit the drawers.
Sounds like your bank
must get robbed a lot
for you to be so
educated on the subject.
Employee training
simulations and all that.
Okay. Couple more tests
before we can think about
throwing you back out on the
street, considering the pregnancy.
"The pregnancy"?
What pregnancy?
Your pregnancy.
We run blood work in the case where you
might be pregnant, among other things,
and, yeah, you're pregnant.
So, you lied to me.
Hey, man. I just got pistol-whipped
and found out I'm pregnant.
Give me a break.
Three and a half
months, though? Really?
I have a history of skipping periods,
I've been stressed like crazy lately.
-I don't...
-You see that stuff on TV
about those obese people that have
no idea that they're pregnant?
So, yeah, that does happen.
Look, it's gonna be all right.
There's worse shit than this.
Should I tell him?
John?
-Yeah, well...
-Whoa, are you kidding me with this shit?
No, but, like, why
would you even say that?
Well, if it was reversed...
If it was reversed, you would have to
go save that baby from that motherfucker
'cause he's a goddamn
garbage fire. And a criminal.
I was no sweetheart
either, Baby.
-You were a kid, Edie.
-Yeah, so was he.
And a lot of things we did,
they were my choices too.
After getting dumped into one
shitty foster home after another,
with one shitty
dad after another,
-he was the only one...
-Whoa, whoa.
Those pieces of shit don't excuse
the shit that John put you through.
You don't know the
things that I did.
And I don't need to.
I know who you are now. And what the fuck
we been doing for the last year, huh?
Like, busting our ass, for what?
I don't know.
Whatever you decide to do with this
baby, you got folks that got your back.
We will figure it out
without that motherfucker.
We can raise funds or something.
Yeah, maybe we could
GoFundMe my abortion.
Hell yeah. Put that shit
on Facebook. What you mean?
-I know my aunties, they'll hook you up.
-Baby Girl.
What, Teenie-weenie-peenie?
The fuck you want?
I don't wanna get you fired.
Oh, I ain't never
getting fired.
Yeah, he sent me a dick
pic on accident once.
He knows I'll send that shit to corporate
if he ever tries to fuck with me,
so, I'm good.
Oh, you coming by later?
Ugh, I have my fucking test tomorrow.
I just wanna get it over with.
Okay. But do not call
that motherfucker.
-I won't.
-Baby Girl?
I'm coming.
-Bye, boo.
-Bye.
What? Damn. I'm here. Okay.
Shit.
John?
-Where is Leo, John? Where is he?
-Come on, John.
-I told you. I don't know where he is.
-I'm getting bored, John.
If I get any more bored, I'm
gonna break your fucking head.
-You know what I'm talking about.
-Ow!
-I told you I don't know where he is!
-Punch him right in the face.
Fuck that little piece of shit!
Fuck!
Aw, geez.
Look at your face. Fuck.
Tell us what you
did with Leo, John.
Yeah, we don't wanna kill you
today. It's my son's birthday.
Hey!
John, the fuck are you doing?
Come on! Fuck!
What the fuck did you do?
Tell me what you did!
-Yo! This way! This way! This way!
-Damn it!
White trash, you
still owe me 20.
I'll pay you back!
Tell me what you did!
Fuck. John. Where are you going?
Ow.
It was already open.
John, whose place is this?
John, whose place is this? John!
-Sweetie's.
-Who the fuck is Sweetie?
-John! John!
-These work.
John, who the fuck
is after us? John.
Shit! Jesus!
Who the fuck are you?
We're friends of Sweetie. Sweetie
said I could borrow his gun.
-And Sweetie said...
-Oh, you talking about this gun?
This my gun now. And Sweetie
ain't around here no more.
But this is all Sweetie's stuff.
No. This Byron's stuff.
Byron's gun, Byron's apartment.
And why do you
have on my shorts?
That's my after-shower
shit, man.
Byron, just call Sweetie.
He'll tell you he knows me.
-Pretty sure Sweetie's dead, John.
-What?
-Who the fuck are they?
-These Sweetie's friends.
Sweetie ain't here no mores.
Now, who the fuck is that?
Hey, Byron, Byron. Look at me.
They're after us, they have
guns, they're very dangerous.
Hey! They in here!
-Shit. Shit!
-Byron, we can work this out.
-You got money?
-Uh, we do. We can get it after.
Nah, man. Fuck your "after."
-Sh... Hold this, baby.
-No, hey... Byron, don't do...
These motherfuckers got money?
They want...
Hey, hold the fuck up.
I know you motherfuckers ain't
knockin' on my goddamn door like that.
What the f...
Oh, fuck. What the shit?
John! John!
John! Listen to me. Bust
ass to the back bedroom now.
-No, no, no, no.
-Go, go, go, go. What the fuck?
Go, go, go.
Fuck it.
What the fuck did
you do? Who's Leo?
Let's fucking go!
Go, go, go, go!
Where's your car?
I don't have my
car. I took the bus.
-Shit.
-Yeah.
Hold up.
Throw me the keys.
Get in.
Oh, shit!
What the...
Yeah, baby! Yeah!
Whoo!
Edie! No, no, no, no, no, no.
Shit.
No way out. No way out.
I got it. I got it.
Go, go, go, go!
Edie. Edie! Car, car, car!
Oh, shit!
Shut the fuck up!
Go!
Wait, no. On your left.
-What are they doing?
-Go.
Shit.
He's coming up this
road. Go, go, go, go, go.
-What crazy shit are you about to do?
-This crazy shit.
Bitch, I'm from Cleveland!
Tell me you don't miss that.
What did you do?
Huh? Oh. Okay. Hey.
Slow down. It's just
a misunderstanding.
What was I thinking
coming to see you?
I step back into your life for
five seconds. Five seconds.
-You know what?
-What?
-This is not my problem.
-What do you mean?
-What are you talking about?
-It's not my problem.
-Come on. What are you...
-Bye.
Edie, hold on. Can we just...
Can we just talk about
this for a second?
Edie. Edie.
Hey! Come on, Edie.
You can't leave me here.
I ain't got no clothes.
Tell me what you did!
Hold on.
-Tell me what you did!
-Don't. Come on, don't be crazy.
Okay! I'll show you,
okay? I'll show you.
-Jesus Christ.
-Just stop already.
You're making judgments
and you don't know nothing.
We're at a rat-fucked warehouse
in the middle of fuck-nowhere.
What, I'm supposed to expect
there's Christmas presents in there?
Baskets full of puppies?
Oh, fuck yeah, Sweetie.
That's a person-sized box.
Please tell me there is not a person
in that goddamn person-sized box.
-Leo.
-Yeah, it's a fucking person. Fuck!
-He's dead, isn't he?
He's not... Oh,
shit. You know what?
-Jesus Christ!
-Uh,
I think he might've
rolled over in the night.
-No, it's fine.
-He can't breathe in there!
No, I poked holes.
I just think he might've covered
'em up when he rolled over.
For fuck's sake.
Leo. Leo, wake up.
No, that's it. Good luck with your
dead body, you fucking dingdong.
Jesus Christ. He puts holes in the
box like he's a goddamn turtle.
Don't do this to me right now, you piece
of shit. Wake up. Don't do this. Leo!
He's alive! Edie, he's alive!
-What the fuck?
-Fuck you. Fuck you, John.
He's alive.
We're good.
He's a card counter.
Player. Card player.
-Nico calls you "card counter," so...
-Wait, this is Nico's guy?
What the fuck, John?
Are you serious?
I told him. I told him I
can't play for anybody else.
It was one game on an Indian
reservation. No one was even gonna know.
What are you not
getting about this?
-All you had to do was play one game.
-Nico would fucking kill me!
Shut the fuck up!
Just tell me exactly
what happened.
Uh, fine. Okay.
So, uh, we hooked up for drinks.
Right? He has a
few. I have a few.
And then I proposed a thing
about a game I had heard about.
And I told you, "I can't
because I work for Nico."
He made me do cocaine.
My wife would kill me if she knew
I did cocaine. She'd divorce me.
Oh, please. I didn't
hear you argue.
Why would I argue? Who
doesn't love cocaine?
And then he hit me because
I wouldn't take the job.
I apologized, and then I
offered you a ride home.
But you didn't. You put
me in this fucking box.
I almost died.
He was gonna call Nico, Eds.
And I poked holes in
the box, by the way.
Oh, like a fucking hamster?
Maybe you are a fucking hamster.
What does that even mean?
Eds, wait. Hold on. Wait, E-Edie, come
on. Would you just wait up for a second?
Take him back to Nico.
Edie, come on. You
know we can't do that.
What "we"? I ain't doin' shit.
Oh, God.
You guys are gonna talk
about fucking killing me,
and then you're gonna kill
me. Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
-Shut up!
Can we just, like, think
this through for a second?
Yeah, 'cause that's your strong
suit, "thinking things through."
Bring him back alive.
Apologize to that jagoff.
Apologize to Nico.
That is your only shot.
You don't have to
do this, you know?
Where are you taking me?
Back to Nico.
And why would I believe that
after he put me in a fucking box?
I apologized for that.
John, Leo, you're both gonna
tell Nico it was a mistake.
You got fucked up and
did some stupid shit.
You know, boys being
boys or whatever.
And tell me, why
would I do that?
Your wife won't find
out you did cocaine.
'Kay?
Do you have any more
of that cocaine?
No.
I need something to eat.
Totally acceptable.
We're happy to stop.
I think there's a burger
joint right up the street.
I'm a vegetarian.
-Jesus. Figures.
-John. John, I swear to God.
Whatever you want,
Leo. Our treat.
I'd like a falafel.
Fucking falafel.
There's a place I
like on Court Street.
-It's just up a few blocks.
-Okay, fuck that.
We're going to the burger place.
You could get fries, or whatever
isn't fucking cow or pig or whatever.
Okay, Gandhi?
I got money. I got it.
Hey, hey!
Just go.
What up, gangster?
Hey.
What are you doing?
You can't put what that vegan
piece of shit did on me.
Would you just stop?
We can figure this out.
I ain't figurin' shit.
I am done cleaning up your messes.
You're a living shit show, John.
You're the fucking Hiroshima and
the 9/11 of fucking human beings.
Hey, don't say
stuff you'll regret.
Regret is all I have.
I regret every second of every
minute I walked back into your life.
Take it back. You don't mean it.
Oh, yes, I do mean it!
And if I had a time machine,
I'd hit the button that said,
"The day before you met
John's stupid fucking ass!"
That would not be a button.
What?
Eenie Meanie.
You remember who came up
with that name for you?
You still there?
Who is it?
You, Nico. It was you.
I was always
proud of that one.
Not that it wasn't right there.
"Edith Meaney." "Eenie Meanie."
So small behind the wheel of a
car, but you were always so...
Mean.
Like a dog with his balls cut.
Dogs are meaner
with their balls.
Always the smartest one
in the room, weren't you?
Unfortunately, you weren't smart
enough to stay away from John.
And let's not pretend
he's not there with you.
The store in an hour.
What'd he say?
Hey. Ow! Hey. What the fuck?
Ow! St... Cut it
out! What the fuck?
What?
John. You're gonna keep your
mouth shut in there, all right?
You're gonna let me do the
talking. Do you hear me?
-Do you?
-Yeah, I got it.
I'ma grab a snack.
No you're not. Hey.
Put that down, or I'm gonna jump behind
that register and grab the shotgun.
I already opened it.
Do you have any money?
I know, but if the doctor calls, it's
good or bad news, I could just...
What do you mean good or bad...
You think it's gonna be bad news?
Well, I... I worded it wrong. Look,
you're gonna make yourself sick, okay?
Hey. Sit down.
-Nic, you work too much...
-What?
...and you make yourself sick,
where's that gonna leave me?
Less fortunate.
-That's not...
-What?
That's not what I'm
saying here. I'm trying...
If the doctor calls, I'm
gonna take the call myself.
-All right.
-Is it off silent?
The kid out front, he
set it to ring and buzz.
The kid outs... Why can't you s...
Forget about it. Forget I asked.
-Hey. My girl.
-Nico.
Long time.
No offense, but I was
hoping for longer.
Well, how long has it been?
Oh, it's that
museum thing, right?
-Five, six years?
-Seven.
That one went south, didn't it?
I put that scrub on the
job. What was his name?
-Mitts.
-Yeah, Mitts.
Big hands, right?
Basketball player.
-Catcher. Baseball.
-Cat... Catcher.
People thought he had
a shot at going pro.
Oh. I guess he never got a shot
at going pro, did he, Edith?
Eenie Meanie.
Always cleaning up
everybody's messes.
Are those for everybody?
Hey! The fuck you doing?
Did I offer you a
fucking piece of candy?
-You gotta be careful, Nic.
-Tell me about it.
You're gonna have a stroke,
where does that leave me?
-Like I said, less fortunate.
-That's not fair.
Georgie worries about
me. Wants me to exercise.
He wants me to take care
of that thing. What is it?
Gut health. Probiotics.
Probiotics.
I think I read
something about that.
Oh. We got a reader over
here. Bobby Book Club.
The only thing you've ever
read in your miserable life
is a prescription on the side of a bottle
that you stole out of some guy's car,
you miserable junkie bum fuck.
Could you get to the
fucking point here, please?
Oh, excuse me.
Did this, uh, unemployable
dick nugget...
Did he tell you about his
last masterpiece he painted?
-It wasn't my fault.
-Hey, what the fuck are you saying to me?
-It wasn't your fault.
-Nothing. S-Sorry.
I gave you one simple
direction. What was it?
Not a fucking sound.
-But it wasn't my fault.
-It wasn't your fucking fault?
You went up there,
the house was dark.
-Open the door. Do it quick.
-All right. Okay.
Don't fuck with us, honky.
Honky? You're white too.
Don't tell him that. I'm trying
to throw him off the scent.
He can see your hands.
-What did I tell you?
-Case the house first.
Case the fucking house first!
Surprise!
Oh, shit.
You fucking ass...
You motherfucker!
How much money did Leo
make for us last year?
-6, 7 hundred thousand, give or take.
-6, 7 hundred thousand.
You know why I like that
money? Because it had no risk.
Prostitution, drugs? High risk.
But a guy who counts cards and
wins a little bit like Leo?
What's the worst
that can happen?
Eh, someone gets the unfortunate job
of scraping his brains off the street.
That's the worst.
But here's the thing.
A guy like Leo, a counter, they
do tend to burn out, right?
-Right.
-So?
Leo had, what, three or
four years left with us?
Give or take.
What kinda projected earnings
lost in that period of time
because of this
unemployable motherfucker?
I like to round
up, so, $3 million.
-Give or take.
$3 million.
But I got some good news
for you, Johnny boy.
It just so happens there's gonna
be a casino poker tournament
in just a few days in Toledo.
And you know what the
prize money is for...
for the winner of that
particular tournament?
Three million dollars.
Neither of us are
card players, Nico.
I'm a card player.
No, you're fucking not.
I don't need a card player.
I need a driver.
You wanna steal it?
It's more fun than that.
The three million dollars is given to
the winner of that particular tournament,
and it's gonna be put into
the trunk of a brand-new...
Uh, the car is still TBD.
What's a TBD?
Uh, to-to be determined.
Oh. A brand-new
to-be-determined car.
You're our getaway driver. All you gotta
do is get in the car... and get away.
Get Perm Walters to do it.
He's your guy now, right?
Perm Walters does not owe
me three million dollars.
Since I mostly worked for
you all those years ago,
you know better than anyone
that I don't do that anymore.
So unfortunately, I'm
gonna have to decline.
She's declining.
Perfectly acceptable.
-Eh.
-Yeah.
I mean, she did a lot
of good work for us
-in the past.
-She did.
-Never failed us.
-Never did.
You know, in fact, if
anything, I failed her.
-No.
-Yeah.
So, when I did, what did I do?
What did I do? I let
you go clean, right?
And why?
Why?
'Cause you're an
honorable guy, Nico.
Honorable Guy Nico.
You had no problem letting a 15-year-old
girl play getaway driver for scumbags.
I don't know if we should be tossing
around the word "honorable" right now.
That's fair, Edith.
That's very fair.
Well... thanks for
hearing me out.
Johnny boy,
if you don't have my three
million dollars by next Friday,
I'm gonna have your skeleton
pulled out through your skin
by a Haitian guy who does
it at a very fair price.
-What's his name?
-Tim.
Haitian Tim.
Oh, you're still there.
Yo, Edie, hold up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Don't
have a heart attack!
Yo.
-So what are we doing?
-What do you mean?
Oh, what Nico said.
You heard him.
He's got, like, two guys on the
inside. Got that thing figured out.
We do that shit in our sleep.
Come on. You know
we've done harder.
Yeah, but what the fuck
do I get out of it, huh?
A chance to get
arrested, shot again?
Are you... Are you
serious? You get...
You get me being alive out
of it, Edie. You get me.
Come on. Really, John? What...
-Are you just gonna let this happen to me?
-You asked for this shit to happen to you.
I bailed you out a lot of times.
Come on, John. How many times are
you gonna throw that in my face.
Are you serious?
Do you know what I've been
doing since we broke up?
-Look, we didn't break up. It's a break.
-Eight months is not a break, John.
For the last eight months, I've been
going to work and going to school
and trying to get as far
away from this shit as I can.
Oh, oh, really? 'Cause I'm
pretty sure you came to my house
three months ago and today.
-Yeah.
Maybe that's because I
still keep punishing myself.
Oh, okay. So I'm like
a punishment for you.
Well, it always
works out that way.
Maybe it's because I keep thinking
that whatever happened to me,
whatever light bulb
that went on that said,
"You gotta grow up and
maybe try for something,"
that it would
happen for you too.
It never does.
What are you gonna do?
-What are you gonna do?
-I don't know. Maybe run.
Oh, come on. You run, and
the next thing you know,
you're hanging upside
down by your asshole
'cause you came back for a pack
of cigarettes or something stupid.
Nico's got nothing better to do
than to track down and kill people
he has personal
grievances with, okay?
I gotta go, John. I gotta...
I gotta go.
We're written in the stars, Eds,
with the sun and the moon and
every fucking thing else up there.
The earth spins, but we're always
there when it comes back around.
We always come back around, Eds.
Oh, shit.
Hey, brother. Can I
bum a smoke, please?
Pl... Just one.
Shit.
What?
I'm gonna need a car.
I got that guy on 105.
Yeah, see what you can
get with... Hold on.
How much money can I spend?
You know, uh... I could think of a
few things we could do to make a deal.
Come on, Stilts. I'm offering way
more than it's worth. Let's be real.
Look, I didn't give you my number
'cause I'm some car dealer.
Oh, shit. You should go.
I need you to take the baby.
It ain't my day, Deena.
Look, I got a hair
appointment last minute.
Since you ain't paid child support in
four months, you taking this motherfucker.
Look, don't make me have to
tell the judge. Who is this?
It's a business conversation.
Business, my ass.
What does she want?
-That's none of your bus...
-To buy his car.
How much?
-Do not...
-Forty.
Oh, you taking that shit.
I know I speak for me and the fucking
judge when I say you are taking that shit.
Did you sleep with him?
What? No.
Did you sleep with
anyone? Since me, I mean.
Are you fucking
serious right now?
It's not a no. Ugh.
I'm fucking sick.
That's what you're thinking about right
now? Me having sex with other people?
-Don't say it. Don't say it like that.
-You're the one saying it.
I know, but now I'm picturing it
'cause of the way you said it.
Something is sick in your brain.
-Oh, like you don't think about it.
-You having sex with other girls? No.
Yeah, you do.
You need help. You need
help. You're not normal.
It's totally a normal thing.
I'm way more "normaler"
than you are in this.
You know what, shut
the fuck up, Satan.
You know what I'd do though,
if I ever found out who?
Yeah, yeah, you'd stick
his dick through his face
or kick his heart
up his ass or...
-You've seen me do it.
-Yeah, I've seen it.
And I happen to remember
you in the emergency room
because Jimmy Pettrinelli
knocked you out.
You know, he was a
wrestler by the way.
He did that pussy-ass shit, and
then my head hit the pavement.
Yeah, I'm just... Yeah.
God, now it's in my head. Now I'm
picturing you and Jimmy Pettrin...
Why would you say his name?
Hey!
I'm not spending the next week
relitigating our shit with you.
The fuck is relitigating?
How the fuck you been to court a hundred
times and not know what litigate means?
Okay, all right. I know you're
like a hot-shit college girl now,
but the rest of us still
live here on planet Earth.
We're sharing a hotel
room though, right?
What? It's a good value.
Oh, my God.
Hey. Hey.
What time is it?
We're early.
We can get beers. I bet
they have a pool table.
Nico's guy's gonna be
here in less than an hour.
Can you just once lay low?
Come on, we can
make a few bucks.
You're just mad 'cause it's the
one thing I'm better at than you.
She's gonna meet
us there later.
Man, get yo ass out here.
You coming?
Come on.
I'm next.
No.
John,
can you get me
another drink, please?
Fuck's sake.
-Come here, motherfu...
-Enough!
Which one's yours?
Get the fuck off me. Get off me!
That one.
You two comedians, hit bricks.
Oh, shit. We have a Yankee fan.
Come here, man. Come here.
Have a good day.
Let me... Let me see that. L-Let me
see that hat... so we can burn it.
Now get the fuck out. Go.
John, say sorry to Gary.
Sorry, Gary.
Okay.
Are we all ready to act like
professionals and go to work?
Sorry, my wife got me on
this meal delivery thing.
She thinks if someone could
be as handsome as Tom Brady,
that he can be a great chef too.
But she was wrong.
Anybody want any pancakes
made out of sand?
All right, Cole. Introduce
yourself like we in recovery.
Cole, Head of Security
at the casino,
and I am in recovery. So if
anybody wants this beer...
Oh, yeah. I'll take it. My
glass smells like dog water.
-Sorry, Gary.
-Fuck off.
Okay, what are we up
against on the day?
A lot of off-duty
cops being brought in,
and that's not including the
two dozen already on security.
The money'll be secured in a prize car
just before the end of the tournament.
When they get a hunch the
final game is wrapping up,
security rolls it out from the
vault and feeds it into the trunk.
Three guys move the payload, three cops
securing the perimeter around the car,
six stationed outside,
four in cruisers.
What kind of car?
-The prize?
-Yeah.
Kenny. Special events
for the casino.
Dodge Charger Scat Pack. Fast.
Zero to 60 in 4.2. Manual.
Manual? It's like they
wanted someone to steal it.
Why do you think I picked it?
First bump, outside of all
the cops and/or security
is that they can't legally have
gas in it while it's on the floor.
Well, that's a problem
since it runs on gas.
Yeah, I fucked up on that one.
So we create a
problem for this car.
Take it in the shop, rig the entire
car to our needs and send it back in.
Or we switch it out with one
we start rigging tonight.
Can we get an identical car?
Yeah. I know the dealer. I work with
him all the time. Massive piece of shit.
All right, we can talk
specs about the car later.
What do we need the
car to do exactly?
How far from the
display to the door?
I'm more worried about
the crowd than the cops.
Meaning, you'd like to avoid hitting
innocent people on the way out?
I would.
You won't be able to go through the front
entrance without doing a lot of damage
to the car and maybe
a lot of people.
I'm assuming you
have an alternative?
The way the car came
in... from the back.
She doesn't love it.
It's a much more complicated
drive out of that place.
Good news. Less
security at that exit,
and who will be there
won't be expecting us.
What about guns?
And what about 'em?
Will we be supplied them?
I don't love that this is one
of your first questions, John.
A lot of the guys on
security are my friends.
Not on the day, they ain't. I
know Nico would say the same.
Hey, if shit's a summer
breeze, shit's a summer breeze.
Obviously that's what I prefer.
-But that person right there...
-John.
...that's my whole world.
And if someone tries to
take that away from me,
and shit goes from summer breeze
to wild wild west real quick,
well, ride 'em, fucking cowboy.
Okay, what else we got?
We got you road maps of every in
and out from here to New York.
Traffic will be a little
busier because of the event,
but I'm guessing it'll be
manageable at that hour of day.
Nico checked in with
his construction guys.
Won't be any roadwork planned that
day to make things funny for us.
Unless we want
'em to be funny.
All you gotta do is say the word.
Anything else you need on the outside?
-Just road.
-I can dig some up for you.
-I'll give you a call later.
-All right, man. I appreciate it.
Yeah.
Yeah, man. Get some sleep.
-Homeboy's gotta piss.
-Mmm. You got two minutes?
Gary, is it cool
to use your office?
Long as you don't
mind the ladies.
You think Gary likes
Black women with big tits?
There's some small tits too.
Um, how many banks
have you robbed, Edie?
You get right to it.
Well, I'm in a room fully
furnished with pornography
with a woman I don't know, so I'd like
to get out of here sooner than later.
Banks. Robbed. How many?
Helped rob. Enough. Too many.
Mmm, 12 banks, three jewelry stores,
a nightclub tycoon's corporate office,
a certain football team
owner's summer home...
That was impressive, by the way.
Police helicopter, live
chase all caught on the news,
and yet you are
here talking to me.
If you're the Wikipedia of
all the bad shit I ever did,
then why are you even asking?
It's my job to sus out just exactly
who it is that I'm working with.
Am I running this job, or
are you? 'Cause I'm confused.
No confusion. It's your
job. One hundred percent.
'Cause, you know, if... if
it's you, it's better for me.
You pull it off, you're Mr. Big Shit
with the boss, and if you don't, well...
Your boyfriend dies.
-Ex.
-Is he though?
-Hundred percent.
-Okay, because now I'm confused.
Nothing to be confused about.
There is. Most definitely.
Because you've had a 100% success rate
all before you were 25 years old, Edie.
-Not all.
-Oh, right.
-And how'd those jobs go? Those, uh...
-...off-the-books jobs?
-They went.
-Right.
Because if they didn't, I
would've heard about it.
And someone who gets talked about like
an urban legend, someone like that
has very picky taste on how things
are done and who they're done with.
Just say it.
Edie, this is the
big black tits of me.
I like to think of myself
as... ...uncommonly simple.
When I'm home eating snacks, I bring
a little vacuum cleaner to my chair
and suck up all the popcorn
that falls in my shirt as I eat.
But my favorite thing in
the world is being home
to make my son an egg salad sandwich
and walking him to the school bus stop.
Your son likes egg salad?
His teachers say he's unique.
And his mother's worried.
However, there is something that
is complicating this picture for me
in a way I do not like.
-Your boy is a liability.
-There it is.
I know it. Nico knows it. Every
low-level dope dealer, bookie,
or small-time asshole up and down the
Midwest circuit of assholes knows it.
And so do you.
So I need to talk about John.
Why don't you talk
to John yourself?
I thought this was your job.
I, uh... I met
John when I was 15,
right before I was extricated
from what social workers describe
as a high-profile case.
My high-profile case was that my foster
father, trying to make some extra money
to score some dope, was trying
to sell my ass to some scumbag
in a parking lot of a 7-Eleven.
Don't worry. It didn't happen.
It didn't happen because someone
happened to see a crying girl
trying to escape a car with two men who
very much fit the description of scumbag.
-And that person was John.
-Was John?
And instead of dope, my foster
father and that scumbag were dragged
from that car and beaten within an
inch of their life by a kid who...
by a kid who, up until recently, was by
my side for the better part of 15 years.
-That's loyalty.
-Yeah.
Respect that.
I just think maybe your
loyalty to your boyfriend
is threatening your
100% success rate.
Maybe you'll like this.
That job you mentioned, the
one you found so impressive,
that was two police helicopters,
five news helicopters
and eight staties on
our ass by the way.
I guess I have to
update the Wikipedia.
You might wanna jot down that
it was John driving that night.
Not me. Because I had two bullets
in my neck and was unconscious.
Thanks to him, I'm sitting here,
like you said, talking to you.
And that's the big
black tits of John.
Let's have a good week.
-All good?
-As long as my union rep's taken care of.
Said he's excited about breaking
ground on an in-ground swimming pool.
That fat fuck can swim?
Oops.
Oh, no.
-What are you guys doing?
-What happened?
Come on. You can't do...
I can't believe this.
Like I promised, same exact car. Tits to
balls. No one's gonna suspect a thing.
I see you're putting
that GED to good use.
You piece of shit.
Fuck you, Mikey.
Yeah, twice is enough for me.
I hired her 'cause,
you know, she's smart.
-Yeah, you fuck your mom.
-Yeah, whatever.
-Yeah, fuck you.
-What a fucking slut.
Jesus. I'm on a sales call.
Yeah, right. That guy
makes as many car sales
as I make child support
payments. I don't.
Uh, what did I say,
huh? Tits to balls.
Tell you what, I'll, uh... I'll take a
little something off for you, all right.
Oh, the security cameras,
they have night vision, yeah?
What are you saying? Ow.
You wanna drive in the dark?
She's saying if we switch the cameras to
night vision mode when the lights are on.
We put the cameras in the dark.
So what are we gonna
do about the gas tank?
-I don't know.
-What?
There, it's empty.
All right, well, fuck
off. Go get to work.
What is that? Kevlar?
You're dead in the
water, homey. Dead.
Whoo-hoo! Go, baby, go!
I'm going to bed.
I don't know if you saw, but
there's a sweet amount of per diem
in these envelopes.
Yeah, I'm still going to
bed, and you should too.
-All right. Whose room?
-That's very funny.
Is that who I think it is?
No fucking way.
Perm Walters.
Edith Meaney. Child.
-Oh, it's been a minute.
-Uh-huh.
I'd like you to meet my date
for the evening. Gloria.
It's an honor.
Pleasure. A thrill.
Now join our little party.
Yeah.
Please.
-So the competition.
-Not anymore. I thought you'd be grateful.
Grateful? For what?
For leaving you with the bulk of the
business. I heard Nico's keeping you busy.
Well, if you feeling entitled
to a thank you, shit, thank you.
And since you ain't working in the
morning, let me get you a drink.
A shot.
-No, thank you.
-Why?
You got some other obligations
requiring you to keep shipshape?
None for me. You?
Nah.
Just here celebrating the purchase
of my girl Gloria's new vehicle.
Ain't that right, baby?
Yeah. My baby's taking
care of me. Vroom.
Oh, shit. Here it come.
I seen them make one of these
on the hotel TV last night.
-Hey, what's this called again?
-A Wildfire.
-Wildfire.
Watch this.
-Ooh, shit. It's beautiful.
-Ooh!
All right, Gloria. Baby,
let's blow 'em out.
-Okay.
-There you go.
-Cheers.
-Big sip now, Mama.
-Whoo!
-Damn, that's... good.
That's weird.
I thought you'd avoid fire considering
all that shit on your face.
Ain't nobody ever teach you that it's
rude to point out other people flaws?
-Rude.
-I never did get the story.
-What was it? A car accident?
-I don't get in car accidents.
What then?
Let's just say the
cost of doing business.
Which reminds me. I owe
you one. Don't I, John?
Well, we can always take
this outside, Freddy Krueger.
Nobody has a sense
of occasion anymore.
Old friends threatening
fisticuffs in nice hotels.
So what is the occasion, Perm?
Only time I seen my pops in a
suit was the day they buried him.
Looking the best he's ever
looked for about an hour or two.
Then they closed that
box, covered it in dirt.
Nothing to celebrate,
except his own death.
So when you ask me what the
occasion, life's the occasion.
Sun up to sun down.
That's the fucking occasion.
They can bury me in my
pajamas when I'm in that box.
Maybe I'll be the reason
someone buys you those pajamas.
Or maybe I'll buy
your ass that suit.
-Why is Perm Walters here?
-Here at this hotel?
-Did Nico put him on this?
-He definitely did.
Nico did not put
him on this job.
So it's just a coincidence that Nico's
other driver just happens to be here
on the weekend of a
job Nico put together?
Maybe he's here for the slots. Maybe he's
here for a Bat Mitzvah. I don't know.
All I do know is that Nico would not keep
me out of the loop on something like that.
Trust me.
Or don't.
Why is Perm Walters
at the hotel?
-I have no idea.
-Tell him we're getting fucked.
Tell John to shut the fuck up.
You understand that the
last time I saw that guy,
he tried to hijack my
job and shot me twice?
I do.
So you have no reason to
believe he's onto this job?
I don't think he's onto this
job because the only people
who know about this job is me
and the people doing the job.
I don't like it, Nic.
I'll ask around.
Hey, Nico. I know
you've been stressed.
You wanna know the best
thing for stress? Exercise.
So I picked you up one of these
portable seated ellipticals.
My Aunt Judy swore by it.
She used it every day until
she died of a heart attack.
I knew it. I don't trust those fucking
guys. That chaperone guy? Or fucking Gary?
Yeah. Why would Nico
put Perm on the job?
You're better than
him. So maybe not.
So it's just a coincidence?
No. No fucking way.
That's it.
-You think?
-Yeah. That's it. That's Perm's.
And it's a fucking work car.
Why would Perm let us know he's
here if he's not on the job?
You think he's that cocky?
He's wearing a fucking mink coat in the
middle of the afternoon on a Thursday.
What do you think?
So what now?
We need another driver.
I can do it. We don't
need another driver.
You have your own job to
do. I'm not risking it.
Yo, nice digs.
Yeah.
You sure this is
the right address?
That's what it said.
Well, hello. I'm Rebecca.
You must be Edie.
Yeah, hi, uh... This
is... This is John.
Nice house.
Well, thank you. We've
been very blessed.
How many square feet is it?
Um... ...I don't know.
I'm not really...
Hey. Sorry. This chair isn't
as fast as I'd like it to be.
Hi, Dad.
Eds.
Hi, Mr. Meaney. I'm John.
Right.
Heard a thing or two.
Yeah. Me too.
Yeah, I'm sure you have.
Your call caught us by surprise.
But, um, I'm grilling up
a storm in the back there.
I just hope that, uh,
dogs and burgers are okay.
Kinda short notice, but
I should go check it out.
Whoa, hey, watch out!
I almost hit you.
-Again.
-Yeah. I ran over her toe once.
They're very unforgiving of, uh,
handicapped people in this house, right?
Say hello to Edie
and John, Sadie.
-Hi.
She'll warm up eventually.
Anyway, are you guys hungry?
I am.
Whoo!
Yeah.
Sunday driver?
If that.
Every once in a while a bunch
of gear head buddies of mine
drag out the old cars and hit
the burger joint a town over.
You know, a bunch of white hairs trying
to feel like their dicks still work.
You get used to the
hand controls thing?
Like races?
Or burning doughnuts in a Dunkin'
parking lot like when you taught me?
I got, like, blown out a
couple times, you know.
And I go back a couple weeks
later, and I get so in the zone,
like I forget my
legs don't work.
I won a grand.
I thought you were reformed.
Edie, listen.
I got a job going
over at the casino.
Uh-huh.
John got into some
trouble, so...
This one of those "do
or die" kind of jobs?
I could use another driver.
Um, I got a pretty good
thing going here, Eds.
-So no?
-I'm a 50-year-old man in a wheelchair.
-That I put you in. I'm very aware.
-Hey, it's not about that.
Eighteen years is a long time
not to go get your daughter.
I was a fucking drug
addict and alcoholic.
And there was no way in hell, with your
ma gone, with what happened to my legs
that I was gonna handle any
of this shit any better.
At the time, I thought
it was best for you.
Not to mention the burden I was.
Pissin' and shittin' myself.
Needing people to drag me out
of... out of a fucking wheelchair.
It's not the life
I wanted for you.
You should've let me choose.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
What did you used to tell me when,
uh... when I got in trouble at school?
"I don't accept 'sorries.'
I only accept change."
Can you, uh, move
so I can get out?
Eds.
Edie.
I did change.
Not for me.
Why didn't anybody
ever change for me?
What?
My ma, my dad, you.
It's not like that, Eds.
How many times you been to
rehab 'cause of a judge?
-I don't know. It doesn't matter.
-Six times.
Okay. Six times.
How many times have
you been 'cause of me?
The last time I went to rehab, it
was, like, day five, or something.
I got over being sick enough,
so they took us on this boat
to, like, talk about what
made us take that first drink
or oxy or whatever.
I was getting ready for my turn.
I don't even remember
what I was gonna say,
but then I had this, like,
insane, um... What'd they call it?
Moment of clarity.
And I said, "I gotta get off
this boat and get to Edie
and tell her I'm gonna be clean
and it's all gonna be better."
And then I jumped.
I heard 'em all freaking out.
Turns out I wasn't healthy
enough to swim a mile and a half
in ice cold water in March.
When I was under there...
drowning or...
dying or whatever...
You know how they say your
life flashes before your eyes?
Well, all I saw was you.
Because you're my life.
I did everything you said.
I got clean. I stayed away from you
even though it fucked me up every day.
I tried to get jobs but...
it's like you asked me to
be this whole new thing.
This whole new person I
ain't ever been before.
That we'd never been before.
And I'm just supposed
to know how to do it.
And then I'm supposed
to do it without you?
Why couldn't you
just try it with me?
You know?
Why couldn't we
just do it together?
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Can we go?
I don't want your
dad to see me cry.
What?
I'm pregnant.
Fuck off.
-It's mine?
-Fuck off.
And I don't even know why I'm
telling you or what it means or...
-Why you're telling me?
-Really...
I'm just saying this
can't change anything.
-This changes everything, Edie.
-No. John.
Everything.
-It's a family.
-John, I don't...
That's not a thing
I think we can be.
It's what we are already. A family.
You and me. It's just bigger.
A family doesn't rob a casino.
-And no kid should ever have to...
-Then why are you telling me then? Huh?
I don't know. Because
I tell you everything.
Look... we love each other.
You know I love you.
-Yeah.
I know.
I just wish you'd stop.
Yeah, right. You just
wish you could stop.
-What are you doing?
-I'm listening for it.
It? It doesn't work like that.
-You don't know.
-I do.
You don't know.
John?
I'm gonna have to
ask you to leave.
Where were you? All
your stuff was gone.
It's in the vents. I don't trust those
fucking maids. Do you? Fuck that.
Um...
Okay. We gotta meet the, uh,
chaperone guy soon. So...
Sorry it got a little
fucked up in my pocket.
Looked fancier when the lady
made it with a bow and shit.
Don't say nothing
about the money.
I only used the money that
we won at the racetrack.
It's a baby. A gold baby.
-Mm-hmm.
-All gold all the way through, she said.
Don't say thank you or nothing.
I wasn't gonna.
You love it.
It's a thank you
for, you know...
I save your life and
I get a gold baby?
We get a baby.
Okay. We should, uh... We
should go. You ready for this?
I'm ready for all of it.
And we're back
at the Mid-Central Spring
Showdown Poker Series.
Two players battle for
$3 million in prize money
and a brand new Dodge
Charger Scat Pack.
And the flop comes.
Two, five, six.
Player leads off with 900.
Oh, my, he cold called. Thomas,
let's see our turn card. And it's...
Yeah, baby.
I heard you loud and clear
the first time. No gambling.
-I love you.
-Love you too.
Killing me, Josh. I thought
we were friends, man.
Here is our river.
-I fucking love you, baby!
-I'm gonna fuck your brains out!
Ha! Yes! Yes! Yes! Whoo-hoo!
I've seen enough.
Hey. Bitch.
Fuck's sake.
Still feeling strong, bro?
Don't you think we should
take this outside, guys?
We should take this outside.
We got a situation
in the north wing.
Hey. Hey. Hey!
Hey! Break it up!
Glass me, bitch? Huh?
Call for backup.
I'ma need backup in here...
Jump out of the car.
Step out of the car!
Shut the car off.
-Get out now!
-Shut the car off!
Go get 'em, baby.
Cut the power!
Shit.
Get out of the car!
Do it now!
Backwards it is.
Jesus Christ.
What are you doing?
Not in the casino.
Move! Get out of the way!
Think you could've pulled
up on the right hand a bit?
They didn't pay me
enough to pull back.
Get out of the car. Get
out of the car. Now!
Bulletproof.
She's headed for the loading
dock. Close the gate.
I got it.
She's coming to you.
There you are, Perm.
Jesus.
-Pull over.
-Fuck.
-I'm trying to help you, dummy.
-Pull over now!
Get the fuck out of the
way. I'm Perm Walters.
Where are you, John?
There you are.
Shit.
John!
John. Come on. Please.
John. No, please.
John. John! John, wake up!
John. John. Come
on. Please. Come on.
John. Come on.
Come on.
Where's my money, Perm?
And why can't you just
get your own jobs?
I could but the best ones are the ones
where somebody already did the hard part.
How you find me though?
I know I swept that car for
bugs for about the last hour.
You're not gonna find it, Edie.
I hid that car and
the money somewhere
where your ass
ain't goin' never...
Shit.
Hid it really close by, I guess.
You wanna make this easy?
You win some, you lose some.
Isn't that what you
do real good? Lose?
John, what the fuck
happened to your face?
Ain't nobody every tell you it's rude
to point out other people's flaws?
Oh, I like that, man.
You use my own shit against me.
But look, a man knows
when he's cooked.
Edie!
What the fuck?
Fuck, fuck, fuck,
fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Sorry.
What's the occasion now, bitch?
Seriously?
-What?
-I look like this
-and you throw it in my face?
-Such a big baby.
-Just a big... ...baby.
-Yeah. Snack.
Hey. How long before
we can have another?
Like, medically?
-Medically?
-Yeah.
Wh... What does
that even mean?
You know what it means.
I'm worried we can't afford the first one.
You're thinking about having a second?
Hey, hey, hey. It's my turn to worry
about all that stuff now, okay?
I got this.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Okay.
All right. Let's get
this money to Gary's.
When you're wrong, you are wrong.
I might owe you an apology.
Sorry, Gary.
Get in the car, babe.
Baby, get in the car.
-What did you do?
-Baby, get in the car.
What did you do?
Edie, we have to go. Now.
This is our shot.
The one we never had.
We can start over.
Edie, I can change. For
you. For our family.
-Why? Wh... Why?
-Why?
I did it for us. For our family.
Three million dollars.
That's enough to disappear.
Edie, it's gonna be okay.
It's me and you. We'll...
We'll...
Fuck.
Okay. Okay.
We'll... We'll just
take it back, right?
Hey. He'll be happy just
to... I mean, all this money?
He always liked you, right?
That motherfucker always had a soft spot
for you, so you'll... You'll just, um...
I'm sorry.
What the fuck is wrong with me!
Okay.
Hey, hey. Hey.
It's okay. It's okay.
Okay.
We're written in the stars.
With the sun and the moon.
We always come back.
All right. A little dark in
there so watch your step.
Watch my step? Been watching these
steps for 30 fucking years, Georgie.
All right. Are you hungry?
I left a rotisserie chicken
in the fridge we can pick at.
How many times you gonna
fucking eat tonight?
Step outside, Georgie.
You want some tea?
You did the right thing.
The right thing?
The best thing. For you.
And for John.
You know what I was
gonna do to him.
I'm assuming you didn't know
George put Perm on the job.
Not until now.
Seeing as there was no point
in boosting the job for me,
seeing as I wasn't
gonna get a cut.
Maybe I did.
Georgie has been stealing
from me for years.
I stopped counting how
many... How much...
But he loves me. Georgie.
He loved me more than any woman
or any wife I've ever had.
Since we were kids.
And he could never help himself.
He could never distinguish those
two things that were contradictory.
Loving me and stealing from me.
That was Georgie.
I guess I needed to
always know that there was
someone around that would
love me the way he loved me.
And now what? Who's
gonna do that now?
How many bathrooms do you have?
How many bathrooms I have? Two.
But the one upstairs,
the toilet is broken.
Get it fixed.
Get it fixed?
Why you obsessed with my toilet?
All through foster
care, even, uh...
even before then...
Before my ma...
Every house I lived in...
Some of those shitholes had,
like, six people living in 'em.
Every house only
had one bathroom.
Someone always
pounded on the door...
on the toilet while
you're in the shower.
And one day I was with my ma and we were
driving in a neighborhood like this...
Uh... I had to go. Like, go.
And, uh, my ma just knocked
on some lady's door.
I was horrified.
She let us in, the
lady that lived there.
She said to use the upstairs bathroom
'cause the downstairs one was messy.
That meant she
had two bathrooms.
Anyway, I just stayed
in there for ages.
No one was pounding on the door.
Later, my ma told me
the lady lived alone.
After that, anytime anyone asked
me what I wanted when I grew up,
I said a house
with two bathrooms.
In my fantasies or whatever, the
second bathroom would be for J...
Would be for John.
So he could keep his messy.
I could keep mine nice.
I'm still gonna get that house.
Get your bathroom fixed.
Take 10% for your troubles.
I already did. And
it's more like 20.
Eenie Meanie.
Always cleaning up
everybody's messes.
Not anymore.
Hey, Georgie? Come in here.
Hey, did you water the tree?
Bitch. I think your
Charlie-Brown-Peanuts-ass tree is dead.
Hey, I love that
Charlie-Brown-Peanuts-ass tree.
Yeah. And since you begged
for it, you should water it.
I got food to deal with.
Hi! Oh, that better
be chocolate.
Fifty percent of the time...
-...it is not chocolate.
-Do you have chocolate all over your face?
Come on in.
Oh, who's that?
Gosh, thanks for coming.
Hey.
Oh, yes, please. I will...
Hi.
John Jr!