It's currently
74 degrees and sunny.
It'll be hot and humid today,
with showers developing
and chance of a thunderstorm.
Yep, I need to go.
I'm, uh, running late.
Are you really
going to this wedding alone?
-Yeah, Mom. It's just me.
-Honey.
What?
I'm just asking him.
Are you okay, sweetheart?
Mom, I'm more than okay.
I'm fantastic.
Never been happier.
Love traveling alone.
Love being alone.
David. Be open.
I'd kick myself
if I never told my son that.
Be open. Life is better
when you're open.
-A hundred percent, Dad.
-And visit more.
Okay, will do. Love you guys.
-Gotta go. Okay. Bye-bye.
-Bye, I love you, boy.
-Okay.
-Bye-bye.
Shit, shit, shit.
Shit.
Can I help you?
-Yeah, I...
-Name?
David Longley. I rented a car.
Hold the fuck
on a moment, please.
Now, okay, David.
When I buzz, open the door.
But listen here,
because this is important.
You gotta open it a half beat
after I start buzzing.
If you try to open it a quarter
beat before the half beat,
or a quarter beat after,
the door won't open,
and we'll just have
to repeat the process,
over and over and over again
until you finally get it.
Okay.
David, I guess
what I'm trying to say is...
doors are tricky.
Sure.
Sure, yeah, yeah.
Doors are... Doors are tricky.
Agreed.
Ah...
Damn it. I didn't...
Try again.
Rushed it. Try again.
Fuck yeah, David!
Hello?
Hello, David.
Longer walk
than you thought, right?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
I'll see you
when you get up here.
Stop right there on the mark.
Slate you're name
for the camera.
Sorry, "slate?"
It just means, "Say your name."
Ah.
Uh, David Longley.
Your car will be
a 1994 Saturn SL.
A Saturn? I thought
they were out of business.
Not here.
Those the only cars you have?
They're the only
fucking ones we need.
What are you doing
with that photo there?
-Oh, your headshot?
-Yeah.
-Is this a problem?
Why?
Because I don't ever remember
taking that picture.
-And? And?
-And?
-And...
I'm not an actor.
Could you say that
one more time, please?
-Could I say what one more time?
-What you just said.
I'm not an actor?
That's it. Yeah. Go ahead.
I'm not an actor.
I think all of us
tend to act a lot, David.
I think we perform
more than we think we do.
That's not necessarily
a bad thing.
There are moments of real,
honest-to-goodness
truth in performance, right?
Sure.
I mean, maybe.
In fact, sometimes...
we have to perform
to get to the truth.
It's a more painful route,
but sometimes pain is good.
I love that.
You should say that more often
when I say the thing I say.
I will. From now on.
Thank you
for taking my note.
Now, do you want the GPS, David?
Uh, no. I'll just hook up
my phone using a USB.
There are no USBs in these cars.
There's no USB
in a Saturn SL fucking 1994.
Of course. Well, I'll just
listen to the GPS on my phone.
But what if your phone
craps out on you?
I don't think my phone will...
crap out.
It might, David.
What if it does?
People's phones crap out.
They crap out
on them all the time.
My phone's never
crapped out on me.
But what if it does, David?
Won't you remember
this exact conversation?
And won't you think,
"Fuck me. Fuck me
so very, very hard"?
I'm sorry, what is this place?
This is
The Car Rental Agency.
Do you want the GPS?
You want the GPS, David?
Sure.
Fuck yeah!
One singular sensation
Every little step she takes
One thrilling combination
Every move that she makes
Remain on
the interstate for 249 miles.
The forecast
for your wedding trip
is sunny skies
with non-stop rain.
Fun fact,
in Hawaii, they call this...
-Liquid sunshine.
-...liquid sunshine.
...you know who
One
You have arrived
at your destination.
Thanks.
Thank you so much
for coming all this way.
You joking? I wouldn't have
missed it for the world.
-Beautiful ceremony.
-Thank you.
This is Sarah.
You guys live in the same city.
-Oh, yeah.
-Oh.
Hi. David.
Hi.
-Nice to meet you.
-Where do you live?
-Uh, downtown.
-You?
-North side.
Mmm.
-Do you like it?
-Like what?
Living downtown?
Yeah.
Well, it's our wedding...
-Yeah.
-...so we're gonna leave.
You two have a good night.
Okay, have fun.
Do you want a drink?
Uh, no.
No, I'm good.
-Very well.
-Thanks.
Hi, I'm David
from the North side.
Oh, God!
-Stop!
-Stop what?
Just stop...
trying to be charming.
Why are you afraid of me?
-You think I'm afraid of you?
-Yeah.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm afraid of hurting you.
-Of hurting me?
-Yeah.
No matter how this plays out,
it probably ends
in me hurting you.
What if I hurt you?
I won't let you.
-I see. You're tough.
-I am.
-And I'm not.
-Okay.
Aren't you tough sometimes?
-Yeah, sure.
-And then other times,
you're just kind of...
mush.
-Mush?
-Yeah. No?
Maybe it depends
on the person you're with.
I don't know.
So I bring out
the tough side in you.
All the good ones do.
Do you believe in marriage?
You seem smarter
than that question.
Well, humor me for a second.
-Okay.
-Go on.
I believe
I shouldn't get married.
Fair.
What about you?
When I was a kid, six or seven,
they made us do
a picture in school.
Of what we thought
the future would look like,
and I drew a picture of me
with a bow tie and a top hat.
Three kids.
It's the truth.
That's all I wanted.
Was to be a dad and be married.
Swear to God.
You want to marry me?
I thought, didn't you just say
that you don't...
Yeah, well, I changed my mind.
Will you marry me?
Oh, man, you have destroyed
some men, haven't you?
Yeah.
And men have destroyed me.
And I'm guessing since...
you're still single,
you've probably done
some destroying of your own.
Especially with that accent.
Is it real?
-Is what real?
-Your accent.
You think I'd fake an accent?
At a wedding? Yeah, maybe.
Came over when I was 13.
Mother American, Father Irish.
Mom was homesick.
What about you?
Parents? Siblings?
-I'm gonna go dance.
-All right. Enjoy.
Okay.
-You coming?
-I don't dance.
I wish you would.
Hey.
I don't dance?
I don't dance.
Oh, for fucks sake.
Remain on interstate
for 237 miles.
Two hundred and thirty-seven
long, arduous miles.
David?
Um...
Yes?
Do you want to go on a big,
bold, beautiful journey?
Sorry, are we... Are we talking
to each other now?
David,
I'm asking you a question.
Do you want to go on a big,
bold, beautiful journey?
-Yes.
-What's that, David?
Yes, yes, I... I do.
What do you
want to do, David?
I want to go on a big,
bold, beautiful journey.
Say it again, David.
Like you mean it.
I want to go on a big...
bold, beautiful journey.
One more time, David.
With a kind of passion that
suggests that before you die,
you need to experience
what it feels like to be big.
Bigger than Earth itself.
No more of this, "We're all
specks of dust" bullshit.
Do you want to go on a big,
bold, beautiful journey, David?
I wanna go on a big,
bold, beautiful,
motherfucking journey!
Great, David.
Take the next exit
at Kiki's Travel Plaza
and eat a fast food
cheeseburger.
Hmm.
Hi, David from the North Side.
Hey, Downtown Sarah.
What are you doing here?
Having
a cheeseburger.
When was the last time you had
a fast-food cheeseburger?
Why you call
it a fast-food cheeseburger?
Isn't that what it is?
Well, yeah,
but I mean, technically,
it's a Whopper with cheese.
Okay. When did you last have
a Whopper with cheese?
I don't know, actually.
About 20 or 25 years ago.
Snob.
When was the last time you had
a fast-food cheeseburger?
I eat 'em every day.
Breakfast, lunch and dinner.
Oh, yeah?
-Mmm...Mmm...
-Huh...
Wow.
-Hungry?
-Mmm-hmm.
Mmm.
So...
So we live in the same city.
Correct.
Yeah.
-Yeah.
Are you gonna...
ask me out or something?
Would you like to be asked out?
I asked you
-to marry me last night.
-Yeah, but that was bullshit.
-Was it?
-Wasn't it?
I guess you'll never know now.
Oh, God.
The pain of early regret.
Also known as dating.
So we're not gonna date?
Wouldn't be worth the risk.
The risk?
The risk.
Pessimistic.
I'm glad we got that
out of the way.
-Yeah, thank God.
-You want an onion ring?
-Please.
-Mmm.
Delicious.
This is the only ring
I'll be getting from you.
All right, well...
Yeah, nice knowing you.
Nice arguing with you.
Did you get the GPS?
Yeah, because...
Sometimes your phone
craps out on you.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Well, enjoy your journey.
You, too.
-Bye, Sarah.
-Bye, David.
-Hey, Sarah.
-Yeah.
What I was saying...
I do dance.
You have arrived
at your destination.
I'm ready for my journey.
Pick up Sarah.
My car won't start.
Welcome
to your journey,
Sarah and David.
Do you have any clue
where we're headed?
None, whatsoever.
You have arrived
at your first stop.
Should we be
trusting the GPS?
I have nothing to lose.
Me neither.
What is that?
Excuse me.
Very bizarre.
What's around there?
Dead bodies.
Shut up.
We have to go through it.
Why?
We just do.
What do you think's
behind there?
More of this?
You think?
I don't know. Come on.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit. I know this place.
Are you gonna tell me
what's going on?
We're visiting
a preserved lighthouse
from the 19th century.
Where?
Canada.
Canada, okay.
Came here
a few years back.
On a little trip of my own.
Are you some kind of weird
lighthouse freak?
Now that you say it,
I wish I was.
Is that... That's your thing?
This is unbelievable.
Why were you here by yourself?
I travel alone all the time.
Me too.
It's funny
how the most beautiful places
make you feel the most alone.
You know?
No matter where you go,
you always
end up going
to the top of something
and looking down at something.
Most places
have a thing like that.
You know,
you go to the top and you...
you look out and you look down,
and you're supposed to have
an epiphany
about who you are and...
about your life and...
where it's headed.
Well, do you know
where it's headed?
No, Sarah, I do not.
Did you have an epiphany
the last time you were here?
No.
Felt nothing.
So you didn't take this all in?
Not even close.
What about now?
Did that really just happen?
Apparently.
A red door
in the middle of the woods.
Like, who put it there?
Next stop
is in 79 miles.
Hey, what's this all about?
Proceed to the route.
I'm talking to you.
Locked?
Yeah.
-Sarah.
-Vincent.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
-Your flashlight.
-Yes!
-Thanks.
-Enjoy.
See you on the way out, Vincent.
I'll be here.
Where are we?
We are at my favorite museum.
What are we doing here?
Probably gonna look
at paintings.
Cool.
My mom's dead.
What painting is that?
That's very funny.
She died when I was 19, but...
growing up, we would come here
at least once a month.
Vincent would let us
have the museum
all to ourselves
during closing hours.
He loved my mom. Loved her.
And then when she died,
I started coming once a week.
Yeah, and then I just got busy,
that kind of thing.
-Happens.
-Hmm.
Well, my mom's alive.
Oh, great.
Yeah. Not dead.
That is so awesome for you.
-Dad, on the other hand...
-Dead?
No. Alive.
I think my dad's alive.
I wish he were dead.
I actually went on a road trip
with my dad once.
-Oh, Yeah?
-Yeah.
We went to the, um...
Baseball Hall of Fame
in Cooperstown.
You like baseball?
What? No, he did.
Well, he "does" I guess.
Um...
And I remember
he brought this big bag
of unshelled sunflower seeds,
and I ate the whole bag
and I got sick.
So you didn't like baseball
and you got sick?
Yeah.
But...
It was actually
a really great time.
We had a great time. He, um...
When I had his attention,
he was actually pretty great.
So tell me.
Why are you single?
You really wanna know?
Yeah.
It's because I cheat.
Even when I don't want to cheat,
I'll end up cheating.
Even when the person
I'm with is perfect, I'll cheat.
Okay.
It makes me feel like
one half of me is always single
and doesn't have to give a shit
about anyone else but myself,
and so then that half...
cheats and...
gets caught.
And then all of me is single,
and that's what I'd rather be
in the first place.
Not the answer I expected.
And why are you single?
Oh...
I suppose I haven't
met the right one yet.
David, you've probably
met the right one,
like, a hundred times already.
Mmm, I wish that was true
even once, Sarah, but...
That's such
a bullshit answer.
I gave you honest fucking truth.
And you're going to give me,
"I haven't met
the right one yet."
Just because
you don't like the answer
doesn't mean
it's a bullshit answer.
You've probably given
the "I cheat" speech
a thousand times.
And I betcha anything it makes
guys want you even more.
Yeah? Any truth to that?
Sounded a little bit rehearsed.
Kind of like your top
of the lighthouse bullshit?
"The most beautiful places
"make you feel the most alone."
Oh, that's a pretty good me,
actually. I'm flattered.
In 0.5 miles,
you will arrive
at your destination.
-Oh, my God.
-Oh, shit.
Is that your high school?
Yeah, how'd you know?
Well, two reasons.
One, those could
only be high school doors.
And the second reason?
I'll tell you later.
-No, wait, wait.
-What?
Um...
You know, I'm not sure.
What?
Well, I went here
for four years,
but I don't know
who or what, when...
-You know.
-It's okay.
-High school.
-Uh...
-We'll find out.
Come on.
Oh, wow!
You've got to be fucking
kidding me.
Jesus Christ.
Hi, David.
David, what are you doing?
-Mr. Nelson.
-You're late. Come on.
No, no, no. You're dead.
-What?
-You're dead.
I was at your funeral.
It's four years from now.
I mean, look, maybe I was wrong,
but get your pancreas checked,
will you? And soon.
David, I don't know what kind
of pre-show routine
you're doing here,
but there's no time.
Curtain's in half an hour.
Half hour, everyone.
Mr. Nelson, how old am I?
You're 15.
-I'm 15.
-Cool.
-How old am I?
-I don't know. 40?
I'm gonna kill you today.
Forget four years from now.
Fucking 40?
You nervous for tonight?
Yeah. You're gonna kill them.
Yeah. Break a leg, okay?
Who's that?
Cheryl Hayward.
She, uh, plays Rosemary.
So, are you in this show?
You're in this musical?
Yeah. I play, um,
J. Pierrepont Finch.
-You're J. Pierrepont Finch?
-Yes.
What? That's amazing.
Oh, you did the show?
God, I wish. No.
Ex-musical groupie.
-Huh.
-Mmm.
After her solo, I, um...
I tell her I love her.
Oh, wow. Okay.
She says, "I don't love you.
I love Clint Whitford."
And I'm... devastated.
Who's Clint Whitford?
This fucking asshole,
prick, college freshman.
He treats her like shit.
-Wow.
-That night...
I mean, tonight, I go home
and I don't even
get out of my costume.
I go up to my playroom,
I plant myself face down
on the couch, and I cry.
You have a playroom?
I cried so hard. Jesus.
God, it feels like it...
Oh, feels exactly
like it felt that night.
-Okay, well...
-Except now I know it's worse.
No, because I know she's gonna
just destroy me all over again.
Okay, just don't...
Don't tell her you love her.
No, but I have to.
Why? You just said that you know
that she's not going
to say it back.
Maybe she will.
She won't.
-I have to.
-David?
Hair and makeup right now.
-Cool.
-Yeah.
Okay.
Break a leg.
Lights in the catwalk.
Yes!
Amy Moore.
Eddie Bora?
Why are you saying my full name?
Uh, I don't know.
But you do it
with Jennifer Hodge tonight.
-Do what?
-Do it.
You must be so excited
for David.
Oh, we're just so proud of him.
He's so talented.
He worked very hard.
Yeah. He went after it,
he deserves it.
Yeah. And he's just
a really special kid.
Just really and truly,
just special.
And talented.
Yeah, and special.
-Okay.
-Enjoy the show.
We'll see you
at the intermission.
And now,
How To Succeed In Business
Without Really Trying.
Dear Reader,
this little book
is designed to tell you
everything you need to know
about the science
of getting ahead.
Now let us assume
you are young,
healthy, clear-eyed, and eager,
anxious to rise
quickly and easily
to the top
of the business world.
You can.
If you have
education and intelligence
and ability,
so much the better.
What the fuck are you doing?
Get out there.
My name is David Longley.
I'm 15 years old,
and I'm the lead
in my high school musical.
Are you saying that to yourself
or you saying that to me?
Uh, both.
You know,
you know the bit in, um...
Bourne Identity,
where Jason Bourne
realizes that he can
be an assassin
without remembering
that he's actually an assassin?
What's Jason Bourne?
...lucky golden few.
You can.
This is Jason Bourne.
How to apply for a job
How to advance
From the mail room
How to sit down at a desk
How to dictate memorandums
How to develop executive style
How to commute
In a three button suit
With that weary executive smile
This book is all that I need
How to
How to succeed
Wow.
I'll be so happy
To keep his dinner warm
While he goes onward and upward
Happy to keep his dinner warm
Till he comes wearily home
From downtown
...in the head
That office chair...
-Cheryl. Cheryl.
-David...
Before we go out there
just listen to me.
Cheryl, I love you.
David, I care about you,
but Clint and I are gonna try
to make things work.
And I know
he can be awful sometimes,
but I have to try.
How did you know
what I was gonna say?
Cheryl,
we need you in the wings.
You two... You,
you break up after six months.
Okay, maybe, but that doesn't
change the way I feel right now.
But not maybe!
Not maybe.
It doesn't work.
It will not work.
J. Pierrepont Finch,
why are you
looking at me that way?
J. Pierrepont Finch,
why are you
looking at me that way?
He breaks your heart.
Clint. He...
He cheats with Amy Moore
during Easter break.
David, what are you doing?
Ooh, boy.
You marry Tate Chandler.
And then you divorce
Tate Chandler.
-Cheryl...
-Stop chasing me, David.
I don't love you.
Well, would you look at that?
It's five o'clock.
Well, here it is 5:00 p.m.
The finish of a long day's work
And there they are,
both of them
The secretary and the clerk
Not very well acquainted
Not very much to say
But I can hear those
Two little minds ticking away
I should have understood.
Now, she's thinking
I'm so sorry. Cheryl.
Cheryl, I'm sorry.
Now, she's thinking
-Cheryl? Cheryl, are you okay?
-Cheryl?
Now, she's thinking
I wonder if
we take the same bus
And he's thinking
That could be
Quite a thing between us
Now, she's thinking
He really is a dear
And he's thinking
But what of my career
And she says
Ah
And he says
Well, it's been a long day
-Well, it's been a long
-Been a long, been a long
-Been a long day
Well, it's been a long
Been a long, been a long
Been a long day
-Again?
-Sure.
Well, it's been a long
Been a long, been a long
Been a long day
That was fuckin'...
How did you know?
What can I say?
A good musical groupie
always knows the songs.
Thanks for the save.
You're welcome.
Ah.
It's actually
the second reason I knew
that those
were high school doors.
I'm secretly a dork.
You're secretly a dork.
Not so secret.
Yeah, not anymore.
High school's really fucking
important to dorks like us.
It's pretty formative.
It's formative as fuck.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
You were
different back there.
How was I different?
Very...
heart on your sleeve.
Mmm.
Yeah, that was me back then.
Back when I thought that the...
Go on. Thought what?
Back when I thought
that everything
would work out for me.
That I'd get what I want
and that I'd be... happy.
Because you're so special?
Where'd you hear that?
Nowhere.
I saw you sitting
behind my mom and dad.
They may have mentioned you
being special, like...
30 times.
I swear to God, if I could
go back to me as a kid,
I would say,
"David, you little prick,
"you're not that special.
Get over yourself."
-Would you?
-I would, actually, yeah.
Yeah, I mean,
it just causes you...
It sets you up
for a spectacular fall.
So what is it that you want,
David?
What do you mean, Sarah?
Are you still...
chasing the Cheryls
of this world?
You know, it's been a long time
since I've felt that anyone
was worth the chase.
Are you chasing me?
Because if you are,
you should just stop.
Seriously, David,
I'm just gonna end up
disappointing you,
like everyone else has,
so, you should just stop.
What are you doing?
I didn't mean stop the car.
Okay, this is getting
too dramatic.
Sometimes we have
to perform to get to the truth.
Doctor Morgan,
please call recovery.
Hi, Sarah.
Hi, Dr. Vernon.
How's everything at school?
I think at this point,
I was having an affair
with my professor.
-Uh, can we just get to it?
-Sure.
Your mom passed away
about an hour ago.
Was she comfortable?
She was comfortable.
-No pain?
-None.
-You fucking swear?
-I fucking swear.
-Did he...
-No.
Your father hasn't been here
in months.
So, she was alone when she died.
I assure you,
she was on a lot of medication.
So, she was alone when she died?
Yes.
Do you want to see her?
Can I just have a minute?
Absolutely.
It was kind of messed up
that I had to relive
my high school musical.
Which you kind of nailed.
I did nail, yes.
But it seems really unfair
that you have to relive
the moment
where you're told your mom died.
I'm not reliving this.
This is happening
for the first time.
I wasn't at the hospital
when my mom died.
I avoided it.
Do you know where I went?
Museum?
God, the fucking museum.
Sarah, that's...
That's kind of beautiful.
Your mother's
favorite place in the world.
It's kind of beautiful.
I'm horrible.
Uh, not even close.
I... Then you don't
know me very well.
Actually, not...
You're... You're...
You're magic. You're a lovely,
formidable force,
is what you are.
Listen to me.
I'm a fucking coward.
Nope. You're here now.
-I'm a fucking coward.
-You're here now.
Yeah, but that doesn't,
-it doesn't count now. It's...
-Why not?
Because it...
It's not real!
This isn't real!
Well, it sure as shit...
feels very real.
Every part of it.
David.
I wasn't at the museum
the day my mom died.
I really...
really love that
you thought that,
and I wish it were true, but...
I was...
screwing my professor.
That's what I was doing.
And she died alone.
Mmm.
I better do this.
Dad.
All I'm thinking
about right now
is the time that Big
was supposed to play on TV
one night after swim practice.
And I remember saying to you,
"Mom, what I really want
is to come home
"from swim practice
"and eat mashed potatoes
while I watch Big."
And do you know what you said?
Without hesitation.
Without a hint of annoyance.
You said,
"Of course, sweetheart."
And you must have been so tired.
But you were never
going to say no.
That word just
never crossed your mind.
It was always,
"Of course," with you.
You just...
gave...
so easily.
-Is everything okay?
-Yeah.
Yeah.
No, not really. But...
it's just...
my son.
My son, uh,
was born prematurely.
Well, I'm... I'm...
I'm sure he's gonna be okay.
There's some complications.
We were just told this morning.
What complications?
What's wrong?
His heart.
There's some...
problems with his heart.
It's called PDA.
Patent ductus arter...
something.
Did they say
if it's fatal?
Yeah, it can be.
He'll... Hey, he'll survive.
Well, thank you for saying that.
Seeing my...
son trapped in that incubator.
If he dies in there
and if I'm not able to hold him,
I don't know what...
What we'll do.
It's gonna be all right, Dad.
It's gonna be all right.
"Dad"?
You... Well,
you're a dad, right?
Actually, I am.
We tried to have a child
for a long time.
And then we were fine with it.
And then she got pregnant.
At 40.
And the next thing you know,
our little David was born.
Do you have children?
No, I don't.
My friends tried to explain
what it's like, but...
it's impossible.
And annoying.
The minute that I saw my boy...
my world changed.
Do you think...
that you'll tell him
about all this?
You know,
with the complications.
My wife and I made a promise.
If he survives,
we'll do everything we can
to protect him
from shite like this.
Excuse my language.
Nah, nah.
We won't tell him.
He'll only know
that he was perfect,
and that he's everything
we ever wanted and hoped for.
That he's...
Special.
-Yeah, special.
-Mr. Longley.
Your wife is asking for you.
I need to go.
Thanks for listening.
Yeah.
Hey.
Yeah?
You're a good dad.
That's all I want.
Just a chance.
I met a boy, Mom.
I really wish
I could talk to you about it.
He's here now.
I think if I let him,
he might always be here.
Who are you?
I'm the guy who buys gifts
because he doesn't know
what else to do.
The Renoir painting from before.
That's my mom's
favorite painting.
Hmm. It's a beautiful painting.
Yeah.
She always liked how helpful
a girl who's not playing is.
She's like turning the pages.
It's like a selfless act.
Your mom sounds cool.
You know, we're not taking
any of this with us.
Oh, sorry, you...
thought these were for you?
Uh, they're for my girlfriend.
Oh, for your girlfriend?
Yeah.
She's really...
bad for me.
It's what I go for.
Fuck her.
-We will be taking this guy.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. See, yeah...
-All right, yeah?
...he's just perfect.
Hold your breath.
What?
My mom would do this thing when
we were in the car together.
She would shout,
"Hold your breath," randomly,
and then we would
hold our breath
and see who can do it
the longest.
-Hold your breath.
-Okay.
You win.
I didn't take a big enough...
Sarah, you're gonna pass out,
and I'm gonna have to give you
the kiss of life.
Ah.
She wants me
to give her the kiss of life.
I think I just saw God.
Congratulations,
Sarah and David.
You've earned a break.
You'll arrive at the scenic
overlook in 21 minutes.
Yay. A break.
What's happening?
I am gonna change.
Okay, no peeking.
Yeah, of course.
Okay, but if I move the mirror,
it's just to see
out of the back of the car.
And maybe,
just a little bit of your face.
There you are.
I don't know
if I trust the angle
of that mirror right now.
Just the face.
Just the face. Just the face.
Hey, can I tell you
something I just thought about?
Yeah.
And I've never told anyone this.
When I was a kid, my mom left.
Oh.
Yeah, no, it's...
I mean, it's fine.
She came back.
She wasn't gone long.
But the strange thing was my dad
never said a word about it.
You know, I kind of...
I'd forgotten it.
Oh.
Yeah. Yeah, I was small, and...
I knew it wasn't good.
I'm sorry.
I know I said my parents
always worry about me,
but I actually always...
I always worry about my dad.
Yeah.
Well, thank you
for sharing that with me.
Well,
thank you for letting me.
Do you think life is short?
Mmm.
Go on.
I don't know. It's something
I've been... thinking,
and I just wanted to hear
my mouth say it.
I don't think life is short.
People say it, you know.
"Life is short. Have fun."
But...
I have to say, for the last
ten years or so,
life has felt
pretty damn long to me.
I agree.
-You do?
-Yeah.
Life only feels short
when you're moving forward
with something
that you don't want to end.
Right. Yeah, yeah.
I haven't moved forward
with something in a long time.
And how does...
How does it feel now?
It's may be feeling
a smidge shorter.
Yeah.
Okay,
how is this a break?
Are we looking down
at ourselves right now?
I think so.
-This is so...
-Beautiful.
I was gonna say strange,
but yeah, that too.
Beautifully strange.
It's strangely beautiful.
Hmm.
When was the last time you were
at a wedding with someone?
Oh.
It's... been a while.
Same.
And what do you think
would have happened
if we had gone
to that wedding together?
Hmm.
Well, I guess we would have
known we were together
-and that would have been...
-A comfort.
Yeah.
I never liked coming
to these things alone.
At some point, you would have
gotten me a drink...
Yeah.
...and
I would have felt...
Yeah.
-You would have felt what?
-I would have felt...
-taken care of.
-You would have been.
Yeah.
What's your drink?
White wine.
Dry.
Very dry.
-Like rocks.
-Like dryer.
Would we have danced
at this wedding?
-You don't dance at weddings.
-I do in this scenario.
-Oh. Okay.
-Yeah.
We're rewriting the rulebooks.
Then we would have danced.
God, it sounds like
we're having a good time
at this wedding.
God, we're having
a great time at this wedding.
Does it make you nervous?
How lovely a time we're having?
A little.
-You?
-Very much.
But I'm okay with it.
Why?
Because I prefer
to feel nervous with you
than feel nothing alone.
That simple.
Are you taking it all in
this time?
You have arrived
at your next stop.
Shite.
-Do you know that door?
-Yeah. You?
Yeah, I used to go there
all the time.
Me, too.
I don't
wanna go in there.
Me neither.
Pass.
You have arrived
at your next stop.
I think now
would be a good time to tell you
I was engaged once.
Okay.
I think now would be
a good time to tell you
I'm a fucking monster.
All right.
Yeah.
Hey.
Here.
I'm so sorry.
Two people saying sorry
at the end of a relationship.
Well, it doesn't get
more boring than that.
Are you sure
you wanna go through with this?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm sure.
Because...
And I know this might make me
sound weak or whatever.
-No, you're not weak.
-It's fine.
But just say the word, and...
we can just forget about this.
And you can put that ring
right back on my finger,
and we can just move on.
Together.
You're gonna love this.
I, uh, upgraded our room.
Check it out.
Oh, wow.
-It's gonna be so great.
-It's lovely.
I also made
a reservation at your...
your favorite restaurant.
-Great.
-Yeah. And I made sure
they had the very, very,
very dry white wine.
-Thank you.
-Drier than dirt dry.
Why didn't we work?
Why did this end?
Just...
wasn't meant to be.
That's such bullshit.
"Wasn't meant to be"?
Wait, you... you didn't say that
when this happened.
Why did you lose
interest in me, David?
You didn't say that either.
...thing where I pick out
your outfit for the night.
I leave you tonight.
What do you mean?
When you're asleep,
I leave you
in the middle of the night.
And when you wake up...
you have no idea
where I am, and you're...
worried sick, and you text
and you call and...
I block your number,
and you never
hear from me again.
-Tell me why you lost interest?
-I don't know.
Jesus Christ!
When did you start
stabbing people?
You chased after me so hard.
Won me over.
When you finally had me,
-what happened?
-I was underwhelmed.
-What happened?
-I was overwhelmed.
-Felt disappointed.
-Didn't wanna be disappointing.
Thought of coming home to you
every day made me...
Break out into hives.
-I wasn't happy with you.
-Or me.
-Or us.
-Blah, blah, blah.
-Blah, blah, blah. Dig...
-Deeper.
I thought we just dug
fairly fucking deep.
Okay.
I'll go.
At first, I was really into you.
I thought I'd met my match.
Someone just like me.
Someone who wanted
to have fun and not care.
Someone...
who knew that
this was all bullshit,
and that it wasn't gonna last.
And then you changed.
You started to care.
Really care.
Because I fell in love with you.
Yes! That!
I didn't ask for that.
It was too much.
I loved you too much?
Yes. Yeah.
No.
So you leave me
because I love you.
No, I leave you because...
Because you love some version
of me that's not me.
And you don't...
You don't know me.
You never really knew me.
And that's my fault?
And what about you?
Hard pass.
I, um...
I genuinely believed
that I could make you happy.
And that's all I wanted.
That hope is everything to me.
Means that every day
that I'm pursuing you and...
I'm pleasing you is beautiful.
You know, it's meaningful
until I have you.
And then, it all...
becomes meaningless.
And then, I start feeling...
myself again.
You know, the me that I was...
before we met.
Except this time,
I'm more tired.
And then I wake up one morning,
and I...
I'm about as fucking empty
as I have ever been.
And...
you'll never make me happy.
That's very, very cruel.
No one's good enough for you.
Deer incoming.
What?
Oh, shit!
Come on.
Crap.
-Sabotage!
-Huh.
You know how to fix
totaled cars?
I do not.
How about burning cars?
Well...
we're good at destroying things.
Apparently.
-David?
-Yeah?
Let's not do this.
Do what?
This. Let's...
I don't want to be the girl
sitting in a café,
holding a ring,
wondering when
you lost interest in me.
I don't want you to be the guy
that I leave
in the middle of the night.
Let's just...
end this before
we hurt each other.
Why are you so certain
we're gonna hurt each other?
Were you not paying attention
back there in the café?
That... that's just who we are.
That's who we were.
It doesn't mean
it has to be who we are, Sarah.
I mean, this whole journey...
I think it's a... it's a chance,
you know, for us to be open.
I mean, life is...
Life is better when you're open.
What does that even mean?
It means... It means... Um...
It means, I love you.
What?
Yeah. I love you.
-No, you don't.
-Yeah, I do.
-You don't. You don't...
-I'm sorry, I do.
You don't know me.
You...
-You don't.
-Yes, I do. I know that you...
I know that you feel like shit
that you weren't there
when your mother died.
I know that you've never been
able to forgive yourself for it.
I know that you cheat,
so no one else
can hurt you first.
And that you leave,
you know, when you feel like
you're being loved too much.
I know you, Sarah.
But I also know that you love
eating fast-food cheeseburgers,
and I know that you love
traveling alone like I do.
I see you, Sarah.
I see you.
And I love you.
And not some idea of you.
I love you, all of you.
Maybe you feel that way
right now,
but what about tomorrow?
What about next week?
What about next month,
once you...
Once you have me?
Really have me?
-Then what?
-Then we have a cup of tea.
We keep it...
We... we lie on the grass,
we read books.
We dance, Sarah.
We just... We dance.
I mean, that life
that we imagined up there.
-It was a fantasy, David.
-I refuse to believe that.
It's a thing we made up.
I refuse to believe that.
Because this
is what you do. You do this.
You, like, relentlessly
chase after someone,
because you think
they're gonna make you happy.
And then when you get them,
you don't want them anymore.
No, no, no, no. Yeah,
I've done that in the past.
But that's not
what this is about.
This isn't about
the chase, Sarah.
It's not about using you
as a distraction
from my bullshit.
It's not even about being happy.
It's about...
It's about believing.
That's what this is about.
For the first time, maybe, ever.
It's about believing
that it's possible.
What is?
To share a life.
It's just...
not worth the risk for me.
I'm sorry.
I mean, it's...
It's okay.
I don't want to upset you.
Thanks for the clothes.
I, uh...
I fixed your exploded car.
How?
It happens more than you think.
Why did you have to fix it?
Because there's more to do,
isn't there?
Yeah.
These are a gift
from the car rental agency.
But it's not raining.
-Okay.
You'll arrive
at Kiki's Travel Plaza
in 21 miles.
Drop off Sarah.
Sarah,
are you ready to continue
your big, bold,
beautiful journey?
Uh...
No. I...
I'm done.
You can do this.
In 500 feet, take exit 57.
I said I'm done, motherfucker.
I'm done.
Sarah, come on.
Take the next exit, 58B, and...
No.
Recalculating.
Come on, Sarah.
Let's finish this out.
In 1.5 miles, take exit 59-A.
Shut up!
Shut the fuck up!
In 1.5 miles,
take exit 59-A.
Thanks, I just...
I just need to go home.
I just wanna go home.
All right, Sarah.
You'll reach home
in one hour and 33 minutes...
-Okay.
-...with normal traffic.
Thank you.
Recalculating.
I just wanna go home.
All right, David.
You'll reach home
in one hour and 33 minutes
-with normal traffic.
-Thank you.
You are home.
Wrong home, asshole.
There's a bug like an angel
Fuck.
Stuck to the bottom
Of my glass
With a little bit left
As I got older
I learned I'm a drinker
Sometimes a drink
Feels like family
Family
Hey, what's the matter?
Where'd you go?
-Uh, for a walk.
-You're wet!
He's... he's upstairs.
-Who's upstairs?
-Our son.
-Our son?
-What's wrong, honey?
"Honey"?
Sorry, how old am I?
You're 57.
Fifty-seven.
-What's this all about?
-I'm Dad.
Yeah, you're his Dad.
And he needs you right now.
That awful girl crushed him.
She's not an awful girl, Mom.
Uh, darling.
-Just go talk to him.
-Okay.
Break you right back
Ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh-ooh
When I'm bent over
Wishin' it was over
Makin' all variety of vows
I'll never keep
I try to remember
The wrath of the devil
Was also given him by God
Ooh, ooh
Ooh
Mom?
Oh. Hey, kiddo.
-Hi.
-You're not dead.
Well, what the hell
kind of thing is that to say?
Oh.
Mom.
Oh, oh.
Hi.
-Everything okay?
-Hey, how old am I?
Did you hit your head
or something?
Just, how old?
You're 12, silly.
I have
the mashed potatoes ready.
Let's eat.
Mom?
I know how tired you are, but...
What is it, honey?
Would you mind
watching a movie with me?
Of course.
Do you think
I'd let you watch all alone?
Jesus. That's pathetic.
Dad?
Dad.
Yeah.
I'm your... dad.
Are you disappointed in me?
No.
No, I'm... I'm...
I'm sorry you're hurting.
It sucks.
Do you
remember when...
Mom was away in the States?
I was 11.
It was just you and me
for a month.
Yeah.
I never told you this before.
I heard you crying one night.
It was late,
and you were sobbing.
I didn't know what to do.
I'd never heard you cry before.
And I wanted to comfort you,
but I was...
Scared?
Yeah.
I wanna go home.
I miss my family, Susan,
and I wanna go home.
Oh, my God!
You're married!
-No!
-I knew that this was...
Hmm.
-Mom?
-Mmm?
What is it, sweetheart?
Can we pretend that I'm older?
Mmm.
-You're good at pretend.
-Yeah, I know.
I want you to pretend with me.
That sounds fun. When?
Now.
-Now?
-Yeah, right now.
Okay.
Begin pretending to be older.
I'm bad with men, Mom.
You're really getting into it.
Where did you even
hear that phrase, sweetheart?
Just pretend...
pretend with me, okay?
I'm bad with men, Mom.
-Now why would you say that?
-'Cause I am.
So am I.
I know.
Why?
Why is that?
Oh, I wish I knew.
I wish I knew.
I'm still trying
to figure that out.
It's okay. It's okay. I know.
When I'm sad,
or angry,
it feels like the world
might fall apart.
That's the world, David.
You know, it's messy,
it's shitty.
It's full of uncertainty.
But... they try
to protect you from it.
They made a promise they would.
-They?
-Uh, we.
We made that promise.
For better and for worse.
And maybe...
Maybe it was for worse.
I don't know.
Your mom and dad love you...
very much.
Yeah.
I have to leave
in the morning.
Well, I know.
For school.
We're still pretending.
Oh, okay.
Where are you headed?
To the city.
Wow. Miss Big Shot.
I'm gonna miss you.
I'm gonna miss you so much.
I'm scared I'm not gonna
be a good adult, Mom.
You know, sweetheart,
you are capable
of being content in this life.
You just have to choose it.
What about being happy?
You can make yourself crazy
trying to be happy.
Be content first.
Choose to be content.
And enjoy
the moments of happiness
that come from that.
Okay.
Can we stop pretending now?
Why?
Because I want you
to tuck me in.
-Snuggy bunny.
-Night.
Good night, sweetheart.
Bye, Mom.
Fuck, yes! Still got it.
You win!
When did you get
so good at this game?
-Wanna play again?
-No, I'm actually... exhausted.
Oh, there's something
I've been wanting to...
tell you for a while now.
What is it?
You should know that...
you're special.
You tell me that all the time.
Yeah, I know.
Love is funny
Or it's sad
Or it's quiet
Or it's mad
It's a good thing
Or it's bad
But beautiful
Did your phone
crap out on you?
It did indeed.
Ah! I told you.
You would have been fucked.
Oh, I was fucked anyway,
many times over.
But I think it worked out okay.
Did you meet anyone on the way?
Is that what you,
um, you do here?
You rent cars and fuck lives?
-Hey. Hey, hey.
-"Fuck lives"?
No... I just...
Is this some kind of...
soulmate service?
-Oh, I like that.
-Me, too.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Some service
that would just find
the exact right person for you?
Would make life so much easier.
It would.
So, you weren't trying
to match me and...
Stacy Dunn.
No, she never picked up her car.
What is this still doing here?
So, Sarah was...
Oh, she came last minute.
Fortunately,
Stacy's car was available.
Sarah made a good understudy.
I love that!
Me, too.
She hasn't been back yet? Sarah?
No.
Thank you.
Anytime.
You have arrived
at your final destination.
Please return your car.
Is this my destination?
It depends, Sarah.
How do you want this to end?
How'd you find me?
GPS.
Ah.
I wanna say something now and...
it's something I've been
thinking, and I just...
want to hear my mouth say it.
Um...
You are worth the risk.
I know you might hurt me and...
I mean, I would be devastated
if you left me
and I would be devastated
if I left you first.
And I know
both things are a possibility.
And that scares me deeply.
You might think
you know how deep,
but you don't.
But if anyone ever were to know,
I would want it to be you.
I think...
I think we could
be content together.
And in love.
Because I am in love with you.
When people keep repeatin'
That you'll never fall in love
When everybody keeps retreatin'
But you can't seem
to get enough
Let my love open the door
To your heart
You got one more door in you?
-I could do one more door.
-Come on.
Let my love open the door
To your heart
I got the only key
to your heart
That can stop you fallin' apart
Try today, you'll find this way
Come on
And give me a chance to say
Let my love open the door
It's all I'm livin' for
Release yourself from misery
There's only one thing
Gonna set you free
And that's my love
That's my love
My love
All the lives I've lived
I'm ready to forgive myself
Deep lake diving in
My love could re-begin
Again
Part of me is missing
I doubt you see
How helpless I feel
Fragile, my heart
I long to be held
I long to be loved
Might be a myth
But I'll take the risk
Such a lonely road
Found a kindred soul
Like I knew you from somewhere
Like magic in the air
Now I see you everywhere
Part of me is missing
I doubt you see
How helpless I feel
Fragile, my heart
I long to be held
I long to be loved
Might be a myth
But I'll take the...
Rewrite my elegy
Childhood memories
Fall in love with me...
Inside my symphony
Fragmented parts of me
Dance in the...
What if we were meant to be?
If we don't jump
We'll never know
Part of me is missing
I doubt you see
How helpless I feel
Fragile, my heart
I long to be held
I long to be loved
Might be a myth
But I'll take the risk
I'll take the risk