[Frogs Croaking,
Crickets Chirping]
[Thunder Crashes]
[Woman] Oh, thank you.
They're pretty peaches.
- Yes, ma'am.
- So, how you been ?
I'm pretty good,
I reckon.
You had any health problems
since I saw you last ?
- Ma'am ?
- Have you been sick ?
Well, back's been
hurtin' a little.
No, no, it's not your back.
Have you been
bleeding somewhere ?
Well--
- Yes, ma'am, a little.
- Yeah.
- Have you been to a doctor ?
- Oh, I--
I don't much like
going to no doctors.
Well, I think
maybe you should go.
No, it's not
a venereal disease.
I just think it's some kind of
kidney or some bladder infection.
But it's been around
for a while.
Could lead to some
more serious problems.
Do you want me
to call a doctor for you ?
- All right.
- Okay.
You kids get on to bed now.
It's nearly 9.:00.
Ah, Mama, can I stay up
just a little bit ?
No.
You heard me, mister.
- Mama ?
- Hmm ?
What does "fuck" mean ?
It's a bad word, hon,
for something nice.
But what does it mean ?
Well, it means making love.
It's how your daddy and me
made your brothers and you.
Take his turtles off, hon.
- Mike, did you hear me ?
- What ?
I said get to bed.
Oh, Mike, your lip's
dragging the floor.
- It's gonna freeze like that.
- You act like I'm a kid.
You are a kid, honey.
Valerie, you may as well
take your glasses off.
-I know he's been hitting you again.
-[ Chuckles ]
- I see your lip.
- Oh, no.
Oh, it--
it just embarrasses me.
It's okay.
Come on.
He got worse.
I went to the store yesterday
'cause we's out of some things.
And he got home from work early,
before I could get back.
He was waiting with a razor strap.
My legs are all cut up.
And I got welts the size of
footballs on my back and my legs.
I feel guilty, you payin' me money
to tell you to get away from him.
You got to get help.
- Legal help.
- You don't know Donnie Barksdale.
He'll kill me if I leave him.
He'll find me.
He said he would.
No, he's not crazy enough
to kill anybody.
He's just
an insecure redneck.
What ?
Um,
I think he's got
a woman on the side.
Yeah, he's been
laying out at night.
[Knock On Door]
Excuse me,
but the school's on the phone.
They say Mike's
in some kind of trouble.
Mrs. Wilson.
Hi. Come on in.
Have a seat.
- Uh, where-- where's Mike ?
- He's in the infirmary.
Now, it's nothing to get
worked up about. He's fine.
He's got a few, um--
Sit down.
He's got a few,
uh, nicks and bruises.
I think he might have a-- have
a pretty good black eye by tomorrow.
But he's, uh--
he's okay.
- He was in another fight ?
- Yes, he was.
His grades are, uh-- are getting
worse too. How's he doing at home ?
Um, not much better.
He's real distant.
Mm-hmm.
Well, Mrs. Wilson,
I don't pretend to be
a psychologist, but, um,
it's obvious to me that your boy's
got a lot of anger in him.
Well, um, it's about this time
last year his daddy passed away.
He's still real
messed up over it.
Yeah. I never knew your husband.
I understand he was a fine man.
Yes, he was.
Well, I don't know how you
feel about therapy, but, uh--
If you think Mike needs somebody to
talk to, I know a gentleman over--
Mike doesn't need a therapist,
Mr. Collins. He can talk to me.
Do you think he will, though ?
I'm sorry, Wayne. I didn't know
you had anybody in here.
- Oh, hi. Um--
- Ruby wasn't at her desk.
Yeah, she's out sick today. Uh,
Mrs. Wilson, this is Jessica King,
- my fiancee.
- Nice to meet you.
You too.
We're just going to be
a couple of minutes. Okay.
Uh, I gotta go anyway.
I got people waiting.
Thanks a lot,
Mr. Collins.
- I'm real sorry about all this.
- Oh, it's my job.
He's just a boy,
that's all.
You're not that Wilson that's
a fortune-teller, are you ?
I don't call myself that.
- I'd love you to read my fortune.
- I'm pretty booked up.
Do you think we'll live
happily ever after ?
[Jessica]
What's the matter?
You see something bad ?
Of course not.
No, I'm sure you'll
be real happy together.
[ TV Chatter,
Indistinct ]
[ Television Continues ]
- Hey, how you gettin' along today ?
- I'm fine, Buddy.
Except the fact I can't keep my car
door from just flying right open.
Have you got the time
to fix it ?
I-I-I can get to it, uh,
about an hour or two.
Uh, you wanna wait ?
Uh, no. Uh, I got to get home.
I got people coming.
Hey, you just want--
you just wanna leave it here,
and I'll--
I'll carry you on home ?
I can have it to you by-- probably
by 6:00. That gonna be all right ?
- Yeah, yeah, that's fine.
- All right. All right.
- Buddy ?
- Yeah ?
Uh, I'm a little-- I'm
a little low on my money this week.
-I was just wondering if--
-Don't you worry about-- No, really.
- No, stop it. Oh, come on, look.
- I feel bad.
For all that
you've done for me,
I just-- I just think
the world of you.
You're about the only one
I call a friend to me.
Thank you.
Yeah, you know.
Annie.
I'll get the truck.
Take your time.
[Annie]
How you been, Buddy ?
I've been having some, uh--
some bad thoughts lately.
But I, you know--
Yesterday, I was feeling so happy.
- Yeah ?
- I was feeling on top of the world.
Good on you.
I-I-I didn't even feel
like I needed my medicine.
I took it anyway.
[ Laughs ]
You know, I'm getting--
I'm getting hooked on that stuff.
Well, I think you're gonna have
a lot of happy days, Buddy.
Yeah, you're gonna
get better and better.
Well, uh, I believe you
when you say so.
Buddy ?
Honey ?
- Honey, what's wrong ?
- [ Exhales ]
You have to tell me.
You have to tell me now.
I'll-- I'll tell you, hon.
If I look
into a blue diamond...
and I think
a negative thought,
am I gonna die ?
No.
Mm-mmm.
You're not gonna die.
You're not gonna die,
Buddy.
[ Crying ] Oh, my God !
Oh, my God ! Oh, my God !
Oh, look--
Okay. Well, thank you.
'Cause if you had said ''yes,''
I would have to kill myself
before the sun goes down.
- Oh, Buddy. Oh, honey.
- [ Sobbing ]
You don't have
to kill yourself, honey.
- You know I'll always tell you.
- Oh, man.
- I'll always tell you, Buddy.
You're fine. You can always
talk to me, Buddy. Always.
- Oh, don't use that, honey.
- I feel embarrassed.
- No. Here. Huh ?
- Oh, no.
- I can't soil that.
- Buddy, I want you to have it.
- This one's Ben's. I don't--
- He'd want you to have it.
Thank you.
- You all right ?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm all right.
- All right.
I-I can walk home. You don't
have to drive me. You can--
No, no. No, I'm-- I'm good.
I'm good. [ Laughs ]
- Yeah ? You sure scared me, hon.
- Oh, yeah.
No, I'm all right.
I'm all right.
All right. You just take it
nice and slow.
- Nice and slow.
- [ Exhales ]
[Tapping]
[Knock On Door]
Could I help you ?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm Donnie Barksdale.
I'm sorry to bother you so late, but
I believe you know my wife Valerie.
Yes, I do.
I know who you are.
Can I come in
and talk to you ?
It's about my wife.
Something's happened to her.
What's happened ?
She okay ?
Well, no, she's not, ma'am.
Ma 'am, I promise.
I'll just take a minute.
All right.
Come on.
What's happened is she's getting
her head filled full of shit...
by a goddamn
Satan worshipper.
Or a damn good con artist,
one of the two.
I know she's been coming over
to see you and your damn voodoo.
You tell her bad things
about me, don't you ?
You ain't no better
than a Jew or a nigger.
Do you know
what this is ?
It's a voodoo doll.
I'm going to use this voodoo doll
on you, some of your own medicine.
If you don't stop
seeing my wife,
I'm stickin' me a pin
in this thing every night...
till you learn
to leave folks alone.
Go back to bed.
Everything's fine.
I bet you love those
little children, don't you ?
And I bet they need
their mama, don't they ?
- What's your name ?
- Get your ass out of my house !
Don't you threaten me or my kids.
Now, what I do here is my business.
If your wife has any sense,
she'll leave you so far behind,
you'll never find her.
Now you get out of here
before I have you thrown in jail.
Messing with the Devil
is gonna get you burned.
Everybody knows that.
I'll see you soon, boys.
Go back to bed.
Come on.
[Engine Starts]
[Tires Squealing]
- Something smells like cat pee.
- It's perfume, Ben.
And you're not supposed to cuss
in front of appointments.
Something smells like cat pee.
- Something smells like cat pee.
- Be quiet!
[ Chuckles ]
He's got a great sense of humor.
- Oh, he loves you.
- [Door Opens]
[Annie] Valerie. Oh, honey,
y-you know, you should 't be here.
I'm sorry about
the other night.
Oh, that's okay.
I can take care of myself.
And I hate
coming over here, but--
I really need
to talk to you.
Maybe you could read for me.
Under a bridge or something.
All right, I'll read for you. But
you got to start listening to me.
I can't leave him.
Don't you understand ?
Hon, he's gonna keep hurting you
till he puts you in the hospital.
I don't have anything
to look forward to.
Maybe you can
give me some hope.
Oh, Valerie, hon, I don't know
how to make myself any clearer--
- [Donnie] Valerie !
- Oh, Annie ! Annie, it's him ! No !
- Calm down. I'll call the law.
- No. No.
No, Annie, no ! If you're
my friend, you won't ! No !
I'll deal with you later,
you goddamn bitch !
You witch !
Get your ass in the truck !
That ain't fast enough !
- I told you not to come here !
- [ Screaming ]
- You let her go !
- All right ! All right !
- [Donnie] Get in !
- Mike, you stay there !
[ Donnie ]
What did I fucking tell you ?
[ Valerie ]
All right ! Ow ! Ow !
Sweet Jesus.
Mike ? Y'all bring
Miss Francis her clothes.
Thanks, hon.
Granny.
[Woman]
Hey, Annabelle.
Gran-- Granny,
what are you doing here ?
I brought you
some persimmons, hon.
Remember how you liked persimmons
when you was little ?
Hmm ?
Granny, you're not
supposed to be here.
How-- How'd you get here ?
Oh, it ain't far to walk.
Ohh !
That boy's got
your granddaddy's eyes.
Well, hon,
I better get back.
Looks like
there's a storm coming.
No, Granny,
it-- it's clear.
Uh-uh.
[Wind Blowing,
Thunder Rumbling]
Annie, always use
your instinct, honey.
@ I've been asleep
when teardrops come to stay @
@ It hurts me, but I know @
@@@It's just
my sentimental way@@@@@@
Now you tell Miss Francis
I'll be home by 9:30, okay ?
- [ Ben ] Bring back something.
- All right, I promise.
- I love you too, Mama.
- I know. And I love you too, hon.
- Be good. Bye.
- [ Boys ] Bye, Mama.
- [ Sighs ]
- You ready ?
I don't know why
I let you talk me into this.
'Cause it's time you quit
living like a nun, that's why.
Don't worry. You're going to be
the prettiest girl here, next to me.
You still a married man ?
I don't know about that.
- Oh, thank you.
- Thank you very much.
- Do we pay him now or--
- Uh-uh. I sign for it later.
- Is it good ?
- Mmm.
- Annie, there he is.
- Who ?
That guy I-- That guy I was
telling you about. Look at him.
He's right over there by the bar.
Don't he look like Antonio Banderas?
Oh, my God ! He saw me ! Shit !
He saw me staring at him.
All right, get your cards out. Tell
me if he's gonna come over here.
I don't have my cards with me.
I am off-duty.
Hello, Mrs. Wilson.
- It's Annie.
- Sit down. You're blocking my view.
Oh.
- Sorry. You remember Jessica ?
- Hi, Annie.
I didn't know you were a member
of the country club.
I'm not.
I kind of tagged along with Linda.
- How nice. It's a great outfit.
- Thank you.
- What's Mike up to tonight ?
- Moping around his baby-sitters.
Yeah ? He's--
He's a great kid.
I was actually thinking you should
have him come down to school and--
Come on, Wayne. Let's not talk
shop tonight, all right ?
- Let's just have fun.
- Okay.
- Hi there, fun-seekers.
- Hey, there.
- How about a dance with Daddy ?
- Of course I will, handsome.
[Wayne] Mr. King, I don't know
if you know, uh, Annie Wilson.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I think I've seen you at church.
- That is quite a dress, Miss Linda.
- I'm glad somebody noticed.
- You want to give it a try ?
- Oh, no. No, I don't think so.
No, thank you.
Come on. I asked you to dance,
not walk on hot coals.
When was the last time
you danced ?
I think it's so long,
I've forgotten how to do it.
Well, I'll make you look good then,
'cause I'm a terrible dancer.
[Linda]
Wayne.
I'll dance.
- Good luck.
- Yeah.
Missed your big chance.
@@@@@@[Country]
@@@ Well, I'm doin' my best not
to open with ''I love you''@@@@@@
@@ [ Stops ]
Thank you.
Ohh !
Somebody
might come in here.
I guess you
better fuck me fast.
[Jessica Moans]
You having a good time ?
- Me neither.
- [ Laughs ]
You seen Jessica around?
She up and disappeared on me again.
She's got a way of doing that.
- What do you think of Jessica ?
- She's-- She's very beautiful.
Yeah, the main thing
about her, she's just...
so full of life.
We're a little different
in that respect.
Oh.
I'm used to tennis shoes.
This kind of reminds me
when I was a kid.
I'd sit out on that porch.
I'd have so many thoughts,
just couldn't count 'em.
How'd you
wind up in Brixton ?
My husband. He got a job here
at the cable plant.
Right.
What ?
Did-- Did you know...
something was going
to happen to your husband ?
In an E.S.P. kind of way ?
- Well, I don't know--
- You don't believe in it.
I don't know.
I guess I just--
I don't believe there
are any great mysteries in life.
I kind of figure what
you see is what you get.
Well,
I didn't know that there
was going to be an explosion.
But... the night before,
I had this real bad,
bad dream, you know.
I dreamt that I was all by myself.
That Ben--
He wasn't
around anymore and...
tried to stop him going to work
the next day, but--
So you can't keep
a good man from work, right ?
Mm-hmm.
You kind
of remind me of him.
[Jessica]
Wayne ?
- I've been looking for you.
- I've been right here.
I see.
- Hi.
Let's go talk to Daddy.
He's feeling real depressed tonight.
That big deal
he's working on went bad.
Oh, we got a major crisis
here, Annie. Excuse us ?
- Okay.
- Bye.
[Ben]
See you later, alligator.
- In a while, crocodile.
- Good night, boys.
Go to sleep for Mama.
- What's that, hon ?
- Blueberry muffins.
Whatcha doin' with muffins
in your pockets ?
Miss Francis cooked them.
Yeah, but what are they
doing in your pockets ?
They're in my pockets 'cause I put
'em there when she wasn't looking...
so I didn't
have to eat them.
- Her blueberry muffins is terrible.
- [Clunking]
Uh, y'all wait here a minute.
Take Ben, hon.
[Preacher On TV,
Indistinct]
[Clanking]
When God's fighting for you,
every soldier's important.
God does not give
one to the Devil.
If every child of God
obeyed God,
the Devil cannot
wipe you out.
He cannot take you out
before your time.
If you obey God,
I don't care what the Devil...
has placed upon your life,
Jesus can deliver you.
Jesus came to bring you
out of your prison house.
- Mama, is everything okay ?
- Yeah, everything's fine.
- You sure ?
- Yeah. Time for you to go to bed.
I know him. He's
a squirrel-hunting buddy of mine.
- But I-I don't think that Donnie--
- I'm telling you it was him.
What makes you think he'd want
to bust into your house ?
Well, his wife,
she's a client of mine,
and he thinks I'm trying
to break up their marriage.
Are you ?
Listen, um,
Donnie's high-strung.
Uh, you know,
ain't no doubt about that.
But I don't think he's the one
that busted into your house.
Listen, I appreciate the coffee
and everything. Take care.
[Buddy] I just can't get through
a wall of some kind in my head...
or, uh-- or my soul.
Sometimes I don't
even know the difference...
between my head or my soul.
I think everybody
has that trouble, Buddy.
All right.
Your daddy--
He took things
away from you when you--
when you were a little boy.
Do you understand that ?
He-- He seen me playing around with
something, like a toy or something,
he'd just
take it away from me.
Did he take other things
away from you ?
[ Laughs ]
Buddy--
- Um--
- You got to find out, hon,
why you hate him so much.
My daddy's a good man.
I don't hate my dad.
He's good to Mama and me.
Every kid needs a hit with a belt
sometime. I mean-- [ Chuckles ]
Buddy, you got to try to get past
this wall that you're talking about.
Hon, you need to talk
about your daddy.
Why don't you tell me why I hate
him ? You're the goddamn psychic !
Huh ?
You're the goddamn psychic !
I think I better go.
I-I have to go home,
um,
right now.
I'm sorry
I yelled at you.
It's all right.
I-I just need--
I just need your help.
I just keep thinking about that blue
diamond. I keep thinking about--
Buddy, if you think about these
things in your childhood, hon,
and you face up to them,
then I will be able to help you.
I know, hon.
I just--
I think you got to do
some thinking on your own.
Okay.
Oh. [ Laughs ]
You-- Ahh !
- [Phone Rings]
- I'll help you there.
- Okay, you put it up there.
- Hey, Ben.
- Hello ?
- You got a lot of pretty things.
I liked looking at them.
You ever seen anybody
skin a squirrel ?
You stick a knife
in its belly and zip.
That's what I'm going to do
to you and your children...
you ever call
the police again.
I did not.
Ow ! Ow !
Ow ! Ow ! Ow !
[ Both Laughing ]
Mama ?
Hey.
- How come you're not asleep ?
- I don't know.
- What's that bat for?
- Oh.
Don't worry, honey.
I'm-- I'm just working on my swing.
How come we never go
to the cemetery and see Daddy ?
Well, we went out there
just last month on his birthday.
Honey, I'm real busy,
you know that.
Well, it seems like you have time
for a lot of strangers.
If we're talking about my
appointments, they're not strangers.
They're the ones
that put food on our table.
But how come we don't
even talk about Daddy ?
Go on, Mike.
I'm trying to read.
[ Gasps ]
[ Bell Clanging ]
- Annie ?
- We're going to have to frame that.
- It's just a painting.
- That's beautiful.
- Annie.
- Hey.
Hey, listen. I know why Kenneth King
wasn't in church today.
- Put your belt on. Why ?
- 'Cause his daughter disappeared.
-Jessica ?
- Mm-hmm.
What do you mean
she disappeared ?
Well, Kenneth woke up this morning
and Jessica wasn't there,
and her bed
hadn't even been slept in.
Annie, you think
she ran off ?
I know her and Wayne were
supposed to be married in June.
- Maybe she got cold feet.
- Maybe.
Maybe this will clear
the way for you and Wayne.
- What are you talking about ?
- Oh, come on.
I saw the way y'all were looking
at each other Friday night.
Y'all both just
had stars in your eyes.
Oh, Linda, that's nuts.
- Yeah. Annie, love is nuts.
- Come on. Go home.
[ Laughing ] Listen,
I want you to get some rest.
You look terrible, okay ?
Bye, boys.
- I got to go.
- [Boys] Bye, Miss Linda.
Ben, get your hand
out of there !
That's for y'all's
cake tonight.
-What am I gonna ice the cake with ?
-I like icin', Mama.
Yeah,
I can see that, punkin.
Miller !
Miller, hon, would you
go ask Miss Francis...
if she's got another
can of icing, please ?
- [Ben] Mama !
- I'm coming, Ben.
[ Engine Starts ]
Where you going, son ?
You wanna ride
in the truck ?
I got a question for you.
You know my wife Valerie ?
She been around
to see your mama lately ?
Hey, boy,
I asked you a question.
Get my hat.
You know, I feel sorry
for you and your brothers.
I mean, your mama
being a witch and all.
If she don't stop
her evil ways,
some day somebody's
gonna burn her up.
And then you boys
are gonna be without a daddy...
or a mama.
Hey, Miller?
You all right ?
He said mama's a witch
and they're gonna burn her up.
Oh, he did ?
- You better mind your own business.
- I intend to, Donnie.
[ Yelling ]
[Donnie]
Motherfucker!
Goddamn it! Fuck!
- Look, fucker !
- [ Cocks Gun ]
Shoot me !
Shoot me,
you motherfucker !
Shoot me ! Shoot me !
You all right ?
[Annie]
Tuscan Rouge.
What was I thinking ?
I want icin', Mama.
Hon, you've had icing enough
to put you in a coma.
And from now on,
I want to know where you all are
every minute of the day.
All right ?
Mike, I'm gonna start
driving you and Miller to school.
I wish Daddy was here.
Well, he's not, hon.
But Mama is. Okay ?
[Phone Rings]
Eat your cake.
- Hello.
- Uh, this is Kenneth King.
- Mr. King.
- I imagine you, uh,
heard about
my daughter's disappearance ?
- Yes.
- Well, um--
Mrs. Wilson,
I don't believe in what you do.
I'll just be
straight with you.
Not only that, I don't like it. But
we've got to the end of the road...
and our investigation looked under
every rock there is to look under,
and we'd like you to tell us
what you can to help us.
Now, no hocus-pocus
and chanting and carrying on.
We know you talk to a lot of folks,
know a lot of folks' business.
You might have heard
something or something.
[Mr. King]
The only thing we know is, uh,
one of Sheriff Johnson's men
found my daughter's car...
sitting out on the parking lot
of that honky-tonk called AyJay's.
But nobody that was there
on Saturday night...
admits to having seen her.
So I'm afraid she might have been
kidnapped or something ?
Oh, Mr. King,
I'm-- I'm sorry.
I don't know anything about
your daughter's disappearance.
I think
we were just hoping--
Is there anything
you can tell us ?
I could read for you.
But that-- that's
about all I could do.
I need you
to cut the cards for me.
Oh, boy.
Thank you.
All right.
You ready ?
Okay.
When were you
getting married again, Wayne ?
-June 20--
- We're supposed to ask questions,
- not you.
- Shut up, Pearl ! Goddamn it !
Look, I have a hard time
concentrating...
with more than one person
in the room.
Well, I'm staying right here. I'm
the law, and I need to hear this.
Please, ma'am, just--
just try to tell us
what you see.
I'm trying.
All right.
All right,
all I'm picking up--
it's like a--
it's a fence.
Like a split rail fence.
Do you know how many fences
there are in this county ?
And some pillars, like,
with an opening going through.
And there's lots of white flowers.
I can-- I--
Y-Yes. And, uh,
is that where Jessie is ?
Oh.
Well, that's-- that's, um, all I'm--
all I'm seeing.
This is just mishmash. I told you
this wouldn't lead to nothing.
You're right. It won't.
I can't concentrate.
- I can't do this now. I'm sorry.
- Please, ma'am.
I really do hope
you find your daughter.
But I'm-- I'm just not the person
to help you with this.
@@@@@@[Fiddle]
[ Playing Frantically ]
Hey, Butch.
[ Whimpers ]
[Annie]
And it was horrible.
But that same chain that was wrapped
around her when she was floatin',
you know, up in my tree, it was the
same chain that I had in my dream.
- I don't know. I just thought--
- Dave ?
Yes, sir ?
I could have sworn there
was an eclair in there.
- I didn't get it.
- Uh-huh.
Tim was in
a little earlier.
So you saw all this
in a dream ?
It wasn't just a dream.
I don't investigate
somebody's dream.
I think she's dead, Sheriff.
And I think she's in a pond.
What do you know about this
you ain't telling me ?
Hmm ? You can get in serious
trouble with holding information.
Does it sound like
a place you know ?
Yeah,
a bunch of places I know.
Split rail fence, a pond,
a stretch of woods.
- Every raw bone ol' boy got that.
- What about the fiddler ?
Well,
ol' Tommy Lee Ballard
plays a fiddle.
But he wouldn't kill nobody.
I've known him since he's a kid.
No, no, it's not the fiddler.
Who are his neighbors ?
Well, his closest neighbor
would be, uh--
Well, let me see here.
I guess-- [ Inhales ]
Well, his property borders,
uh, Donnie Barksdale's place.
Do you know
Donnie Barksdale ?
Ma 'am ?
Tim ! On the gate !
[Mr. King] You did get
a search warrant, didn't you ?
I want everything
to be legal and proper.
Didn't have to.
Got permission from the owner.
Donnie Barksdale
gave you permission--
His wife did.
I told her it was routine.
We're checking all the ponds
in the county.
[Sheriff Johnson]
Donnie's gone fishing today.
[ Chattering ]
[ Valerie]
Excuse me. Sheriff Johnson ?
- How much longer y'all gonna be ?
- Long as it takes.
All right. You just said you're
gonna be a few minutes.
And we're
going on two hours.
Hey, Pearl !
I think I got something !
False alarm.
It's just an old bicycle.
None of y'all brought a Thermos
of coffee out here ?
That day at school.
You looked kind of strange
at me and Jessica.
Did you think
something bad then ?
Shit.
Come on.
- Donnie, he called. I told him--
- Pearl !
Shut your mouth !
Goddamn it, Pearl,
what are you doing on my property ?
I'm on Sheriff's business, Donnie.
I got permission from your wife.
You think I let that
little ninny talk for me ?
How'd your arm
get all scratched up ?
Stray cat. She didn't like it
when I killed her.
- Now what brought you here ?
-Just routine investigation.
We're checking
all the ponds in the county.
- I knew it was you.
- No ! You-- Uhh !
Hey ! I'm on County business,
Donnie. Don't fool with me.
- Hey, Pearl !
- What ?
- You need to take a look at this.
- Watch him.
Hault up, boys !
- It's her !
- Donnie ?
Get those hooks
out of my baby !
- Get her off them hooks ! Ohh !
- Cuff him !
- No ! No !
- Mr. King !
- No ! Ohh !
- Get an ambulance !
I think he's
having a heart attack !
- I didn't do this !
- Get him out of here !
This ain't right !
Pearl !
Bitch ! [ Spits ]
Bitch ! Bitch ! Pearl !
Come in.
Somebody might
come in here.
I guess you better
fuck me fast.
You want some coffee ?
Mrs. Wilson ?
No, thank you.
Have a seat.
Why-- Why have you
called me here ?
Tomorrow Donnie Barksdale goes
on trial for murder...
and I feel
that we have a powerful case.
In fact,
today the coroner verified...
Donnie's tissue
under the victim's fingernails.
Now, I only have one weak link
I got to worry about.
- What ?
- You.
You see, you're how we found out
where the victim's body was.
And how you found out,
well,
that might open up
a real can of worms for us.
Psychic phenomena,
E.S.P., dreams, visions.
The defense
could go to town on you.
And if that's not bad enough,
I understand there was bad blood...
between you
and Donnie Barksdale.
Yeah.
He threatened my kids.
That's what I heard. I also heard
that you threatened him right back.
Told his wife
to leave him.
Donnie's quite
a ladies' man.
Were you involved
with him ?
- What ?
- I can deal with any revelation...
right now.
But at the trial
there can't be any surprises.
So, is there anything I need
to know about you or Donnie...
or Donnie's wife
or the victim ?
No.
Will that be all ?
Yes, ma'am.
You know, Mr. Duncan,
the victim had a name.
It was Jessica King.
Mr. Hawkins, how long have you
worked out at AyJay's ?
About ten years.
Now, were you working at AyJay's
on Saturday night, April 8 ?
- Yes, sir.
- And did you see the defendant,
-Donnie Barksdale, there that night?
-Yes, sir.
Could you describe the circumstances
when you saw him ?
The circumstances were I come
outside to throw out some trash.
And do you recall
what time it was ?
About midnight,
I reckon.
Anyhow, I seen Donnie Barksdale
out there by his truck...
havin' an argument
with this white lady.
She scratched his arm
and he slapped the tar out of her.
About that time,
I go back inside.
Is this the woman
you saw with Donnie Barksdale ?
- Yes, sir.
- Your Honor, let the record show...
that I've just shown Mr. Hawkins
a photograph of Jessica King.
You just said that your attention
was drawn to the defendant's pond.
Drawn in--
Well, drawn in what way ?
Me, Wayne Collins
and Kenneth King...
went to see a woman,
name of Annie Wilson.
What made you think this woman
would be able to help you ?
Well, word around town
was that she was a,
uh--
- Well, I don't know the right word.
- Isn't it fortune-teller ?
-I guess so.
-What did this fortune-teller see...
when she looked into
her little crystal ball ?
Well, she didn't have no ball.
She had these, uh, special cards.
What did she see when she looked
into her little special cards ?
Uh, she didn't actually
see nothing then.
But next day,
she come to see me and...
told me
she had this dream.
- She had a dream ?
- Yes, sir.
She'd seen this pond and it looked
a lot like Donnie Barksdale's and...
then she woke up
from her dream...
and she went outside
and looked up in this tree.
I'm all ears.
She seen Jessica King...
floatin' in the tree,
half-naked, with a chain
wrapped around her.
Floatin' around a tree ?
Yes, sir.
Floatin' in a tree,
half-naked,
with a chain
wrapped around her.
Thank you, Sheriff.
That little squirrel,
Weems, is just mean and skinny.
Never have known
a Weems worth a damn.
Well, he was
just doing his job.
Uh, Mrs. Wilson ?
Can I talk to you for a minute ?
- Um--
- Uh, just call me later on, okay ?
- Oh, okay.
- Okay, bye.
Buddy, I got a lot on my mind.
It's not a good time, okay ?
Um, Mrs. Wilson ?
You did tell me to do some thinkin'
and talkin'. And I've been thinkin'.
What ? What ?
Can you tell me why
I do things to myself...
when I think
about my daddy ?
All right, well--
Bud, you call me later, hon,
and we'll talk, all right ?
- I need to talk to you.
- Buddy.
I've been thinking about my daddy
and I've been touching myself.
- Touching yourself? How ?
- Why do I do that ?
It's not a good time.
- Something's bad wrong with me.
- Look, Buddy--
And I-- I keep thinking
about that blue diamond.
You look into the blue diamond,
you won't think a negative thought.
I promise. Now, hon, I'm going
through a hard time myself. I'm--
I just-- I can't talk
to you now, okay ?
[Man] You're gonna burn
in hell, Annie Wilson !
Now, Mike, I know you skipped
school and went to that trial.
- How'd you know ?
- A little bird told me.
It's time you started making things
easier on me instead of harder.
- [Phone Ringing]
- I'm very disappointed in you.
- The phone's ringing, Mama.
- Second of all,
I'm gonna have to testify
at that trial tomorrow.
- The phone's ringing, Mama.
- I'm not deaf, Miller.
Let the machine get it.
Donnie Barksdale's side, they're
gonna try and give me a hard time.
They're gonna call me names
and I--
I just want y'all
to be prepared...
if you hear any bad stuff
about me, all right ?
Now, we're all gonna have to
be sticking together on this one.
[Woman]
Annie Wilson, it's Buddy's mother.
Buddy's done gone crazy.
He's threatening to kill his daddy!
He's got Odell tied up
in the backyard,
accusing him
of horrible things.
- Have you called the police ?
- He said if I did he'd kill Odell.
He wants you.
[ Buddy Sobbing ]
Hey, Buddy.
Buddy, put that strap down and
tell me what he's done to you.
I'm here, Buddy. Like you said,
you can talk to me, honey.
It's too late for that !
It's too goddamn late !
This here is a criminal.
And he's gonna be punished.
Bud-Buddy.
Buddy, it's Annie.
- You shut up ! You shut up !
- It's all right.
- Get away ! Where were you ?
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You knew everything
and you did nothing.
You ruined me.
You ruined me !
I was just a little boy, Daddy.
It got so I was embarrassed
to go to school, Daddy.
How could you do that
to your little boy ?
No, Buddy. You put that down.
No, Buddy.
You put that down, Buddy.
You put that down. You listen to me.
You get away !
You get away ! Get away !
All right, Buddy. All right.
It's all right. Come on.
Why-- Why didn't
you help me, Annie ?
What ?
Why didn't you
help me ?
- I had you for a friend and then--
- I am your friend, Buddy.
Now I have nobody.
I have nobody !
But I'm gonna--
I'm gonna kill this thing.
- No !
- No, Buddy !
No !
Help me !
- Help me!
- Look at that goddamn thing.
And you tell me what kind
of thoughts you have ?
You look!
You look
into that thing !
[Sirens Walling]
[Duncan]
Mrs. Wilson ? Mrs. Wilson.
Mrs. Wilson, your husband,
Ben Wilson Senior,
was one of the men killed last year
in the explosion...
out at the Reinhold
Cable Plant.
Yes, that's right.
And you were left with three small
children to raise on your own.
Yes, sir.
How do you provide
for you and your sons ?
I get a little bit
of money from Social Security...
as a result
of my husband's death.
And, uh,
I also give readings.
- Psychic readings.
- Yes, sir.
What does being psychic
enable you to do ?
I see things...
and I, you know--
I sense... things...
that-- well, they
hadn't happened yet...
or they were happening
someplace else.
My granny told me that I--
I had a gift that runs in my family.
And she told me that
I shouldn't be afraid of it.
I should just always use my instinct
and I'd-- I'd be all right.
So, you're swearing
before this court...
that you didn't get your information
about this tragedy...
from any other means
than your special ability ?
- Your gift.
- Yes, sir.
I'm swearing that. Yes.
- Thank you, Mrs. Wilson.
- Yes, sir.
- I have no further questions.
- [Judge] Mr. Weems.
[Weems]
Mrs. Wilson.
How many fingers am I holding up
behind my back ?
- Objection, Your Honor.
- Your Honor,
my client is sitting in this
courtroom on trial for his life...
partly because of powers
that this woman claims to have.
Now, in all fairness, I believe
I should be given the opportunity...
to test
the alleged powers...
instead of having to stand here
and take her word for it.
You have a good point.
Objection overruled.
Can everyone in the jury box
see how many fingers I'm showing ?
How many fingers,
Mrs. Wilson ?
I don't know.
You don't know ?
Seven.
Seven fingers.
That-- That doesn't
prove anything.
Your Honor, I can't do this,
you know, at the drop of a hat.
Well, then, ma'am, how about doing
it at the drop of a dollar bill ?
What are you trying to say ?
I'm trying to say maybe this special
gift of yours doesn't work...
unless you're
being paid for it.
Like they say in the army,
''No money, no honey.''
No, that's not true.
Are you aware that in Hatcher County
it's against the law...
for a psychic to set up shop
and charge people money ?
Well, I don't charge money.
You just testified
that you do charge money.
No. I accept donations.
People give me gifts.
Oh. A distinction
worthy of a lawyer.
Mrs. Wilson,
you a rich woman ?
- No.
- Why not ?
If I had psychic powers and could
read the future, I'd be filthy rich.
I'd be playing
the Stock Market.
I'd be over in Mobile
betting on the dogs.
I'd certainly warn my husband
not to go to work...
on the day I know the Reinhold
Plant's gonna blow up...
leaving three little ol' children
to be raised in a carnival sideshow.
Well, it doesn't work
that way, sir.
I can't use my gift
for personal gain.
Except for those, uh,
what you call 'em, donations ?
You've had some personal trouble
with Donnie Barksdale, haven't you ?
Yes, I have.
Just a few weeks ago, you told him--
I believe the exact words was...
you was gonna have
his ass thrown in jail.
- But he was threatening my kids.
- Ain't it also true...
that a few weeks ago in one of
those famous readings of yours,
when you were doing
your so-called E.S.P.,
you told Valerie Barksdale,
Donnie's wife,
that Donnie was just
an insecure redneck...
and that he wasn't really
crazy enough to kill anybody ?
Yes, I did say that.
Then why today are you
saying he did kill somebody ?
Wait a second.
I've never said that.
You might as well have, ma'am.
You wanted his ass in jail.
-He's on trial for his life.
-I just told the sheriff what I saw.
And how could any of us
ever forget that ?
Jessica King just
floatin' up in that tree,
naked,
with a chain...
wrapped around her.
It must be
so much fun for you.
You must be having
the time of your life...
entertaining yourself
with your dreams and your visions.
You think it's fun seeing decomposed
bodies in my tree, do you, sir ?
You think that's fun ?
Do you think it's fun I have people
trying to strangle me in my sleep ?
Now I'm sitting here
and I'm blaming myself...
'cause some poor crazy man tried
to burn his daddy half to death.
And you think I'm sitting here
having fun ?
I'm sorry, sir.
You're crazy if you think that.
No more questions,
Your Honor.
[Judge]
You're dismissed.
Like they say in Hollywood,
let's just cut to the chase.
Did you or did you not
kill Jessica King ?
I did not.
Did you or did you not see Jessica
King on the night she was killed ?
Yeah, I seen her.
Would you describe
the circumstances, please ?
Well, I'd been seeing her
for quite a while.
Would you clarify what
you mean by "seeing" ?
I mean, her and me
had been having sex.
Okay, go ahead.
Well, she called me
about 1 1.:00.
So I told her
I'd meet her out at Ay Jay's.
And I told my wife
I was going out for a beer.
- What happened after that ?
- Well, we got in an argument.
She told me she didn't
want to see me no more.
-Did she tell you why ?
-She said she was getting married...
in a couple of months and she
wanted to stop playing around.
At least
till after the wedding.
And during the course
of this argument with Miss King,
did you at any moment
strike her ?
Yes, sir.
What happened
after you struck her ?
Well, she banged her head
pretty hard when she went down,
so I-- I decided
to take her to the hospital.
- Did you reach the hospital ?
- No, sir.
Are you feeling okay ?
I'm fine.
I wanna go back.
I don't wanna go
to the hospital. Someone--
Someone might see me.
She said she was feeling better,
so I took her back to Ay Jay's.
I dropped her off,
then I went on back home.
And that was the very last time
that you saw Jessica King alive ?
- Yes, sir. The very last.
- Donnie,
are you guilty
of the charge against you ?
I'm guilty
of cheating on my wife,
of being a bad husband,
a bad Christian.
But I ain't guilty
of killing Jesse.
I swear to God.
No more questions,
Your Honor.
Mr. Duncan.
Mr. Barksdale,
you're a wife-beater, aren't you ?
I've swore to tell
the truth here today.
Yeah, I've hit
Valerie before.
I guess
it ain't no secret.
So, you admit to having a history
of violence against women ?
You also admit to having
beaten up the victim...
on the night
that she was murdered.
I wouldn't exactly say
that I beat her up.
You're the expert. You tell me.
Just how badly do you...
have to beat a woman before it fits
your definition of ''beating up'' ?
Now, your story is that you've
been having an affair...
with the victim.
But tell us why a beautiful
young woman like Jessica King...
from one of the finest
families in Brixton,
just about to be married to a good,
decent professional man...
and with a bright,
shining future in front of her--
Why would a woman like that get
involved with something like you ?
I asked her that
myself one time.
She said I was the only man
in town who knew how to fuck.
[Murmuring]
You're really disgusting.
You know that ?
- Objection, Your Honor.
- Objection sustained.
Mr. Duncan, you will refrain from
making those personal comments.
I apologize, Your Honor.
It won't happen again.
So, let's get this straight.
Let's clarify this.
You're saying it was
just a coincidence...
that on the very same night that you
physically assaulted Jessica King,
someone else put
her body in your pond ?
I'm not saying
it was a coincidence.
- What are you saying ?
- I'm saying I got framed !
Oh, well, what an original defense.
Did you think of Jessica King
as a stray cat ?
No.
Did you tell Sheriff Johnson that
a stray cat had clawed your arm ?
- Yeah.
- Didn't you just tell the court...
-Jessica had scratched your arm ?
- Yeah, but--
Didn't you tell Sheriff Johnson you
got scratched by the stray cat...
because she didn't like it
when you killed her ?
Yeah, but I was lying.
My wife was standing right there !
-How do I know you're not lying now?
-Because I'm not, goddamn it !
- It's her, goddamn it !
- Be seated, Mr. Barksdale !
She's the reason I'm up here !
She's a goddamn witch !
She's putting spells on
every-goddamn-body in town !
Witch ! Witch !
Yeah, you run !
[Judge]
I'll have order in the courtroom.
In Brixton today, a sensational
murder trial was concluded.
Donald J. Barksdale
was found guilty...
in the sex and strangulation
killing of Jessica King,
daughter of the prominent Brixton
businessman, Kenneth King.
Is everything gonna be
all right now, Mama ?
Yeah, hon.
We can get on
with our lives now.
I guess I'm the last
person you wanna see.
How you been ?
Terrible.
Annie, if you tell me to get going,
I will. I wouldn't blame you.
But I need you
to read for me.
Give me a hand.
I feel like I can't
hold on any longer.
I know Donnie's mean and everything,
but I feel real lost without him.
You know, I ain't never
been on my own before.
And I'm-I'm scared, Annie.
You don't need to be scared, hon.
You'll be fine.
You see that
in the cards ?
Mm-hmm.
Right through here.
But can you see
what-- what I'm thinking ?
Can you see that
in the cards ?
What do you mean ?
Well,
I've been thinking
some real bad, bad thoughts.
Unchristian thoughts.
Like what ?
Like--
I'm glad that girl's dead.
Jessica.
She was messin' around with my
husband and deserved what she got.
No one deserves that.
Like I said,
I know it's unchristian.
What ? What, are you
seeing something bad?
I don't know.
It's not clear.
[Woman Crying]
- Fuck you !
- [ Gasps ]
[Clattering]
Wayne ?
It's not normally
like this.
You need
to lie down.
I'm really not sleepy.
I think if you sleep,
you'll feel better.
Thank you, Annie.
Oh. It's okay.
Wayne.
I don't think
this is a good idea.
No.
It's not.
I just thought we could
forget all this for a while.
You want to,
don't you ?
I know there's
something between us.
I can't.
I guess
I still feel married.
You're not, though.
- He's gone.
- I know.
You gotta learn
to deal with that.
The same way I gotta learn to deal
with the fact that Jessica's gone.
She's dead.
Oh, Wayne,
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
I-- I don't think
Donnie Barksdale killed her.
- No, no, Annie.
- I'm really sorry.
I can't-- I can't do this.
It's finished.
I know. I wanna let
that bastard rot in jail.
- But he's guilty.
- No, Wayne.
I see it.
I see he didn't do it.
- Do you see who did ?
- Uh, I'm trying, but I-- I--
I don't know yet.
What are we gonna do ?
Well, if I had
a piece of clothing...
or maybe I could go
out to the pond or see if I--
It's not over.
Jesus.
[Thunder Crashes]
[ Knocking ]
Come on in.
Well,
what brings you out here ?
Well, I'll just come
straight out and say it.
I don't think Donnie Barksdale
killed Jessica King.
Well, sure he did.
It was an open-and-shut case.
I'm telling you he didn't.
The person that killed Jessica
is still out there someplace.
What's the deal ? The Barksdales
been threatening you ?
- No.
- I'll talk to Pearl Johnson.
This has nothing to do
with the Barksdales. Listen.
I know that Donnie
didn't kill Jessica...
the same way that I knew
that her body was in his pond.
And do you know
who did kill her ?
No.
So, what do you care ?
The son of a bitch is in jail.
I got a warning today.
I think somebody is
gonna try and kill me.
What do you
want me to do ?
Reopen the case and find out
who really did it.
- I can't. He's been convicted.
- Well, you can talk to somebody.
I've got no basis to open this case.
I'd look like a fool.
I don't give a damn
how you look.
Now, you listen to me.
I know you had
an affair with Jessica.
So how do you think you're
gonna look if people find out...
you had sex with the victim
the night before she was killed ?
Do you want money ?
No. I want you
to reopen the case.
There's a saying about
letting sleeping dogs lie.
You think you're in danger now ?
Look at it logically.
The real danger begins if this case
gets reopened and someone starts...
worrying that you're gonna have
another one of your damn dreams.
All I know is,
the wrong man's in jail.
I don't care how awful he is.
And I helped put him there.
I can't live
with something like that.
So you find a way
to reopen this case, sir.
Or I will.
Buddy !
Buddy, I'm here if you--
- [ Woman ] Hello.
- Hi, Miss Francis. I'm back.
- Good.
- How are the boys ?
They're fine. They went to sleep.
You want me to bring 'em over ?
No. No. Listen.
Could we stay over
your house tonight ?
- Sure you can. You all right ?
- Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
-[Creaking]
-Come over. I'll make a bed for you.
- All right. I'm just gonna lock up.
- Okay, doll.
- Okay, thank you.
- Bye-bye.
Buddy !
Oh ! Did you see
Buddy Cole ?
Buddy ? No. I thought he was
at the hospital over in Benton ?
- Oh, he is. Maybe I imagined it.
- Are you okay ?
I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
Ever since you told me what you told
me, I feel like I'm going crazy.
Annie, I can't stand
another night of this.
I need you
to read for me.
It's no good.
- Try it again.
- I can't make it happen.
How about
what you said today ?
What ?
The pond.
What if we did
go back out there ?
Do you think
it might help you ?
I-- I--
I don't know.
Yeah. Uh, maybe.
Yeah, okay. Well,
it's worth a try, right ?
You mean tonight ? No, Wayne.
I can't-- I can't do that.
I got my kids. It's dark.
You know, it's, uh-- it is a pol--
it's a police matter now.
How long do you think
that's gonna take, Annie ?
It's gonna sit on somebody's desk
for months. Nothing's gonna happen.
It's over for them. They've got
their man. It's up to us.
I know that, Wayne. But I'm
telling you, I don't see anything.
I can't keep running
from things.
[Thunder Crashes]
Maybe if you just
sort of walk around.
All right.
Oh, shoot !
Jeez, you all right ?
You okay ?
Yeah.
What are you
doing here ?
You seeing something ?
I've been thinking
some real bad, bad thoughts.
Annie ?
I'm glad that girl is dead.
Jessica.
She was messin' around with my
husband and deserved what she got.
I couldn't sleep.
Met the girls for a drink.
Take off your clothes.
[Jessica's Voice]
Aren't you taking yours off too ?
[Duncan's Voice] There's a saying
about letting sleeping dogs lie.
You just fucked him,
didn't you ? Hmm ?
Donnie Barksdale ?
So ?
Why would you do this to me ?
Hmm ? I love you.
Maybe I wanted to be
with a man for a change.
- Watch your mouth.
- You watch your mouth. Fuck you !
- I'm sorry.
- We're through.
I don't like being spied on.
The only reason I'm with you
is 'cause my daddy likes you.
You horrible little bitch !
I'll show you a bitch if you
don't let go of me. Let go !
- I think we better go back.
- Nothing's coming to you ?
No.
Nothing.
You know.
I knew if I got you close enough
to it that you'd see it.
- Wayne, I told you--
- No, no. It's okay.
I swear to God, Annie,
it's okay. It's okay.
I wanted you to.
I swear to God.
I wanted you to see it so bad.
I mean, that's why we're here.
I'm not some killer, Annie.
I'm not.
You don't-- I mean, do you know
what it was like with her ?
She was so fucking hurtful
and spiteful and all of it--
Wayne, I'm not gonna--
But all of it just happened
in this flash of a moment.
- Wayne, I--
- Listen to me. I'm a good man.
If it had been you instead of her,
none of this would have happened.
Wayne.
It's all right, you know ?
I won't-- I won't tell.
I-I-I won't--
I won't tell anybody.
No, Annie--
You all right, Mrs. Wilson ?
I thought you were supposed to
be in the hospital.
I escaped, Mrs. Wilson.
I'm free.
Buddy, I'm so sorry
I wasn't there for you.
- I should've--
- Now, don't you say another word.
You was the only one
that was a friend to me.
And I love you.
You're the soul
of this town, Mrs. Wilson.
And you just need to keep doing
what you're doing.
I washed it.
Will you come back
into town with me ?
Yeah.
You know you're
gonna have to go back.
Yes, ma'am, I know.
Can I have your keys,
ma'am ?
Well,
I just talked to Wayne.
He pretty much admitted
to everything.
I've known that boy
half my life.
It just goes to show,
you can know somebody and...
not know 'em.
How's his, um--
How's his head ?
Well, you put
a pretty good dent in it.
Oh, no, Sheriff,
I told, uh--
I told the deputy
it wasn't me who did that.
It was, um--
It was Buddy Cole. He saved me.
- No, ma'am. It weren't Buddy.
- Well, yes, it was.
- Why don't you just ask Wayne ?
- I did.
He don't remember
what happened.
Head injuries is funny.
-I'm telling you, it was Buddy Cole.
-What I'm tryin' to say is,
it couldn't have been Buddy.
I-- I just called up
at the State Hospital.
- He told me he escaped.
- Ma 'am.
Buddy Cole is dead.
He hanged himself
in the shower room...
6:00 this evening.
Subtitles spellchecked by [PhoeniX]