MAYA OF THE STORM SURGE
Come on.
Come in.
Well done, Maija!
- Anna!
Once, when the old man was
plowing a field...
elves appeared to him.
The horse suddenly stopped
...and never moved again...
and it didn't help
no trick or gimmick.
That's when Dad remembered that you have to
to peek between the lace and the head.
Then he saw that the field
in the field were a lot of elves.
Come on, Olle.
That's the kind of old folk...
You'd rather read a big book to your children
a book. There are no elves.
Why not?
It is unlikely if anyone
has not seen them.
You shouldn't believe in that,
what cannot be proven.
I have to believe in God too,
even though I have not seen Him.
There are.
The Catechism also says to
to ask the Creator to protect us...
the forest and the sea, and
elves, witches, wolves and others.
Is that so?
Yes, it is. Believe me.
Bay window.
Evening in the house.
- Come on in.
Put the Hindrik fire in the oven,
so we can see the guests better.
Is this your son?
- Yes.
We're not interrupting, are we?
- Please sit down.
It's nice to have some long-distance travellers here.
What's your name?
- Janne.
Janne is the third oldest.
In other words, an empty pocket.
I understand.
I have two sons too.
And then those two.
Oh, right, the wine column?
- Here, have a warm one.
Olof's people already have beer
and a painted table and a silver watch.
A real silver watch?
- Yes, it is.
Is this the case?
See.
Maija, we have guests.
I can cover.
Kullskär has been so
the fishing has been so poor lately.
that we have had to go out fishing.
- That's what I've heard.
You can catch fish in the outer archipelago.
I was thinking about going there.
- I see.
Where to?
- To the outer island.
Give it a rest, Janne.
Any other news?
On. The kind of news...
that Telleskar's boat
went down last week...
and all the men with it.
How many men?
- Three.
Josef and both boys.
The will of God.
Give us a happy ending,
give eternal joy.
But everything happens
Thy holy will...
and therefore I declare your wonders.
- Amen.
What do we think of Janne?
What about him?
- He was handsome.
Why do you think such things...
when you like Peris so much?
You can think what you like.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
- You wonder.
No...
I was thinking of words.
- What?
Like the word "good", for example. Good.
And then add "said Boman".
"Good, said Boman."
Who is this Boman?
and what does his "goodness" mean?
Is it different from mine?
And what I need to do to
in a hundred years' time to say:
"said Maija of Vestergård".
Where would I say something?
About this cow? Or the forest?
You really don't think about anything sensible.
You're all... I don't even know.
What is the word that I am?
- Let's have a race.
Who will fill their gullet first?
- Me.
You're not scaredy-cat.
- We'll see about that.
One, two, three, now.
Are you milking?
Are you scaredy-cat? I win!
Done.
Can you see now? Who's the rascal here?
Come on! You'll scare the animals.
Maija. Wake up, Maija.
Come on, get up.
- Why?
Come on. I need your help.
I think you can help.
This has been going on for more than 24 hours.
Sent way too
too late to get help.
What can I do?
- You just do as I say.
You stay calm.
If nothing else, you pray.
Greta, now you're getting a push.
Good. Push.
A little more, Greta!
Good! A little more. There you go.
Maija.
It is in the hand of the Lord how much
we each have days left.
Our Father, who art in heaven.
Hallowed be your name.
Let your kingdom come.
Your will be done.
My life and my death...
in their hands is my Lord my God.
My time, my hair...
already read it once...
Just go home.
I'll finish this alone.
I don't want life to be like that.
Birth and death
is something everyone has to face.
Before that, there is no
ready for adult life.
For you they came now then
both at the same time.
What happened?
Is it Per?
- No.
Give him a hug.
Maija!
Veenemo, Veenemo...
show me my future acquaintance.
show my future acquaintance, show me a picture
of the groom, show me my happiness.
Veenemo, Veenemo...
Show...
- Maija.
Did you see anything?
Did you see my picture?
I don't really believe in that.
Do you really believe in those
the veenemas and all that?
What are you bothering with?
Do we have guests?
That's what I'm talking about.
What?
Wouldn't you think now
this other one anyway?
He is older and also more sensible.
Yes, I had thought of him.
Yes, Janne meant Maija.
Very clearly.
Well, what the hell.
We have nothing against Janne.
We can keep it that way.
Go go go.
Maija!
Come back right away! Maya!
Did you say something to him?
- I didn't say anything.
He ran away.
I apologise. He's like that.
No problem.
You will soon become
a ladies' man. Before me.
You will leave here with him.
Somewhere out in the open.
I heard him talking
about it with that Erker guy.
From where?
To what they were talking about,
when they first visited.
Where to? I didn't hear.
Not while you were back
in your own worlds.
But that's where he's coming to get you.
Of that I am sure.
He'll be back,
when the divisions of land have been settled.
Then you will get married.
Then you need to be an adult
a woman. And you will spend your wedding night.
It feels like a thorn in the flesh all the time,
when I remember that Janne.
And that I must put him down
a part of my life from now on.
That's how it works.
And when I pray...
...I also pray for forgiveness,
because I am unable to like Janne.
And that it would last a long time before
before I have to leave with him.
You'll get used to it.
I certainly do,
Per to propose soon.
To make life go on,
as it should.
How do you know,
how life is supposed to go?
Everyone knows that.
Maija! Keep your head on straight,
so I can get your tresses in order.
I stand still like a candle.
Don't complain there.
This hair needs to be put up
really smooth and beautiful.
Is it now well and truly?
- Yes, thank you.
It's like I'm in a vice.
Be human.
Here's a bridal bag for you.
It's one of my better pillowcases.
Be careful with it.
Now go.
Vallborg is already waiting in the village.
First I would like to
look at myself in the mirror.
Mirroring is a sin.
About.
You're pretty.
Hello.
Don't you have a sewing kit with you?
Mom didn't say to take it.
Perhaps he thought that he would not
this wasn't a normal trip to the village.
Could be.
Your mother is known to use
every moment to her advantage...
and that's what I learned for sure
to pass on to his daughters.
Let's move the cups,
so there are no stains.
Don't, my good man,
give me everything.
When I give you something,
I give what I feel.
Little girl, there you are
your first nest egg.
Magnus, now congratulate the bride.
Yeah...
Congratulations.
Lisa the Pepper gave it to him for a pittance.
How much was there?
Goodness gracious!
Veenemo, Veenemo,
show me my future bridegroom.
Veenemo...
All the forest and sea fairies
and anyone who hears me now!
Why do I have to?
Girls. Be human.
Anna. Come on,
and we'll go to the coffee machine.
Welcome!
Maija, hi.
Let's go, Erker, for coffee.
Hello, Maija.
You can put this on your shoulders.
Didn't hit the shit, thankfully.
It can be put...
Thank you.
Oh shit.
So that's the kind of sums we're talking about.
It's not going to work.
I know we have no guarantees.
Me and Maija are young
and strong and we will pay you back.
With interest.
- Suitable for.
I will agree to any interest rate.
I'm sure I can pay it back.
How?
- By work.
I sell almost everything I ask for.
I'm at sea from morning till night.
And Myrskyluoto is good
for seal hunting.
According to my calculations, the logs are
paid in five years.
With interest.
Five years.
I decide now
trust Janne's word.
Thank you. You won't regret it.
This helps with the tension.
A wife is made for her husband,
but man was not created for his wife.
The wife must be
in honour of her husband.
as Saar also called it
Abraham as his lord.
Me, Maija...
Maria.
I, Maria Lovisa Mickelsdotter...
I take you, Johan Eriksson.
my husband...
to love you
for better or for worse.
Excuse me.
Can we get under the covers?
Sure.
Damn.
You look like you're being taken to the slaughterhouse.
You look like a woodchuck yourself.
I don't remember,
that it was that much fun.
I'm weighed down by poverty, fall...
and the guilt is cold.
But I believe, O Jesus.
you will not abandon me.
Your love will save...
and wounds deep heal.
Not a very catchy tune.
Well sorry if you don't like it.
I... have looked at a place for us.
Its name is Myrskyluoto.
You can be there as you like.
What if you don't want to?
I have nothing here.
I will not inherit a farm or a barn.
I need to build something of my own.
Something for us.
- Why all the way there?
Anna, mum and dad, little brothers.
Old Olle and Vallborg will stay here.
Yes.
But you can catch fish there.
There you can create one
the world you want.
Can be put on the floor as a roof
and a shirt as trousers.
And it's beautiful there.
Totally empty and free.
The sea indefinitely.
And wind.
And sunshine.
And that would be just us.
That's all.
Why would anyone put on a shirt?
Why not?
Aren't they great?
And there you can watch the shadows
on the wall, and no one will think you're a fool.
Don't be afraid, Mary.
What?
- Nothing.
Don't be afraid of anything.
Everyone can see.
After all, we are married now.
Have you forgotten?
The house rises up to that.
Look, Maya. Next summer
we will live in a new house.
I will build a pier on the beach.
If we ever get your beer.
We can sleep in the barn,
until the house is ready.
I'll get a rocking chair,
so you can sit in it.
Here we have
a home and a barn in one.
The lady is good and comes in.
Or should I carry both you
and the cow over the threshold?
On top of the door
nail the twigs crosswise.
Why?
They protect the Tulip
from evil spirits. And us.
Okay.
Is it good now?
If it's important to you,
it must be important to me.
We are married, after all.
What are you afraid of?
Maija...
But if such a
comes across you in the field again...
spit is the only thing to do
over your shoulder three times. Like this.
Then you have to run.
What was this? A goblin?
- An elf.
Then there is the hostess of the sea.
It's really horrible.
It has its hair loose, and it floats
in the waves and wants to take your breath away.
That's what you need to be particularly careful of,
because it's more dangerous for men.
But I've been wondering...
that maybe it's just lonely,
long dead soul...
who has had a sad life.
and that's why it's so angry,
that it hurts others.
And of course, the mermaid is dangerous...
but with it helps
throwing salt in the sea.
That's good to know. Thank you.
I have not yet told you
about the spirits of the forest and the stones.
Row upwind.
Let's test the nets.
Keep it up.
Not that. There you go.
About. Dad, come and lift.
This is ready.
Not you, Maija.
- Yes, I did.
Let Maija raise.
She's stronger than you think.
You heard what Dad said.
About. Then the following.
Janne.
You have to be careful.
- And catch fish.
You get hungry too, don't you?
- Yes, but...
Janne. Mistress of the sea
is not in a good mood today.
I say to her, "Get lost, bitch".
"I already have a lovely wife,
and I don't care about your temptations."
Promises that you turned back,
if the wind rises at all.
I'd rather eat though
hay than live without you!
I promise.
And throw them to the master of the water
the first fish to appease him!
Janne! Did you hear that?
The Lord bless us and keep us.
Veenemo!
Don't take Janne away from me!
He is my husband!
He's not yours!
Janne...
I didn't realize...
that winters can be so long
and cold even when you're an adult.
I am fully accustomed to
living in a barn.
Maybe I am an animal at heart.
Not next winter though
we can't be in the barn.
even if you turn into a pig.
Why? This is a palace.
It will be the most visible in the world.
That's where your mouth comes in.
And your eyes.
And your lovely hair.
And your peace.
And your certainty.
And your shoulders.
And your strange mind.
And your courage.
We need to make many,
so we get all the combinations.
Let's fill this hole -
with a small face,
hands and feet.
Children can grow up in a new house
and on these beaches...
under these stars.
Just bring it on.
You don't get the best in town for cheap.
Maija! Come on.
We have a lot to do.
Ma'am, come and taste
the best bagels in town.
God's gaze is on you too.
Hello.
Take a look,
what we have to offer.
Could be a silver box,
with a nice pattern?
Or even a string of pearls?
Well... How much?
Not much. Just three rubles.
Parrot!
A new necklace for the lady.
No! Maya!
Hello.
Yes. Nice 1 250.
Yes.
A very fine yarn.
Have you spun yourself?
- Yes.
And stained too?
- Yes. Which I can do now.
Lake cane with flowers, birch leaves,
mushrooms and milk peas...
Right.
Beautiful.
You have an eye for this.
950 grams.
250 grams.
So here is...
That's about the same as this.
Great. Can you sign there?
A wooden stamp will do, of course,
if you can't write.
There you go.
Two rubles and 50 kopecks.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
Come on, Maya.
Your expression when the snake was hugged
around your neck.
You were like a fish out of water.
I would like to have such a snake
To go with the tulip in the barn.
Maija.
Shall we go back to buying a snake?
Does it apply to you?
The child is not in trouble, is it?
- Why did you take the money?
What money?
My brother-in-law.
I now have our money.
- That's what it is.
That's what I'm asking.
Why you of all people?
Isn't that usually the man's responsibility?
We can agree that you too
to wear them from time to time.
What do I do with them? I don't know how to
even write my name.
Are you up to it?
- Just do your part.
The new pier is handsome.
A bit pretentious, perhaps.
But when you get your beer, you...
And after that? A frigate, huh?
Help is needed.
Shipwreck.
- Where?
Near Isokar.
Six men are stranded in the water.
I'm coming! Anyone else coming?
- They've gone to the mainland to fetch...
but it is not certain whether help will arrive in time.
Now it's just us.
Just go ahead.
Blessings of the Lord. Come back.
We managed to save two men.
Four remained in the sea.
Maija!
Dear!
Maija.
Hot water. Here you go.
Hot water. Linen...
Towel. Blanket.
Maija.
Maija! You must not leave me. Maya.
Here, Maya.
Open the south-facing windows...
Open the south-facing windows.
Then you pour the glowing
biscuits in a cold bucket of water.
What do you say?
Do as I say,
to get the baby out.
Glowing crackers...
Maija...
Very small.
Our girl.
Maria.
Maria, come on in.
August and Mikael, come too.
Come on.
Look at your new little brother.
Do you want to hold him?
Here you go.
- Book!
Here are some pictures.
- And screamers.
You don't understand yet.
Let me see.
Pictures and letters.
Santa's got something for your mum too.
Let's see.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
Now you can get started.
Draw A.
What if I never learn?
Then you must be a bit stupid.
What do you mean?
It says "sheep".
Here's a picture.
- Maria.
Don't you understand, stupid?
- Maria!
Don't stare with your dick eyes
or I'll bang you!
Mikael, come here.
I said that because he's stupid.
Mikael.
You know the difference between right and wrong.
That's why I think you're asking
apologize to your sister soon.
You have the same
fierce nature as I do.
Yes, because I was born from you.
You certainly are.
Mikael. Mum's little support head.
Maria. Take the little ones inside.
Come on.
They intend to destroy
coastal fortifications.
Bomarsundin and all.
And everyone who does not them
help them in this, they will slaughter.
That's the Englishman.
Everyone should be
opposing them.
All these gods
from the outer islands will be taken away.
After all, you don't have to help them.
I wasn't thinking of taking part.
Not one way or the other.
I am Ålander.
Not a Finn,
not Russian, not Swedish.
Must then do
what needs to be done without your help.
This is a long war,
that spans almost the entire world.
Here the wars
the Russians and the English.
Almost all of Europe
From Crimea to the Baltic Sea.
And you think,
you can opt out.
Fuck!
I guess I'll just...
This stone is for a farmer...
and this to the mummy.
This bird feather is for water.
Jesus gets everything without,
but not a single treasure.
Why doesn't Jesus get the treasures?
Because everyone believes
in him anyway.
Why don't the eagles make a sound?
Don't they dare?
Why wouldn't they dare?
Because they know there is a war on.
You put such good gifts on the spirits
and to Jesus you promised without a word...
that we have nothing to worry about.
Come and sit here.
Don't look over there.
Come on.
Where to?
Shouldn't this be... What?
Come on.
"A soldier shoots a man."
"The girl is combing her hair."
"A man shoots himself."
Is that what it says?
- Yes.
Sounds terrible.
Can I take it already?
- Please.
You too, Professor.
What?
Do they serve fresh bread here?
Oh, how wonderful.
Careful! Goes down the wrong throat.
I'm choking.
I told you.
that bad...
...is a long way from here.
Should I take out more loans?
What do you say?
Nothing will come of this stinginess.
Maija, you are...
When we came to this cove, you said.
you were going to build a bigger dock.
because one day
we'd have your beer.
Kaljaasi... I was only joking.
- Wouldn't that be great?
It came from the back.
Now I think it's time
the time for the last prayer.
You have to leave. Now.
You have to go.
I don't have time. I can't get on the boat.
They can see me.
They are killing me.
What will happen to you if I am killed?
No one is killed.
Hide in the barn.
They won't find you.
I'll come and tell you then,
when you can leave. At night, maybe.
I can't leave you and the children.
- They're looking for men.
They don't care about women and children.
Now go to the barn.
Listen. Now you stay calm.
The Royal Navy
First Lieutenant John Wilson.
This is the sea cadet Harris.
I hereby declare this region
in the name of His Majesty.
There are no men on the island, sir.
Where are the men?
Bring them here at once.
Where is Dad?
Do others live on the island
other than you and your children?
Hello.
Blessings of the Lord.
I see.
Search all the buildings on the farm.
If you can find men,
bring them to me.
Yes, sir.
Take four men and search the area.
You four, search the area.
Please hurry.
Take action.
It's OK.
Harris, set up a table,
map and chairs.
Yes, sir.
Tables in that room.
- Let's go.
Let's hurry up.
Janne.
Dear Lord.
Are you OK? Are the children?
You have to leave. Everyone's asleep.
Access to the beach and the boat
and row to the mainland.
There, you could try for Ostrobothnia.
I can't take the boat.
- Yes, you can.
They discover in the morning that the boat
is gone, and they go after it.
Or blame you and the children.
Saboteurs will be hanged.
Then I'll take you.
Back to Souda
before they wake up.
Maija. The journey is too long.
- Come on.
Maija...
Maija. Now the moment has come...
when neither of us should be afraid.
No! No.
Please come back.
No...
I guess even a lousy porridge is better
than none at all, right?
Hey, you.
You just did.
Hello?
For the viisi.
He's certainly not very sharp.
Thank you.
Now let's just be quiet, let's press
our heads and do as we're told.
Nothing bad will happen to us.
Nothing is going to happen to us.
Get out of here.
Keep it quiet. Jesus Christ.
Mikael, come down from the Millstone!
If you fall from there, you're dead!
Have you been lonely?
Mum...
Keep your eyes on the job.
Just keep on gutting.
We are not afraid.
Do you think it will freeze soon?
Sea. Freezing. How soon?
Ice. At sea. Ice.
Ice.
When?
Quick.
Ice.
Coming soon.
Quick.
Thank you.
Harris, he says,
that the sea will soon freeze over.
Yes, sir. So we're staying
and the others leave.
Probably towards the south.
We'll stay on the outpost.
We have to be prepared for everything.
- Of course.
About this.
- What does it matter now?
It always matters.
For God's sake.
Watch out for small ones.
Don't come out, no matter what.
Let it go!
You don't touch the tulip.
Hands off, woman.
The cow becomes a good meal for us.
You will not stop us.
We're going to have a feast.
Or do we have to slaughter you too?
Let him go. Now.
He will prevent His Majesty
men from doing what they want.
And whatever they want,
if you don't mind my asking?
Eat a cow.
The cow is our only hope.
When you ever leave here
and all this terrible stuff is over...
and if I and the children
are still alive.
we cannot cope with the following
winter without a cow.
Can he hear me?
Does he understand?
The cow is our lifeblood.
Me and the kids will die without it.
Let the cow go.
With all due respect, sir,
we're going to eat a cow.
We want meat, don't we, boys?
- Yes.
Which of you will defy my command?
Clear and direct
Lieutenant's order.
Who would know if we announced
you were killed in battle?
Arrest him for sedition.
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Keep going.
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
Enter.
I would like to ask an officer...
Excuse me.
Help.
I don't understand.
I'll show you.
If an officer would bother.
Come on.
Out.
Cow...
Cow.
I...
Logs.
Me.
Water. Wa... water. Me.
There's too much work, and the room is
full of men lounging around.
Surely they're not all
are incapacitated.
You can too, I suppose.
at least do a little something.
Is everything all right, sir?
A lady apparently
asking for help with her workload.
Are we helping?
I don't know if it's worth it
to burden men any more.
Yes, sir.
Look how thin I've become.
What's in it for you,
if we die?
So who's going to fuck you?
Can I take it?
Harris,
draw up a schedule of the day's work.
Defying orders or getting out of work
is considered insubordination.
Yes, sir.
Ask him about the chores to be done.
- Yes, sir.
Give men a splash
whisky to refresh your mind.
Right away, sir.
Good.
We have a new soldier.
Your turn.
Oh dear.
Oh, eleven.
- Very good.
Let's pick up the pace.
Let's go.
Bring all your gear.
They're going somewhere.
I hope they die.
They bleed and die.
Come on.
It's for everyone. Hurry now.
The seer and the lord of the sea
and the lady of the sea.
the cunning Englishmen
To a watery grave.
sink to the bottom,
so they can never get back in.
We do not wish anyone dead.
Not even the enemy.
Good people don't do that.
I hate them!
They came without permission
and forced my father away.
I can only hope for their death.
You are not the kind of person who hopes
the death of others. You're my girl.
Hate destroys the hater.
You don't know,
what kind of person I am.
Mikael! What are you doing?
Put it away and get out
out of the lieutenant's room.
Bring a blanket!
Help the boy!
Medic!
Sir! Sir!
Help the men.
Excuse me.
I didn't mean to. Mom.
I killed them.
- No.
You have not killed anyone
but the war.
No, no. No problem.
Come here, everyone.
Now we crossed our arms.
The Lord bless and keep you
these fallen ones...
Hello! We could use some help here.
I order you to work
In the name of His Majesty.
Give me my sword.
Please help!
Poor thing.
You're somebody's son too.
Don't be afraid. You'll get better.
Don't touch me,
when I'm on duty!
Sir.
It's me. Harris.
- I said back off!
I am a member of the Royal Navy
Lieutenant of the Royal Navy, damn it!
Take him to rest and give him some water.
Check the wound later.
The lieutenant will calm down now.
Come on. I'll help you.
Lying there resting.
Tomorrow I will change the bandage.
Hopefully the fever will go down.
I haven't seen them in years.
I miss Janne terribly too.
All this is
is just a gap in humanity.
The honour of an officer...
...and a royal killing machine.
My husbands do not get
see me like this.
If they see me like this,
they will kill me.
Calm down.
- They are animals.
I am an animal.
We are all animals.
That's what war does to you,
you know.
Rest now.
Lie down.
Who are you?
Whose island is this?
Is your life here?
Maija.
My... my name...
John.
Is that the whole world?
I think this is
just a small piece.
The world must go on beyond the edges.
And then it comes from the other side
towards. Because the world is round.
Yes.
What does it say?
"Madrid".
Madrid.
Russian! Come on.
Sir...
Come on, Maya. I think you're finally
get your island back.
I leave these dice to you.
Have fun and remember me.
For you, little lady,
I leave you a piece of the big world.
Always keep your eyes on the horizon.
Can Dad come back now?
Oh.
To port, please.
Mum?
- No?
What are you doing?
- I'm shouting. Scream too!
Come on, let's go.
We have to eat.
Come on now! Let's go fishing.
But Dad is not here.
It's all right.
There are pants in the cupboard for you too, Maria.
They are easier to work in.
A bit more from that side.
About. Pull, August.
I'll try.
- You can. There you go.
More from that side.
Focus, August.
What? Has he been
at sea with children?
Dad. I missed him terribly.
My God, how are you
lost weight. And the children too.
There is hardly anything left of you.
My mother sent me this.
- Yes, here you go.
Do you wear trousers now?
They are more practical.
You should try.
Come on.
Engelsmanni left that behind.
You don't understand any of this, do you?
Let's throw it away.
- No.
It was a gift from a friend.
"I thank you, my heavenly Father.
Through Jesus Christ.
that tonight I'm going to be
from all danger and sin...
that my life and all my
all my work may be acceptable to Thee."
It goes like water.
"Your holy angels
be with me...
lest that evil enemy
would gain nothing from me."
I wonder if Maria has that sin
so much on her conscience yet?
Against the word of the Lord
don't argue.
Come and sit down, Mary.
Now, here's the thing.
that you and the children
are going to Vestergård.
We can't leave.
We have to wait for Janne.
He'll be here any minute.
Nothing will come of it. You're not going to make it.
Janne will be home soon.
You don't even know where he is.
He is safe and on his way home.
Do you have any idea how many men left
and how many were caught?
Yes Janne you
Vestergård can also find you.
We are waiting for Janne here.
This is our home.
I have to go to the milking.
Maija. Wait.
Stop this madness.
What's crazy about knowing
where you belong and where you want to be?
As if you could decide that.
As if any woman could.
I can.
Janne is not coming back.
He must be dead.
Here he comes. I've seen it in a dream.
Jesus, how childish.
He comes because he loves me.
Love has nothing to do with it.
Go ahead.
Say whatever you want to say.
I can see that you want to.
You imagine that life is
is nothing but love and play...
and that you can decide how it goes.
So you have nothing to fear.
That you can manage with this creature for your children
and that everything will be fine.
I don't imagine such a thing.
But I can decide for myself,
what I want to do.
That's the kind of wife Janne wants,
who decides for herself what she wants?
Doesn't your Peris tolerate that?
You used to laugh a lot.
Don't you get it,
that I'm worried about you?
See how scared I am?
I always have been.
- You haven't.
Yes, I have.
- No, you're not.
Yes, I am!
Yes, I have.
- No, you're not.
Give my regards to grandma.
We miss her.
I feel really bad
to leave you here.
Maija does
as is best for her.
I will protect you from the seers
and from the lady of the sea, until the Father comes.
I aim at the Millstone every day...
so I can see Dad as soon as he comes in.
I have sharp eyes.
- Yes, you do, darling.
Soon you will see your father. First
as a tiny dot on the horizon...
and soon you'll be on the dock.
I'll be watching again today.
Poor little thing.
What is it?
Where is Mikael?
He was on the beach
and watched his father on the millstone.
Then at least I thought I saw,
that he fell into the sea.
I did not see,
that he had surfaced.
Me, August and Hindrik are looking for
for him, but we couldn't find him.
Mikael...
Mikael!
Where is Mikael?
It's OK.
Now let's sleep.
We'll talk more about it tomorrow.
Little boy.
The Lord bless him
and keep him.
May the Lord make his face to shine upon him...
and may he have mercy on him.
May the Lord turn his face to him
and give him peace.
In the name of the Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
It's a busy time...
the passing years...
the male knees fade into oblivion.
Always bright -
the song of souls...
the heavenly chord remains.
I baptise you, Gabriel Johansson.
Father...
The boy's...
and in the name of the Holy Spirit. Amen.
Yes, he does.
We'll start loading the cargo, you see.
Maya, please, we don't do that.
we can't do that. It's a terrible risk.
It's a terrible risk to live on such a meagre income.
Such a life
is quickly dislocated.
Now I am it,
who is not afraid at all.
It's not that difficult
than many other things.
Can I get on board the beer cooler too?
And me?
Not just on board.
The Father teaches about you
the best fishermen in the world.
Yes, such a beer glass would be handsome.
Now we have to feed the baby.
You start thinking,
how you're going to present it to Saka.
Please help Janne.
- Good. Then let's lift.
Janne, there is no time for that now.
You boys take these.
That's the way to freight
so much stuff...
that you do not know
where to put all the money.
As long as you can pay off the loan.
The loan will be repaid
and everything will be fine.
You then have to brush ash on the bow.
- Ashes?
Everyone knows that the only way
to keep the ship afloat in a storm.
Do you hear, father-in-law, that wife of mine?
Calculates loans on a pegboard
and repayments like a rich bourgeois...
and the man of the modern world -
and then ask to shake the ashes
like an old-world witch.
Go ahead and laugh,
as long as you put the ash on it.
The network will be forged,
when it hits the bottom.
Maria.
Maria, take a look
for your little brother.
Where are you going?
I'll have to check it out
on the back to see if there are any driftwood.
There was such a strong wind today.
Driftwood?
- That's right!
Get in the sledge.
I'm pulling you.
- No.
You'll never be able to.
I can do it.
You can't.
- Come on.
We will all survive until next spring.
Sit here.
Next winter I won't be able to pull you.
Then there is enough money to do so,
you don't know where to put it all.
Then we'll have your beer,
and the catch will come.
You're as thick as a seal
from all that eating.
"Mum combs the girl's hair.
Mommy dresses the boy."
I read too.
"Mommy combs the girl's hair."
What about this?
- "A man shoots himself. The mother dresses the son."
Can't sleep?
Did the baby kick?
I saw...
Come to bed.
You can take a sauna at least once
once a week while I'm away.
Let's not waste wood.
You are so beautiful.
Am I?
Further.
And always.
Don't be silly, Maya. The last sandwiches.
- You have a long way to go.
We'll be fine.
We have potatoes and herring.
This is the last trade mission.
Then the money will be there.
I'll go back to that,
for the little one to be born.
I'll take care of Grandpa.
Do you have any first
razor yet, August?
Maija!
Don't forget!
I love you!
Mum.
They must have had to
go further away to the shops.
Janne wants a good price.
Here they come! I saw two men
coming down the ice towards us.
What made me bake in the first place
the last of the flour right now?
They get to the ready table
and get fresh bread.
I see them!
Take care of him.
The second is August...
And the other is Janne.
Maija.
Girl darling.
No.
Not this one.
Excuse me.
The father fell into the ice.
I tried my best.
Mum... Excuse me.
I couldn't pull him up.
He sank below the surface.
Maija...
- I don't want to!
Well done, Maija.
Good! You'll be fine.
Well done, Mary!
The child is too small.
Maija.
Here we go.
The girl has to eat, Maya.
We were sure,
the baby would not live.
I issued an emergency response.
We baptised him John.
According to his father.
Maija. Everything is ready.
We're off to Vestergård.
The goods are packed.
This is where you will be.
Life on the slipway is too hard.
You can't survive alone.
Johanna is so small...
and you have other children.
Maija!
Don't forget!
I love you!
We're staying at the Stormy Swamp.
Maija...
Everything I love is here.
Including those that no longer exist.
How could I leave them here?
I'll change into dry clothes.
Who's walking in the wet now.
Bring Johanna to me.
For Maija?
Yes. For me.
Oh my goodness, Mary.
Why didn't Maija take her father with her?
With his guarantee, maybe,
but for a widow and children...
This is not my father's business, it's my business.
The Kalyasa will be ready in the summer.
and the work continues
just like before Jannen...
After all, Maija has no men for beer.
Janne taught the boys well.
They know how.
August is already taller than me,
and he has his father's shoulders.
Hindrik is coming up fast behind,
and so is Gabriel.
No.
I would never get my money back.
A house without a host.
Just a female human being and children.
Just a female human being?
I survived the war.
The death of my husband and child.
I have survived hunger
and toil.
How it is less,
because I'm not a man?
How Maija dares
talk to me like that?
I'm not a do-gooder.
Maija and her children move into her father's home
and stop this kind of madness.
I'm not crazy.
And I'm not afraid.
Give him a loan.
Okay.
The maturity of the bond
However, a name is required for the extension.
Someone's name,
the person who has the right to sign.
Will Maija's father write it?
The woman's name is not legally valid.
It's true in court.
Just like a loan shark.