Baby, I'm sorry.
I didn't... I was
holding... Like this.
I was holding your hand.
And I'm still...
I'm looking and looking
and looking. I'm looking.
I'm looking for my perfect...
for my perfectly...
My perf... ection.
Yes. All of it. All of it!
You don't believe me.
'Cause I asked you to help. Yes!
But you're in your box.
Your little precious box.
Your little box of... mud.
You think it's yours.
You think you did it.
What about I take
the... lights out?
The rights out, tights
out, fiiiights out!
What now? Huh? Bitch.
You think I'm locked out.
I'm the one inside.
And I'll spit you out.
I am the first and the last.
I will make you a million
dollars in one day.
And all you got to do is give
me your face and your eyes
and your liiife-blood!
The Devil's gonna get
you rich in two minutes
if you just... Jaaackpot!
A flipped up, tipped
up, tiiick-tock.
I've got my tripped up God-cock.
More wicked boxes.
And I know who set 'em here.
I will show my
will to all of you
that smile with
the pride of pigs.
And all the pigs will
listen when it's too late.
The pigs and liars will burn
forever when it's too late.
And all your boxes
will be saaand.
We're going to be talking
about what happens
if you are ready to have a baby,
but your partner, your spouse,
your significant other,
is not ready to have a baby.
That can be a really
difficult place to be in.
And it can actually be a lot
of dealbreakers
for relationships.
Especially when one person
really does want
to start a family.
And that's what they wanted
from day one of their
life and they know that.
And then maybe the other
person just isn't ready yet
...or really just doesn't want
children or can't see them...
What's this?
Can I help you?
What's that mask for?
You didn't see the signs
coming into our village
of our rules and
regulations, Sheriff?
This is Pueblo.
No, it's not.
I was just at a residence
right back there.
That is Sevilla County.
That may be,
but the border is there.
This is Santa Lupe.
You don't ever come
when we ask for
your help, Sheriff.
-You're trespassing.
-Butterfly!
People are dying of
this thing, right?
-People are dying.
-Now, look.
This one here, he's got it
hanging off of his nose.
I mean, what are we doing
here? Listen. Just...
I am listening. Shut up!
When you're on our
soil, put on your mask.
Put on your mask, Sheriff.
Hey, you don't have to...
0-1, to all monitoring units.
Got a call into the office
advising about a disturbance.
0-8, 0-4.
Hi, Sheriff. It's another
disorderly conduct with Lodge.
But I was gonna see
where Tooley's at.
Uh, no, I'll take it.
Ten-four. Uh, you sure?
It's at the mayor's.
Sheriff?
I heard you. Well,
what does that mean?
Is it his office,
his house, the bar?
Bar. But I was gonna check
what Tooley's twenty was.
No, I'll take it.
Blonde bitches named Sarah
think they're Rosa Parks.
If I added her on
Snap, what would I say?
Uh, take a pic of you with me.
Prove that you're an ally.
No, but really.
I don't know. Send
her a dick pic.
See if she can guess what it is.
-What do I do?
-I don't know.
Bro, no mask?
No, I'm good. Bro.
What's that smell, by
the way? A little reefer?
I don't know. Your ass?
And then, just the spillover.
Two, three hundred
construction jobs, ongoing.
The solar offset's a
whole 'nother development.
Sure, sure. But, what?
We just let these
guys build this,
whatever it is, data complex
and then they up
and close it down
for whatever reason? We
just got to eat that?
Phil, there's clawbacks
on everything.
Gross receipt taxes,
payback of property.
There's no wishing tech away.
Whether we jump on the
boat now or get bulldozed,
these guys, they're bringing
an actual infrastructure
for a real future.
-A real future.
-That's right.
Can we count on
your "yay" tomorrow?
What is the problem?
Well, he... he's outside.
I had to lock the door
to keep him outside.
It's been a whole
hour like this.
I can't understand you.
Yes, you can.
He's disturbing
the peace. Again.
He's blocking the entrance.
Whose entrance? What are
you even doing in there?
It's takeaway drinks only.
Those are town council members.
That's essential business.
Well, you can't just call
essential business
whatever you want.
It's a city council meeting
wherever city council
people congregate.
It's the Mayor's
office if I'm inside.
Okay, then you are open.
And you have a
paying customer...
Customer?
He's aggressive, he's dangerous,
he needs to be locked up.
Where would you
have me send him?
These are your streets...
No, they're your
streets, Sheriff.
...that you locked down.
They're your streets
to keep safe.
And where is your mask?
I don't...
He doesn't have a mask on!
-All right.
-He's coughing!
Okay.
-No mask either with this guy?
-All right.
Hey.
You get your little Instagram?
Yeah, I got my little Instagram.
Again, history repeats itself.
And, uh, I mean,
let's talk about 1956.
Let's talk about the number
56 for just one minute.
In California, you have
Jesuit-educated Gavin Newsom.
And he said to California,
as he became the first governor
to lock down his state,
he said, "56% of you will
get Corona in eight weeks."
Which is exactly 56 days.
Of course, they keep looking
at that lab in Wuhan, China.
And if you look at
that lab in Wuhan
when it was established,
it was 1956.
Of course, that's the
year Tom Hanks was born,
the first celebrity
with the virus.
Mr. Sleepless In Seattle.
By the way, Jenny Durkan
was the mayor of Seattle
when it became the first city
in the world outside of China
to have someone get the virus.
And she was the 56th mayor.
This is Gematria.
Ancient practice of
coding numbers into words.
It's a simp...
How many coincidences
need to occur
before we call this
pattern a design?
I-Is the end goal of media
the end of mediation?
We are here on this plane,
somehow, as these things...
-Hey.
How was your day?
Good.
How was yours?
Good. I got those for you.
Yeah, I'm all right.
Something happen to you?
What do you mean?
Your limp.
-Oh.
-Hurt your leg?
Just some...
...stupid nonsense
down at, um... the bar.
Not... Not with Ted.
Just, you know, Lodge.
You know, the homeless?
It wasn't Ted.
Whoa.
What's this one about?
Yeah, just an image
I had. I don't know.
Very weird. I like it.
I sold two more
of the new dolls.
Really?
Which ones?
The spider legs
and the girl sleeping
on the tongue.
Uh-huh. Well, that is
great news, Louise.
Wha... She can't
just email this, huh?
Well, she does
and then she checks my phone
to see if I opened them.
Yeah, well, that's
why I told you
you should put a passcode on.
I did put a passcode
on last week.
Hey, you remember the
deal when she moved in?
That it was just
'til... 'til April?
You remember there's
still a pandemic?
I don't like it either.
She took my work space.
I mean, if she was an invalid,
that'd be one thing, but...
You know, even you
said it feels like, uh,
she's watching you all the time.
No, I said it's like I'm
being watched all the time.
Not just by her.
I-I know it feels that way,
but it's not.
I promise. Hey, look at me.
I promise. Okay?
I'm sorry.
-No, no.
-I'm sorry.
-Oh, I'm sorry, darling.
-No, no.
Hey, you don't...
Don't apologize.
-Okay?
-Okay.
I love you, baby.
I am getting better.
I know you are.
I know.
No truth can be verified.
There is no truth on the
level that you and me live at.
Please, ask yourself why
are we using Zoom now?
What even is it?
And it appears right
at the same time
as deepfake and lockdown.
So why are you on
the computer, then?
-Iron's what kills people.
-Morning.
Hey, Dawn,
the hot water got
all used up again.
Did you hear about
this? Clade X?
Mmm.
In 2018. This is not a
secret. Please look it up.
They did a whole
pandemic-modeling exercise
at Johns Hopkins. Now...
How do you simulate a pandemic
two years before a
pandemic even happens?
Please ask yourselves that.
How'd you sleep?
I'm out of sleeping pills again.
Thank you.
-Okay. I'll pick some up later.
-Okay.
Why do I even talk?
I'm just an old
lady who's crazy.
-Who's lost her mind.
-Mom?
What were you saying?
I don't have to say it.
You can read it. Here.
Look at this.
Pandemic Modeling Exercise.
Event 201. This
is from last year.
Read it. Out loud.
Please. Out loud.
"Prepare the government, health
officials and business people..."
Business people.
That's interesting.
"For the breakout of an
unprecedented coronavirus."
Coronavirus. They used
that word in 2019.
You need to get your
own laptop, Dawn.
Your daddy was up
against all these things.
The corruption.
It was just more buried.
What, you don't think he was?
You were at Ted
Garcia's last night.
It was his complaint, right?
Right?
He rings his little bell,
and you come running.
The fact that you can
just stroll on over there,
business as usual.
What do you all even
say to each other
when you get there?
"Hi. How are ya?"
Mom.
Where even is your anger, Joe?
That's my question.
Where's your anger, Lou?
Hello?!
This, this is how Ted Garcia
gets away with everything.
When I think about what
your daddy would have done
if he was still sheriff...
There are more reported cases
in New Mexico prisons
than in all but four
counties in the entire state.
Only McKinley, San
Juan, Bernalillo,
and Doña Ana have more,
yet these counts are dumped
into the state totals every day!
Why? They're in a prison!
I would love to
hear the rationale
of why a restaurant in Hobbs
has to go out of business
to fight a disease
in the Navajo nation.
Whoa.
Hey! Hey!
What is going on here? Fred!
He can't go in without
a mask, Sheriff.
Says who?
You can't handle him like that.
All right? Get
your hands off him.
-All right, let him in.
-I can't breathe in a mask.
It's a mandate, Sheriff.
Isn't it? Since last week?
There's a way to do it.
There's a way to treat people.
Just let him in.
What?
He can't breathe in his mask.
You want him to starve too?
I can't neither.
No. No.
Out!
-Get out.
-What is this?
I have groceries.
-I haven't checked out yet.
-Out!
Come on, Fred.
-Wait a minute.
-I'm sorry.
You're welcome back any
time wearing a mask.
Why are you doing this?
I can't breathe in it.
That's much worse
when you have to wait in
line for a ventilator.
I can't breathe in the mask.
Get out!
-Excuse me, Sheriff.
-Yeah.
I'm sorry, but you need a mask
if you're going to be in here.
It's okay.
I-I don't.
But...
I'm sorry, but you're just not
going to treat people like that.
-Joe, what...
-I can't.
Sheriff, I...
-There's a mandate. I have to...
-Hey, Joe.
It doesn't... doesn't matter.
Hey.
Good morning.
Hey, Tony.
How we doing?
Okay, Mayor. I think.
We're... We're fine.
Well, that's good.
That's good. That's good.
Listen,
Joe,
you know,
if a healthy person
with a mask...
Oh, here we go. Mm-hmm.
...gets exposed to
a Covid-19 person...
-Uh-huh.
-...without a mask...
Yeah. Yeah.
...then they got a 70%
chance of catching it.
But if we all wear them,
then we can reduce the
transmission to 1.5%.
You don't even know what
you're talking about.
1.4% of nothing is what?
And actually, Joe,
this is simple because
there is a state mandate.
No, that's... It's
not enforceable.
It is enforceable.
It absolutely is enforceable.
Made so by the Governor and
the Department of Health.
You just gonna keep filming?
Is that... You
getting it? Uh-huh.
What the Mayor's talking
about... Hello, sir.
The Mayor's talking
about policy. Okay?
If you don't want me
in here without a mask,
you must change the law.
County commissioners are
right here in Eddington.
Put it on the agenda.
Get a county ordinance
prohibiting me, and
Fred, and the rest of us
that want to live our
lives without a mask...
Would you... Would you
put that... Excuse me.
Excuse me! Is that Fred's?
Put it down.
Joe.
I-I-I just...
Okay.
Go on. Go.
What? What?
Everything's fine.
Okay?
You know who this is for?
Fred, come on,
before you get hit by a car.
-All right, now listen to me.
-Yes, sir.
I want you to take this.
What is this? What is this?
It's for you. You have
yourself a good day. Okay?
Wait, wait. Can I pay
you back for this?
No, no, no.
Uh, Sheriff, Sheriff.
Wait, wait, wait. Please.
A picture. A picture?
Okay.
-Ready?
-Hold on. Hold on.
Smile.
Ladies and gentlemen,
what have you,
this is Joe Cross,
sheriff of Sevilla County.
And, first off, allow me
to say that I'm asthmatic.
I know. Who cares?
But I do find it very difficult
to breathe in these masks. Okay?
Now, second off, there
is no Covid in Eddington.
There's no Covid
in Sevilla County,
yet a state mandate pushed
by our mayor and his governor
says that I cannot shop for food
without risking
an asthma attack.
And you cannot exercise
your freedom of choice
without being, you know,
uh, publicly shamed.
Bec...
Because what I just saw
just... ...a moment ago...
Uh...
I mean, I just...
How... How did we get here?
Okay? And even worse,
is it worth it?
Is it worth it to combat a
virus that isn't even here
at the cost of being at
war with your neighbors
and your... your family?
Because that... that's what
community is, isn't it?
It's a family. Okay?
Because you can ruin a man's day
or you can do the right
thing and you can be kind,
and you can free his heart.
We need to free
each other's hearts.
And that's why I'm
running for mayor.
Mayor of Eddington.
Did he just say what
I think he said?
I have, uh, served this county
as sheriff for seven years
and it has been my honor,
and I would be honored
to serve you as mayor.
Hey!
-Yeah, right.
-You're going to be okay.
Okay, here comes another one.
Three cops for one guy.
Here we go.
Sheriff, this for real?
Yes. All right, we got to make
up for lost time. Who's this?
A day drinker. OWI.
I'm not gonna tell you
any more because one:
I don't have to,
and two: you're gonna do
whatever shit you're gonna do.
Wow. How much did
you drink, kid?
Um, honestly, low-key,
not enough for you
to put me in here.
He refused to take
the field test.
Okay, campaign signs. Now
which one of you has Photoshop?
Oh, uh, my uncle does,
but I think it expired.
Okay, un-expire it. Get on
down to Kinko's in Las Cruces.
"Joe Cross for Mayor." Okay?
Guy, you can draw, right?
Just stick figures.
Okay, good. Look, here's
what I want. A man.
I hope you're
locked and loaded...
He's got a face mask...
...because you got to get me.
...but he's got x's for
eyes 'cause he's dead.
Look, I know I made
a mistake, okay?
I know what you guys
are trying to do.
I know what kind
of cops you are.
Look, I don't know
what else to say.
Now I need your boys' support.
Okay, this is what
we're doing now.
You've been deputized. This
is our campaign office.
So, yes, right? Yes!
Hell yeah.
Yes!
-Yeah.
-Okay, good. Okay.
Guy, look, do me a favor.
Get one of your friends to buy
one of Louise's
dolls again. Okay?
Oh, yeah. Yes, sir.
I'll pay 'em straight back.
Can do. Does it
matter which one?
Just one of the new
ones. Doesn't matter.
Hey, hey, Sheriff,
check this out.
What's that? Three
hundred yards?
Three-fifty. No scope.
Promise?
Yeah. I still got the
AR out for practice.
That's beautiful, Mikey.
But you ain't shit
'til you beat mine.
Sheriff's Department.
Hey, Sheriff, if you win,
what does that mean for here?
Well, we get a bigger budget,
I'll tell you that much.
Sheriff, it's for you.
Okay.
Hey, Guy, let's get going
on signatures. All right?
Get ourselves on the ballot.
Hello.
Joe, I'm outside your office.
I am recording
this. Fair warning.
That really necessary?
You are a public servant.
So are you.
Yep.
And I think it's, uh,
better if we just let it
all out on the table. Okay?
I got nothing to hide,
you got nothing to hide.
Okay.
Well...
First I'd...
I just want to apologize
if I offended you
for this morning or
for last night...
No. No apology
needed. You didn't.
Okay.
Because if I did...
then that would
help me understand.
Well, your term
is up, and, uh...
your town is dead.
Now, how can I help
you understand?
Look, Joe...
Six feet.
We never talked about it.
The whole, you know...
The whole...
Can we just talk? Can we
just... Just the two of us?
Yeah. We are, we are.
Okay.
So maybe I just
talk to your video.
Ask where all your
deputies went?
Okay, well, why don't you
just ask your governor
about her little Catch
and Release policy. Okay?
Because if it wasn't for that,
maybe I could hold
on to my deputies
and the people we arrest.
I know... I know one of them
was fired for excessive force
and another one
was forced to quit
by a YouTube first
amendment auditor.
Yeah. Okay. Yes,
that is the same auditor
that drove away your
worthless police department.
Your Under sheriff died
from a fentanyl overdose.
From handling fentanyl. Okay?
And your Captain and
your Chief Deputy...
He confiscated it
without gloves.
-...took jobs in Rio Rancho.
-That was devastating!
You can't keep your
own office going,
but you're gonna run mine?
Leave your mess here and
start a whole new one.
And I do think it's
because of the person
that's name you might not
want me saying on camera.
Oh, s-say her name.
Okay? Because I think you're
the one that doesn't want it.
I do think it's because of that.
Is that what you think?
Well, I'll tell you
what I think, Ted. Okay?
I used to think that
you were some big deal,
but now I realize, and I can
tell you flat-out to your face
that I am a much better
human being than you.
And I'm gonna make a
better, and stronger,
and more honest leader than you.
So let's just let
the voters decide.
You're making a mistake.
Is that why you ran
here all panicked?
I came to save you
from embarrassment.
Oh, gee-whiz, I'm tearing up.
Forfeiting 30 years
of property taxes,
and you won't say because
of some NDA you signed,
but you want a "yay"
from everyone here.
He explained this
already, Paula.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Explained what?
Why doesn't he explain
about the water and energy
these data centers consume
when we're in a
historic drought?
-We're always in a drought.
-Yes, exactly.
And we're making
up for the energy
and water with the solar
that we're bringing in.
Okay, so... so let's
talk about the solar.
No. Uh, I'm sorry.
You know what?
Can we call the question, Phil?
We've got to just call it.
Excuse me?
Okay. All right. Uh, item 50.
Third reading of a
resolution approving...
What?
...a series of six
industrial revenue bonds
for the construction of a, uh,
proposed hyperscale data campus
in Eddington, New Mexico.
Excuse me? A question
needs to be seconded,
and I am the
agreed-upon Chairwoman.
Point of order!
Can we not fucking
shut this bitch up?
Just chill.
Question has been called.
I've got my second.
Mask over nose.
Like you're writing.
Hey, you know,
you might actually read
that while you're reading
because you're
forgetting half of it.
Ted, hey,
this is what you
need to focus on,
not your dumb-ass Sheriff.
Just the shit with his
wife's mental health,
-we shut him right down.
-I've said it already.
I don't want to go
there. I meant that.
-So you fucked her...
-No!
-It's a small town.
No, I did not.
I went out with her a couple
of times 20 years ago.
She was weird. She
wouldn't let me touch her.
I didn't want to touch her.
So I dropped it.
And then out of nowhere,
her whackadoo ma
came after me, like,
six months later
when she got
apparently pregnant.
That was six months after
I never touched her.
You see how that sounds, though?
And her mom, who is
crazy, is very online.
Oh, before I forget...
The Governor says thank you.
Well, that's nice.
Would have been nicer in person.
Yeah, well, you
get that through,
you can tell her yourself.
Be in her office when
she goes to Washington.
Hey!
Whose car do you think that is?
-You said I could.
-I said what?
You said I could borrow
the car to hang with Brian.
What do you think you're doing?
You said I could borrow the car.
What's this I'm hearing
about a gathering last
week, and you were there?
If you mean Saturday, that
was, like, five people.
We were double-distanced
and we all wore masks.
That's not six feet.
Excuse me?
Just who do you think
you're talking with?
-Sorry.
-We are in lockdown.
I'm the one forcing lockdown.
Anyone sees you out at a
gathering late at night.
It's not late and
it's only five people.
My son undermining my policies.
You catch this, and
you could die. Okay?
-Do you know how death works?
-Yeah. I'm just trying
-to see my friend...
-No more Brian.
So I don't have to kill myself.
Just go. Out of my face.
Only Brian. Only!
It's Mom's birthday, by the way.
Good for her.
What am I supposed to
do with that, Eric?
You want to send her a
letter? I'm just saying.
-She ain't dropped us any pins.
-Okay. Whatever.
-Who cares?
-And wash your hands.
Covid stays alive on
paper for five weeks.
When my son and me
woke up one morning
to find that my wife, his
mother, had abandoned us
without a note, without a word,
we were devastated.
All hope seemed lost.
But we had our
community to lift us up.
We had Eddington.
And when I first ran for Mayor,
it's 'cause I wanted to
give back to the town
that has given me so much.
Since then, we've
helped the Governor
in her mission to start building
a 100% clean energy economy.
We're working to provide
homes to new technologies
and create new,
reliable, secure jobs.
And as we walk
towards the next term,
I'm ready to continue
leading our town
and fighting the pandemic
and the racial and
economic inequities
that Covid-19 only made worse.
Racial inequities? What the
fuck is he doing to fight that?
Well, he's Hispanic.
Okay, but who are...
Where is he getting
these Black ladies from?
What, is he shipping
in people now?
What is this? The Jeffersons?
Re-elect Ted Garcia for mayor.
We can't go back. We
can only go better.
Race you to come up
with a better slogan.
And you too.
I already put eight
of them on the board.
-Oh.
-Uh, well...
How about... Wait, so...
theirs goes, "We can't go
back, we can only go better."
So we go, "Yeah,
we can't go back,
but we can, like, you know.
We can learn by our mistakes."
Yeah.
And Bitcoin.
Use it to get county residents
on the block chain, too.
You know, get 'em motivated.
-Hey, before I forget.
-Hey, Sheriff.
-I got in with the city clerk...
-Back up.
...and we need a
chairperson and a treasurer.
Hey, Sheriff, look at this.
I got 43 names on
the petition...
-Hey, finish this up for me.
-...but we're gonna need 150.
I ran through the
council meetings
that are all on YouTube.
You're gonna want to see this.
The man that's forcing
this item through
is a man that turned off
his people's lights
in the middle of a
global health pandemic.
What about their businesses
that you shuttered?
You already got the state
to make that nice road
that you say is for tourism,
but all I see is it leads
straight to the site
of this hypothetical
data campus.
Pardon me. Is Paula in?
So what is Solidgoldmagikarp?
Is it like, what,
Microsoft or...
Oh, not even. It's
some random AI
or Deep Learning or some crap.
Warren's the one that got Ted
to run in the first place.
Land commissioner is his, too.
Okay, I'm gonna go.
What would I say?
I-I wouldn't say anything
'cause she's annoying as fuck.
She's worse than my dad with
her social justice shit.
-Where are you going?
-Getting another beer.
Dude, you have to drive us back.
Oh, shit, I love that book.
Sorry, what?
I love that book.
You know she was awarded
the Lenin Peace Prize
by the Soviet Union?
Oh, really?
I'm Brian.
Hi.
I know you're Sarah.
You were, like, a year
above me, I think.
Okay.
It's weird to be
gathering, right? Like...
Feels like this will be
in the news in a few days.
Superspreader.
Sorry.
You guys want a beer?
-Sure.
No. No, you're fine. She's
just doing her own thing.
Oh. Okay. Cool.
So, wait, what did he say
when he came up to you?
He said something
about my book...
Who's your friend?
I don't know.
She's just trying to make her
old-ass boyfriend jealous.
She has a boyfriend?
Where is he?
Not here.
Oh, there he is.
They're not dating anymore.
She dumped him
because he's a cop.
Or then he broke up
with her. Whatever.
So many privileged white kids
suddenly crying about
"anti-racism", it's just like...
Yeah, no. I get it. It's true.
I mean, really, it's just
another display of privilege.
Yeah, but like,
at the same time, not all white
kids are all that privileged.
Uh...
Like, there's different
sorts of privilege.
You know, like race and class.
Did you drop your red
cap back there, Bri?
Shut up. You know what I mean.
You know, I'm promoting you.
Really?
I mean, I...
Don't you think?
Yeah. Of course.
So, what? Uh...
Sergeant?
You like that?
Y-Yeah. Thank you, Sheriff.
You know, I'm actually
older than my dad
when he was Sergeant.
Well, your dad was Captain
when I was deputy.
So, you know, we all
got to take these steps.
He only ever made it to Captain.
You know, hopefully one
day I'll earn Captain, too.
And, uh, Sheriff, this...
this ain't 'cause of the news?
What news?
Yeah, cool. Great.
Hello? Lou?
...ruin a man's day,
-or you can do...
-Hello?
Lou?
And that's why I'm
running for Mayor.
Mayor of Eddington.
I have, uh, served
this county as sheriff
for seven years, and
it has been my honor,
and I would be honored to
serve you as Mayor. Okay?
And I will continue
to fight for you, uh,
even if it's against
the government,
okay, if that's what that means!
Uh, because w-we need to
stop these lies. Okay?
We need to reopen
our businesses. Okay?
Covid may be a problem,
but it certainly
ain't our problem.
Thank you super-duper very much.
Ladies and gentlemen,
what have you, this is...
The image is true,
language is evil.
Now, your physical body
might have been assaulted,
as mine was. But we
are evolving right now.
And this now is not natural.
We are being invaded.
Human thought is
being phased out.
It is against God,
what is happening.
There is a new God arriving.
Hey. Hey.
Where were you?
You don't tell her
what you're doing.
Lou.
Why should she tell you?
Hey. Where were you?
I took her to a talk by someone
she actually wanted
to listen to.
Baby, let's... Ooh.
This is how you defend her?
By abandoning your office?
Lou, come on, open
up. Let's talk.
Has she not gone through enough?
I was worried about you.
Where were you?
I'm doing this for us, Rabbit.
Okay...
I should have told you first.
I just... I got so excited,
and I didn't want to overthink
it, so I just did it.
But I should have told you.
I'm-I'm sorry. I just...
This whole town is
just lying down,
and if we see what's happening,
and we see that it's wrong,
and we can't see this
as an opportunity to...
to do the right thing.
We can... We can
bring this place back.
We can build it back up.
Lou?
Did you know
that this used to be
a copper mining town?
You need to be quiet.
I'm sorry.
I don't know how you don't
remember what they said.
About her not having stress,
about how she can't have stress,
but I can't.
So... I'm not being dramatic.
I cannot slip again.
Y-You won't slip.
I'm gonna catch you.
People are gonna be
looking here now.
-No, no one's looking.
-And sticking their noses in.
-No.
-And shaming her.
Try to say "me,"
baby. Not "her."
You really just
don't give a damn
what happens to his department?
I mean, you hardly did
before. But, I mean...
I don't want this thing
with Ted. You understand?
Okay.
This is your thing, and
it's Mama's, it's not mine.
Okay, but I'm-I'm
defending you, Rabbit.
Let the child ventilate.
Let's have dinner tonight. Okay?
Baby, I'm your husband,
and I will not do anything
you don't want me to do.
Your real husband wouldn't
have to say "I'm your husband."
Dawn, please! Okay?
He'll listen to you,
he'll understand you.
He won't have to wave
your vows in your face.
Let's just get
together. You and me.
We will make a decision
together as a team.
If you want me to
retract it, I will.
Absolutely, no problem.
Just, yes, you, me,
dinner, tonight. Can we?
-Fine! Fine!
-Please? Yes?
-Just go!
-Yes. Okay. Okay. I'm going.
Dinner tonight. Dinner
tonight. Thank you. Thank you.
Hi!
If you ever look at the
Mayor's Advisory Board...
Well, that board
is actually one man
and that man is Warren Sandoval.
Eddington's quote... "City
Economic Development Official."
And when Mayor Garcia talks,
it's Sandoval's
voice you're hearing.
But who's Sandoval speaking for?
It ain't you!
Maybe it's for your Governor,
who he's been on vacation with.
Maybe it's for the
people that got the mayor
to get that expensive
new road built
out there in the
desert, with your money!
Did you ask for that?
And did you know
that it leads out to a
top-secret development
just within the city limits?
Well, you should!
They've annexed 800 acres,
it has been re-zoned,
the development and
utility agreements
are getting into place.
Replacing your businesses
with their server farms.
Solidgoldmagikarp. Look it up.
This is Deep Learning.
That is deepfake
from the deep state.
And to whose benefit?
The same people
that always benefit.
It's not you.
Bro. Bro, who are
you talking to?
There's nobody here.
And here we've got an
Eddington youngster
who has yet to
join the workforce.
You should tell
them about the time
my dad dumped your wife.
The fuck?
Fucking faggot.
Shit.
Hey, do I cut or...
Yes! Yes! And delete
that last part.
Of course.
The part with him talking.
Yep. Yep.
Fuck you, too.
-Sheriff! Sheriff!
-What?
Hey, hands up, don't shoot!
Hello.
What are we doing here?
-What is this?
-We have a right to assembly.
Assembly? For... For
what? What are we...
No justice! No peace!
No racist police!
Racist police? Who?
A third of my
department is fucking...
Come on, guys.
Get out the street. You're
blocking through traffic.
We don't need police permission
to protest police
violence, Michael.
Police violence?
But what violence are
you talking about?
Now, kids, listen here.
This is not legal.
-So if you could please stand...
-Slavery was legal!
During slavery it was
illegal to free a slave.
What about the Navajo Long Walk?
What we did to them
and the Apache?
That's all the
same government...
Okay, you can always
tell when somebody's
learned something new
in Social Studies.
A man was just brutally...
-Just get on the sidewalk.
-...brutally murdered by a cop.
That didn't happen here.
It happened! Is that not enough?
Fucking traitor!
This happens all the time!
Brian, Daniel, Michelle,
whoever you are, do
your parents know...
Just take this to the sidewalk.
...you're here
making some trouble?
Okay, I didn't make Covid. Okay?
I'm not the reason you're
all being locked in.
Call whoever the fuck you want.
-What?
-Call whoever the fuck you want.
Okay. Uh, listen.
I'm leaving now
for five minutes.
When I come back,
I expect you gone.
Five minutos. Disperse!
Michael, you should
be with us. Come on.
Black Lives Matter!
The man identified
as George Floyd
by the lawyer
representing his family
was later pronounced
dead at the hospital.
Today the mayor called
it wrong at every level.
What we saw was horrible
and utterly messed up.
Okay, what was he being
detained for in the first place?
I don't know, but I heard
something about
excited delirium.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, and what's
going to happen when
they release the footage
of him resisting?
Are they going to
get their jobs back?
So you saw this yesterday?
Mike, you saw it yesterday?
-Uh, yeah.
-You didn't say anything?
You okay?
-I mean, it...
-Well...
It was everywhere.
Jesus Christ.
There's already
riots in Minneapolis.
Breaking into stores,
stealing shit.
I mean, what's it going to prove
if you set your own fucking
neighborhood on fire?
What the...
"Pig roast"?
What the fuck are these
fuckers doing, man?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Now they're driving
into churches?
Sheriff, look at this. These
cops are just letting it happen.
We got to be ready.
They're coming here next.
-You know they are.
-Okay.
-Bunch of fucking hoodlums...
-All right! Look.
That's not a here problem. Okay?
It's... It's bad. It's an
awful tragedy, okay? It's bad.
But i-i-it's a bad apple that's
across the country, okay?
Now let's just let our
kids blow off some steam.
Michael, are you okay?
Yeah.
I got no cash, bro.
I will make you cash!
My tooth's infected.
How many people did you invite?
There should be more coming.
Yeah. No, just because there's
a protest at the Round
House in Santa Fe,
and that's where we
should actually be.
Like we've got to be careful.
We can't just feel
happy with ourselves.
Yeah. I mean, I obviously
agree with that.
Yeah, and sorry, but you called
yourself anti-racist earlier,
and we can't just take that.
Like, do you know what
that would actually
take and mean?
Because I'm not an anti-racist
either, but right now
we're playing at maybe
being, like, White Critical.
Maybe we're White Traitors,
but the goal is to be
White Abolitionists.
And that means actually...
...changing institutions,
dismantling whiteness
and not allowing whiteness
to reassert itself.
But we're pretty much
light-years away from that.
Are you fucking retarded?
What the fuck are
you talking about?
You're white.
And that really gets
it nice and creamy.
Let's put in some olives,
so that we build the flavor.
Oh, yeah. All of
it. That's great.
Capers. You like
capers? I like capers.
Remember to film
Mikey's promotion
and to put it on
TikTok or whatever...
Whoa.
Before you vote,
remember Schott Solar...
60 million dollars in
grants in the garbage.
Those were the same
kind of high-interest
bonds he's bragging about here.
All right, council
member Garcia moves to...
It's multi-generational.
You commit suicide,
you can't be buried in
the Mossad cemetery,
so why's he there
if not as a message to say "It
wasn't suicide, we killed him"?
Joe?
This is the son-in-law.
-Joe?
-Yeah. Hey.
I am so sorry.
-Oh, yeah. Here we go.
-I texted you,
but it never went
through, I guess.
And a bouquet. Sheep's clothing.
-So sorry.
-Hi, there.
Son-in-law? Husband?
Sheriff? Mayor?
Well, mayor-to-be.
Well, we'll see.
Yeah. Joe Cross.
Sorry. I'm... Hello, I'm Vernon.
-Vernon.
-Yeah.
Oh.
J-Jefferson Peak?
Yes.
How you doing?
I'm Joe. This is my home.
-This...
-Uh-huh.
Is Nicolette and
her husband Will.
Are you kids hungry?
How much did you make?
Well, enough for two.
It's cold. That's too bad.
Please sit down.
Please. Would you
like to sit down?
Thank you.
You guys sit.
Uh, well, where are
you all coming from?
A potluck.
With no food.
Well, can I offer you, um...
something? Some... Anything?
No, no. We're stuffed.
You mind if I...
These are amazing.
Yeah, those are all Lou.
She's been making them just
like that since she was ten.
Since you were ten.
Oh, it's just a hobby.
Everybody needs one.
The worst times
in my life is when
I fell out of function
with my hobbies.
Yeah, and they've been
selling really good, too.
That one must be new.
Oh, it's... it's been
there for a month.
God is speaking through you.
I'm sorry.
That's Lou's father.
The original sheriff.
He passed away seven years ago.
You were with him.
His heart just stopped
in his chest, apparently.
Who knows if he could
have actually made it?
I do.
When my dad died, my
brain completely reset.
He was a civil engineer in DC,
working for the government.
Just like you're about
to, right? When you win?
Well, not... not
for the government.
For the people.
Is the idea.
Your brain reset how?
What does that mean?
Breakdown.
It took five years
experimental therapy
to unlock even just
fragments of memories.
Some of which were that I'd been
very effectively brainwashed.
We talked about this.
Um... What were the memories?
The memories are
of being gifted off
by my father, to his colleagues.
Who exactly they
were, I don't know.
I do know there
were ten other kids,
and we were taken to
a private forest grove
in Northern California
where we were stripped nude
and photographed and...
things I hope you can't imagine.
And then they released us,
and they hunted us down.
And I escaped.
I was the only one to escape.
And those are my memories,
which are now extremely vivid.
So if they were
hunting you down,
why would they release you?
The game was to catch us.
Well, okay.
Um, I want to be
respectful here.
Um, but I-I just...
I don't understand.
I mean, you... Who did this?
And... you were the
only one to escape?
You say you were a child.
Your question is to
make me feel shame.
I didn't escape on my
own. I couldn't have.
Joe, you want things
simple and neat.
You think that because
something's evil,
there can't be love.
When there is love,
that's the slavery.
And evil is sentimental.
And a predator can fall in love.
And he can help
his victim escape.
And I can't say his name...
But they called his
death an overdose
just five days
after he let me go
and my father, who sold me,
committed "suicide"
that same week.
I understand.
It is unbelievable. It
sounds insane to me,
just hearing it coming
out of my own mouth.
My brain still
hasn't truly accepted
that I'm actually talking about
things that happened to me.
Yes, it is, um,
hard to believe.
And...
I mean, I'm sorry.
I cannot imagine...
You can imagine. You know it.
It's easier to not get it.
It's evil.
Your father was sentimental.
Oh.
What does that mean?
We are in a fight against evil.
And part of that is
fighting against denial
and denying denial.
Now I just told you my story.
Will and Nicolette
helped each other
escape a ten-by-ten foot cellar
when they were pre-teens.
You go to Brussels next week.
Their testimony's under review
by the International Common
Law Court of Justice.
Evil!
If you want to know a society,
you look at what it
does to its children.
What you two went through?
What your daddy did?
Lou. Sometimes, baby,
it's just to listen.
You cannot just ignore!
The average pedophile abuses
between 50 and 100 children
in their lifetime! Per abuser!
And they keep these kids quiet
so that they think that
it's just... It's only them.
That it's this rare thing
that only happens to them.
And they do fill these kids
with shame because they...
they want them to
never even ask,
or never even realize
that maybe this happens so much
because there is this
whole entire network,
that maybe all these demons
-are in league with each other...
-Okay. Okay! That's enough!
I don't even know what
this is. I can't... No.
Last night was the same thing.
I've had two hours
sleep in two days.
I'm sorry, I can't
just let you turn this
-into a free-for-all.
-You know what that is.
It's at herself.
It's late.
I'm just going to wash this.
Hey.
Hm?
Can I ask you something?
I-I've been meaning
to ask you...
And... And I won't ever again.
All those things that
you were saying outside?
Uh, all those things that you...
...the things you
were saying earlier?
Did your dad...
Did your dad... ever... t...
Or... Or... Or...
Or was it Ted?
Was it Ted?
Was that what it was?
Is that what it is?
Hello. Yeah.
Sheriff, the riots,
they're here.
They're on Broadway,
right outside.
What? Where? Where?
-You got to get over here.
-What? Where? Where?
They're on Broadway.
They're right outside.
We... We could use
your help over here.
-Hello?
-Where the hell are you?
All my goddamn windows
smashed to hell,
and I can't get a...
We got to just, obviously,
cancel this town hall.
-No. That is not obvious, Paula.
-Yes, it is.
This is a blip. We
will disperse it.
What's a blip?
Oh, no, my signs.
What's wrong?
Jesus!
Nothing. Dog in the road.
Dog in the road. Uh...
Damn. Uh, I'll call you back.
What?
The cops and the Klan
go hand in hand.
The cops and the
Klan go hand in hand.
Why aren't you out there?
I was, but they're filming.
Why do I even fucking
have you guys?
They're trying to use
us being out there
-to make it worse.
-Sheriff, I know. Okay?
I'm the one with
the speech tonight.
But my two deputies,
whose only job is this...
But Sheriff, I did...
...but how is it
that I'm the one...
-...going out there?
-I did go out there.
We went out there. We
both went out there.
Sheriff, there's
been new information,
and it changes
the way we engage.
It's simple, but
you got to see it.
Sheriff, they're just
trying to piss us off
so they can film us
and use it against us.
I know, Sheriff, it's
going to be fine.
No!
Ain't nobody coming
to protect us.
We got to start our own...
Shut the...
-Oh. You see it's not at all...
-Mike.
-...like fascists in Michigan.
-Do you understand this?
Do I understand what, Tooley?
I just know you were
dealing with it yesterday,
and I'm wondering why it's
ten times bigger today.
Yeah, with the Sheriff.
And it's ten times
bigger everywhere.
What the fuck?
Yeah, don't on purpose
misunderstand me, man.
I'm just asking you
a normal question.
What is going on?
There is a riot happening
right in front of your faces,
-and you're checking your email?
-I know! I know!
Sheriff, when we go in there,
we're going to need a
direction of clearing,
a direction of movement.
Look, we cannot let Paula shut
down the town hall. Please.
It's too important.
Sheriff, the state police say
they have no more
available units.
They've deployed
everybody to Albuquerque.
Listen. Stay cool.
Okay? And stay together.
Yes, sir.
Step over to the side for
your own safety, okay?
Our priority is your safety!
Step back.
-Please step out of the road!
-We understand your frustration.
We're trying to keep
you safe. Can you relax?
Hey! You can't do that! Hey!
Hey, back it up! Back it
up! Hey, can you stop?
We understand what
side you're on.
If you're gonna help,
stand over here, okay?
Everybody, for your own safety,
please get out of the street!
-We're a peaceful protest.
-You do not have a permit.
We don't need a permit.
Yes. You go to the county
commissioner's office.
We appreciate your service,
but we do not need
you guys today.
You need to have a permit
in order to be here in
the middle of the street.
Actually, this is
public property.
It's not safe...
Are you a lawyer or something?
-This is public property...
-Get up out of the...
...and the First Amendment says
we do have the right to convene.
Our institutions are
protecting murder!
Does your dad know that you're
out here creating this circus?
We're talking right
now on stolen land.
Stolen land!
Whose stolen land?
Stolen from who?
Yeah, and we're calling for
the defunding and abolition
of the corrupt and
homicidal police state.
Defunding?
What are you talking about?
Do you want to see my budget?
Yeah, I would... Don't put
your fucking hand on me!
I'll put my hand where I want.
Now listen here, you
little son of a bitch.
What the fuck?
Okay? You just need
to shut the fuck up!
Sheriff, look at this!
Look what they done.
Thousands of dollars
in goods they took.
John, I know. Now...
Maybe you shouldn't
put racist fucking
lawn jockeys in your
racist fucking store!
You fucking Nazi!
I'm a Nazi? You're fucking
destroying property!
Gloria? Oh, my
God, baby, it's me.
-Baby, it's Daddy. It's Daddy!
-Get the fuck away from me!
-Who the fuck are you?
-I'm so sorry.
-Get the fuck away from me!
-They took you!
They took you from me!
It's not my fault,
they took you from me.
Michael.
Do you just not even
care about what happened?
I'm seriously asking
you, not as a cop.
-Seriously.
-Yeah, it's an outrage.
It's a horrible incident.
Nobody hates fucking
bad cops more than cops.
Bad cops? Evil
fucking racist cops!
You're wearing the
uniform of a system
built on hundreds of years
of institutionalized racism!
You know you got Aryan
Nation boys with you?
-You know that, right?
-No! Fuck off! Michael.
Your family is fuckin'
ashamed of you!
Michael, not that. Can
I just say something?
You should be joining us! Do
you even know why you aren't?
This is... I know I have
not experienced racism,
but you... you have!
This is not my place!
This is not my fight!
I am a hypocrite.
I know that, but all I can do
is stand here and
fight for justice!
-So stand with us!
-Do us all a favor.
-I am so serious.
-Can you take a kneel?
Shut up. No.
Guy, do not engage!
Listen, you've got
to protect Paula's.
They're wrecking
everything, okay?
Get over there, right now!
-That is our priority.
-Yes, sir.
Police violence in Eddington!
Do you even know what
your dad really is?
Do you know what he has done?
You mean to your wife?
-What?
What about your mother?
Where is she? Huh?
Do you ask these questions?
What about your fucking
crazy whore wife?
Her bat shit mom
sending crazy shit
to my house my whole life!
Maybe that had
something to do with it!
I was just trying to
explain the situation here.
Okay? Everything is...
Everybody calm down!
Everyone! 8 minutes and 46
seconds on the ground now.
Calm down!
Yeah. Now this is
how you do a protest.
John, I will be right back.
Yeah, right.
Were you even here?
Okay.
Hey, what these people want...
-Pardon me.
-...will not stop.
This is a good message.
This is good. Peaceful.
No more violence.
It doesn't end
until they pull you
out of your bed in the
middle of the night...
No violence, just peace.
...and who are
you going to call?
-But the violence...
-What the hell?
...the violence just angers me.
You want to defund the police?
There won't be any
police there to call.
Hell yeah, brother.
And if the people go home and
get their guns and come in,
and the threat sees
this, they will leave.
They will leave.
-Go home and think about it.
-Peaceful!
Shit, shit, shit. Fucking shit.
Yes. Okay.
Yes. Damn.
Hey there, everyone. Hey.
Well, this is nice
to see. Finally, huh?
Dining together.
Community. I almost
forgot what this was like.
Paula, thank you so
much for opening it up.
It's so good to see
everybody. Yeah.
Hey there, Ralph. It's, uh...
Real good to see everyone. Hey.
Um...
Well...
Uh...
I was hoping for
a better turnout.
But, um...
But how's anyone
supposed to get here
when you got to
wade through that?
And my deputies are-are
keeping it safe.
Uh...
And yes, these protests,
it's a real thing, okay?
There is an imbalance
in this country.
And what happened to
that man... undefensible.
Absolutely disgraceful conduct.
But I am not the
problem here. Okay?
And if... if you believe that...
d-do you really think that
the power is with the police?
It's the leadership.
The... The power is with the
leadership of this country
on down to the leadership
of this community.
Okay? Now do you want
to talk about brutality?
I have kept this town safe for
the better half of my life,
but if there is one thing
that I feel shame about,
truly, it is in keeping quiet
about something that
I shouldn't have.
Okay? About Ted Garcia.
Our mayor.
Because the man is...
purely and simply...
a predator.
Okay? Yes. Ted Garcia
is a sexual predator.
I know. I see your
faces. I know, okay?
How do I know this?
Well, I should know this.
My wife, when she
was 16 years old...
he gets her pregnant.
Forces her to abort.
Tiny little innocent
baby. Murdered.
And Ted turns his back.
Her life is ruined.
Ted's life? Ooh. Well,
he's off to the races.
And for what?
Well, you vote him
back into office,
and you're going to
find out for what.
Okay? And you look
to his own wife.
But you can't. Why?
Because she's gone. Took off.
Okay, now that is
none of my business.
I can only speculate why.
But let me tell you something.
You look to history.
And what that man did to
my wife, my darling...
Let me tell you something.
That is predator behavior.
It is, okay? And what's worse...
is it's...
It's...
It's rape.
Let's call it what it is.
Let's face it. Statutory.
Ted Garcia. Let's
call him what he is.
And we're saying it,
and we're going to be saying it
in the days and the weeks ahead.
Because that is what
this election is about.
So you vote Joe Cross.
Take back our community.
Save our soul.
Thank you.
Wow. Good?
Post it.
Okay. You sure?
Just don't make
me think. Post it.
Stand up, fight back!
-What do we want?
-Justice!
-When do we want it?
-Now!
If we don't get it...
Shut it down!
Shut it down! Shut it down!
...did not let
Ethereum's price fall
below $201 level.
Ethereum is trading much above
its 20-day exponential
moving average.
Baby?
I-I had to. He cannot
get away with it.
Baby, is that for here?
Please...
Have a good night, brother.
The way you did it is repugnant,
but tonight's the
most you've ever done
for that girl in your life.
Whether she sees it
or not, I don't know.
Yeah, this is my
fourth message now.
What you done today...
no matter what excuse
you come up with,
no matter when you
come to your senses,
you have wrought
destruction upon our home,
and upon me, and on Facebook...
With words that don't even...
I... What are you saying?
Your life is a fiction?
So who then? Who is your abuser?
Am I? You say the name
if you call me a liar,
your mother a liar.
With no warning and no honesty.
Just poison.
Bitch!
The name I have now
is Louise Cross.
I was born Louise Bodkin.
And I am speaking now
to deny my husband's
announcement yesterday,
which was false, and a
falsification of my true life.
I was abused, but
not by Ted Garcia.
That is a fiction
invented by my mother
and kept alive by
her and my husband.
But it is not my shame,
it is my abuser's.
And he was one of millions.
I am one of millions.
We are not a coincidence.
Hey, Sheriff. You okay?
Sheriff, we got a noise
complaint on the mayor's house.
I guess he's doing
a-a fundraiser.
Is it too touchy?
Do we leave it?
We do leave it, right?
Yeah, of course we do.
Sheriff?
What are we doing here?
♪ Make 'em go, "Oh, oh, oh" ♪
♪ As you shoot
Across the sky-y-y ♪
♪ Baby, you're a firework ♪
♪ Come on, Let
your colors burst ♪
♪ Make 'em go, "Oh, oh, oh" ♪
♪ You're gonna leave 'em
all in awe, awe, awe ♪
♪ You don't have to feel
like a waste of space ♪
♪ You're original, cannot
Be replaced if you... ♪
What are you doing?
You're not here on rape charges?
That didn't really pan
out for you, did it?
♪ Make 'em go, "Oh, oh, oh" ♪
♪ You're gonna leave 'em
all in awe, awe, awe ♪
♪ You don't have to feel
like a waste of space ♪
♪ You're original,
Cannot be replaced ♪
♪ If you only knew
What the future holds ♪
♪ Maybe a reason why all
the doors are closed ♪
♪ So you could open one ♪
♪ That leads you To
the perfect road ♪
Turn the noise down!
♪ Like a lightning bolt,
your heart will blow ♪
♪ And when it's
time, You'll know ♪
♪ You just gotta ignite The
light and let it shine ♪
♪ Just own the night
Like the 4th of July ♪
♪ 'Cause, baby,
You're a firework ♪
♪ Come on, show 'em
What you're worth ♪
♪ Make 'em go, "Oh, oh, oh" ♪
♪ As you shoot
Across the sky-y-y ♪
♪ Baby, you're a firework ♪
♪ Come on, Let
your colors burst ♪
♪ Make 'em go, "Oh, oh, oh" ♪
♪ You're gonna leave 'em
all in awe, awe, awe ♪
♪ Boom, boom, boom ♪
♪ Even brighter than
the moon, moon, moon ♪
You're going the wrong way!
No, I'll go in your blood.
I'll be your poison!
You put this in me.
No. I was holding her hand. No.
It was right after ballet class.
She said, "Bread
pudding, bread pudding."
I said, "No, baby, no.
I can't get you dessert.
I can't get you dessert."
Why'd you let go of my hand?
I was still holding your hand!
It tastes the same.
Just tastes the same.
Wine into water.
Wine into water, wickedness.
Wickedness! Wickedness!
Why?
You poisoning me?
I'll poison you!
I'll pump in your guts!
I will pump until you blow up!
I'll infect your home!
I'll infect you
from the outside.
You want me dead?
I'll be the death of you!
You devils! You
called this plague!
You don't want me. You
don't care about me.
Give her back. Give her back.
Eric?
Yeah?
I thought we agreed absolutely
no one in the house.
-Yeah, I know.
-So what's this purse?
What purse?
Come here and look
at what purse.
You think I didn't see
you with that little girl?
Eric, you should be...
Dad?
Hi, you've reached
Louise. Leave a message.
Hey, Rabbit.
ID?
I was exposed to somebody
a few nights ago,
and he definitely had it...
Yeah?
Sheriff.
You need to be ready.
It's really bad.
But I think you
might be Mayor now.
Who-Who's that?
Oh. He's new. I think that's
the next door property.
Is that Brian? His friend?
Whose friend?
Yeah, must be a neighbor.
And...
Well, hi, Tam.
She found the body.
Hey, Sheriff.
You found it?
Yeah, I did, Sheriff. I-I
called you as soon as I could.
I didn't go in, but Sammy
broke off from my walk,
and he went in,
and I tried to get him
back as soon as I could,
but he was in there and I
think he was licking things.
And I tried to get
him back, and...
Okay.
-I called you. I'm sorry.
-What is that?
Yeah, she called them, too.
Well, just in case they
needed to see. I...
See what?
They have been waiting outside.
I guess this is
the Pueblo border.
No, this is not. Negative.
-I think it is, though.
-It is.
We're on the county line.
This is Sevilla County.
But on the other side of
the house, that's Pueblo.
It's the same at mine.
Oh.
Is that Butterfly?
Yeah, Detective Butterballs.
And that's the Pueblo
Sheriff down here.
Pueblos don't have sheriffs.
He's not even police.
But he goes around
and blesses shit.
Apparently he's in charge
of all Pueblo matters.
This is not a Pueblo matter.
-I know.
-We are Eddington.
This is Eddington.
Well, what the hell is that?
There's been more
lootings in town, too.
Shops all smashed up.
That's BLM talk.
You've secured the
search warrant, right?
I did. It has been signed.
I got a runner bringing it down.
Mm-hmm. And, uh, what about OMI?
I didn't want to call
them until you got here.
I called them.
They're on their way.
Needle in a
haystack, but I found
a single five-five-six casing.
Uh, okay.
Well, what...
Just put it right
there on the counter.
Uh, how... how many
impacts you count?
Well, don't worry about it.
I-I also found good quality
tire tracks back there.
Truck or SUV.
What are you even doing here?
This is our crime scene, and
you are contaminating it.
Now get out of here!
Okay, let's focus.
DRT here. DRT there.
Sheriff, I tried to
get some CCTV footage.
Hard-drive got took.
Bless you.
That's for a handwriting expert.
Look... Look at those "E" s.
Uh-huh. Okay,
but, well, look at this. Now
what is this? A ladies purse?
-Guy, would you come help?
-Yup.
This here...
Whoa, whoa. What are you doing?
Forensics.
Ah, shit.
Well, it's compromised,
it's too late. Go ahead.
I'm getting to be really happy
you guys don't help
us with jack shit.
Oh, but now you want to help us.
With all your resources?
Same resources as you.
-More technology, more people.
-Sarah Allen.
-We've got gloves.
-Born 2001.
That's the girl
that was shrieking
at you during the riot.
Look, she's got the
Blacks Lives Matters pin.
All of this is getting
thrown out now.
You understand that?
Unless you find a judge
even stupider than this one.
Hey, don't you have some
sort of alcoholic domestic
at one of your casinos?
This ain't yours, man.
The shooter's on tribal
ground. This is a Pueblo case.
Give me your evidence
and get on down the road.
Victim was here, okay?
This is where the
harm was committed.
This is our case.
Well, we got the shell casing.
Congratulations!
Do what you want with
the shell casings.
There is no cross
commission here.
We respect your sovereignty.
Respect ours now.
Oh, you respect our sovereignty?
Okay, let's call
the Feds and the BIA
and see what they
want to do. Easy.
Okay. Uh... Let's, um,
go talk to this Sarah
Allen because I...
All right. Well, we're
going to take it from here.
Don't let him dink
with the crime scene.
What crime scene?
It's your toilet now.
Officer Jimenez, can you
please leave the property?
Watch how you approach me.
Okay, so you were there
with your boyfriend...
He's... He's not my boy...
He wasn't my boyfriend.
-I barely even knew him.
-Okay, you're in his house...
-I was hardly there.
-You were in his house.
And then later that night,
he's dead, his dad is dead.
Are they... Are they really
dead? Like how do you know?
Yeah, well, we were
there. They are deceased.
And, um... And your
purse is there.
Sarah, we went
through your socials.
You didn't do yourself
any-all favors.
I'm not trying to...
For example, here's
a quote, from you.
Uh, "Free your communities,
arm yourselves..."
No, that's completely
taken out of...
I don't... I don't mean
literal arms. That's not...
It's preaching
rioting and looting.
Do you know, being an
accessory to terrorism...
I'm not a part of any terrorism.
...is terrorism.
That doesn't make... The looters
and rioters, they are separate!
I'm not any part of that, and
none of the protesters are.
The rioters, they're being
planted by the Right.
They're trying to make it
look like it's the protesters
so that scared old white
people won't complain
when Martial law happens!
Uh, good afternoon,
ladies and gentlemen.
My name is Joe
Cross. Joseph Cross.
Sheriff of Sevilla County.
Last night around midnight,
Mayor Ted Garcia and
his son, Eric Garcia,
were struck down by
cowardly sniper fire.
Now, I do believe we
have sufficient evidence
to believe that the perpetrator
was a member... or members...
of the Antifa terrorist group,
capitalizing on the
recent tragic events
in Minneapolis to sow chaos.
Now, to the criminals
that committed this act:
you will soon find out
what justice looks
like in Sevilla County.
You will find out. It
will not be tolerated.
And now a personal
message to the individuals
planning to take
their criminal conduct
out of the streets and
into the neighborhoods.
I would tell them:
if you value your life,
you should think twice,
because the people of
Eddington like guns.
And I encourage
them to own guns,
and they're going to be
in their homes tonight
with their guns loaded.
And if you try to break
into their homes to steal,
to set fire, to commit
physical injury and/or death,
then I'm highly recommending
that they blow you
out of their homes
with their guns.
Eddington, New Mexico,
despite its meager population,
is quickly being co-opted
in online circles
as a poster town
for anti-government,
anti-police violence.
Meanwhile, Albuquerque's new
public safety department,
designed to relieve stress
on the city's police,
will deploy unarmed personnel
made up of social workers,
housing and
homelessness specialists
and violence prevention
coordinators...
Ooh.
Thank you.
I had to post a whole
statement against her video.
And her phone's not ringing.
Vernon blocked me.
Can you try her again and
see if it rings for you?
I've been trying.
It's not working.
So what does that mean?
Did she block you?
Did something happen to her?
Did you pay the phone?
So she did? She blocked us?
How did she meet Vernon?
Did you introduce her?
All I did was I-I
encouraged her to
do her own research.
And she was mad at you, so
I took her to Albuquerque
because he was there to do
that talk. That lecture.
I didn't like some of the
things he was saying, but...
I was so relieved that
she was getting involved,
and I thought her head was
coming out of the sand and...
I actually ain't leaving
until something is done.
Yeah. Um...
Sheriff. The kid says
he'll only talk to you.
He's been avoiding eye contact
like he's on something.
I saw him at the riots.
The next morning,
after I sent the picture to,
uh, him, out there...
To... To Michael.
-Yeah, Michael.
-Okay.
The next morning,
I-I went to Eric's to see if...
You know, if...
See if that girl
was still there,
if she slept over or whatever.
Sarah.
Yeah.
Uh,
but that's when I
saw police cars.
Okay.
Um...
Uh...
Yeah, you just sit...
sit tight, okay?
And, uh...
Hey, Guy, get in there. I
got to go grab my phone.
Hey! You need any help?
Do you know... Do
you know Michael?
No, no, no.
I did see him talking to
Sarah at a protest, and...
I mean, he...
He looked like he
could kill somebody.
Like he...
But obviously I didn't
actually think that.
We gotta get to his
place, like, now.
Before he can flush anything.
Look, can I leave?
Can you not do
anything with me here?
You can step outside, Brian.
He's ambitious.
He's been cozying up to you,
you know. Getting real close.
Maybe he kills the mayor,
then you win, and you
help him get sheriff.
I don't know.
Uh... Maybe he's been
spying this whole time.
What whole time?
I mean, his dad was here first.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm not trying to
make this about...
I didn't even see the
race with Michael,
until all this Blacks
Lives Matter stuff.
But now here it is. Okay?
So... So who is he now?
Is he more of an
officer or more...?
But we need evidence.
I mean, that's just motive.
I mean, I have motive.
You know, and Eric wasn't
white, he's Hispanic.
Yeah. Blacks hate
Hispanics, too.
All these other colors
are just fake minorities
stealing their coupons away.
They hate them more
than they hate whites.
Okay, Mike.
Just... There were
some allegations made.
And, uh, we need to specifically
look at your Instagram.
Just so we can clear you. Okay?
Allegations like... like what?
We just need to take a look
at your Instagram
messages, specifically.
And, uh, that's it.
We'll be done with this.
It's okay. All right, come on.
So...
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm just documenting that
this message has been
opened, as you can see.
Okay. And, uh,
hmm...
What?
Yeah. I know. Eric
Garcia, right?
Mikey, well, it's
Eric Garcia and...
with this young lady that
you have a connection to...
Connection? Hardly a connection.
I hardly know her.
Does that say something?
I mean, it is the day before
he got fucking shot, Mike.
And he's taking pictures
with your little girlfriend.
Tooley, I swear to God, man.
Okay.
Hey.
Mike, how old's this girl?
I don't know. Like 18.
Like 18? So not 18?
She's definitely 18. Is
that what the allegation is?
Mikey...
Sheriff, my point is,
I hardly know her.
And we haven't done anything.
All right, look, it
didn't bother you
when you got this photo?
It doesn't bother you
to see her like that?
No. I mean, the only
reason that bothers me
is because someone was
trying to bother me.
But then I completely
forgot about it, Sheriff.
Sheriff?
Yeah.
Could you, uh, step
outside, please?
Can I step inside, please?
We got a 10-80 in the back seat.
Now, why wasn't this
checked in immediately?
Checked in?
I would've checked it in
by the end of the day.
Sheriff, you knew I had
the gun out for practice.
You're the one that
told me to practice.
It's just a coincidence, right?
That it's just the same
caliber as the murder weapon?
Sh... Sheriff, you can
give this to ballistics,
and you will see it's
not the same gun. Simple.
Okay, we got to search the unit.
I mean, what for? We
already established
the gun's in the
back of the car.
You know what for.
-Okay? Is that all right?
-What?
You don't need my permission
to search my unit.
I know I don't need
your permission.
I'm just asking you.
And I got nothing to
hide, so we can proceed.
Good, good. Come on.
Let's give him a
little bit of space.
Who? Excuse me.
I don't give my
permission to him.
Hell fucking no.
I don't care if you
give him permission.
No, but I don't trust him.
I don't care if you trust him.
Okay, fine, why
don't we just get
our Pueblo friend to do it?
Since you're just... everywhere!
You know, third
party, no conflict.
Okay?
-Fine.
-Yeah?
Yeah.
Hey, you have gloves?
Got a bag.
Got something.
What... What's that?
What the fuck is that?
I've never seen that before.
"To a marvelous mayor."
-It says that?
-This is his fucking watch.
-Sheriff.
-Excuse me.
What the fuck?
That wasn't there...
What do you mean?
Do I have permission
to arrest him?
-Can you believe...?
-Hands up, Mike.
-This doesn't even feel real.
-Come on, Mike. Hands up.
-Don't go near your weapon.
-Hands up for what?
-Okay.
-Sheriff, here's his weapon.
He's been disarmed.
What is going on
right now? I can't...
I've never seen
that watch before.
-Hands, Mike!
-It's impossible.
Hey, easy! Take it easy!
All right, step inside
the cell please, Sergeant.
Hey, Guy. Put this into
evidence and send the gun
-out to the lab, okay?
-Hey, Sheriff.
Sheriff, if I'm
really being arrested,
I need to make my
phone call. Please.
All right.
Sheriff, please. Please
don't do this to me. I'm...
Hey.
I haven't done anything wrong.
Uncle Jamie, uh,
it's me, Michael.
I'm in the hol... holding cell
at the Sheriff's
Office in Eddington.
I-I've just been arrested,
and I'm being set up.
They're planting shit on me,
and they're saying
that I killed...
...I killed the mayor and... and
his son, and... and I didn't.
I'm gonna need some help.
I'm gonna need a lawyer...
I love you and Aunt Kyra.
The meaning of a
candlelight vigil
is different for everyone.
Candles get lit one by one.
It's a symbol for spreading
a message of support
from one person to another.
As darkness surrounds us,
a good man and a
bright young boy
struck down before they
could do their work
towards real progress
in this town.
Progress towards a
better, more equitable,
more connected future.
Work that will still be done,
and we'll see to it
that it is done...
in their memory and their honor.
Hello? Help!
Hello?
Pueblo Police.
My daughter went
off with a man...
-I'm sorry.
-...and I think that they
or she, or he were just here
because when I came back,
-all her stuff was gone...
-Ma'am.
...all her artwork and
the car and everything.
I'm just here to ask you if
there's a gun in the house.
-Sheriff.
-They took everything.
Sheriff, are you there, Sheriff?
Yeah, but have you seen
this AR in the house?
I have no idea.
Do you think he could
have done the murders?
His name is Vernon Peak.
Yeah?
Sheriff, we got a
dumpster fire in the back.
He was a person of color
who beat the odds to
become a person of power.
And they got killed
by that same system.
Even the killer's
a victim of it.
And I'm a part of it.
I'm just another
privileged white kid...
...and my job is to
sit down and listen,
which is what I plan to do
after making this speech,
which I have no right to make!
This vigil is happening
on stolen ground!
I was putting the stupid
watch and gun into evidence.
Oh, the watch and
gun are stupid?
I swear on God, Sheriff.
I wasn't gone for
more than one minute.
You weren't supposed
to be gone at all!
Shit. Where the fuck is
the fire extinguisher?
I already used it.
It wasn't enough.
-I know. I know...
-What?
I know, I know, I know.
Th... This is the new thing.
This happened
after I called you.
What the fuck am I looking at?
Whose fucking key is this?
-This your key?
-I don't know. No!
-No? Then why did you open it?
-No!
What you're seeing
is what I saw.
What do you mean?
What am I seeing?
I don't even know what
the fuck I'm seeing!
You are how I was.
You're not making
any fucking sense!
Somebody had to
let him out, right?
You take Zia, I'll take Main!
Hands, Mike!
Put your hands behind your head.
Put your hands behind
your head, Mike.
Turn around and walk
backwards towards me.
Down on the ground, Mike! Down!
Now! Get down on the ground!
What the fuck are
you doing, Mike?
Sheriff, he won't listen to me.
He's just standing there. I
don't know what's going on.
Mike, what the fuck, man?
Mike.
The whole place smells like gas.
What the fuck?
Mike, please, man!
What is this, Mike?
Mike! Put your hands
behind your head!
I can't. I can't.
What are you saying?
What the fuck is going on here?
Put your hands behind
your fucking head, Mike.
They said if I talk or move,
they're gonna shoot me.
I don't...
What do we do?
Should we advance?
Do we fall back?
Can we fall back?
This feels really
not good, Sheriff.
I've got cover! Go, hands on!
No. No, no, no! No. Stop!
Freeze!
Put the bag down.
Rabbit?
I knew you'd come back.
It's because of what
I did, isn't it?
I'm being called upon, aren't I?
Am I being called upon?
They're-They're coming after me.
Is what I'm supposed to do...
Is this... Am I supposed to...
Do you want me to finish this?
So...
it was Vernon. And Lou.
I need to leave.
I cannot be here.
What if they're back for us?
If they did kill Ted... What
if they're back to kill me?
I killed Ted.
I did it.
Vernon... Vernon is a fake.
He was a false temptation,
and she let herself get
tricked, and she went with him.
I'm the one that's taken action.
All I had to do was start it.
And now I have to finish it.
We are in the center
of it right now.
We are in history.
See?
Get down!
My back!
No! Is it them? It's them!
Is it them?
It's Vernon, they're
trying to kill me!
Freeze!
I'm going to shoot!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, Sheriff.
Oh, my God, are
you okay? Sheriff?
Sheriff, I saved you.
I saved you.
Oh. Oh.
-Jesus.
-This guy is barely...
105. Take him to the tent.
Look at this guy.
There's no treating
this in the tent.
105, he goes to the hot zone.
Come on.
This one's done anyways.
Crazy.
105. What do you
want me to say, man?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, Sheriff.
Oh, my God, are
you okay? Sheriff?
Sheriff, I saved
you. I saved you.
♪ I've been holding onto pieces
Swimming in the deep end ♪
♪ Tryna find My
way back to you ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm needing
A little bit of love ♪
♪ A little bit of love
♪ Lately I've been
Counting stars ♪
♪ And I'm sorry that
I broke your heart ♪
♪ It's something that
I didn't want for you ♪
♪ But I'm stepping
On broken glass ♪
♪ And I know This
is my final chance ♪
As a firm believer in truth,
self-defense, Second
Amendment rights,
it was hard to do
what I had to do.
But I had to do
what I had to do,
which we all have to do
when it's our time to do it.
So what do you think
about Michelle, Big Mike?
Do you think he's actually
going to run for President
or is he going to stick
with his diet camps
and keep talking
about health foods
instead of his husband's war
crimes and drone warfare?
What's up, Gainesville?
New homeowner in town.
New house, new us.
Gator Nation,
baby. Let's get it.
♪ These open wounds
Ain't healing ♪
♪ Tryna find My
way back to you ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm needing
A little bit of love ♪
Okay.
I'll show you the rest later,
so I don't get us pulled over.
And when they broadcast
the 18 gigahertz
signal from the 5G system
employed all across the world
for one minute three
different times as a pulse,
it'll cause those
lipid nanoparticles
that are baked into the shots
to swell and release
those pathogenic contents.
But today is about
a major step forward
in the tech industry
here in New Mexico.
And my son-in-law,
the Mayor of
Eddington, Mayor Cross,
wants to take this opportunity
to give a warm thanks
to Solidgoldmagikarp
for choosing as their home
Sevilla County and
Santa Lupe Pueblo,
on whose shared land this
data center now resides.
We are now, both and together,
one of the privileged places
where the future is being built.
And at this moment,
when unheard of, wicked things
are being perpetrated
by our government...
World Economic Forum,
population control through
disease and vaccine,
with the people that
created the virus
now giving us the cure...
All of us Useless Eaters.
The opportunity at
this dark moment
to sculpt a brighter future
is something to be cherished.
And earned.
We are now home to an advanced
supercomputing infrastructure
powering the future
of a technology
that will indeed
change everything
and solve problems we've
never been able to solve
and all the while using the
least amount of energy and water
as any data complex
in the southwest!
Sir. Sir, pardon me, sir.
You do not have
permission to film here.
This is a private event.
And that's because of
what we're doing in solar.
And what the
Pueblo's doing, too!
They got their new
wind farm building up,
taking part in New Mexico's
370-billion-dollar investment
in renewable energy.
Pushing advancements in wind,
in solar, in geothermal,
and soon the Governor's hoping
to announce hydrogen, too!
Plane hits a building,
two buildings,
they don't fall that way.
That's how they go with
controlled demolitions.
You detonate the bottom.
Why am I just noticing
that you need a haircut?
Did you have a good day?
I did. I may have had a
little too much to drink.
There's never been a
licensed MRNA vaccine
and that ain't because there
haven't been clinical trials.
It's because there were
significant adverse effects
on the animals
they tested it on.
And the deepfake of Uncle Joe
getting his jab is
no contradiction.
The man in the video had arms
hairier than any ape.
I'm surprised they didn't use
their AI Picasso
to fix those arms.
I'm sorry.
I went a little too
far with the blush.
They have deprived
you of your identity.
And that deprivation
and that slavery
keeps you from being an
agent of actual change,
and it keeps them
right where they are.
Well, guess what?
You are not alone.
Guess what? Your pain
is not a coincidence.
You are not a coincidence.
We are not a coincidence!
Will you fight?
I will!
I'll do it for me as a child,
and I'll do it for
my future children,
and I will do it
for your children
and your future children.
And I will do it for
their physical bodies
and I will do it for
their digital bodies.
And I will win
because I have fortified
myself in Christ,
and I'm talking about the
Lord Christ, Jesus God!
And with the Holy
Spirit as our shield...
Good night.
♪ Said he'd build
me A courtyard ♪
♪ He promised he would ♪
♪ And spend time
In my courtyard ♪
♪ Whenever he could ♪
♪ In the corner, a tall tree ♪
♪ So shady and cool ♪
♪ And a white marble fountain ♪
♪ In a clear, sparkling pool ♪
♪ A lovely stone courtyard ♪
♪ With a lacy iron gate ♪
♪ And a bountiful garden ♪
♪ Where I could wait ♪
♪ Yes, he built me a courtyard ♪
♪ Like he promised he would ♪
♪ And I know that
He'd come to my side ♪
♪ He would if he could ♪
♪ Patterns On a
courtyard floor ♪
♪ Illusions of all
I'm living for ♪