That dry wall again.
Hi. I've got a surprise
for you.
No.
What if you've been hounding me
for like over a year?
I'm serious.
An actual lipstick carousel?
I found it on a state sale.
I told you it was gonna be
a blessing to move up here.
I still need to check
the state of the motor
but it's in pretty good shape.
I'll text you some pictures.
Or, you know,
you could use it as an excuse
to come up and see the house.
Well, you got to come up
and visit sometime.
I'm telling you, this house...
something about it
just drew me to it.
Okay, yeah. I gotta go.
I'll text you pictures later.
Bye.
Oh... Hi.
Do you like your new home?
Yeah.
Me too.
Oh, Oh. Ma'am, ma'am!
You can't be in here.
Uh, the floor's not safe.
Oh.
I'm just trying to establish
what kind of time frame
we're talking about here
since we have the baby on the...
- Ah...
- Hey!
- Hi!
- Did you just get in?
Yeah. I tried calling you.
Oh yeah. No, sorry, we just...
Ah, it's just plumbing
Armageddon situation.
- That sounds promising.
- Not really.
How bad is it?
It's not great.
The amount of rock that
I can see in the sub floor...
The drain's probably
been leaking for years.
And they didn't find any of that
in the inspection?
They probably missed it.
But look we can handle
the re-pipe.
But you're gonna need
a structural engineer
to take a look at that floor.
Anyone you recommend?
Uh, I can make some calls.
- Thanks.
- I'll get on that.
Yeah, so that's my day.
Miss, miss? Found this
lodged in the drain.
Oh.
I know how you gals,
you're all sentimental
about your jewelry.
- It's not mine.
- Nice bloke, though.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, come on.
Let me get to that suit.
Hi, Lou.
- Ah, this is unbelievable.
- This is nonstop.
As soon as we finish one thing,
something else explodes
or rots or leaks.
It's like we're living in a
in a never-ending game of the...
You know what's the thing
where it pops up and you...
- Whack-A-Mole?
- And you whack 'em.
You sure it's a Whack-A-Mole?
Ah!
Why can't anything be easy?
Hey, I'm easy.
House is disintegrating
around us
and you are cracking jokes.
Hey.
It's an old house.
We knew what we were
getting into.
Hmm.
It'll be great once it's done.
You'll see.
We'll get through it.
You're right. We always do.
Hey yo, watch out!
No. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Lou?
Ssh.
She's looking for you.
Oh, my God.
- You scared the shit out of me.
You wanna put me
in premature labor?
Come here.
I wanna show you something.
Huh?
What do you think?
Yeah, nice work, Professor.
Ahan. Who says intellectuals
can't be all manly?
Ooh. And all that.
Check this out.
Baby TV, over here is up
and running.
We are live.
As you can see a motion detector
and oh, a microphone.
Hey, baby.
And it's all operated
wirelessly.
- Pretty cool.
- Pretty impressive, right?
Here. What?
You're forgetting something.
Oh shit. Is that the...
I need to shower
or we're gonna be late.
You're going...
You gonna wear that?
- Yeah, you don't like it?
- No, I love it. Beautiful.
- Just to impress, right?
- Fetching.
Looking gorgeous.
Remind me again
who we're supposed
- to be impressing tonight?
- Uh, Dean Whittier.
Is that the guy
with the moustache?
No, no, that's Barkley.
That's uh... that's the chair.
Oh, God. Everyone in Academia
looks the same.
It's all smoking jackets
and facial hair.
Just look for the guy with a mo.
So, tell me
how did you two meet?
We met the old-fashioned way.
- Yeah...
- We met at a bar.
Right.
I was out one night
having drinks with friends
and I spot this guy alone,
sitting at the bar.
I just got in the country
and so I was...
So, he finally works up
the nerve to come over
and he offers to buy me a drink.
Well, I actually bought
a round of drinks for her
and her maids.
It was all a trap...
Which was a rather
steep investment on my part
- during that time.
- Oh, okay.
Apparently,
I was worth the splurge.
- Well, apparently.
- I was a little tipsy.
- And we get to talking.
- That's right,
and she tells me about
her antiques business, right?
Hm-mm.
And, he mentions this old watch
he has
and he's been meaning
to get it restored.
So, I said
I'd take a look at it.
Which was a lie, of course.
- There was no watch.
- No watch.
And I just wanted
to see her again.
So, I spend the next 24 hours
scouring all of lower Manhattan
trying to find a watch.
I find one, I bring it to her.
- Total fake.
Hm-mm.
It wasn't my proudest moment,
but still works.
And I got a date out of it,
didn't I?
Thank you.
Tuna tartar?
I wish. Thanks.
Don't worry.
You'll be eating it all again
soon enough.
My downfall was always
the cheese.
So, where'd you end up settling?
We bought a house by the lake.
Oh, it's stunning up there.
John and I have toyed
with the idea
of moving up there for years.
- Which property?
- 8317 Lake view.
Oh yes.
I knew a man who lived up there
many years ago.
Unfortunately,
his wife became quite ill.
Anyway, you must be
over the moon.
- It's your first?
- Ah.
- Yes. Yes, it is.
- Brilliant.
A new job and a baby on the way.
So much to celebrate.
Cheers.
You heard Bartlett
raving about my work
on the advisory committee?
I mean, I'm telling you Jules,
there's a real opportunity here.
I'm gonna play my cards right
and I could be running
the department
in, I don't know, five years.
Huh? Everything okay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
You barely said a word
the whole drive home.
You told that woman
this was our first.
What would you have me say?
I passed it as an exactly
cocktail conversation, Jules.
You don't have to lie about it.
Well, she asked
a simple question.
I... I gave a simple answer.
Right.
God forbid,
you upset our fancy new friends.
Hang on, Jules. Jules, Jules.
It's not like that.
You know it's not like that.
There's people
in the department,
people that were way before,
that know what we went through.
I mean, isn't this meant to be
a fresh start for us?
You know,
giving this a fresh go.
How are we gonna do that,
if we're just clinging
on to the past?
Daniel, he was your son.
It's like sometimes you forget
he even existed!
And you forgot he ever died.
No. Jules, please stop.
Please, just talk to me. Wait.
Jules! Jules.
- Vitals?
- BP of 149 over 90.
I need a Doppler and an IV.
How far long is she?
Thirty-two weeks.
Ma'am, can you hear me?
- Good Julie, one more.
- One more, one more.
Go, go, go.
One more. I know you're tired.
- Go, go, go.
- One more, one more.
Got ya. That's it, that's it.
Start compressions.
- Why isn't he crying?
- It's fine. Jules, it's fine.
Is he okay? What is happening?
- What's happening?
- It's alright.
- Can I see him?
- Just try to relax.
Why isn't he crying?
I can't hear him.
Let's go again. Right now.
- What's going on with my baby?
- He's fine, right?
Julie, I'm so sorry.
Hey.
You're in the hospital.
You had a bad fall.
- Is she...
- She's okay.
Baby's okay.
You suffered what we call
a partial placenta abruption.
Abruption? What's that?
It's when the placenta
becomes partially detached
from the uterine wall.
Is it dangerous?
Well, it can be life-threatening
if the placenta fully separates
but as you can see,
the tear appears fairly minimal.
And so far the situation
seems to be stabilized.
Bleeding stopped
and your baby's
got a good strong heartbeat.
However, it is standard practice
to exercise caution.
What does that mean?
It means I want you on bed rest.
Strict bed rest for the duration
of your pregnancy.
No driving, no lifting,
no cooking.
Other than the occasional trip
to the bathroom,
you need to be in bed idle.
You're saying you want me in bed
for the next eight weeks?
I know it's not ideal.
But we don't want you going
into early labor.
Anything before 37 weeks
is considered preterm
and can put the baby at risk
of low birth weight
or respiratory distress.
We're in the middle
of a renovation
and we're overseeing everything.
I would strongly recommend
putting any major projects
on hold,
until after the baby comes.
Do you have any family
or friends in the area?
Anyone who can help you out?
Not since we moved, no.
Well, if you need support,
we'd be happy
to offer a referral.
Any other questions?
When can I go home?
To avoid preterm labor,
you need to follow
a few simple rules.
One, you need to remain
in bed 24 hours a day.
Two, you're allowed brief trips
to the bathroom
and one ten-minute bath
every three days,
no more.
And finally,
the most important rule.
It's crucial
that you avoid stress.
Anything that raises
your blood pressure
not only endangers the health
of your child,
but could re trigger
the mental dissociation
you experienced
after your last pregnancy.
My advice, try to enjoy the R&R.
Alright. Here we go.
The brakes.
And easy. Easy does it.
Let me take this.
Alright, there we are.
I'll get the shoes.
Yeah, gonna get rid of these.
Right. Let's get you on the bed.
- Alright, you good?
- Yeah.
Alright.
Right. Now, you ready for this?
Because I have you
all hooked up.
- I'll supply it.
- Got you some lotion,
- got your some prenatals.
- Oh.
- I know what you're thinking.
- How you're gonna reach them.
Well, I got you
this cool grab stick.
You can just,
you know, try it out.
Nice.
Here some trashy magazines,
I know you love those.
Read it to your heart's content.
An iPad, your laptop and uh...
oh, vintage
entertainment system.
Very vintage but courtesy
of the English's department's
- uh... supply closet.
- Wow.
It's old but antique, maybe,
you know?
Maybe it's worth a fortune.
No?
Mini fridge, stacked full
of amazing awesome shit.
Because that's kind
of a husband I am.
Oh, and the best part.
- Walkie talkies.
One for you.
Eighteen channels,
23-mile radius.
So, we can communicate
anywhere in the house.
Anywhere.
Or we could you know, text.
Yeah, but what's the fun
in that?
Try it out.
Go on, turn it on.
Attention all units...
Ssshhhh. No, no, just um...
Get to change the channel.
We can ignore that.
Just uh, uh...
next, next channel. Shit.
Got it?
Break a break.
It's big daddy,
come in hot mama.
Got any request?
Ah, sure could use a cup of tea,
big daddy.
Ten-four. Hot mama.
Shot of hot liquid lightning
comin' up.
Over and out.
- Go say over.
- Over and out.
Nice. Alright.
Oh, and uh...
don't you go anywhere.
Three times faster
than our leading competitor,
Our little one...
Mommy must be hearing things.
The breeze.
The winds now fasting up to 39.
So, this just gives you the idea
that the winds are going to...
Looks like we have some
weather rolling in.
Maybe they'll cancel
your classes
and we can bed rest it together.
What do you think?
Binge-watch Grey's Anatomy?
Eat our weight in popcorn.
- Are you listening to me?
- Yeah no.
Um, this funny thing happened
in our faculty.
Meeting today,
and I'm just texting...
Hahaha. LOL.
What happened?
- With what?
- In your meeting?
Oh. Well, you had to be there.
Otherwise, it's just...
stupid.
- What's that?
- What's what?
That, the package right there.
Oh, that's just some stuff
that I ordered for the house.
Did you...
did you go downstairs
and get it?
Jules, you know
what the doctor said.
- You can't
- I was careful.
Doesn't matter!
There are rules.
You can't get up.
You can't just...
just move around.
- He made it very clear...
- Jesus! What are you?
My frickin' jailer.
"I can't get up.
I can't walk around."
I can't go outside.
I can't continue
with this renovation
cause God forbid the fumes
and the noise,
might cause me undue stress.
Getting that stupid box
was the highlight of my day.
I just...
It sucks.
I get it. I do. I...
I am sorry. Alright.
Hey. I am sorry.
I just don't know I...
I worry, you know?
Thank you.
Thank you for doing this for us.
And thank you for being
on your best behavior.
Your mommy and I
really appreciate it.
I love you.
Goodnight.
Night.
- Hm?
- Wake up, wake up. Wake up.
- What?
- There's someone in the closet.
What?!
Fucking shit!
Daniel.
Oh. You scared this shit
out of me.
- You sure you're feeling okay?
- I...
Jesus.
It's probably
just your sleep mind, alright?
Let's get some rest, love.
Come.
You were supposed
to pick them up from school!
Where were they, Todd?
Girl, you need that kick
that man to the curb.
Hey there!
What you doing?
Ssh.
Haw. Hide and seek?
Where's your mama?
Goddammit, Lou.
Lou! Get off! Off! Yes, off!
9-1-1, what's your emergency?
Please help.
There's someone in my house.
What's your address, ma'am?
8317 Lake view. Hurry please.
- We have a unit on the way.
- Are you in a safe place?
I'm in my bedroom.
And where is the intruder?
Down the hall.
Is your bedroom door locked?
No.
Ma'am, can you get to the door?
Ma'am?
Yes.
Jules?
Hey. You alright?
You okay? Yeah?
Daniel Rivers.
Deputy Gates.
We spoke on the phone.
Alright, yes. Any more news?
No. Still unable
to locate a suspect.
Did you get a look at the guy?
Didn't turn up a child, either.
A child?
Your wife thought she heard
a child in the house.
Well, looks like we've got
everything we need.
If there's anything else
we can do,
just give us a call.
Right, yes.
Of course, thank you Officer.
Here, I'll walk you out.
Sorry for wasting your time.
Go ahead and say it.
I know you're thinking it.
Should I be worried?
There's just a misunderstanding.
You don't believe me?
What am I supposed to think,
Jules?
Mental dissociation
or a fixation on a child?
- I saw something.
- That wasn't there.
I feel like we're on a verge
of something here. We...
I need to know
that the past is behind us.
that you're not relapsing.
It's not like last time.
I'm calling Doctor Meadows.
I'm going to bring you
someone in.
- I don't need a babysitter.
- It's not for you.
It's for her.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
Can baby sister
come out to play?
Andrew?
Andrew? Is that you sweetie?
It's mommy.
Can you come back please?
Please? Can you hear me?
Jules?
Hey. I heard the door slam.
- You alright?
- Yeah.
I was just trying
to Facetime with a friend.
It's not working.
Right.
Hey. Hi, I'm Daniel.
One-nineteen over 80. Very good.
Delmy.
I never heard that name before.
It's pretty.
It was my grandmother's.
A fine German name,
as my father would say.
May I?
One-forty. It's perfect.
How have you been sleeping?
Hm, not great.
That's the irony of bed rest.
All the time
in the world to sleep
and unable to do it.
Do you have kids?
Um, my husband and I tried
but my body just wasn't
equipped for it.
I'm sorry,
I shouldn't have asked.
No, please.
Sharing my journey is important.
In my experience
there's more than one path
into motherhood.
I consider myself a proud mother
of the countless babies
I've helped bring
into this world.
Daniel told me about your son.
He also told me about Oakview.
How long were you there?
Six weeks.
Post partum depression?
It was part of the psychosis.
I kept seeing my son.
My mind wasn't ready to let go.
I know it's difficult bringing
a stranger into your home.
But I want you to know
I'm here for you.
Whatever it is you're feeling,
whatever it is
you're experiencing...
you can trust me.
I appreciate that.
You should get some rest.
Easy.
There you go.
I can manage from here.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'll be in the other room
if you need me.
Oh God, no.
I thought she'd never leave.
Baby sister coming.
Delmy!
Well, probably just
a Braxton-Hicks contraction.
Is it uncommon?
Just the body's way
of preparing for birth.
She's alright?
The baby's fine.
To be honest, it's you
who I'm concerned with.
I understand
you've been having some uh...
some experiences.
The insomnia
has just been messing
with my head a little.
Tell me about the boy.
How old was he?
Four, maybe five.
The age your son would be now?
Perhaps your mind remains
unwilling to let go,
even after all these years.
Would you uh...
would you mind giving us
a moment?
Uh, yeah.
Julie, no one ever said
that bed rest would be easy.
And more often, than not
the psychological challenges
outweigh the physical ones.
Especially for someone like me.
As I see it,
we have two options.
We can move you to the hospital.
That would allow to finish
your pregnancy
under the supervision
of a highly qualified
medical staff. Two...
No.
No more hospitals.
The other option is you remain
here at home.
My caveat being you have
to restart your medication.
What about the baby?
You are 35 weeks along.
The meds would have little
to no impact
on your baby's development.
Right now,
the most important thing
you can do for her,
is to take care of you.
Try to get some rest.
It could be
an isolated incident.
Or, it might be a precursor
to a more significant
psychological break.
And she clearly thinks
she's seeing
your previous child.
The medication should alleviate
her symptoms,
but if they do persist,
you may want to consider
admitting her
to a mental health facility.
It's for the best.
Good girl.
Lou.
You wanna play, buddy?
Alright.
Alright, you ready?
You ready? Here you go.
You see him, too?
Andrew?
Sweetie, are you there?
Baby sister wants to see you.
Don't you want to come out
and play?
Are you here to see baby sister?
You should leave.
What do you mean? Why?
She wants baby sister.
Who? Who wants baby sister?
You almost done in there?
Just a few more minutes.
No. No, wait.
Please don't leave.
I want to know
who wants baby sister.
Don't want you pruning
on my watch.
Here we are.
Nice and warm.
We gotta take care of our baby.
Did you feel that?
She kicked for me.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Must not forget your pill.
I'm just asking you
where you found her?
Well, I got her number,
I told you from the hospital.
I told you that.
Right. But did you call
her references?
Did you do a background check?
Anything?
Meadows recommended her,
so, I didn't think
it was necessary.
I mean, she is...
lucky she was even available.
I want her out of the house.
- Are you serious?
- Yes!
Delmy is a godsend.
- I don't trust her.
- Why?
I just don't.
That woman, she's the reason
I'm able to go to work
and not endlessly worry
about you all day
being here by yourself.
So, if I'm gonna let her go
or even consider that,
then I... I think I deserve
some kind of explanation
or reason why something.
Fine.
Go on.
The boy I've been seeing,
he's not in my head, Daniel.
What are you talking about?
I've been hearing him
in the nursery
through the baby cam.
Daniel...
- it's our son.
- Stop it, Julie.
- It's Andrew.
And I know it sounds crazy,
but he's reaching out.
- Jules, Jules, please.
- Please don't do this.
- He's trying to warn us.
- Please...
He's trying to warn us
about Delmy.
- What are you talking about?
- She wants our baby.
And that's why
he's reaching out.
- He's trying to protect us.
- Stop it. Stop it.
Stop it! Stop!
Our son is dead. He's dead.
You think I don't know that?
You think I don't know that?!
You think that fact
doesn't burn a hole
in my heart every goddamn day!
I was the one that held him!
Praying for him to breathe.
So, you don't have to tell me
that he's dead, Daniel.
I was there.
Everything okay?
- We're fine!
- Yeah.
- Daniel...
- Just...
You two are getting friendly.
Have you been taking
your medication?
- Have you?
- Don't you dare blame this
on some fucking
chemical imbalance?
You're seeing our dead son,
Julie.
So, just for a second here.
Imagine though what its like
from my perspective.
I know what that's like!
I am well aware
of what you think of me.
I hear the whispers,
I see the look on your face.
That awful mix of pity and fear.
I know you think I'm cracking.
That I'm on some hormonally
fucked downward spiral
but I'm not.
And if I were you, I...
I'd probably be on the verge
of hospitalizing me too.
But it's not in my head.
It's not.
Daniel... our son.
Our son, he's reaching out.
He's trying to communicate
with me.
And instead of your judgment,
I could really use your support
right now.
I'm sorry, Jules.
I think you need more
than my support.
Okay, call me then.
Nice and strong.
- You should eat something.
- I'm not hungry.
You know we all want
what's best for you, right?
I lost my first child
at 18 weeks.
Pregnancy was going alone fine
and out of the blue,
my water broke.
An incompetent cervix.
That's what they told me.
I managed to conceive
three more times
but never carried any to term.
I felt so hollow, so alone,
kept... asking myself
what I'd done to deserve it.
And I remembered a story
I'd heard as a child.
About a family who lived up
around this lake.
Three small kids,
mother pregnant with the fourth.
She and her husband
were on the way to the hospital
in early labor when their car
skidded on some ice.
Crashed into a tree.
The impact taking the life
of their unborn daughter.
The woman was inconsolable.
Every night,
her cries could be heard
around the lake
lamenting the loss
of her baby girl.
She didn't eat,
barely left the house.
The faces
of her three living children
just reminded her
how she'd failed as a mother.
How she could never truly
protect them.
And eventually,
it just became too much.
She took her own life?
That story reminded me
that I wasn't alone.
That mothers have been
bearing the burden of loss
since the beginning of time.
But it's what you do
with that pain,
that defines you.
A mother's grief
is a powerful thing.
You either learn
to make peace with it
or it eats you alive.
What was her name?
The mother?
Oh um, Kinsey, I think.
Melandra Kinsey.
You should try
and get some rest.
M. K.
Courier Archives.
Hi. Uh, I was wondering
if you could help me.
I'm trying to track down
an old news story
that your paper
may have covered.
How far back you're talking?
Um, late 60s, early 70s.
Uh, doubt it.
Our digital archives only cover
the last few decades.
Unless it was a major
news story.
What are you looking for
exactly?
Uh, it was a suicide.
A local woman
named Melandra Kinsey.
- Let me get your email.
- I'll see what I can find.
Andrew, sweetheart.
I need to ask you
something important.
Hi, sweetie.
The person
who wants baby sister,
is it someone named
Melandra Kinsey?
Andrew?
Where'd you go?
Delmy! Delmy, need help.
What is it? A contraction?
How many have you had?
Julie?
There was someone.
How long?
Twenty, 30 seconds.
It could be early labor.
Let's start monitoring
and see if it progresses.
Wait!
I'm just gonna get my kit
and throw on some clothes.
No, no. Please don't leave.
There's nothing to fear.
You're bringing a baby
into this world.
I'll be right back.
Oh, my God.
Ah. You're having contractions?
It's early stages
but if she progresses
we'll head to the hospital.
It's happening, Jules.
We're havin' a baby.
Baby sister coming.
You okay?
We have to go.
- Nooo. No, no, no.
- Hey, hey, hey Jules. Relax.
- No need to rush.
- It's an early labor.
No, it's not safe.
We need to leave.
- No, no Jules. Jules relax.
- Wait.
Let me go.
Julie, you need to listen to me.
It's very important.
- Relax.
- No, there's no time.
There's no time.
She's already here.
- Who? Who's here?
- Melandra Kinsey.
Julie, Melandra Kinsey's
just a story.
No, she's not! No, no, no.
I found her name
in the change of title.
She lived here.
Look. This was her bracelet,
Daniel.
Jules, Jules.
- She killed herself.
- Please sit down, Jules.
- And not just that. She killed her three kids.
- Love...
She couldn't cope with the grief
- of losing her baby girl.
- Can you...
And... and she took them
with her.
- Just sit down please.
- She drowned them all in the bathtub.
It was a long time ago.
You knew?
You loved the house.
I just wanted you to be happy
so, I was protecting you
as well.
For what? Lying?
By deliberately withholding
the truth from me.
Cause I was scared!
Do you know
what it was like for me?
Coming home and finding you
in a pool of blood.
Watching you struggle
day in and day out
after Andrew dies, and...
and I just... I can't...
And I can't help you.
This house made you smile
again, Jules.
Made you happy.
But you didn't believe me.
I told you
that there was something
going on in this house
and you wouldn't listen.
Neither of you.
You both made me think
- that it was all in my head.
- Just...
Because it is all in your head.
Hey love. Just...
No, it's not Daniel.
It's not all in my head.
It's not.
Melandra Kinsey is here.
- Please. Julie.
- She's in this house.
Julie.
And she wants our baby!
Jules.
What the hell.
Better hide. Mommy's coming.
Get the chair. Get the chair.
We're getting out of here.
Come with me. You alright.
Leave her alone!
Daniel.
Let's go!
Come on.
Daniel. Oh, Daniel.
Honey. Daniel?
Hey, Daniel.
Fuck you!
Hello.
Can anybody hear me? Hello?
My name is Julie Rivers.
I live in 8317 Lakeview Drive.
I need help. I'm in labor.
Great, Julie.
We're doing this right now,
sweetheart.
Okay, don't think. Just push.
Push. Give me everything
you got, Julie.
Keep going, keep going.
You're right there.
- That's it, that's it.
- That's it.
Hi.
It's okay, its's over.
You don't get this one, bitch!
Jules!
Jules! Jules!
Okay.
Come on. Oh, come on, please!
Don't. Stop.
- Take her.
- No. No.
Just get her out.
Go.
I'll come right back.
Get away from her.
This is my child!
Get out!
Daniel, you okay? Daniel?
Help! Help! Please, my wife.
Jules. Jules.
Hey, hey. Jules.
Hey! In here!
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go right.
Sir, I need you
to clear the scene.
- Sir, what's her name?
- Julie, Julie.
Julie? Julie?
How long has been down?
A few like...
A few minutes, five minutes.
Don't have a pulse.
Start compressions.
Julie?
He's calling for you.
Andrew.
Hi, love.
Alright. Mommy's got you.
Let's go again. Clear.
Picking up a faint heartbeat.
Let's do some compressions.
Julie, can you hear me? Julie?
You stay with us.
Come on, Julie.
Please. Jules, Jules.
Please come back to me.
I love you.
I love you so much.
- Come on.
- Julie.
Will you take care of him?
Of course.
Goodbye, my love.
We'll be waiting for you.
- Come on. Stay with us.
- Come on, Julie.
Picking up a faint heartbeat.
Going one more time.
Clear.
Yeah.
Again. Ready?
Mommy.
- Daddy, can I get one?
- Hm-mm.
Mommy get one.
- Yeah.
- Ah.
Um.
You want it?
- Yeah!
- Yeah.