No!
- Yeah.
- Yeah hello,
my name is Dwaine Derkly.
Am I speaking to Edward Ipus?
Yeah, hi.
Yeah, hi. I'm calling
from Woodland Foster Homes.
I received your online request
for biological
parent information.
- Yeah, of course.
- We've gone ahead and
retrieved your documentation
from the Woodland Archive,
and we went through
your admittance registration
documents,
where your information
would be listed.
Did you find anything?
Well, the document lists
your weight and size.
The date of birth is unknown.
There's no biological parent
contact.
So, if there's anything else
I can help you with...
uh, just send me an email.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday
Sweet dog boy ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-Thank you.
-I love you.
Yeah. I just found out
that today is probably not
my birthday,
but thank you.
-You talked to Woodland?
-Yeah.
Well, then I guess
you can't have this.
- No...
- Oh, no,
this is a birthday present,
so...
And you just made a wish
on a birthday cupcake
knowing it wasn't your birthday.
-No, that's not fair.
-Uh-uh.
- Give it to me.
- No...
Okay, fine, fine, fine, but...
You can have it,
but it's bad luck.
God, I'm nervous.
What's this?
Oh.
Here.
I think you have to scan it.
AnceStory.
What's your story?
Please insert your finger
into the gene reader.
It will collect a microdroplet
of your blood.
It's just a pinprick.
Uh... Yeah, I guess.
Thank you. AnceStory
is analyzing
your DNA.
Did you feel anything?
Uh... I don't think so.
Hi, Edward. I'm Sylvia
from customer service
at AnceStory Genetics.
Just to let you know,
we've processed your DNA.
So, Family Connections has
been activated on your profile.
Our health specialist
will be in touch soon
to go through
your health results.
Thank you.
Maybe it was a panic attack.
Like the suddenness
of connecting to my brother.
But it's everything
I've ever wanted.
I mean,
maybe you should call him.
Or if you want to wait
until I get home,
we can call him together.
- I'm nervous, you know?
- Yeah.
It's going to be okay.
This is exciting.
You're right.
I'll pick up soup dumplings
on the way home, okay?
I love you.
I love you too.
Bye.
Hello. Edward?
Uh, Hi. Yeah. Manuel?
Hi.
Yeah, it's Manuel here.
Um... This is strange.
-Um...
-Yeah, for sure.
Yeah.
-Hey, Edward. How old are you?
-Uh...
you can call me Ed. I'm 31.
Thirty-one.
No way.
It's you.
What do you mean?
This will sound crazy,
but... I have a twin.
He was kidnapped
when he was a baby.
And Mom's been looking for you
ever since.
Edward?
Are you there?
I didn't know
Portugal was so green.
- Yeah.
- Give me another one.
What does that mean?
"I want
a cream-covered codfish."
Oh, that's a bit gross.
Come on, this is, like,
your national... food.
You gotta get used to this.
You're going to have
the creamiest...
wettest fish.
Oh, my God, so many butterflies,
so beautiful.
Oh, my God.
It really is amazing.
Do you know
where you're going?
Uh...
I don't think
the GPS is working.
-No, it's not locating us.
-Hmm.
-Shit.
-Okay, yeah. Pull over here.
I can ask for help.
Be right back.
Yeah.
Would you
mind helping me with something?
We're, um,
perdidas, uh...
Mrs. Vieira:
Lost, yeah.
Um... And we're looking
for this house.
Okay.
All right.
Um... Well, thank you.
What happened?
Let's get out of here.
What the fuck?
- God. It's huge.
- This is insane.
Brother Ed.
-I can't believe you're here.
-Hi.
Hey.
It's so nice to meet you.
- This is crazy.
- It is.
Did you
have a good trip?
Yeah.
- How do you feel?
- This is amazing.
Wow.
My brother.
Welcome home.
Let me show you around.
This is the living room
with a fireplace,
it's very warm.
It's good in the winter.
I want you to feel at home,
brother.
I'm sure you will,
because we're twins
and we have a deep spiritual
connection in this family.
It's strange, but it's true.
What? I'm not kidding.
It's not a bad thing.
Oh.
Those are my pets.
Hi.
They're beautiful.
Are they brothers?
-Mm. Lovers.
-Oh.
Wow. I like the one
in the purple shirt.
That's Carlos.
The other one is Castanheda.
Well, hello,
Carlos and Castanheda.
It's good to meet you.
I love these birds.
Yeah, that's Mommy.
Wow.
She's so beautiful.
She really is.
Let me show you this painting.
This is our great,
great grandmother Beatriz,
painted by Goya.
Eighteenth century.
It's original painting.
Um... Is Mom around?
You know, Mommy
is not feeling very well today.
It's better if you meet her
tomorrow.
God, that was intense.
Maybe we should have rented
a place or something.
No, what?
Manuel is fucking hilarious.
I guess.
What's the matter, brother Ed?
You don't like me?
This is my birds.
This is Carlos, Castanheda.
They are lovers...
Like me.
I love you more than anything
in the world.
Hmm.
Thank you for taking
time off to come with me.
Of course, baby.
We're family.
Hey, brother Ed.
Brother Ed.
Huh?
Do you want to meet her?
What, now?
Yeah.
Hmm?
My boy.
My son.
I've been dreaming
of this moment
since the day they took you.
You're perfect.
You're so beautiful.
My son.
You're the most
perfect thing in the world.
You're perfect too, Mom.
Oh, fuck.
-Hey.
-Hey, good morning.
Morning.
What?
-I met my mom this morning.
-What?
Yeah.
How was it?
It was beautiful.
Yeah.
But...
I was a bit freaked out by her.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Why? What happened?
It was a weird moment.
Like...
when I first saw her, I was...
She's had a little
too much work done.
-Like, on her face.
-Okay.
How bad?
-Like...
-Like the whole,
-the whole thing.
-Yeah,
- like...
- Hmm.
Yeah.
Oh, baby.
How are you feeling?
I don't know.
-Strange.
-Mm-hmm.
Hi.
Sorry.
Sorry, you scared me.
-You're Ryley?
-Yes.
-Amelia.
-Amelia,
it's... so nice to meet you.
-Yeah, nice to meet you.
-It's just such a pleasure.
Oh, you're so talented.
Thank you.
You did it?
- Yeah.
- Oh, you draw so well.
You should draw me
one of these days.
Oh.
I love to pose.
Well, I love to draw, so...
...perfect pair.
Amelia, thank you so much
for having us here.
I mean, this is so special
for Ed to be able to meet...
his family.
Are you from New York?
Yes. Um... I...
I've lived in New York
for nine years,
um, but I'm originally
from Boise.
Oh, Idaho.
Yes.
The land of potatoes.
I love potatoes.
I cannot eat them.
Yeah, I mean...
But I love them.
They're the best.
Potatoes are so good.
Um... How do you know Idaho?
I was in America
a long time ago.
Okay.
It was already
a very idiotic country.
Puritans in love with guns.
Right?
I mean,
it doesn't compare
to this place.
It's just gorgeous here.
It's like a fairy tale.
It is.
I mean, this house must be...
When was this built? Like,
a million years ago?
Time is a whore.
Time is like this...
perfidious master.
It blooms tragedy into comedy.
It transforms magic
into science.
Time eats us.
Like potatoes.
Well, it was so nice
to meet you.
I'm going to go find Ed,
'cause he's probably...
running around somewhere,
um, but I'll see you later.
You have
very sensual lips.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
What are you doing?
Trying to write a song.
About what?
Uh...
It's embarrassing.
Well, come to bed, it's late.
I just heard
something really weird.
What?
I think your mom
and brother sleep together.
What?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
-Yeah.
-How?
Because I just heard them.
Oh.
That's weird.
Exhale.
Bring your hands
down to the floor.
Dive your body down.
Inhale, halfway lengthen.
Exhale.
Step back into plank pose.
Or chaturanga.
Inhale and release up...
into upward-facing dog.
Exhale, push back,
downward-facing dog.
Take another breath in.
Oh.
Hi, my boy.
Come here.
Come in, come.
Oh, my boy.
This is my new boyfriend.
Isn't he beautiful?
And they are my slaves.
-Hello, Edward.
-Hi.
We represent
your mother's estate,
and we are,
according to her wishes,
formalizing you
as co-beneficiary,
along with Manuel,
to all of your mother's assets
when she passes,
currently valued
at 65 million euros.
We have drafted
all the paperwork.
So, if you could just sign here,
we can go ahead
and start the process.
Mm.
I don't even speak Portuguese.
Oh,
it's just a pro-forma
giving us power of attorney
to take care of this legally
for you.
And it's best
if you stay in Portugal
for the next month
because Portuguese
bureaucracy is quite slow.
Yes.
It's very slow.
- Uh...
- And Edward,
I'd prefer if we keep this
our little secret.
Okay.
Sure.
Ryley.
Hey, Jay.
Oh my God. How are you?
Uh, it's so good
to hear your voice.
Yeah, good to hear you,
too. Are you in Portugal?
- Yeah.
- In Lisbon?
No. We are in the middle
of a forest,
in a remote palazzo.
- It's very European.
- Wow. Okay.
I'm in the meditation room
right now.
Wait, can you hear me?
- Can you hear me?
- Yeah.
How is it?
Yeah, it's just, it's...
- it's weird.
- Oh, yeah?
They have a mausoleum
in the house.
- Oh, that is weird.
- I know.
Jay?
Hello?
-Hey, Ryley.
-Sorry.
My suitcase was
literally reorganized,
like she had come in the night
and folded my underwear.
- No, and it wasn't Ed?
- No.
Okay, that's really scary.
And I've been having
the weirdest dreams.
It's like
they've brainwashed him.
Yeah.
You gotta try
talking to him.
No, I promise.
Tomorrow by the latest.
You gotta
get out of there.
I just have to convince Ed.
These people
sound like freaks.
Yeah.
I know.
Ryley.
This is good
for your anxiety.
This vision that haunts you...
it haunts me too.
You must fight him, Ed.
You must...
block him from your mind.
Close your eyes, brother Ed.
What?
What the fuck?
It's okay, brother Ed.
It just means
you're part of this family.
What?
Close your eyes again.
Do you see
a vision from the past?
Or is it Mama?
What are you doing here, Ryley?
We have a gift,
brother Ed.
What the fuck?
What the fuck? Stop that.
Fucking stop.
Get the fuck out
of my mind! Stop that!
Calm down.
- Stop.
- It's okay.
Stop. This can't be
fucking...
This isn't happening.
Please stop! What are you doing?
Oh, God!
It's okay.
Okay, brother.
This gift is a blessing.
You know I love you, right?
I'm sorry.
I'm not in the mood.
That's okay.
Baby, I've been thinking.
We should get out of here.
I don't feel comfortable here.
I mean, these people are weird.
They're really weird.
I mean,
they... they give me the creeps.
And if we leave now,
we can go to Lisbon
or we can go to the beach.
Or we could go back to New York
for a couple of days
and enjoy
the rest of our time off.
These people are strangers,
basically.
They're not your real family.
Fuck you, Ryley.
What did you just say?
You're being a real bitch.
Excuse me.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Look at me.
You did not just
call me a bitch.
I'm done with this.
I'm leaving with or without you.
You better grow up.
- Hey.
So, did you talk to him?
Yeah. We got in a fight.
Uh, that's annoying.
And I found weird shit
online about the house.
What do you mean?
It used to be owned
by a Portuguese witch.
A witch?
-You sound crazy, Ryley.
-No, I don't know.
The thing is, I think...
Ed is really
falling in love with them.
- Mm-hmm
- He's always wanted a family.
Yeah.
And it's like he's
buying into their bullshit.
I don't know what to do.
Can you change your ticket?
I don't know.
Okay, well,
you've got to get out of there,
so just figure it out.
I'm... I'm sure
you can change it
or buy a new one
if you have to.
They're not that expensive.
Just get yourself over here
as fast as you can.
- I'll call you back, Jay.
- What?
Ryley.
Brother.
Brother Ed.
-Brother Ed.
-Hmm.
Come see Mommy.
She's dancing.
What?
Mommy's dancing.
My son.
I haven't danced in years
Oh, my sweet boy.
Oh, my loved ones.
Is this Manuel?
Mrs. Vieira:
- Papa.
- Oh.
Oh, he's their dad.
Ed and Manuel's father.
He looks exactly like them.
Your daughter.
Mrs. Vieira:
- She was in love with him.
-Yes.
Mrs. Vieira:
Wait.
Hold on.
Here, speak slowly.
Automated voice:
Hmm.
- My daughter told me
- Arthur's mother was a witch.
In exchange for eternal youth,
she has children with her sons,
but when she has daughters,
she kills them.
My daughter said
Amelia locked her father
in the basement
and tortured him.
She said she wanted
to free him...
But the truth is my daughter
never came back.
Oh.
I'm so sorry.
Hey babe.
- You wanna come dance?
- Can we talk?
Come on, we're having fun.
I... I really don't feel
like it. I need to talk to you.
Come on, I can show you
some Portuguese music.
I don't want to fucking dance.
This is weird.
This is really weird.
I don't feel comfortable here.
Why are you ruining this moment?
You're making me want to cry.
You're making me cry.
Why are you ruining
this moment with my boys?
Why?
She wants to take my boys
away from me.
I'm sorry.
What the fuck?
Why did he block me in?
You want me to ask him
to move it?
No.
We'll walk.
- Where are you going?
- Come on.
This is it, we're here.
Senhora Vieira?
Senhora Vieira!
What are you doing?
Ryley.
Are you crazy?
Shit.
Hello?
It's Ryley.
Senhora Vieira?
-Senhora Vieira?
-Ryley?
What are you doing?
Senhora Vieira,
it's Ryley.
Shit.
Look at this. This is your dad.
It looks like Manuel.
No, but look at the date.
It's 30 years ago.
Think about it.
They never talk about him.
They don't have
any photos of him.
Wake the fuck up.
These people are psychos.
Don't say that, Ryley.
Oh, my God.
How... How are you
not hearing me right now?
You just broke
into someone's house.
- This is so fucked up.
- What is?
All of this.
You saw the photos.
I'm sure
there's an explanation.
Why are you doing this?
Okay. I love you,
but I'm leaving.
All right?
-Come on, baby.
-Don't do this.
We gotta go, all right?
Why?
Okay,
just forget about this.
What's up?
Hey.
What's going on?
Can you move your car?
-It's blocking the garage.
-Mm-mm.
It's parked out front now.
You can take it for a spin
if you like.
I'm going to wait in the car.
What's wrong with her?
Nothing. She just wants
to go explore a bit.
Yeah, I understand. It's okay.
You should do it.
Go explore.
Hello,
my name is Dr. Sunderson,
and I'm calling
from AnceStory Genetics.
I have this as a secondary
contact number
for Mr. Edward Ipus.
I've been trying to contact you
for quite some time now.
We found a genetic anomaly
in your DNA,
and what it suggests
is disconcerting.
There's a high probability
of inbreeding confirmed...
Ma?
Hey.
I poured us some tea.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean for this
to happen.
It's okay.
Ryley's a good girl.
I think we're going to have
to leave for a few days.
It's okay.
Drink your tea.
Mmm.
Ryley.
Where are you, Ryley?
I just want to talk, Ryley.
We need to talk.
Get the fuck away from me.
Ryley?
Are you okay?
I feel tired.
Ryley.
Where are you, Ryley?
Ryley, open this door.
Open this door now, Ryley.
Open the fucking door!
Open this door.
Open this door!
Listen to me!
Help me.
Baby, are you okay?
Oh, God.
I feel tired.
Manuel.
You...
What have you done?
No!
My love.