I don't want to be me.
Is that a weird thing to say?
It's true.
So tired of feeling
like none of it matters.
I try so fucking hard.
I bang my head against
the fucking wall.
Every minute.
Every second.
But nothing changes.
It doesn't get better.
I'm still right here.
And it's all the same.
What do you want?
For it to stop.
Hey, Polly, it's Ryan.
Uh, we haven't seen you in
pottery the past couple of weeks.
You know, you still have
six pre-paid classes left.
Did you want us to
pause your membership?
Email back and, uh,
let me know. Okay, bye.
It's Lainie. This is a reminder
to pick up the cake on Thursday.
You said you could,
so don't flake.
Anyway, let me know
how it goes tomorrow.
Hey, kiddo, it's Bobby.
Um, sorry to tell you this, but you've
gotta work that double tomorrow.
Everyone else has got plans.
This is Mom. You
didn't return my text.
Anyway, did you print out
the forms you need to bring?
Call me back if you
want to practice.
I have a lot to offer.
I did well in school.
People think I'm smart.
Why would anyone say that?
Who would say that?
Definitely not a smart person.
I'm a hard worker.
I just got distracted.
I think I...
Uh, I think that the last
few years have been good.
And I think that I
just needed to...
Miss Gibbons, what made you
want to come back to school?
Because I'm supposed to.
Can I help you?
Well, I... I don't...
I don't know where I...
Ma'am?
I thought I knew
someone that lived here.
I used to know someone
that lived here.
I remembered.
Or I thought I remembered.
Mrs. Trott? She lives next door.
A cab brought me.
I have a number I can
call on the fridge.
My son, he left me a
card in case I needed it.
When they moved, his office
transferred him to New Jersey.
Ma'am, do you wanna...
Do you wanna come
in for a second?
No. Get out of the cold?
Come in. Thank you.
We can have a seat
in the living room.
Can I... Can I have
a glass of water?
Yeah, sure. I can
make you some tea.
No, no, I don't
want to be a bother.
Please. It's okay.
Here. Come. Come, sit.
I'm sorry.
You're too kind. It's so late.
Oh, it's all right.
Here you go.
Do you... Do you have your phone?
I can... I can call for you.
Oh, no, I... I could
never make 'em work.
Even the flip
ones. Tiny buttons.
I have the number. My
son, he gave it to me,
that if I was ever in
trouble, I... I could call.
Yeah. Yeah, ma'am,
you told me already.
You just relax. We'll
get you sorted out.
It's so cold outside.
The fire feels nice.
Are you married?
No.
So pretty, though. Thank you.
Do you have children?
A baby?
Mmm-mmm. No.
This house, it's a lot
for a young woman...
Well, I'm not that
young anymore.
You are to me.
But isn't that the way it goes?
Yeah, it belongs to my sister.
She and her husband,
they rent it to me.
They live across town.
They have a little girl, and
wanted a bigger yard and all that.
It's a nice place to live.
Yeah, I'm very lucky. I
could never afford it.
I should take little
better care of it, but...
How old is your niece?
Aly's five. About to turn six.
She's having a big
party next week.
That's nice. It's a good age.
I'm sure it is.
So much more to do.
I'm gonna start now.
What?
Ma'am, are you okay?
If you wanna give me that
card, I can call for you.
I can get my phone and...
This will be for you now.
Maybe... Maybe we
should wait outside.
You're going to die.
I'm sorry. But it's true.
What are you talking about?
You can be sad. You can be scared.
You can be a lot of things.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't change the truth.
You are going to die.
Tonight.
Unless...
Unless I don't...
I don't understand.
You won't.
I think that you're a little bit
confused and that you need to leave.
I remembered someone
who lived here.
That was a long time ago.
It doesn't matter
though. Not really.
What do you want?
You have to do things.
You were so kind to me.
Thank you for the water.
I'm gonna call the
police now, okay?
You can't do that. I will.
I wouldn't.
Don't tell anyone.
I wouldn't tell anyone at all.
Don't you dare.
Get up.
You need to leave.
This is not okay.
They're yours now.
No, I don't want them.
You need them. No, I want
you to get out of my house.
I don't know what's wrong with
you, but you have three minutes,
and then I'm gonna
call the police, okay?
You got every right to be upset.
This is the worst
thing I've ever done.
This is not okay, what you're
doing. Do you get that?
So you need to leave.
Please, go home.
Polly?
How do you know my name?
I thought it was a nightmare.
But I didn't wake up.
You won't wake up.
I'm sorry.
Mom? Hey, there.
Did you get your form you
need to bring? No, wait.
The most fucked-up
thing just happened.
What is it? So,
there was this woman.
She came to the
door. I let her in.
She said she was
looking for somebody.
What? She was like 80 years old.
Hold on a second. You let
someone in your house?
Mom, are you listening?
I'm listening.
Okay, so, she came to the
door and I let her in,
'cause she needed to
call a ride or something.
And then she started...
It-It... It got all weird.
What happened? She told
me I was gonna die.
Polly. I was just
trying to be nice.
Honey, you're not
making any sense.
Mom, I don't know
what to tell you.
It was creepy. She
had a box. A box?
What kind of box? That's
what you're gonna ask me?
Well, was it a bomb?
No, Mom, it was not a bomb.
That's the first thing
that I would've said.
That's the first thing that people
say. "Oh, my God, it's a bomb." No.
It was just an old wooden box.
She left it on the road.
It's just sitting here.
Well, she was probably
just senile. Maybe.
You said she was old. Maybe
she was confused, off her meds?
I don't know what she was.
But she's gone now? Yeah.
Yeah.
I'm sure you're okay, Baby Doll.
If not, go over to Mrs. Trott.
Well, she's still out of town.
I feel like that woman never sits
still since her husband died.
I should call the
police, don't you think?
Well, I think you need to
focus, but I'm sure it's fine.
She said I was gonna die.
Oh.
It was probably just
some weird cult thing.
Okay. Mom, that doesn't
make it any better.
You're not making it better with
anything that you're saying.
So, are you ready for tomorrow?
Did you figure out
what you're gonna wear?
No. Polly. You gotta focus.
This is a big deal, sweetie.
And Lainie called...
Yeah, I know.
That's why I got
off of work early,
and I was planning on
doing that right now.
And I know what Lainie
fuckin' did. Okay, okay.
Honey, it's gonna be
okay. I'm 32 years old.
I've had job interviews before,
and I'm just thinking
about going back to school.
I don't even know if that's
what I want. I know. I know.
But we have to start somewhere.
I've been praying
on it, you know?
Yeah, I was being
a bitch. Sorry.
No. I just don't want you
distracted, that's all.
Okay... let me call
you back in a bit.
I'm gonna try on some outfits.
I'll send you some pictures.
Are you gonna be up for a
while? I'll be up, Baby Doll.
Okay. Love you. Bye.
♪ Because it's hard
for me, my baby
♪ And the darkest hour
is just before dawn
♪ Each night before
you go to bed, my baby
♪ Whisper a little
prayer for me, my baby
♪ And tell all the stars above
♪ This is dedicated
to the one I love
♪ Love can never be exactly
like we want it to be
♪ I could be satisfied
knowing you love me
♪ And there's one
thing I want you to do
♪ Especially for me... ♪
♪ And it's something
that everybody needs
♪ While I'm far away
from you, my baby
♪ Whisper a little
prayer for me, my baby
♪ Because it's hard
for me, my baby
♪ And the darkest hour
is just before dawn
♪ If there's one
thing I want you to do
♪ Especially for me
♪ Then it's something
that everybody needs
♪ Each night before
you go to bed, my baby
♪ Whisper a little
prayer for me, my baby
♪ And tell all the
stars above... ♪
♪ This is dedicated to the
one I love ♪ To the one I love
♪ To the one I love ♪
Mom? Yes, baby.
I'm going crazy.
What now?
Don't "what now" me.
I mean, what happened?
I'm going crazy.
Are you gonna tell me?
I could have sworn I thought you
were here, just now, upstairs.
I could hear your voice. I
could smell your perfume.
Polly, Baby Doll,
you gotta calm down.
Mom. This is silly.
Put it out. Just
give me a second.
You said you were gonna quit. I
know. I know, I know. I know. I will.
I think you're just nervous.
Did you pick an outfit?
I don't know. I
don't fucking know.
You should eat something,
because when you were here before,
I thought you looked skinny.
Hello?
Anyone there?
Tell me what's happening.
Check the closet.
Maybe I'm in there.
Shut up.
Polly, what do you see?
Nothing.
I feel sick.
Well, I think you're ready, but
I think you should wear a jacket.
That one you have, the blue one.
I'm proud of you, Polly.
This is gonna be a
big day. You'll see.
You know what I was
thinking about this morning?
Your first day of school.
You probably don't
even remember,
but Dad took you and Lainie
in that green truck of his,
and you were so excited.
Aw.
You know, it doesn't have
to be so hard, Baby Doll.
It really doesn't.
I'm so tired.
You're not even listening to me.
It's getting late,
I should be in bed.
Mom, what if...
Yes, baby.
Nothing. Never mind.
It's not gonna... I don't know.
Mom? What?
It's sitting right here.
What is?
The box.
Well, maybe you
carried it back inside.
I didn't.
Maybe you weren't thinking.
Why don't you believe me?
Honey, I always
believe you. Always.
Polly...
What do you see?
The sand's not falling.
Well, you haven't started yet.
What?
Did I tell you
about the hourglass?
Maybe.
I didn't though.
Oh, it doesn't
matter, Baby Doll.
Mom, what are you talking about?
Polly...
I'm not your mother.
What?
Mom?
Mom, stop it.
Are you listening?
You're gonna die.
Do you understand?
But you were always
so slow, weren't you?
♪ I know it's hard
for you, my baby
♪ Because it's hard
for me, my... ♪
♪ Each night before
you go to bed, my baby
♪ Whisper a little
prayer for me, my baby
♪ And tell... ♪
We know everything about you.
Everything you would never tell.
Hobbies drop away like flies.
You never had a job for
more than four months.
You can't make a choice
that really matters.
So you waste away, hiding.
You're an open
book to strangers,
but you shut down the
second anyone gets close.
It's too hard, too
scary, too risky.
So you never feel a connection.
You never feel love.
You barely feel
anything anymore.
You put $26 in
your pocket today.
You were counting
down the registers.
Bobby never checks.
Did you feel something then?
You are going to die.
Unless... Unless what?
Unless, unless, unless,
unless, unless, unless...
Look at the box! Look at it!
Go see, Polly.
See what we gave you.
Three things.
Three things go inside.
One, two, three.
Something you hate,
something you need,
something you love.
I don't understand.
You'd better learn.
Time is watching you, Baby
Doll. Tick-tock. Tick-tock.
Do you understand, Polly?
What goes inside,
only you decide.
We and I will know you lie.
"Something you hate."
"Something you need."
"Something you love."
Something I hate.
This is insane.
Hi.
Um, please, I need
to use your phone.
My phone's not working, and
I need to call the police.
Hold on. Wait a second. I
thought you were a delivery.
Uh, babe, hold on. Someone's...
What's going on? I need
to use your phone, please.
What's the matter? Can I...
Can I just come in? Please.
You live around here? I
live across the street.
You're the only
person that answered.
It's late.
My phone is not working.
Baby, baby, just
give me one second.
My husband's flying back from
Kentucky. He's at the airport.
I just really need
to talk to someone.
There's something
happening, and I need help.
One second. I waited all day.
I don't know. She says she
needs to call the police, but...
Did you talk to Oscar?
He called about the fence.
He can come tomorrow, but I'm
gonna have to call to confirm.
I can call. I could do it.
I can be here too. Yes, that's
fine. That's absolutely fine.
No, I can be here all
day tomorrow. It's fine.
Okay. Well, yeah,
I... I'll be here.
Hold on. Sweetie, hang
on. Hold on. Ma'am?
Someone keeps calling.
I need help. Oh, hi!
Yes.
Yes. One second.
The police just called.
What?
She just got here.
What are they saying? Okay.
Okay.
Absolutely.
Let me get right on that.
See something, say something.
You can never be too careful.
Look what you made me do.
We are everywhere.
We are nowhere.
No one else can help you.
No one ever could.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
This isn't happening.
Please, please.
Oh, my God.
Go away!
♪ ...knowing you love me
♪ And there's one
thing I want you to do
♪ Especially for me
♪ And it's something
that everybody needs
♪ While I'm far away
from you, my baby... ♪
Hey, Baby Doll.
Polly?
Polly? You're dead.
You having a bad day?
You're not him.
Hey, there, don't
talk like that.
I did what you said! I put
them in the fucking box!
Something you hate, Baby Doll,
not something
you're supposed to.
We and I will know you lie.
I remember you
used to wake me up.
You used to get so
scared, didn't you?
Always seeing things. under
your bed, in your closet.
"Daddy, please come see."
I would look so hard,
I would search for you,
but I never did find
anything, did I?
Please stop.
Maybe Daddy lied.
Maybe we were always there.
Maybe.
You're wasting time, Baby Doll.
Tick-Tock. Tick-Tock. Tick...
You don't want that
sand running out.
Why don't you pull
yourself up off that couch?
You already know the answer.
What do you hate, Polly?
What did you believe in?
What did you lose
the day I died?
What are you hiding?
We and I wonder.
You know...
You let him die.
You let him suffer.
Dad prayed to you every day.
I prayed to you every day.
Is there something I hate?
I hate you.
I see you.
Polly?
Do you see me?
Bitch.
You whore.
Polly?
I see you.
Do you see me?
What do you see?
Tell me. Answer me.
Did you hear what she said?
You're scared.
She thinks you're dumb. You are.
You are dead! You are dead!
You are dead!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Hello?
Jesus, I've been calling
you for the last 20 minutes.
Are you close?
Lainie? Polly?
Are you there?
Polly? How do I
know this is you?
What does that even mean?
You call me, past 10:00, when I told you
not to call the home phone this late.
You call me five times and
you tell me someone died?
You said you were scared. You said
something could happen to Aly.
What is going to happen to Aly?
I didn't call you. You did.
Tell me what's going on. I cant.
I can't. Wait.
Are you okay? No.
Tell me what's going on.
You won't believe me.
Hey. What... There you are.
I see your car on the street.
Why didn't you say
so? Wait. Wait.
Just park over here.
No, no! Don't let me in!
No, don't let me in!
Fuck!
Think. Think.
What do you want?
Tell me.
What do I need?
Please.
Whee!
Time to go to bed now.
Where is she?
There she is!
Peek-a-boo!
Time to go to bed now.
Where is she?
Okay, give me that foot.
This little piggy
went to market.
This little piggy... This
little piggy stayed home.
little piggy had roast beef.
This little piggy had none.
This little piggy cried "wee
wee wee" all the way home.
This little piggy...
This little...
Whee!
..."wee wee wee"
all the way home.
This little piggy had none.
This isn't happening.
..."wee wee wee"
all the way home.
This isn't happening!
No, I won't!
Not this, please! Please!
Please. This little
piggy stayed home.
This little piggy
had roast beef.
And this little piggy had none.
This little piggy went...
This little piggy...
..."wee wee wee" all the
way home. All the way home.
This little piggy...
Where is she? Where is she?
This little piggy went...
..."wee wee wee" all the way
home... all the way home.
This is fucking crazy. This
little piggy went to market.
This little piggy stayed home.
This little piggy
had roast beef.
This little piggy had none.
...all the way home.
..."wee wee wee"
all the way home.
This little piggy
went "wee wee wee"...
Where is she?
...all the way home.
This little piggy
went "wee wee wee".
This piggy went to market.
This little piggy stayed home.
This little piggy
had roast beef.
Something I need.
Fuck.
Fuck. Fuck.
Quit your crying!
Humble yourself.
Baby Doll.
We and I will know!
No, no.
No!
Oh, my God!
I cut my fucking toe off!
Take it, please! Please!
♪ And there's one thing
I want you to do... ♪
What was wrong? Tell
me what was wrong!
No.
Tell me what you want.
Please! I'll do anything!
Anything. Just don't hurt her.
I can't.
Please.
This little piggy went to market.
This little piggy stayed home.
This little piggy
had roast beef.
This little piggy had none.
This little piggy had roast
beef. This little piggy had none.
This little piggy...
You tricked me!
This little piggy
had roast beef...
Wee wee wee...
This little piggy
went to market...
stayed at home.
This little piggy
had roast beef.
This little piggy had none.
This little piggy
went "wee wee wee..."
...all the way home.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Something you need.
Something I need.
Lainie!
Lainie! We're in here.
Aly!
Lainie!
Lainie! Lainie!
Lainie?
Please.
Please, please.
Please wake up.
Please.
Wake up. Please.
Please wake up.
Please.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
She didn't do anything!
♪ Each night before you
go to bed, my baby... ♪
No! No, no!
♪ Whisper a little prayer
for me, my baby... ♪
Fuck you!
It should have been me!
Go away!
Auntie P! Auntie P!
What are you doing?
Say something.
Please... Please don't...
Auntie P. Don't be silly.
You haven't finished, have you?
You killed them. No. You did.
Bad girl. Bad.
I made a mistake!
There are no mistakes!
Only choices.
Right and wrong.
You saw what you wanted. You
gave what you wanted to give.
But did you truly
need it, Auntie P?
Or did you truly need
to give something easy?
It wasn't easy...
You must suffer not to suffer.
Are you ready to play more?
What do you love?
What do you love? I loved them.
Did you?
Think hard. Real hard.
I loved you!
I wanna play.
Can we play?
Read me a story. Please.
This little piggy
went to market.
This little piggy stayed home.
This little piggy
had roast beef.
This little piggy had none.
And this little piggy
went "wee wee wee"
all the way home.
You're dead.
No. I'm right here. With you.
I think you should take my nose.
Won't it be funny, Auntie P?
Mmm. You should take my eyes.
Are you sure?
Really?
No!
No! No!
What if you're wrong,
Auntie P? What will happen?
I bet it's bad.
You're wrong.
Will it be over?
Something you loved.
Will it stop?
I'll always love you.
We will see.
What are you doing, babe?
Have you been here long? 'Cause,
um, Mark thought he heard someone.
Lainie.
Are you okay? I
called you earlier.
Your hand.
Polly, what's going on? Aly?
Polly? Are you okay?
Are you okay? Mama!
You're okay. You're okay.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Everything okay up
there? It's okay.
We're fine. It's
all right. Sorry.
What's happening, Auntie
P? I'm sorry. It's okay.
I was being silly.
You are silly.
Baby Doll...
This little piggie...
I wanna play, Auntie P.
Come here.
I wanna show you something.
You should come see.
I wanna play, Auntie P!
I love you.
No.
You're a liar.
I did everything.
I gave you everything.
Something I hate, something I
need, something I love, I did it.
What more do you want?
Where are you?
Talk to me.
Just stop. Please.
Anything you want...
Take it.
No! No!
Let me go!
Why won't you let me go?
What is it? What is left?
She...
She knocked on the door.
She knew what she wanted.
She gave it to me.
Hello!
Anyone home?
Hello?
Somebody...
Can somebody help me?
Please.
Somebody.
Thank you.
Thank you. I'm
sorry it's so late.
Are you okay?
I was just dropping
something off.
My sister's just
down the street.
I was supposed to bring
her something. Um...
I was supposed to go there,
but I... I forgot my key.
I'm... I'm locked out.
Sorry, I don't understand. Do
you... Do you need something?
Um, I think I just need...
I just... I just need to
come in. Just for a second.
Uh, you know, this is
actually my parent's house.
I'm just here visiting
for the holidays. So...
They're... They're at a work
party right now. I... I can't...
I just need to call my sister.
She just lives right
down the street.
Right there.
My name is Polly.
Are you okay?
No.
No, I'm not.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry to bother you. I just
don't know what else to do.
But if I am freaking you out, you
can call the police. I just...
No, I'm just...
You can tell me what happened.
I can't.
Uh, I'll be right back.
My... My parents will be
home in a few minutes.
Here. Drink this. I...
I made some tea tonight.
It might help warm you up.
What is that?
Your name is Tara?
How did you... How
did you know that?
I just do.
Thank you for the tea.
That was really,
really nice of you.
Look, um, I think... I think
that you should maybe go...
I just knew it. I
can't explain it.
You'll understand. You will.
Soon.
What's going on?
I don't want to be me.
Is that a weird thing to say?
It's true.
Tired of feeling like
none of it matters.
I want it to...
so bad.
I can change everything.
But not me.
I try so fucking hard.
I bang my head against
the fucking wall.
Every minute...
every second.
But nothing changes.
It doesn't get better.
I'm still right here.
And it's all the same.
What do you want?
For it to stop.
I'm going to start now.
Your parents aren't coming home.
That wasn't true. Was it?
I think that you...
I know. I know.
But it doesn't matter.
This belongs to you now.
No, no. Get up.
Get up. Look, I was just trying to
be nice. You really need to leave.
I don't know what
your fucking deal is.
You're going to die.
I'm sorry.
It wants me...
...to kill you.
It won't let me go.
You have to do things.
It never, never stops.
Get away from me.
It wants you! No!
Take it.
No!
Stop. Die.
No! No!
Please.
Why?
Why? Tell me.
Why me?
Someone knocked on my door.
And I just opened it.
No one ever knocks.
Not anymore.
Then someone finally...
They could have
knocked anywhere.
I could have knocked anywhere.
But I didn't.
I think it chooses us...
because we are broken.
You were nice. I can tell.
It doesn't matter.
I tried so hard.
The things we do to ourselves.
It's never enough.
Alas, everything I was...
everything I could be...
I was so afraid.
The box needs that.
The sand needs it.
Don't be afraid of dying.
Don't be afraid.
Thank you.
Aly's five. She's
about to turn six.
We're having a birthday
party for her next week.
That's nice. It's a good age.
I'm sure it is.
So much more to do.
I'm gonna start now.
What?
Ma'am, are you okay?
If you wanna give me that card,
I can call you a car or...
I can get my phone
and call you an Uber.
This will be for you now.
You are going to die.
Unless...
Unless, unless, unless,
unless, unless, unless...
You don't want that
sand running out.
Unless, unless, unless...
It's too hard, too scary.
I won't do it anymore.
Come and see.
Did you feel something then?
You whore! You said
you will not desire.
Help me!
What do you love?
No! No! No!
You're wasting time, Baby Doll.
You are going to die.
I don't want to be me.
You are dead!
Unless, unless, unless...
Polly?
Aly!
Oh, I love you.
I love you.
Mama's pissed at you.
Mama's always pissed at me.
What happened to you?
What did you do?
Tell Mom I'll be
right back, okay?
Okay?
You can't play, okay?
Give it to me. What?
Listen to me. I should
never have given it to you.
Give me the box.
What are you talking
about? Do it, now.
Who are you?
What?
I... I think you're confused.
My parents and I,
we just got back.
We were on vacation
for Christmas.
You have the wrong house.
Oh...
I thought... I'm sorry.
It's all right. I'm sorry.
I'll be in in a minute.
Come on.
Something you... want.