Downloaded from http://720pMkv.Com
(WOMAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
(WOMAN WAILING)
(WAILING)
WOMAN ON RADIO:
If you get a chance,
get over to Marin.
Check out
the Marin County Arts Fair.
It's amazing,
and it'll be going on through
this Thanksgiving weekend.
Well, nothing's changed.
We've got fog and low clouds
in both the East Bay
and here in San Francisco.
And we're
looking at a high
of 69 degrees
once these clouds burn off.
The time now is 7:23.
Stick with your girl here.
CLAIRE: Oh, my gosh.
We'll be coming
at you with much,
much more music.
(JAZZY MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Hello!
Yoo hoo!
Tommy, turn it off.
We gotta make a baby.
(PHONE RlNGS)
Yeah?
l can't do that now,
'cause l got a drainage issue
with a floor in Paris that. . .
We have
an issue that needs. . .
Resolved first.
. . .to be resolved.
Right now?
lt's red.
Okay, good.
Listen, l'll
talk to you later.
l thought you had
a sentence hearing.
l do,
so we have to hurry.
We've got
seven minutes
for us,
1 5 minutes for resting
with my hips elevated,
and l'll only be
four minutes late
if l check my
messages in the car
and there's no traffic
on the bridge.
Okay.
How about 1 0 minutes for us
and 1 2 minutes
for hip elevation?
Nine and thirteen.
Okay, deal.
Come here.
No. No, no, wait.
lt's actually supposed
to work better
if you're on top.
Okay.
l thought l'd never
hear you say that.
So nice.
CLAlRE:
l know what they said,
reduced sentence,
but l think l can
get a new trial.
ALEX: Claire,
l don't know if we should
bite off that much.
lt's a first offense.
We can ask for leniency.
CLAlRE:
The jury forewoman
is an advocate.
She's not an impartial juror.
l don't know.
l hate to push.
This is a rape case.
l don't wanna piss
the judge off.
Trust me on this, Alex.
JUDGE:
Please tell me
you're joking.
Your Honor,
my client is looking
at some serious time in jail
and irreparable damage
while these guys
are laughing
all the way to CNN.
That's ridiculous.
Your Honor,
juror number nine
is a rape victim.
And very much
to her credit,
she's a major fund-raiser
for a sexual assault hot line.
l must point out however,
that the prosecution
should have
submitted those facts
at the voir dire.
And the prosecutorial
misconduct does not
stop there.
Really?
How do you figure that?
This very D.A.'s office
handled
juror number nine's case
eight years ago,
and l find it
impossible to believe
that no one on their team
recognized her.
This is outrageous.
JUDGE: Counselor.
(PEOPLE CLAMORlNG)
REPORTER 1 : Ms. Kubik,
do you feel that justice
was served?
We're very pleased
that Gary Norris will be
receiving a new trial.
REPORTER 2: His victim
might say she's been raped
all over again,
this time by the system.
My heart goes out to her,
it really does.
But when
the rights of any defendant
are violated,
we are all at risk
until injustice
is redressed.
Good job.
CLAlRE: Thanks.
l need to talk to you.
Good, l need gossip.
That was luck, Kubik.
Just like your
Bruins last night.
Sorry about that.
She scores again.
Well, the heart of
American democracy
beats on.
Would you punch up
my calendar, please?
Personal or business?
Both. Thanks.
Hi, big guy.
Good work, Claire.
We're proud of you.
Thank you very much.
l guess l'll just type
"partner" in right here
next to January 1 st.
l didn't know you
were clairvoyant.
Really? Are you serious?
We'll see.
Yes!
Not bad.
l think that was
just lucky.
Bring it on, girl.
Pretty.
TOM: Pretty nice.
CLAlRE: Pretty lucky.
Well. . .
l'm taking you
to pool school.
l don't think
you have a shot.
Thirteen ball off the five
in the corner pocket.
Not in this lifetime, pal.
Oh, yes.
Okay.
Excuse me, please.
That is not fair.
That is not fair!
You can't hold. . .
No, you can't use
your left hand now.
You're a mutant.
Hey, guys, look!
This was
the scene in City Hall
earlier today.
REPORTER 1 : Ms. Kubik,
do you feel that
justice was served?
We're very pleased
that Gary Norris will
be receiving...
REPORTER 2: His victim
might say she's been raped
all over again,
this time by the system.
You look great!
CLAlRE: My heart
goes out to her,
it really does.
But when the rights
of any defendant...
Look at you.
...are violated,
we are all at risk until
injustice is redressed.
REPORTER 2: How about
the family? Do you have
any comments for them?
Wow.
l just want one.
(BANGlNG)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERlNG)
Honey, lock the door.
Someone's in the house.
MAN 1 : Leave!
MAN 1 : Hurry!
MAN 2: Wait up!
(DOG BARKlNG)
TOM: Damn kids.
lt's okay, honey.
225 Dover.
Send somebody right away.
They're gone.
Are you okay?
Oh, God.
l'm fine.
(BELL RlNGlNG)
How old is he?
Fourteen months.
Uh-oh. Cute baby alert.
Hi. Can we meet your baby?
Hi ! Oh, my God,
what a doll.
He's in a pretty good mood.
(BOTH CHATTERlNG)
There's this, well. . .
Because he had on
a T-shirt or something,
and the T-shirt was just
a huge hit afterwards.
Men all across America
were buying T-shirts.
l always liked
lt's a Wonderful Life.
(BOTH ARGUlNG)
CLAlRE: Nice.
Christmas domestic.
Yeah, that's the spirit.
lnteresting.
Real interesting.
CLAlRE: Keys, please.
What is it, baby?
BOTH: FBl !
(SlRENS BLARlNG)
Get down !
Get down, honey.
What?
Get down !
Get down on the ground now!
TOM: Okay!
Stay down !
Leave her alone!
(MAN CHATTERlNG ON RADlO)
AGENT 1 : You cuffed him?
You cuffed him?
AGENT 2: l got it, yeah.
AGENT 1 : Did you cuff him?
Screwed up
the whole damn thing.
You know you're looking
at a multimillion
dollar lawsuit, right,
Mr. Mulkins?
Excess use of force,
harassment,
reckless endangerment.
How's that for starters?
lt's Mullins, Mrs. Kubik.
Special Agent Mullins.
You have a warrant
for the arrest of someone
named Ron Chapman.
My husband is Tom Kubik.
Your computer is
obviously having
some kind of
a psychotic break.
lt wasn't our computer.
lf your people had
gotten any closer,
you would have
burned the guy,
all right?
Fine. Forget about it.
lt wasn't our computer.
lt was Marin P. D.
They ran all the fingerprints
after your house was
burglarized,
and l'll tell
you something else.
The AFlS flagged
your husband's.
They've been in
the system for 1 2 years.
And once again,
what is he being
accused of?
l'm sorry,
but l can't tell you.
Come on.
You know
that having been
subject to arrest,
l have the right
to know the charges.
No, you don't.
Not when it's
a military court,
and not when
national security
is involved.
Military court?
(CELL PHONE RlNGS)
Hello?
Oh, my God.
Thank God l caught you.
l was totally freaked out
that you were gonna be
out of town or something.
And l caught you
on the news.
Claire, you have to stop
letting them
mess with your hair.
Jackie?
Sweetie,
l just need some money.
l hate to ask...
Well, not really,
but anyway
can you just help me out?
Please?
My landlord's
breathing down my neck
right now, as we speak.
lf you say no,
l'm gonna be evicted.
Can you come get me?
l know what it could be.
Maybe what it is,
is that he did something
that he doesn't
even know he did,
and so he's in, like. . .
That's enough, Jackie.
No, but he's in, like,
witness protection or
something.
Just stop it, please.
Sorry.
Next time you need help,
call your other sister.
No, wait.
You don't have
another sister.
l didn't call you, Jackie.
You called me.
Yeah, and l came here
to pick you up, and it's,
like, the first time
you've tried to
see me in months,
by the way.
ALEX:
The base is in San Lazaro.
lt's about 45 minutes
south of L.A. on the coast.
CLAlRE: Uh-huh.
Yeah, l booked you
a flight into
John Wayne Airport
in Orange County.
Okay, with luggage?
Luggage, rental car.
You should be on the base
between 1 1 :00, 1 1 :30.
Good afternoon, ma'am.
May l see l. D. , please?
All right.
(SOLDlERS CHATTERlNG)
Mrs. Kubik.
James Hernandez.
Ron and l were
in the same unit.
This must be
a terrible shock to you,
ma'am,
but if there's
anything l can do. . .
Anderson. Atchison.
Chapman. Green.
Ron was a good Marine.
Now, l won't keep you.
Good luck.
Thank you.
At the end of the hall,
ma'am.
Room B, ma'am.
What the. . .
Where the hell
are his clothes?
Suicide watch, ma'am.
l want
clothes put on him
right now.
You'd have to
file that request
with the brig command
on your way out.
(CHUCKLES)
ls your name Ron Chapman?
(SlGHS)
Yes.
How. . .
l don't know what to say.
l had no choice.
l had no. . .
They were
accusing me of something
that l didn't do.
Please believe me.
Believe you?
Well, l believed that
you were raised
in a foster home.
l was.
That you were never married.
Claire.
That you don't
have any children.
That you love me, Ron.
Tom. Whatever your name is.
(CLAlRE SNlFFLES)
l do love you.
But l did not do this.
Okay?
l swear that
l never did this.
And l didn't
want to tell you,
'cause l didn't
want you to leave me.
What happened?
My lawyer's here.
Mrs. Kubik?
Sorry to interrupt.
First Lieutenant Embry.
Terrence.
Hi.
l'm older than l look. So. . .
Well, l'll let you two. . .
l'll wait in the. . .
Claire.
Just let me go
talk to him, okay?
First Lieutenant,
is that what l call you?
Lieutenant.
Okay, why the hell
haven't you filed
a request
to get him out of
those goddamn chains
and into some clothes?
Right, yeah.
l'll take care of it.
Lieutenant,
l'm an attorney.
May l please see
the charging document?
We call it a charge sheet.
Fabulous. May l see it?
Can you give me
the basics?
Article 85, desertion.
Article 90, assaulting
or willfully disobeying
a superior
commissioned officer.
Murder? Nine. . .
Yes, if convicted,
he'll get
the death penalty.
(GASPS)
Who's prosecuting?
Major Lucas Waldron
has been detailed
as trial counsel.
He any good?
The best.
How about you?
l do okay.
Have you ever
won a case?
No.
l'm going to defend you.
l know you didn't
kill nine people.
EMBRY: Mrs. Kubik,
this is a. . .
l don't want you
involved in this.
l'm already involved.
You don't understand.
Military law is not
the same.
l'll learn.
We're gonna
fight them, okay?
Together.
(BELL CLANGlNG)
TOM: You remember those
three American kids?
Students who were killed
in that café in El Salvador,
back in '99?
Not the camera, man.
lt was a little town
called Monte Azul.
A member of a rebel group
threw a satchel bomb
into that café.
Press had a field day.
Right. Everybody went nuts.
So they call up my unit,
Detachment 27,
to locate the rebel leader
who was responsible.
He was a terrorist
by the name of
Danilo Chacon.
And your orders came from?
Our CO at Camp Lejeune.
Bill Marks.
Anyways. . .
Wait. l'm sorry.
Brigadier General Marks?
Special Representative
to the Joint Congressional
Committee
on Military Appropriations,
Bill Marks?
Yes. He was
Colonel Bill Marks
back then.
Under his orders,
we were sent into
a little village
called Las Colinas.
lt's not even a village,
even.
Just some fields,
a few huts.
Danilo Chacon was supposed
to be hiding out there.
And. . .
lt was supposed
to be routine.
But somebody lost it.
(GUN FlRES)
TOM: l hear gunfire.
(GUNS FlRlNG)
By the time
l get to the other
end of the village,
nine people are slaughtered,
and. . .
God damn.
l'm just standing there.
Old women, men, kids,
just dead.
And l lost it.
l jumped the guy
who did it.
And next thing l know,
l'm looking at first degree,
nine specs.
Who did it?
Hernandez.
Jimmy Hernandez.
He ordered me to
keep my mouth shut.
Said he was
teaching them a lesson,
that Marks would
back him up 1 00%.
l told him to go to hell.
Major Hernandez?
Marks' top aide?
Yes.
He introduced
himself to me yesterday,
in the waiting area.
What?
Claire,
l want you to listen to me.
l want you to
stay away from him.
He's extremely dangerous.
Do you understand?
So, General Marks. . .
See, he's like
the most decorated,
most powerful, most. . .
And you're saying
you were framed
by General Marks and
his special assistant.
(STAMMERS)
That's our defense?
Yup.
(CAR LOCK BEEPS)
Claire, would you
sit down for a minute?
l'm not gonna pretend
l'm looking forward
to seeing the firm's name
even remotely connected
to this.
As it stands now,
nobody knows Ron Chapman
is Tom Kubik.
Alex, my husband is innocent.
l'm not considering
any other possibility.
And l'm even
less interested
than you are
in seeing his name
associated with
a mass murder.
Claire, l just want you
to understand
all the possible
unforeseen consequences.
You know what, Alex?
l'll make it
real easy for you.
lf the firm's name
gets dragged into this,
you don't have to fire me.
l'll resign.
Hey, Josh,
remember that thing
from the 20. . .
Thank you.
Claire, can l do anything?
Yeah. l need a lawyer,
somebody from
the Marine Corps,
somebody who's
beaten them before
and is hungry to
beat them again.
Where will you be?
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
(FAX MACHlNE WHlRRlNG)
Bill. Bill.
William.
(CHARLlE LAUGHlNG)
l'm looking for
a Charlie Grimes.
Well, don't tell me
you need a lawyer,
because you are one.
l followed the Norris case.
Talk about
a rabbit out of a hat.
Are you Charles W. Grimes?
You just can't get
over my decorator,
can you?
Welcome to
Grimes and Associate.
Associate?
Delilah?
Rumor has it that
you're a very good
attorney,
formerly of the JAG Corps.
ln another life.
And in that former life,
you had an affair
with your
superior officer's wife,
and they pushed you out.
Let's not dwell on
my youthful offenses,
Mrs. Kubik. What do you want?
The military has
set up my husband,
and they've assigned
some junior varsity
lieutenant to defend him.
Who's prosecuting?
Waldron.
Tell your husband
to cop a plea.
Try to make a deal
with the judge.
Military justice
is to justice
as military music is
to music, Mrs. Kubik.
Wake up and smell the napalm.
Charlie, you're not
gonna believe this shit.
They busted me again.
lt's like
every time l turn around,
they slap handcuffs on me.
That's because every time
you turn around,
you've got some
private's privates
standing at attention, Lola.
You know, l perform
a very important service
for the military.
There's a novel defense.
You do somebody
at the base, too?
Yeah, actually.
How about your lawyer here?
ls he any good?
When he gets off
his ass, yeah.
How about it, Mr. Grimes?
LOLA: Man,
turn this shit off.
Nice to meet you, Lola.
LOLA: l'm due in court
in an hour.
CHARLlE: Hey! ln an hour?
(KNOCKlNG AT DOOR)
Jackie.
l'm here to help,
'cause what are
sisters for?
Wow. Tacky.
You got evicted,
didn't you?
What happened to
the money l sent?
Too little too late,
too much credit card debt.
JACKlE: All l need's
an extra phone line.
CLAlRE: What for?
My new job.
Psychic hot line.
Don't laugh.
l'm really good at it.
MAN ON RADlO:
Twenty-nine past the hour
if you're on your way to work.
Otherwise, kick back.
l got you covered,
wall-to-wall.
Good morning, Lieutenant.
EMBRY:
Good morning, Mrs. Kubik.
l'm gonna kill
that goddamn clock.
Hi, G. l. Joe.
Ma'am.
"Ma'am."
Claire,
did you just hear that?
He just called me ma'am.
Shall we?
Yeah, let's
get out of here.
CLAlRE: So l do not
need any security clearance
for the pretrial portion.
Yes, exactly. The only
portions of the trial
that are classified
are those pertaining
directly to the incidents
in El Salvador.
So, l just. . . You know,
l hope she didn't
think l was staring.
Who?
Well, your sister.
Don't worry about it.
She understands.
She's psychic.
Okay.
CLAlRE:
Well, what do you know?
Mr. Grimes has decided
to join us after all.
Mrs. Kubik, you do know
that Charlie Grimes
has a history of
being a major drunk?
Are you sober, Mr. Grimes?
Four hundred and
sixty-two days,
Mrs. Kubik.
Ain't life grand?
Fill me in.
Pretrial hearing is in 1 0.
Ten what?
Minutes.
What?
You don't think
they'll be impressed
with leather?
Who's the judge?
Colonel Farrell.
Yeah, it would be.
Full bird colonel
at his terminal rank.
He'll piss all over us
because we're civilians,
and he won't give a shit
about reversals down the line
because he's
about ready to retire.
You file any motions?
Absolutely.
Dismiss all charges,
insufficient evidence.
CHARLlE: Motion denied.
You haven't even
read the brief.
No doubt neither has Farrell.
The whole
military judicial system
is based on denial.
Then we fight
the system.
No, no, no.
You play by the rules.
You do not
fight the system.
Fight the system,
you lose.
lsn't that right, Embry?
Say, "Yes, sir."
Yes, sir.
Don't be a sap, Embry.
Nobody in a uniform
can think for himself.
This is a pretrial hearing,
Mr. Grimes.
The goal is to listen
and not reveal anything.
Do we have
anything to reveal,
Mrs. Kubik?
Claire.
Claire?
No.
CHARLlE: No?
Then that ought to work.
Which one's the prosecutor?
Trial counsel.
We call them
trial counsels.
Mrs. Kubik,
l'm Major Waldron.
How do you do?
Hi, Lucas.
Charlie Grimes.
lt's nice to see you.
Bullshit.
BAlLlFF: All rise.
Be seated.
This Article 39-A session
is called to order.
l'm Colonel Farrell
of the U.S. Marine Corps.
Where the hell
is the accused?
(DOOR OPENS)
Charlie Grimes.
l'll explain later.
Sergeant Chapman,
you see the charges
against you.
How do you plead?
Your Honor,
before my client
submits a plea,
would you please
address our motion
to have all
charges dismissed?
Motion denied.
Since you are painfully
unfamiliar with our
court-martial system,
we don't have clients here.
Sergeant Ron Chapman
is the accused,
and l'm still waiting
for the plea.
l plead not guilty.
Not guilty.
FARRELL: You may be seated.
Your Honor,
prosecution requests
the court's ruling
on the permissibility
of the accused
being represented
by his spouse.
Your Honor. . .
l'll allow it.
Thank you, Your Honor.
The prosecution requests
a short pretrial
period to ensure security.
Granted.
Opening statements are
scheduled for
one week from today.
Objection ! Your Honor,
there's no way we can
prepare defense
for a capital case
in one week.
Noted and overruled.
Are we done?
Your Honor, l'd like to add
that the defense
has no intention
of waiving our
right to a public trial
as guaranteed by
the Sixth Amendment.
WALDRON: Your Honor,
this case involves
national security
and classified information.
We would like
defense counsel
admonished
that any attempt
to try this case
in the media
would be a direct violation
of this court's order.
CHARLlE: Your Honor,
co-counsel and l are
civilians
and not subject
to military orders.
Any such orders, sir,
will be taken for
informational purposes only.
Be advised, Counsel,
that civilian or not,
you can go to
the brig and
be disqualified
from participating in
this trial altogether.
BAlLlFF: All rise.
And so it begins.
See you soon.
He's supposed
to be the best.
What the hell was that?
l said you should
follow the rules.
l'm the wild card.
You could've gotten us
thrown off the case.
Nah, it's too early.
See, if they think
we're gonna go public,
we might get an idea
how scared they are.
What do you think, Embryo?
l think, "Why me?
Why was l assigned
to this case?"
(CHARLlE LAUGHS)
CHARLlE:
Seven guys in Tom's unit,
and all of them say he did it.
But only two of
these eyewitnesses
are on their list.
Hernandez and Troy Abbott.
Now what happened
to the other five?
Dead.
CHARLlE: All of them?
Dead how?
Two were killed in combat,
the Gulf and Panama.
One was murdered.
And the other two,
accidents.
Accidents?
EMBRY: Mmm-hmm.
l know a couple of Pl's,
ex-Green Berets.
Not very ethical,
but maybe they
could get us the
unofficial version
of how these guys died.
Could be useful.
Here we go. Troy Abbott,
Sacramento, California.
Doing four to six in Lompoc,
armed robbery.
And Waldron's office
is trying to
expedite his parole.
Now, why am l certain
he's gonna succeed?
'Cause it's the Marine Corps.
"Be all you can be."
BOTH: That's the Army.
Yeah, Mrs. Kubik,
l really think our theory
should be that
Hernandez acted alone.
l mean,
no one's gonna believe
that Brigadier General Marks
was in on this.
ln other words,
you don't believe it.
Mrs. Kubik,
that's not my point.
Do you believe Tom or not?
Easy. He's just
expressing his opinion.
lsn't there something
you should be
doing somewhere else?
Not really.
Can l get you
another coffee, sir?
No, ma'am. l'm good.
Okay.
Come here.
Now, l'm gonna have
to agree with Embry.
A guy like Marks
smells, looks,
tastes credible.
Put him on the stand,
he's just gonna give
Hernandez credibility.
EMBRY: Right,
that's what l'm saying.
Well, young man's had
an original thought.
(PHONE RlNGS)
You know what?
What?
JACKlE: That my line?
CLAlRE: No.
Go to hell.
CHARLlE: Another one.
Hello?
MAN: Mrs. Kubik,
will you hold
for Major Waldron?
Yes, l'll hold
for Major Waldron.
WALDRON: Hello, Mrs. Kubik.
Hello, Major.
Why don't you folks
come down to my
office about 9:00?
Let's try to
work something out.
We'll be there.
l can't believe it.
They want a deal.
l love being a wild card.
Mr. Kubik, sir,
voluntary manslaughter,
only one specification,
that's only five years.
Plus one condition,
that you sign
a nondisclosure agreement.
And as your counsel, l. . .
CHARLlE: Claire,
tell the man
to take the deal
of the century.
Sweetheart?
Honey,
l won't do five minutes
for a crime l didn't commit.
Do you have any idea,
any of you,
do you have any idea
what it's like to spend
23 hours a day
in a 6-by-8 cell?
Five years in Leavenworth.
They'll make sure
l'm dead
long before that.
So, motion denied.
(RlNGS)
Come on in.
Based on our conversation. . .
That's all right, Major.
We're here to tell you
we're gonna pass.
Thanks anyway.
Mrs. Kubik.
Personally, l'm quite happy
to go to trial with this case,
but there is a lot
of interest in putting
this thing behind us.
lt works for everyone,
command and your husband.
And Major Hernandez
and General Marks.
See you in court, sir.
WOMAN ON TV: ...here on
the Fantasy Jewelry Hour.
MAN ON TV: You can
normally expect to pay $1 99
for a ring like this.
Yes, you would, Jim,
and this beautiful piece
is available right now...
So, no deal.
Can you believe
l asked my husband to do
five years in prison?
Go ahead.
Tell me what a waste of
oxygen all lawyers are.
MAN ON TV: So if you're
on the phone right now,
don't get off the line.
You're not gonna
wanna miss this.
WOMAN ON TV: That's right.
You're curiously quiet
on the subject.
Jackie, would you
please turn that down?
l mean, come on. . .
(CLAlRE EXCLAlMS)
MAN: Your husband
came to my village
and killed my family.
(GUN CLlCKS)
And it's true,
lawyers are
a waste of oxygen.
Drop this deal. . .
(KNOCKlNG AT DOOR)
EMBRY: Jackie? Mrs. Kubik?
(THUDDlNG)
(CLAlRE MOANlNG)
Hey.
He ran out.
JACKlE: Claire?
Claire, are you okay?
TOM: Bastards!
lt's Hernandez.
Oh, God damn.
We turned down their deal,
and he's trying to scare us.
Baby, you don't know
how these people work.
l don't know
how any of it works.
TOM: What do you mean?
This other life of yours.
You don't believe me,
do you?
Of course l believe you.
Baby, l'll take a polygraph.
There's no need for it.
lt's not even
admissible in court.
The hell with the courts.
l wanna do it for us.
Hey, Ronnie
or Tommy or Paco
or whatever it is.
You haven't changed a bit.
Major Hernandez,
this is
an unethical ex parte.
l'm just here to help.
What are you doing here?
Hey, you ought to
plead this out, Ace.
Major. . .
Tom, don't! Stop it!
Stop!
You're making it worse!
(MEN GRUNTlNG)
CLAlRE:
Who let Major Hernandez
in here?
He's not authorized
to be in here!
See? Look at your killer!
CLAlRE:
He is provoking my client!
Who is in charge?
Who let him in here?
Look at your killer!
He's not supposed
to be in here!
SOLDlER: Major Hernandez said
he was a defense witness.
He is not a witness
for the defense!
Who is in charge?
l want to talk to
whoever is in charge!
(DOOR SLAMS)
WOMAN: ls your real name
Ron Chapman?
TOM: Yes.
Regarding the incident
at Las Colinas
on March 1 5, 1 988,
will you answer my
questions truthfully?
Yes.
Did you actively participate
in the death of anyone
during the 1 5th of March,
1 988, shootings?
(DOOR OPENlNG)
Mrs. Kubik?
You passed.
Of course l passed.
Are we being monitored?
No, it's absolutely secure.
Absolutely secure?
What do you mean?
What do you think l mean?
And, Lieutenant Colonel,
were there any eyewitnesses
to this massacre?
Yes. We had
seven eyewitness
statements
all l. D.-ing
Chapman as the shooter.
Thank you.
Nothing further,
Your Honor.
Colonel LaPierre,
you were, and still are,
a special agent
with the Criminal
lnvestigations Division
in charge of this
investigation, yes?
That's correct.
So when you say
that the investigation
was not flawed,
you're basically
giving yourself
a big thumbs-up.
l'm just expressing
my opinion.
So help you God,
no doubt.
Now, is it possible,
Colonel, that these
so-called witnesses
were coached
before you got
your hands on them?
l guess it's possible,
but unlikely.
And are you aware
that of the seven witnesses,
two were
subsequently killed
in combat?
Yes, l'm aware of that.
And another three,
three relatively young men,
have died as well?
Yes.
Let's see.
There was a Lieutenant Allen
of Longview, Texas,
hit and run.
A Sergeant Stenstrom of Taos,
New Mexico,
accidental drowning.
And the other,
an unfortunate
mountain climbing fall.
That sounds right.
Does it?
Well,
that's interesting, Colonel,
seeing as how
l just made up
those causes of death.
l mean, there was no
accidental drowning
and no mountain climbing fall.
l do have the details
of these tragic deaths
including a fatal
home-invasion robbery,
if you'd care
to look at them.
l'm a little fuzzy
on the details.
l wasn't in charge of
those investigations.
No further questions,
Colonel.
My investigation was
strictly by the book.
No further questions.
(CELL PHONE RlNGS)
CLAlRE: Hello?
CHARLlE: Claire,
it's Charlie.
You know
the witness in Tom's unit
who was murdered?
(SOLDlERS WHlSTLlNG)
Yeah, home-invasion robbery.
He was killed
right in front of his wife.
And the word is,
she accused the military
of having been involved.
Will she talk to us?
Problem there is
that she disappeared
right after that.
(DOORBELL RlNGS)
Hey. ls this a bad time?
Hey.
A bad time? No.
l was thinking
we could go over
the Hernandez cross.
Well, l was just
taking a break,
'cause, l was going over
the Hernandez stuff myself,
and. . .
(JACKlE CHATTERlNG)
Please don't be mad.
lt wasn't him.
lt was all me.
Mrs. Kubik,
l want you to know
this doesn't
affect anything,
okay?
l mean, my work.
l'm totally up for it.
He is.
Come on, Claire,
we were just
going over his briefs.
Claire, wait.
You never can take
anything seriously,
can you? Nothing, ever.
Yeah, that's right, Claire.
You know,
you get to be the lawyer,
so l gotta get to
bang one, right?
We're closed. Closed !
Sorry, lady,
we're closed.
WOMAN: Excuse me.
Can you tell me
how to get to State Street?
Sure. Two blocks down.
WOMAN: Thank you.
Sorry.
Want some cheese?
Yeah, l could make
an omelet.
l'll make one.
You want cheddar?
American? Swiss?
Cheddar's good.
MAN: Mrs. Chapman?
lt's Kubik.
Okay, Mrs. Kubik.
l want to tell you
about what
l do for a living.
This sicko bothering you?
'Cause l know how
to deal with weirdos
who hang around
the frozen food section.
l teach guys
to beat the box.
Who are you?
l teach techniques
that enable anyone
to beat a polygraph,
like special
operations personnel
who might be captured,
interrogated
behind enemy lines.
Basically, l teach people
to create a new persona.
That way, when they lie,
they're not really lying.
Why are you telling me this?
l don't know.
But my guess is, you do.
Hey, who are you?
Who sent you?
l was just asked
to convey this
message to you.
Just so you'd know,
along with everyone else.
Good night, Mrs. Kubik.
JACKlE: Okay, get out of here.
Hey, honey.
ls it true?
What?
That you get that
kind of training,
to beat the box?
What are you talking about?
The polygraph, Tom.
Sure,
but l didn't beat the box.
l told the truth.
Why didn't you tell me
you could do that?
'Cause it just didn't
occur to me.
That's not a part
of who l am anymore.
Well, that's it, isn't it?
That's it right there.
How do l know
who you are?
Claire, you're the only one
who knows who l am.
You know what?
That's it. l. . .
l don't care anymore.
l did it.
l shot them all. Yeah.
For the fun of it. Why not?
Who the hell cares, Claire?
You know, the man you've been
waking up to every morning
loves,
just loves to kill women
and children in cold blood.
'Cause l. . .
Who the hell knows why,
Claire?
Am l making any sense?
Does what l'm saying
make any sense to you?
No.
(BOTH SOBBlNG)
TOM: This whole base
ain't secure.
They know every move we make.
Tell me.
How do they know, Charlie?
How do they know?
CHARLlE:
Good question, Mrs. Kubik.
Good question.
Damn, Charlie Grimes.
Hey, Renny.
lt's been ages.
Did you come to
beg for leftovers?
No, l just want
to look through
your trash. Okay?
(MAN SlNGlNG) White shroud
Clear blue sky
The sea swells a bit
When sailors die
Was that a word?
(MEN CHEERlNG)
ls this a clue?
You're so very far away
But l'm sure it's you
What's the problem?
Take it easy. God damn !
(THUMPlNG)
MAN: Hold his legs.
No. No.
Hold him.
CHARLlE: No, no, please.
Come on, come on.
l just don't believe it.
l refuse.
And my sister-in-law
used to say
truth is less fun
than fiction.
Terry would never do that.
You're screwing him,
so you know him?
Excuse me,
Mrs. Ron Chapman.
l gotta sit down.
(KNOCKlNG AT DOOR)
Well, well, well.
What happened?
Lucy, you got a lot
of explaining to do.
Charlie, you all right?
Who did this?
Just some of the old gang
from down at the club,
the same group
that mysteriously knows
every move we make.
What are you talking about?
How did they know
about the polygraph?
Tarot cards?
Were you with them?
Were you drinking
with Waldron?
Wait a minute. Every Friday
everybody drinks there.
We don't talk about cases.
Charlie,
you were in the Corps.
You know
what it's like, right?
Claire, you can understand.
l understand you're fired.
What? No, listen.
This case will be over,
and you'll be gone,
but l'll still be here.
Did you know about this?
What? Wait a minute.
Did you? Did you know
about the attack
on me and Claire?
Or was it just
a coincidence. . .
What? You seriously
think l would do. . .
What do you say
we go to the hospital,
Charlie?
l'm worried
about your ribs.
Just get me some ice.
Hell, l've been here before.
And l won't be there
for Hernandez.
l got word.
Troy Abbott got his parole.
l gotta go track him down.
HERNANDEZ: Well,
kind of sick.
See, Chapman taunted
the victims.
He tossed his gun
around like a cowboy,
kind of showing off,
and then
he executed them.
Please continue, Major.
l ran to the south
end of the village,
but it was too late.
They were all dead.
Chapman was still shooting.
(GUN FlRES)
MARlNE: Chapman !
Two other members of the unit
assisted me,
and we got him down,
we got his weapon.
Major, you say
Sergeant Chapman
did some sick things.
Yet you, his XO,
allowed him to proceed
without any supervision?
l didn't realize
he'd take it that far.
Had Chapman ever been
cited for this kind of
behavior before?
No, he had not.
CLAlRE: ln fact, wasn't he
the most experienced
and reliable member
of Detachment 27?
Before you answer,
that's a direct quote
from a report you filed.
Defense exhibit A.
HERNANDEZ:
Chapman was a good Marine.
Courageous. Honest.
l thought so.
The kind of good
Marine who would not
go along with a cover-up. . .
WALDRON: Objection.
. . .for you who actually
committed the killing.
Objection !
FARRELL: Sustained.
Make that your last outburst,
Counselor.
Jury members,
you are instructed to
disregard that accusation.
Major, how is it
possible that seven men,
spread all over a village,
would witness
the exact same thing?
We all got to the barn
at the same time.
Wow. How convenient.
Doesn't it make more sense
that some of those
alleged witnesses
were ordered to lie
on their C. l. D. statements?
They were not ordered to lie.
CLAlRE: How do you know?
l would know if
something like that
happened to my men.
CLAlRE: And if
something like that
happened to your men,
you would tell us?
Of course.
l wouldn't lie about it.
But, Major,
you were trained
and often compelled
to lie about your
clandestine missions.
As l understand it,
you're trained to
beat a polygraph.
ls it true you
possess that talent?
l'd only use it
if interrogated
by the enemy, ma'am.
That's good to know.
So, tell me this, Major.
Do you consider me a friend?
(MAN AND WOMAN CHATTERlNG)
Hey.
l ain't done
nothing with her.
l ain't interested
if there's gonna
be pimps involved.
No, no. You got that
all wrong, brother.
That ain't me.
Shit. l should be so lucky.
No, l'm just supposed
to deliver this
to Troy Abbott.
That you?
Yeah. Who from?
lt's from Jimmy Hernandez,
down at the base.
GRAClE: Hey, Charles.
Grace,
what are you doing here?
Got a call from the base.
You got a call
from the base?
Yup.
Bullshit
you got this call !
l got this. . .
What, bitch?
Who you raising up?
Get up!
GRAClE: l'm gonna whup
your nasty ass self!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
l'm tired of this shit!
CHARLlE:
Why are you always
getting into trouble?
GRAClE: Why you always
trying to play daddy?
CHARLlE: Apologize to the man.
GRAClE: l ain't. . .
Do you want me
to apologize, baby?
Do you?
Gracie can
apologize real good.
Do you?
Do you want me
to say sorry?
l'm sorry.
CHARLlE: So they paroled you?
TROY: Yeah.
Then they bring me
all the way to
this dump to testify.
Why? What really
happened that night?
TROY:
Hey, l don't know, man.
lt was years ago.
El Salvador.
Some massacre shit.
CHARLlE: l'll bet
some damn officer
ordered it too, right?
You ain't thirsty?
Yeah. Shit, yeah.
l'm just, you know,
just chilling.
(GRlS-GRlS GUMBO YA-YA
PLAYlNG)
(MAN SlNGlNG)
They call me Dr. John
Known as the night tripper
My satchel of
Gris-Gris in my hand
Day trippin' up
Back down the bayou
l'm the last of the best
l'm known as the Gris-Gris man
Sellin'
Gris-Gris Gumbo Ya-Ya
Hit it now
Hey, now...
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
So then what
did you say back?
That's like. . .
Yeah, what'd you say?
Come on, tell us.
We never get to
hear shit like this.
Come on. Damn, man.
All right, hey, hey.
Who we gonna tell,
you know what l'm saying?
What'd you say?
That l was
nowhere near
the place.
And they want me to say
that l saw this guy shooting.
GRAClE: Damn.
That's intense.
You gonna do it?
Hell, l already did it
in my statement to the C. l. D.
l just gotta testify
to what l already said,
you know?
GRAClE: What's C. l. D.?
Criminal
lnvestigative Division.
Yeah,
but what about
this poor guy?
Forget the poor guy.
l mean,
what are you gonna do?
Your XO comes up, says,
"You see Chapman
shoot the wetbacks?"
You say, "No, sir, l didn't."
He says, "Be sure about this.
Your career's on the line."
Everybody else
said he did it.
So l say
what they want to hear.
One more witness,
no difference. Right?
Right.
(CAR LOCK BEEPlNG)
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
WOMAN: 91 1 . What is your
address and emergency?
Yes. 1 01 45. Yeah. Yeah.
All right, ma'am.
ls this an emergency?
No, there's somebody
trying to get in the house.
CHARLlE: Claire?
Hello? ls he in?
No. No, no.
lt's okay.
l'm sorry.
CHARLlE:
Claire, open the door.
False alarm?
CHARLlE: Claire?
Yeah, it was a false alarm.
Thanks.
CHARLlE: Claire?
Charlie,
you scared me to death.
That guy was out there.
What guy?
You've been drinking.
Who, me?
Oh, my God.
No. No, no.
You got it wrong.
See, l'm just a victim
of hazardous
working conditions.
Frightful life.
Sure you are.
No, really.
That man was
watching the house.
No. Ain't nobody out there.
What is this?
Looks like a recorder.
Hmm.
ls Abbott on here,
saying he never saw
what he agreed to
testify to in court?
You didn't?
l most certainly did.
And you know what?
He was nowhere
near the shooting.
l mean, nowhere near it.
Charlie, this is fabulous.
This does it.
This proves they're
setting him up.
Charlie, l. . .
You really think
l wanted to give up
483 days of sobriety
and start all over
at day one, Claire?
l'll make some coffee.
Wait a minute.
Not so fast.
See, l figure,
"Hey,
you already slipped,
Charlie.
"So what's one
more gonna hurt?"
How about it, Claire?
One for our side.
l can't. l'm trying
to get pregnant.
Well.
l'm not trying
to get pregnant.
l am certainly not
trying to get pregnant.
(WHlSPERlNG)
You're absolutely right,
but a judge will be
more lenient.
(lNDlSTlNCT WHlSPERlNG)
FARRELL: You're late, Counsel.
Prosecution
requests a sidebar.
Make it good.
Your Honor, our next witness,
Troy Abbott, has disappeared.
What?
WALDRON: Things are gone
from his room.
Now, we've
notified the MPs. . .
Notified, my ass.
You let him out of jail,
and you turned him loose.
Watch your language.
Your Honor, we have a tape
that impeaches Abbott's
original statement
and fully vindicates
our client.
WALDRON: What tape?
There was no discovery
about a tape.
Why, you with discovery.
You got spies all over.
ln my chambers,
everybody.
Court is recessed.
All rise!
TROY ON TAPE:
l mean, what are you gonna do?
Your XO comes up, says,
"You see Chapman
shoot the wetbacks?"
You say, "No, sir, l didn't."
He says, "Be sure about this.
Your career's on the line."
Everybody else
said he did it.
So l say what
they want to hear.
One more witness,
no difference. Right?
Without Abbott,
we can't authenticate
this tape.
For all we know,
he may have been
coerced,
any number of things.
lt's inadmissible.
What?
Your Honor,
you admitted Abbott's
C. l. D. statement.
We need this to rebut it.
This tape clearly
exonerates Ron Chapman.
The C. l. D. statement
was taken by
an objective party.
Bullshit! He lied !
They lied !
How the hell is
that objective?
The tape is excluded.
What's next?
Your Honor!
Excluded, Counselor.
Major?
We're out of witnesses,
Your Honor.
The prosecution rests.
Your Honor,
this is a capital case.
An objective judge
would admit the tape,
and you know it.
We'll hear from
the defense next Friday.
This is grounds
for an appeal.
Honey?
Claire. . .
We'll appeal this.
Claire, stop.
You can't fight them.
Tom, don't talk that way.
We'll get another break.
l know we will.
You do not know
these people.
Stop it before you
get yourself hurt.
We can win this.
l am not gonna let
them do this to you.
What are you doing?
ls that a. . .
Must have done it
when they installed
the phones.
And you two were
so ready to blame Terry.
So self-righteous.
Let's go to Farrell,
demand a mistrial.
Denied. There's no way
we'd ever be able to prove
that Waldron or Hernandez
had anything at all
to do with this.
Then what?
We are out of witnesses,
and we are out of time.
Maybe it's time
we heard from
the brigadier general.
Not on the stand.
No.
You think we should
pay him a visit?
l think you should
pay him a visit.
Why me?
Are you scared of him?
(CHUCKLES)
No, but l'm just a thorn
in the Marine Corps' ass.
But you, my dear,
you're the pretty, young,
sympathetic little wife.
l don't play those games.
Shit.
(CHATTERlNG)
General Marks?
No press, please.
l'm not press.
How do you do?
Miss. . .
Kubik. Claire Kubik.
l'm representing my husband,
Sergeant Ron Chapman?
Mrs. Kubik. Good day.
General Marks,
you gave James Hernandez. . .
l have nothing to say to you.
. . .the order
to eliminate Danilo Chacon
and his terrorist
group at Las Colinas.
You knew they fully
expected Detachment 27
to come under attack.
You're a dignified man, sir.
End the cover-up.
How dare you?
Your man James Hernandez
overreacted and opened fire.
You know what happened.
Young lady,
you are way out of line.
Listen to this, sir,
and tell me
how out of line l am.
CHARLlE ON MACHlNE:
This is C.W. Grimes
and Associates.
lf you want to
talk to Charlie,
you should
leave a message
after the beep.
lf you want to
talk to Delilah,
you should get
your head examined.
(BEEPlNG)
CLAlRE: Well, Charlie,
that was a great idea.
The man flicked
me off his suit
like l was a flea.
l am gonna lose my mind.
l mean,
we cannot let them
get away with this.
There has to be
somebody who was there.
somebody who's. . .
WOMAN: Directory assistance.
The Herald.
CLAlRE: Of course not.
When you settle down,
l do have something to say.
WOMAN: You're
representing your own husband
in the court-martial?
MAN: ls there
a military conspiracy
at work here?
CLAlRE: You know
that l cannot
legally comment on
the details of
a court-martial proceeding.
l would, however,
like to say,
emphatically,
that my husband is innocent.
There is a man
who's a stranger to me,
who said to me last week
that all lawyers
are a waste of oxygen.
(SNAPS)
As a wife and as an attorney,
l greatly fear
that justice in this case
will not
ultimately be served,
and l would like to
challenge that man
or anyone who has
firsthand knowledge
of what happened
that day in El Salvador
to please come forward.
Charlie?
WOMAN: Laurel, just to recap
today's press conference
with attorney Claire Kubik,
she's continually insisting
that her husband is innocent.
This attorney and wife
is clearly
standing by her man.
Reporting live
for Channel 1 2 News,
this is Karen Cobb.
(CELL PHONE RlNGlNG)
Hello?
ALEX:
You just had to do it.
You just had to.
The whole firm
just saw you on
the 6:00 news.
Hello, Alex.
l have been expecting your. . .
Claire?
l'll. . .
You'll. . .
l'll send you
my resignation tomorrow.
Claire?
Get in.
No.
Wait. Okay, wait. No.
Where are we going?
l want to know the truth.
l want to know
what happened
at Las Colinas.
You don't care
about the truth.
All you care about is
saving your husband.
MAN: Get out.
Get out.
You want to know
about Las Colinas?
Women like you,
beautiful, young,
and the old people
begging for their lives.
Jesus Christ.
lt was 1 2 years ago.
They all look the same,
a bunch of
gringos in uniform. . .
Don't be foolish.
lt's a photograph.
l just want to
show you a photograph.
l remember him,
the one with
the patch on his eye,
the blood still fresh from
the explosion at Monte Azul.
This man was
at Monte Azul?
Of course he was.
He killed Danilo Chacon.
Chacon was in the café
in a secret meeting
and this man was there.
He was there.
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
That's how he hurt his eye.
No, but Danilo Chacon
blew up the café
and killed the three
American students. . .
You people believe anything.
The students were killed
by mistake,
because the American military
didn't know they were there.
To cover it up,
they blamed the rebels
and pretended to
look for their leader
in Las Colinas,
but they knew
he was already dead.
They knew
they had killed
him with the bomb.
Thanks a lot.
You're welcome.
Well, if it isn't
little Miss Six O'Clock News.
You're drunk.
You were supposed
to call me, but. . .
When you got. . .
Charlie?
l called you.
l was out, but you
could have called back.
l thought we had
an agreement.
Excuse me.
l thought we had
an agreement.
l thought. . .
l thought me and
you was partners.
But you know,
partners don't
decide to do dumb shit. . .
Charlie, it worked.
. . .without telling
the other part of the team
that they'd done
some dumb shit.
Charlie?
What?
l just spent
an hour with the guy.
He's the real deal.
He saw the whole thing.
Tom's innocent.
This proves it.
There's a cover-up,
Charlie,
and it's bigger
than we thought.
l need you sober.
Yeah.
Come on.
Yeah, all right.
Let's get you home.
Okay, baby. All right.
No, Charlie.
Chris, last one.
Just one more.
Forget about it.
l got it. l got it.
Come on, partner.
All right, partner.
(SNORlNG)
(BANGlNG)
Damn, what was that?
What? Oh, my God !
Shit! lt's oil !
(WHlSPERlNG)
Hi, sweetie.
(GROANS)
l had the worst dream.
l dreamt l was pregnant
and these people came
and took the baby away.
You one lucky girl,
you and the gentleman.
l want you to
take something.
Here, baby.
Don't you worry
about a thing.
You'll have another baby.
What?
Don't you worry.
You'll have another one.
Jackie?
No. No.
l'm so sorry.
No. No. No.
That's not fair.
No.
l'm so sorry.
Be strong. Be strong.
You have to rest.
(SOBBlNG)
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
CHARLlE: Claire,
it's Charlie.
CLAlRE: Come in.
Hi.
How's your neck?
lt's all right.
l've had worse whiplash
just looking around
at pretty women like you
on the street.
l'm truly sorry, Claire.
l wanted that baby
so much, Charlie.
You know,
l kept thinking,
maybe there was
something wrong
with me,
or l didn't deserve it,
or l wouldn't be
a good mother.
l really didn't think
they'd do something
like this.
l'm at zero, Charlie.
Hey, whoa.
Whoa, now.
Listen to me.
l know about zero.
l've hit bottom,
and l was on
my way back there
before the accident.
But you know what?
l think we were
spared for some reason,
and you gotta believe that.
So, for you and me,
kiddo, this is day one.
Okay?
Hey, you got
another visitor.
Hello.
Merry Christmas.
You all right?
l owe you an apology,
Lieutenant.
We were mistaken.
EMBRY: That's okay.
Although, l'm not sure
merry is the right word
to use around here.
Well, that's where
you might be wrong,
Mrs. Kubik.
You see,
if it's true James Hernandez
injured his eye
in the bombing
at the café,
he would have got
immediate treatment
for it.
And they just keep records
of those covert operations
so people like us
can go look them up?
No,
he would have insisted on it
for insurance purposes,
so the government
couldn't screw him
out of compensation.
Thank you.
Agent Mullins!
l just need
a minute of your time.
Somehow l'm confident
it's not my rugged good looks
to which l owe the honor
of this visit.
The press accepted
the official version
of the story.
Well, what if Chacon
didn't blow up the café?
Mrs. Kubik. . .
What if James Hernandez,
the XO of my husband's unit,
blew up the café
and killed the American
students by mistake?
What if
Brigadier General Marks,
to cover the whole thing up,
staged a raid on Las Colinas?
What if all this
is not my job and
none of my business?
l'm just asking you
to help me look into it.
Make it a lean one, chief.
Why not?
l know you have
your sources.
My sources?
You keep saying
it's not your job.
MULLlNS: Good.
l wasn't sure
you were listening.
Well, Agent Mullins,
then whose job is it?
Come on, whose job?
God damn,
what a pain in the ass
you are.
Hernandez was
injured in the explosion.
There has got to be
a classified medical
document somewhere.
(SCREAMlNG)
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
Yeah?
MAC: Hey, Charlie,
it's me, man.
Hey, Mac.
l've been
checking out the rumors
about how those witnesses
in Chapman's unit really died.
Hell, l've been all
over the place, man.
l got expenses,
phone bills,
plane tickets.
lt's gonna cost you, man.
lt's gonna cost you.
Well, you told me that.
l found the wife
of the one who was murdered.
Lisa Stenstrom is
living in Mexico,
and she swears
the military
killed her husband.
Yeah?
Just inside, ma'am.
CLAlRE: Have you heard
from Charlie?
JACKlE: Yeah.
He called about an hour ago,
but he was really weird,
like he didn't want
to talk on the phone.
Well,
like Charlie,
l don't know
if l should talk
on the phone.
He did say he was in Mexico.
ln Mexico?
What is he doing in Mexico?
l don't know.
So you're on your way
back here or what?
Yeah, but l'm gonna stop
in Los Angeles first.
All right. Bye.
So, l'll see you.
(CAMERAS CLlCKlNG)
CLAlRE: General.
You all have
had him all night.
lt's my turn.
Shall we?
We uncovered the real reason
you sent Detachment 27
to Las Colinas.
Uncovered?
lt's a matter of
public record.
Well, not really.
What is a matter
of record, though,
is that James Hernandez
sustained an injury
to his left eye
in the bombing
at Monte Azul.
Eyewitnesses place him
in the truck
from which
the grenade was thrown,
and he had that injury treated
at a hospital in San Salvador,
before Las Colinas.
Your gung ho raid
was a decoy
for your bombing.
You know,
this fairy tale of yours
would have to be based
on classified material,
even if any of it
were remotely possible.
Now, you're bluffing,
and you're doing it badly.
After you.
Thank you.
You know,
General Marks,
we'd be only
too happy to have
you testify under oath
and allow
the court to fully
explore our evidence.
For example,
classified document
dated 3-1 4-88.
Major Hernandez's
medical report
for a shrapnel wound
at Santa Maria hospital.
You know,
that's the same day and
mighty close to Monte Azul.
(ELEVATOR BELL DlNGS)
You have no shame.
Look what
you're willing to do
to free a murderer.
Pick up the phone
and call the right people.
l want the charges dropped
or the document goes public.
Haven't you noticed
that you've been
unlucky lately?
Now, caution might be
the order of the day
for you.
l am not afraid of you.
l've already
survived you once,
you smug son of a bitch.
The real question is
will you survive me?
Make it go away, General,
or the document goes public.
(ELEVATOR BELL DlNGS)
For both our sakes, sir.
(SlRENS WAlLlNG)
Pull over, right here.
Jackie. Jackie?
Jackie?
Ma'am.
JACKlE: Claire?
You all right?
Oh, my God. Yeah.
What the hell's
that all about?
Colonel Farrell wants
us in court tomorrow
morning at 0800.
Waldron filed a motion
to have you disqualified
from the case
for talking to the press.
Any word from Charlie?
l've been trying him
on his cell all day.
Just getting voice mail.
We've still got Hernandez's
medical report.
l'll do my best.
Farrell wouldn't admit
a classified document
any more than he would
the Abbott tape.
Maybe you should
take the deal.
There's no more deal,
not now.
l'm sorry, Mrs. Kubik.
Why don't you
spend the night out?
l don't know if
it's a good idea to be
around here tonight.
l. . .
l could use
a little time
on my own.
(DOOR OPENlNG)
Hey. You heard from Charlie?
No.
What's going on, honey?
l don't know.
BAlLlFF: All rise.
Be seated.
Major Waldron, Mrs. Kubik,
please approach.
What the hell is this?
For reasons of
national security,
the Department of
Defense has determined
that charges against
Sergeant Ron Chapman
are to be withdrawn.
Court is closed.
Sergeant Chapman,
you're free to go.
Oh, my God.
Shit. Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
Hey, Charlie. Listen,
in case you're interested,
pal, we won.
We're going to Marin.
We're blowing this town.
lf you ever want to call me,
that's where we'll be.
Hope you're okay.
Jesus. Look at this.
What do you suggest l do?
Have Jackie meet us
on the next block
with her car.
Will there be more of
them at the airport?
CLAlRE: Probably.
Why do we need to bother?
Let's just drive.
Here you go.
Thanks, Embry.
Okay, good.
Thank you for everything.
Yeah. You take care
of yourself, Mr. Kubik.
You, too.
Okay.
Thanks, Jackie.
Well, kid.
Ma'am.
Old man.
Turns out you're okay.
Well, you too, kid.
Thank you so much,
Mrs. Kubik.
Thank you, Lieutenant.
We're gonna take our time.
EMBRY: Okay.
So we'll call you
when we get there.
Probably around 7:00.
Bye.
CLAlRE: Bye.
LlSA:
About a week before
Paul was murdered,
he started making phone calls
to an old Marine Corps buddy,
who, incidentally, was killed
about two months after Paul.
l don't know what
they talked about,
but it really upset him.
You have no idea
what it's like
to see somebody you love
killed right in front of you.
CHARLlE: And you believe
this is somehow connected
to the military?
Yeah.
lt's just a feeling,
'cause Paul knew him.
You know?
Well, he just seemed
to recognize him,
the thing he did
with the hands.
Paul seemed to
know who he was.
TOM: You think that
owl's still around here?
You know one thing
that bothered me
more than anything?
l couldn't protect you.
l had to stand by
while they hurt you.
Shit. l should have
got more champagne.
l love you.
(PHONE RlNGS)
l thought you unplugged that.
l did, but l tried
Charlie one more time.
CHARLlE: Hi, Claire.
lt's me.
Sweetheart, l'm sorry.
Look, l'm...
l'll be right back.
l'm sorry
l wasn't there today.
l didn't mean
to let you down.
Yeah, Charlie.
Hi.
Look, Claire,
l'm real sorry.
l just. . .
l couldn't get there.
Why today, Charlie,
of all days?
l mean, what if Marks
had opted to testify
or what...
You know what?
l don't want to
talk about it.
l thought l had a friend.
l am your friend, kiddo.
Sure you are.
Just say a toast
for my husband
while you drink
yourself silly.
Goodbye, Charlie.
Listen. l am your friend.
l was being your friend today
more than you'd care to know,
kiddo.
What do you mean?
We need to talk.
l just don't think that
now is a good time for it.
Where are you going?
l think AA meetings
are supposed
to be anonymous.
TOM: l'm gonna get
some more champagne.
CLAlRE: Okay. Hurry back.
CLAlRE:
Are Marks and Hernandez
going to give us trouble?
ls Tom still there?
No. He's going to the store.
All right,
get to your computer.
Pull up your calendar.
Find out where
your husband was
on January 20, 1 997.
Why are you
doing this,
Charlie?
Look it up, Claire.
lt's important.
CLAlRE:
Tom was in Santa Fe,
New Mexico.
He met a collector.
l picked him up
from the airport.
CHARLlE: February 1 0, '97.
Houston, Texas. Trade show.
Claire, listen to me.
Those are the dates
that witnesses were
murdered.
Stenstrom was murdered
January 20, 1 997,
in Santa Fe, New Mexico.
Allen died in Houston,
Texas, February 1 0.
And wait a minute.
Didn't Hernandez say
that Tom tossed his
gun back and forth,
taunting his victims?
ls he ambidextrous?
Yeah.
Stenstrom's wife
said the man
shot her husband,
then tossed
the gun back and forth,
showing off,
and shot him again
with the other hand.
l can't talk
about this right now.
Sure.
l'm sorry.
l'm sorry, Claire.
l just thought
l ought to let you know.
Fine. l gotta go.
l thought you
went to the store.
l grabbed the wrong keys.
Those are the right keys.
Those are Jackie's.
Oh.
What are you
working on there?
Nothing.
You want to run out with me
to get some champagne?
l'm not really in
the mood for champagne.
Ouch ! Tom.
l'm sorry.
Well, well,
let's just talk then.
Talk about what?
About what you
were talking about
on the phone.
What, you think
l'm stupid, Claire?
You must.
Why didn't you come to me
to talk about it?
You must like to keep
your secrets with. . .
Your life is
one big secret.
Did you do it, Tom?
You can tell me.
l certainly have
a right to know.
Risked my life for it.
Lost a baby.
Claire. . .
Did you kill those people?
Yes.
Yeah. Yeah.
l did. l had to. . .
lt's what l was
trained to do, Claire.
They lied to me.
They told me
they were terrorists.
Told me to interrogate them
and so you do what you have to
do to get every,
any kind of information
you can out of them.
And so l did.
Because l was the best at it,
and they knew it.
What about
Stenstrom and Allen?
Stenstrom saw me on
the street one day,
and he told Allen,
and they needed to go away.
You see?
Do not
look at me like that.
l do not, not deserve it.
Sorry.
l'm a bit tired.
l was just protecting us.
We'll get over this.
You'll see. Honey. . .
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
No!
CLAlRE: Stop it! Stop it!
Tom ! Oh, God,
you're hurting me!
You're hurting me.
(CLAlRE SCREAMlNG)
Stop it. Tom.
Stop it! Stop.
Look at me.
Honey. Honey. . .
Shut up. Shut up.
You're a liar.
Liar. Don't lie to me.
Liar.
(PANTlNG)
l didn't want
to have to do
this to you, Claire.
Tom. Tom.
(GUN FlRES)
Tom.
(BOTH GRUNTlNG)
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
lt's okay. lt's okay.
(SOFTLY) l'm sorry.
(MAN CHATTERlNG ON RADlO)
MAN: You're listening
to the Bay Area's
number one station for sports,
news and information.
You have a whole
suite of offices here,
Charlie.
Yeah, but don't talk about it
because l might get spooked.
l mean, who knows
what might happen?
How are you holding up?
l'm okay.
Same old associate?
Yeah.
She's back there in
the back somewhere.
l just brought her
a bone back from lunch,
so she's probably busy.
Hello. Sorry.
Come see me.
You're beautiful.
Hello.
You know, l often ask myself
why l never left San Lazaro.
Then it occurred to me that,
hell, l never left
because l didn't have
anyplace else to go.
You know, it could
read Grimes and Kubik.
lt's gotta say Grimaldi.
Huh?
My maiden name.
And, Charlie,
you gotta do something
about these colors.
What?
Well, l'm very sensitive
about my work environment.
Really?
Yeah.
So?
So l was thinking
about a tropical color.
Just like really pretty,
with a little contrasting
trim on the windows.
Claire!
Charlie,
check out this exterior.
l mean,
it's skid-row chic,
l understand that,
but, you know,
the watermarks gotta go.
That's a given.
So we could make it. . .
(l'M NOT THE ENEMY PLAYING)
(WOMAN SlNGlNG)
l don't know you
Don't know those
melancholy eyes l see
Do you even know me?
Your scent is familiar
Your voice familiar,
but those words you speak
Are not familiar to me
You can't love nobody
unless you love yourself
Don't take it out on me, baby
l'm not the enemy
Are you the man l love,
the man l know loves me
Come on, talk to me, boy
l'm not the enemy
Your worries, your stress
Are both the root
of your unhappiness
Fueled by insecurities
The pressures of being a man
is hard
Don't think l don't understand
Put a little faith in me
You can't love nobody
unless you love yourself
Don't take it out on me, baby
l'm not the enemy
l said, we can't be happy
until you're happy
with yourself
Come on, talk to me, boy
l'm not the enemy
Ooh, what l feel
is unconditional
l love you at your best
and at your worst
Don't shove me out
l'm here for you
l'm on your side
You can't love nobody
unless you love yourself
Don't take it out on me, baby
l'm not the enemy
Are you the man l love,
the man l know loves me
Come on, talk to me, boy
l'm not the enemy
You can't love nobody
unless you love yourself
Don't take it out on me, baby
l'm not the enemy
We can't be happy
until you're happy
with yourself
Come on, talk to me, boy
l'm not the enemy