What's your name?
- Shelly Gardner.
- Just need the first.
Oh, sorry.
How tall are you?
- 5'7".
- Age?
Oh, a gentleman never
asks a lady her age.
36?
Sorry, I lied.
I'm 42.
But this house is huge.
I mean, distance helps.
- Oh.
- Oh, gosh, I'm sorry.
I'm so nervous.
I've been on the Razzle-Dazzle
for so very long and...
I just haven't
auditioned in a while.
But it's exciting.
Yeah.
You have an act prepared?
I do. I'm a dancer.
Music?
Yeah.
I gave it to the maestro.
Okay.
Did someone raid a cemetery
for this fuckin' audience?
Oh, shh.
- Oh!
- Oh, shit!
- Go!
- Did that just rip?
- Shit.
- Go, go, go, go, go!
When did they install
that new door handle?
- Like, three months ago.
- Oh, God,
that thing is asking
for ripped costumes.
Are you sure? Is
it really ripped?
Yeah, it's ripped.
I have, like, 20/20 vision.
Good for fuckin' you, Jodie.
Okay. Yeah, bye.
That's good as wow!
I caught my wing on
that door handle!
It's a trap. They're
so desperate for money,
they're tryin' to squeeze
it back out of us.
Paranoid.
Oh, God, but you know,
they have to change that.
I mean, look at
this gaping hole.
Okay, let's keep
it movin', Shelly.
I will, I just... look at that.
Oh, gosh.
I mean, I love that darn wing.
You know, of all the
wings in the entire show,
that's the oldest wing.
- Ida is gonna kill me.
- Oh, whatever.
That old Russian bitch has
hated me for, like, nine years.
Because you keep losing
rhinestones and feathers.
Oh, I'm not tryin' to be
a klutz out there, Jesus.
I'm tryin' fuckin' dancing.
Like, what am I supposed to do?
I am dancing.
It's just so
disappointing, you know.
Lemons, and now this.
Lemons?
They've just recently
been so expensive.
Clip-ons, Shelly. Clip-ons?
Okay, can you
please put them on?
Okay, well, I am. I mean,
gosh, they're 89 cents apiece.
You know, lemons are
not even really food,
you know, they're
like a garnish.
They're more like herbs.
They're like accessories.
- Who needs lemons?
- Let's go!
Okay. Okay, okay.
Let's go!
The music's about to change.
Well, I'm buying some nice
salmon steaks for dinner
because I'm entertaining
tomorrow evening.
Music's changing.
I got this beautiful
salmon steak idea
from Ina Rosenberg's cookbook.
She has beautiful lemon
slices on the salmon.
Oh!
What? So I need them.
I need the lemons.
Shells, you've got
the wrong clip-ons.
Oh, my God. I mean,
when did they put
that door handle on anyway?
Like, two weeks ago?
It was, like, three months ago.
Oh, my God, I keep
forgetting that it's there.
Well, yeah, because you're old.
I mean, I'm older.
I'm not that old.
Okay, come on.
Come on!
Let's go!
Fuck you, door handle.
...I could go back
in time, you know,
and see the door
handle, say to myself...
You ladies mind moving
a little faster?
Everyone else is out there.
You're the only ones acting
like you're at fuckin' brunch.
Oh, like anyone gives
a flying shit, Eddie.
What are there, 12 people?
Excuse me. You know
who gives a shit?
I do. I give a shit.
It's my job to get you on stage.
Have we ever not made
it on the stage, Eddie?
- Shell!
- Jesus.
Cue 453, go.
So, who's the guy?
Rick. He saw me leaving
the parking lot.
Oh, a stage door
Johnny situation, huh?
Paging stage door Johnny!
- Shh! Shh!
- Aisle four!
No, he recognized me
in the parking lot.
Uh-huh.
Does he think you're
a escort on the side?
Annette, no!
What? Guys think that.
Well, they do.
Well, Rick is nice. He likes me.
He doesn't think that.
Please scan your item again.
Well, it's on there.
- It's right there!
- Wait, wait.
Please scan your item again.
No, it's telling you
to scan it again.
Please scan your item again.
Put it in the bag.
- Oh, no.
- What?
Oh. Have to cancel tonight.
Workin' late.
Yeah, rain check.
Sorry.
You wanna return the fish?
No. It's okay.
Shit.
Fuckin' hell.
She's open.
Good. But then I won!
So what the fuck does it matter
if I previously lost, you know?
Oh, really, you're gonna have
an orange right before dinner?
Well, there's only enough fish
for, like, two people, Annette.
I'm tryin' to get
it where I can.
Oh, gosh, I'm sorry guys.
A little impromptu soiree.
But I got enough.
Men like to be fed.
Shelly, who is this guy anyway?
Oh, Rick the dick!
I bet you he was married.
Well, he was divorced.
Didn't have a ring.
Uh-huh. Did you
check his pockets?
- He liked me. He...
- Uh-huh.
That's why we're
eating his fish.
Look, girls, you don't
have to worry about me.
I am a very lucky person.
I mean, I am. I have luck.
It's in me. You
know what I mean?
I mean, it's in me.
Not everybody has that.
Sure.
You gonna save your winnings
for when you retire?
What? Retire?
Are you crazy? Like,
bankers retire.
I... What do you
think I have a 501k?
No, I'm not gonna retire.
I'm not gonna retire.
I'm gonna work.
And then, I'm gonna
work some more.
And then I'm gonna die.
I'll probably die in my uniform.
- That's my plan.
- You don't wanna retire?
You know... you know,
it's not an option, Jodie.
Yeah, isn't it
like a requirement?
No!
Esme Rodriguez is 83.
She is still cocktailing.
Oh, my God, she's 83?
83!
I know because I was
invited to the party.
I didn't go 'cause I
don't like soft foods.
Well, I can't wait to retire.
You're 19!
It just seems, like,
it's such a wonderful
time in life.
I don't... I don't know!
I just think it seems fun!
You know, learning new things.
Maybe taking up a new language.
No, you can't learn
a new language
that late in life.
The brain doesn't work that way.
Well, I wanna learn French.
I love languages. I can
say "Je m'appelle Jodie."
- That's good.
- I know how to say
"My name is Jodie"
in five different languages,
including English.
But that's like the most
useless phrase, though.
You could just point at
yourself and say, "Jodie."
Useless? Are you kidding?
Shelly, let's learn
French together.
No, no. Je m'appelle Shelly.
Hey, guys, you know what?
I like my life, right?
I like it. I like my job.
I mean, most people don't
like playing grab-ass
with a bunch of coked-up
gamblers at 10:00 a.m., but...
- But you are one so...
- But I don't mind it.
They amuse me.
That's right. They amuse me.
And then I can go drink
and gamble on my own time.
Annette is a bon vivant.
Oh, French.
- Who's that?
- Oh, it's Eddie!
- Wait, what?
- What?
Wait, that is gonna be so weird!
Eddie is coming here?
Jodie, what were you thinking?
Well, no, it's not...
and he's like...
he's like our dad!
He's not like our dad.
He's seen our boobs,
like, a thousand times.
Have you never heard of
an impromptu girls' night?
When was the last time
you saw Eddie, anyway?
Oh, no, no, no. I
haven't seen Eddie
since I left the show,
and I have not missed him.
Well, that's not nice.
I feel like we're all
kind of like a big family.
Okay, well, if this is a
family, it's pretty fucked up.
We're tits out all the time.
No, like, you're our mom, and...
Wait. You're tryin' to
make Shelly your mom
- and Eddie your dad?
- Ugh.
I mean, I feel like
this is a family.
- We're a family.
- Okay.
Well, you know what, girls?
I will be the girl outside
getting drunk very fast.
Okay.
- And we used to do that thing.
- Oh, God.
And just sit there like
this, not say a word.
- Oh, wow.
- Naked.
Put it everywhere.
You know what I mean?
- Look who's here!
- Welcome, Eddie.
Hey, ladies. Hey,
Annette, good to see you.
Oh, no, no, no, I'm
not gonna hug you.
- I'm sweating.
- That's okay.
No, no, no, really.
I am not gonna hug you
because I am sweating.
- Okay.
- It's gross.
But it's awful good
to see ya, Eddie.
- Yeah. Yeah, you, too.
- Yeah. Mm.
Show's not the same without you.
It isn't? Really?
I kind of feel like it is.
Oh. I mean,
technically, it is.
- Yeah.
- It is the same show.
Um, just meant figuratively.
Yeah.
Hey, um, who took
over my track again?
Was it, um... wait.
Uh, Valerie?
- Francine.
- Francine!
Francine, yeah.
She sucked.
I mean, she can't fouette.
She really... she's
a terrible dancer.
But how did she
take over my track?
She does the pas de deux
in the fairy ballet?
She can't partner.
I mean, does she even
know how to partner?
Yeah, I mean, it's
been six years
since you left the show.
She does it every night.
She figured it out.
So, Eddie brought some wine.
Yeah. Should I go open it up?
Yeah.
A little Malbec for anybody?
Annette? Mary-Anne?
I'm allergic to red.
Yeah, no.
I'm, um... I'm
drinking margaritas.
Okay.
I just... I brought
it because...
well, it's funny.
When I was on Siegfried and Roy,
those guys would have
us over on the off days
and I went pretty hard
on the red wine, so...
Wait, they went
hard on red wine?
Yeah, well, it's ages ago.
Uh, there was this one
time when I got caught
in the escape trap
with a white tiger.
- What?
- Yeah. No.
- No!
- Yeah, no, yeah.
So, you know, the tiger's
supposed to disappear off stage
- during his trick, right?
- Uh-huh.
And so I'm down, um,
opening the trap
door onto the floor.
- Yeah.
- And the tiger knows
to go through the tunnel
and into the holding pen.
And somehow,
I got caught in the holding pen
with the white tiger.
And I shit myself.
That is insane!
Did the tiger swat at you?
- No.
- Oh.
They're very well trained, huh?
Oh, very. Yeah,
it's impressive.
- Wow.
- Thank you.
I mean, that's scary, though.
Great story, Eddie.
I'm still hungry.
That was, like,
two ounces of fish.
I have some cup of
noodles above the fridge.
- Oh.
- If you want that, sweetie.
Thank you.
- Eddie, are you okay?
- No.
I think I swallowed
a teeny fish bone.
- You?
- Um, so listen.
I didn't come here
tonight just to, um...
I got somethin' I
need to tell you.
Are you okay?
Muffy told me that
the show is closing.
I'm sorry. What?
Yeah, the show's closing.
Oh! Way to bury
the lead, shithead!
Don't call me a
shithead, Annette.
Well, then, don't
fuckin' drop a bomb
in the middle of a dinner an
hour after you've arrived!
I mean, hold on. Hold on. I
mean, Muffy is senile, okay?
She's, like, a
thousand years old.
- She's about to die.
- Muffy is not senile.
Just tell me what she said.
She said the new casino owners
wanna put their own
stamp on the place.
So they brought in the circus.
That show's doing
really well, so...
I mean, who puts
money into a circus
that's not Cirque
du Soleil, right?
That's dumb.
I knew when we started
sharing our theater,
when they started taking
over our Thursday, Friday,
Saturday shows,
it was a bad sign.
No shit. And also,
no, you did not.
- Yeah, I did. Yes.
- No, you didn't.
- Ah, you guys, wait.
- No, you did not.
You guys, our show is legendary.
It is, but Le Razzle-Dazzle,
it's... it's old.
It's the last show of
its kind on the strip.
I know, that's what
makes it so special,
the fact that it's the last one.
It's a show.
It's the costumes, the sets.
Look, it is a dinosaur, Shelly.
I think we're gonna
get notice tomorrow.
Are you kidding?
You heard this from Muffy?
Yeah.
Oh! What is wrong with you?
Do you like being the
bearer of bad news?
No.
Just it was important
information.
I wanted them to
hear it from me.
Oh, really? Well, your
important information
just broke her fucking heart.
You're saying that you don't do
the straddle, bitch?
I see your warm up
every single night.
I don't look good.
Okay. Yeah, bye.
That's good as wow!
Good evening, ladies
and gentlemen.
I regret to inform you
that Le Razzle Dazzle
will have its final
performance in two weeks.
On behalf of Muffy, as
well as our long-time
producing partners
at the casino,
the decision to close the show
has been a hard one to make,
but it's been an
incredible 38-year run,
and they wish to thank everyone
for their hard work
over the years.
Did you guys know?
No! Did you know?
This is your 15-minute call,
ladies and gentlemen.
15 minutes to curtain.
I just want to say
on behalf of myself,
your hard work and dedication,
it's been something special.
I wish everybody a
great show tonight,
and a great show over
the next two weeks.
Thanks.
Hey.
You know what?
If they just poured
a little more money
into the advertising campaign...
I mean, our press shots
are from the early '80s.
Aren't you in some
of those shots?
Yeah, I am.
You had the Hindenburg solo.
I did.
How long did you do it?
Well, when I was cast
in '87 until about '99
when Renata joined the cast.
Then she took it over.
I bet you were great, huh?
Did you ever wanna get married?
I was married when
I was really young.
For a short time.
Yeah.
Well, what happened?
I was dancing.
I was already in the
show here when we met,
and he didn't like Vegas much.
He got a job in New York.
The show here was
really thriving,
and there was a lot
of press around us.
It was very exciting.
I was very young.
And so I stayed here.
What did you do?
Well, we tried to make it
work for a couple years,
but eventually he
met somebody there
and he tried to convince
me to come to New York
and dance, and I tried it.
But, you know, I went to an
open call for the Rockettes,
I went to an open call
for a Broadway musical,
I just missed the
thrill of the show here.
You'd be a perfect Rockette.
Yeah, I found all that
kicking very redundant.
Hi, you've reached Hannah.
Leave a message.
Hey, Hannie.
Oh, I tried to call you Hannah
and honey at the same time.
Oh, my goodness.
Hannie. That's funny.
Um, just checking in to
see if you wanted to,
um, you know, get a bite,
get a cup of coffee?
I don't know. I don't
really drink coffee,
but, um, what I really
like is a nice drink.
But, yeah, that'd
be inappropriate
'cause you're, what, 20?
Oh, my God, you're 22. How
do I delete this thing?
Oh, my God! Oh! Oh!
To listen to this
message, press one.
To delete your
message, press two.
Just shut up!
I'm trying to leave
an important message.
Oh!
Okay.
To hear your options again,
- press three.
- Yes. Yes, okay. Mm-hmm.
Okay. Okay.
Oh!
Message sent.
No! Oh, God!
C'est la vie.
I went to a dance call today.
You did? Already?
Yeah, what'd you go out for?
Mm, it was a show called
Hedonist Paradise.
I can't believe that's
the title of a show.
What, like Le Razzle
Dazzle's any better?
Le Razzle Dazzle is a
name that's evocative
of another time in
history, of Paris,
of the theater in a way.
You get all that from
Le Razzle Dazzle?
Well, what do you get
from Hedonist Paradise?
I get girls grinding on poles,
doused with water like animals.
Like, it's totally tasteless.
- Tasteless?
- Yes!
You... I... you know,
I can't have this
conversation again.
Well, what do you want
from me, Mary-Anne?
If you think this is so
terrible, why are you here?
I mean, what makes you
wanna do this job...
Because it's a job, okay?
And it pays American dollars.
I don't know.
You wanna see the combination?
Sure.
Okay.
Oh, so there's a chair involved.
Uh, yeah.
So, well, you're, um,
like, backwards on a chair.
And then... and
then you're like...
♪ Mm, mm, mm, mm,
mm, mm, mm, mm ♪
♪ Slap the thighs, up the
body, through the hair ♪
Hold.
And one, two, three, four.
And ass, ass, uh, uh.
Cut it. This is ridiculous.
One and a two, hold.
- And body roll.
- Okay, yeah.
- And body roll. And hold.
- I'm not mad at it.
And one, two, three, four.
And uh, and uh.
And then you go around.
Uh, on the chair.
- Oh!
- And one...
And hump the chair. And
pulse, pulse, pulse.
And down.
And then you go around.
- And then you go up here.
- Oh, God.
Okay, stop. Stop, please.
I can't. I can't anymore.
I would never audition
for a show like that.
Never.
Okay.
- Yeah, okay.
- I'm sorry, it's just...
- Okay.
- I can't. I can't.
I mean, how am I
supposed to react?
I don't even know what
I'm gonna do for Christmas
if I don't have this.
Hey, Shell.
Hey.
- Here you go.
- Oh, thanks.
All right.
You know, since we lost
those shows, these checks
feel like they're getting
slimmer and slimmer.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Hey, Eddie.
I mean, are you
sure this is right?
This is a lot less than I
thought it was gonna be.
Well, it's less
because less shows.
Oh, well, I know
that, obviously.
I was just thinking, you know,
800 divided by 11 shows minus
the three shows we lost.
Well, you might have been
makin' slightly more
than the ones we lost
because those shows were,
better sold, generally.
Oh.
Um, if you want, I can
check with accounts payable.
Nah.
They're not gonna do
anything about it, right?
No, probably not.
You know, I just,
uh, done the math
and reworked my budget
according to what I
thought it was gonna be.
Organic milk is so
expensive these days.
Oh, they docked me for the wing.
Oh.
- The rip.
- Yeah, shit.
I mean, it must have been bad.
I mean, it wasn't
on a seem, you know?
No, I think Ida had
to reorder the fabric.
Oh, she did?
Yeah.
Just to repair one wing.
You know, the show's gonna end.
Oh no, I get it.
You're never gonna need that
fabric for anything else.
Well, I'm sorry to me, then.
- Bye.
- Ciao.
To listen to this
message, press one.
Hey, Hannie.
Oh, I tried to call you Hannah
and honey at the same time.
Oh, my goodness.
Hannie. That's funny.
Um, just checking in to
see if you wanted to, um,
you know, get a bite,
get a cup of coffee?
I don't know, I don't
really drink coffee,
but, uh, darn it, I'd
have a cup of coffee.
Or maybe I could have some tea.
And, uh, um, you know...
You know what I really
want is a nice drink.
That'd be inappropriate
because...
Well, I could always move in
with you, and pay you rent.
No, my lease is up
in, like, ten months.
You're gonna gamble
it all. I know you.
No, I will not.
I'm gonna lose my house
like you lost yours.
Stop. Hey, Phyllis, you
want another ginger ale?
- Oh, yeah, please.
- Yeah. Jack Daniels?
- Oh, yes, honey.
- Thanks, Annette.
You know, I don't like that.
It makes you think
like I'm irresponsible.
I am not irresponsible. I'm
thinking of opening an IRA.
Oh, I think you're too
old to open an IRA.
Okay, whatever.
I just... I mean, you know me.
- I make money.
- Exactly.
You know, you could always
get together with Eddie.
What?
- Oh, my God, that's a first.
- You could.
Who are you?
Hey, Tony, I need
a Jack and Ginger.
- Hey, we're cutting the floor.
- What?
You and Esme can go home.
- Who's staying?
- Jennifer and Jessica.
Of course they are.
Well, you can tell one of
the assholes over there
to drop that to Zsa Zsa
Gabor in the nickel slots.
Who?
Zsa Zsa!
That's insane.
Look, fine, then if not me,
I just... I think you want
a guy around the house.
You keep dating
these business types,
who come to town two three days,
and you cook for them like
you wanna get married.
I don't. I don't
wanna get married.
Well, I think you forget
guys come to Vegas to get a
story they can go home with.
Like shtupping a showgirl.
- No, Annette! Yes, Annette.
- It's true. Come on.
And you know that.
But you see, you
and Eddie, I mean,
you guys have a history
and he lives here.
Yeah, we have a bad history.
All histories are bad with men.
But you have history.
And you know, he's...
I don't know, he's
a solid enough guy.
I don't particularly like him
or even find him
that attractive.
But, you know, he might
even have a pension.
Do you have a pension?
I don't have a pension.
- No.
- Exactly.
And you know, I
mean, he's cute-ish.
I can also... I can
also get you a job here.
What, cocktailing?
Yes.
Hey, Esme.
You know what? Fuck them.
Right? Screw them.
Seriously.
Hey. You want a cigarette?
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, is that you?
- Oh! Oh!
- Hey, Shelly.
You got my message.
It's so good to see you.
My goodness, what
are you doing here?
I mean, of course, you know,
I'm happy to see you,
but I mean, jeez,
you could show up at my
doorstep anytime, anywhere.
Oh, it's just so
good to see you.
God, I'm sorry. I'm such a mess.
I mean, I just haven't
had a lot of sleep lately.
Hormones.
Why aren't you in school?
Um, I had to come home
for Lisa's birthday, so...
Oh, it's Lisa's birthday.
I mean, I gotta send her a
card or a call or something.
You don't have to do that.
I want to. I will.
I mean, how is she?
She's, um, how are she and Jeff?
They're really good. Uh,
I'm graduating in May, so...
Oh, I know. I know, hon. Gosh,
you're graduating so soon.
I just can't believe it.
And Becky's graduating, too,
so we're gonna do, like,
a joint party kinda thing.
Oh, really? Becky
is graduating, too?
Yeah, good for her.
Good for Becky.
Yeah.
It's a lot of family time,
so I wanted to get out
of the house anyways.
Sorry.
Oh, you look so beautiful.
- No, I don't.
- Yes, you do.
You're so beautiful,
so grown up.
I just can't believe
I haven't seen you
in what, like, over a year?
Yeah.
So, um, do you have a boyfriend?
Just tryin' to focus on
getting out of school.
Oh, well, plenty of time for
boyfriends, you know, later.
Mm-hmm.
Have you, uh, declared a major?
I'm studying photography.
Oh, my God, that's so exciting!
Thanks.
Uh, Lisa said it
wouldn't be that useful
to have any sort of arts degree,
but it's the only thing
I'm really passionate
about, so...
Well, I think it's brilliant
that you're doing that.
I mean, being part of a creative
community is... It's the best.
It's the best.
It's pretty solitary. It's
not really a community.
Well, you know, being
an artist is solitary,
but if you're passionate
about it, it's worth it.
You know what?
I really should get going.
Oh, no, no.
I was just gonna say if you
wanted to stay for dinner.
Yeah, I just stopping
by to say hello.
I have to get... I have
to get home for dinner.
Well, I mean, can't you
just give him a call
and say that you're gonna
have dinner here tonight?
It's just one night.
I don't know. Becky
just got home, and I...
I mean, Lisa wouldn't
mind, would she?
Just one dinner.
One night.
I really can't, Shelly.
You know, I was... I was
thinking that, you know,
since the show is closing,
that I could probably get
a couple days off and
come visit you in Tucson.
- What?
- Yeah.
The show is closing.
I can't talk about it too much.
I'll just dissolve into tears.
But, you know, I could
finally have some time off
and come visit you in Tucson.
I could come to your
graduation if you want.
Um, I'll think about it.
Okay.
Come give your mom a hug.
Mm.
Oh, geez.
You know, if you ever
wanna see the show,
there's only a couple left.
What?
Ugh.
Uh, I... I didn't mean it.
Just, you know, just
so nice to see you.
I... trying to find a
way to see you soon.
Um.
Yeah. Little misstep.
It's okay.
Okay.
- See you, Shelly.
- See you.
I have, like, a big girls night,
it was too much fun.
I was, like, hurting.
You know what,
like, if I get home,
- like, starving.
- Yeah.
- Then I have no dinner.
But normally if I'm starvin',
I could just get food court.
'Cause it's like you
need energy before,
but also... it's...
You'd think they could
get our set in place
before our damn call times,
so we can warm up.
Our entire crew is out there.
I saw it.
- You did?
- Mm-hmm.
It was pretty awesome.
The Dirty Circus was awesome?
Yeah, it was really funny.
Mm-hmm.
And the acts were really
hard and impressive.
Sounds like every other circus.
I've never seen a
circus like that.
And that made it awesome?
Yeah, kind of.
Got turned down for three shows.
- What?
- Which ones?
Boy, I look too old
for Jungle Island,
Paradise Hedonist,
Paradise Island,
whatever the fuck.
"Look too old."
Like, they were
absolutely looking
for girls who were barely 18.
Like, they were like,
"Did you turn 18 yesterday?"
What were the others?
Oh, I'm not stacked enough
for Oz Land or Pin up Girls.
No, honey, you don't
even want those shows.
They're so bad.
They're so low class.
Low class?
What is this?
The show is famous!
It's a tradition
that had its roots in France!
Oh, my God!
Fucking France show!
I mean, it's the last
remaining descendant
of Parisian Lido culture.
Shelly, nobody knows
what the fuck that means.
Well, just like
the shows in Paris.
I mean, you think
85 is a big cast?
There was 160 of us
back in the '80s.
American Express did
a travel campaign,
and they flew us
all over the world,
and photographed us
in different sites.
They shot me on the
Great Wall of China.
I was very special.
I'm sure, Shell.
Super special.
Well, I mean, Las Vegas used
to treat us like movie stars.
The iconic American showgirl.
The Las Vegas showgirl.
We were ambassadors.
For style and grace.
You know, it's just...
it's the costumes.
I mean, it makes you feel
like you're stepping out
of the pages of Vogue magazine.
I think that's why women
like to come to the show.
The glamor is undeniable.
The glamor. I think I
can deny the glamor.
I mean, maybe
times have changed.
Yes.
Shell, they've changed.
And times are brand
spanking different.
Ladies and gentlemen, this
is your half-hour call.
30 minutes to curtain.
Mm-hmm, casting call.
Oh, my God, Hannah!
What a nice surprise!
Come on in!
What are you doing here?
I just thought we
could have that dinner.
So, what's the plan
after graduation?
I don't know. I think I
might save some more money
and then, I kinda just
wanna travel around.
Like, I really wanna
go to Europe, but...
Oh, that sounds amazing.
You've got to do that.
- It's just expensive.
- Yeah.
Hey, you know, being a
photographer is just...
- it's just hard.
- What?
- It's a hard career path.
- Says who?
Like, everybody.
Really someone said
being an artist is hard?
Someone put that dumb
sentence in your head?
Yeah. Lisa, for one.
Oh, well.
That's what parents say when
they want you to get a job
that, like, pays money.
Honey, well, she's not
your actual parent.
I mean, she might think she is.
But doing a job that
you don't really love,
that's hard.
You know, when your
calling is out there,
just waiting for you.
You know, money doesn't make
a boring job that much better.
What does Lisa want you to do?
Uh, she thinks I'd be great
at, like, graphic design.
Well, does that
interest you right now?
No.
Well, forget about it.
Hard.
That's the dumbest phrase anyone
told anybody with a dream.
I'll meet you in Paris.
- Oh, my God! What was that?
- What?
I saw something scurry
across the room.
- What, like, a mouse?
- Yes!
- No.
- Oh, my God, yes, yes.
They live in the hidey-holes.
That's where the gangsters used
to keep their money
before I moved here.
I wish I knew where it was.
Oh, my God!
- There it is again! There it is.
- Wait, what are you doing?
Let's go for 68.
Go on cue 68.
Quiet and blackout.
Resepct the process people.
Stay focused.
Shelly?
Standby for 771.
Can we get dancers
in their places?
Before, I don't know,
before hell freezes over.
Thank you.
Thanks, everyone. Great show.
See you tomorrow.
Oh!
- Hi.
- Oh, my gosh!
Oh, hey.
Hi!
I saw the show tonight.
Oh, you did?
Well, that was sweet of you.
I, um, it means a lot
to me that you came.
I wasn't sure if I was
even gonna tell you.
There was barely anyone there.
Yeah, well...
I think that was the worst house
we've ever had in the history
of the whole entire show.
What was there, like,
18 people there?
I wish I'd known you were here.
I would have done
a little shout out
or kind of point or something.
I thought you were just
heading back to the Kelly's.
What'd you think?
I think I thought it
would be different.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, like harder
dancing or something.
Oh, you know, we just
make it look easy.
It's kind of just a
stupid nudie show.
Well, it's a spectacle
with dancing nudes,
but it's certainly
not a nudie show.
Dancing nudes, is that,
like, a technical term?
Yeah, yes, it is.
What's the point of that show?
I mean, what was that?
Why did you invite me?
Maybe you thought
I wouldn't come?
I don't know.
I don't know why I did come.
Although, uh, I guess, it's
because I just hoped...
I wanted to know
that it was worth it.
That it was better
than me after all.
What?
That you didn't put this
lame trash above me.
It's not!
I disagree.
Plus, I didn't put
anything above you.
- I provided for you.
- I keep forgetting
that you're not actually
a reasonable person.
That you left me in
the casino parking lot
with a Game Boy while you
did two shows a night.
I didn't think it was
appropriate for you backstage.
Well, yeah, it wasn't.
I couldn't afford help, Hannah.
I just did the best I can.
I just did the
best I can, Hannah.
And if you can do what
you love for 30 years,
you know, and be passionate
about your career...
What kind of career is this?
You're in the goddamn back
of 80 topless dancers.
This was worth missing bedtime
for most of my childhood?
Was it?
See, this is why I came tonight.
I wanted to see a
reason in all this,
and tonight I finally didn't.
Shelly.
Look, I'm sorry, Hannah.
I'm sorry you didn't get
what you wanted from me.
You know, but if you
could forgive me,
anytime, anytime in your life,
I would love that.
But I can't defend
myself anymore.
I just can't.
Hey, I'm still here.
Sorry, I thought
I saw Shelly go.
- Yeah, I'm going. I'm sorry.
- That's okay.
Are you... are you...
you're Hannah?
Yeah, I know I probably
shouldn't be back here.
Did you come to see the show?
Um, yeah.
Yeah, what'd you think?
Uh, not really my thing.
She talks about
you all the time.
Yeah, uh, I think
I should get going.
Yeah, no, sorry. I didn't mean
to keep you, it's just, uh...
It's good seeing you.
You, too.
Oh, hey, sweetie.
Uh, what are you doing here?
I just, um, wanted to come over.
Okay.
Can I come in?
You know, it's just,
um, is everything okay?
I mean, it's just not
a good time right now.
Um, it's just, my
mom, she won't...
she won't answer
my... my... my calls.
And... I wanna talk to her.
I understand it's hard.
Give her time.
Your mom's just sad.
I mean, that you left like that.
I know, but I still
wanna talk to her.
Look, it's a bad time right now.
I just... I just
can't do it right now.
- I can't.
- Shelly, I'm really scared.
I didn't... I didn't know
that I could never go back.
I didn't know that I
could never go back,
and I'm... and
I'm really scared.
I'm sorry, I just...
I just can't.
Not right now. I
need to be alone.
I'm doing something.
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Every now and then I
get a little bit lonely ♪
♪ And you're never
comin' around ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Every now and then I
get a little bit tired ♪
♪ Of listening to the
sound of my tears ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Every now and then I
get a little bit nervous ♪
♪ That the best of all
the years have gone by ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Every now and then I get
a little bit terrified ♪
♪ And then I see the
look in your eyes ♪
♪ Turn around, bright eyes ♪
♪ Every now and
then I fall apart ♪
♪ Turn around, bright eyes ♪
♪ Every now and
then I fall apart ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Every now and then I get
a little bit restless ♪
♪ And I dream of
something wild ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Every now and then I get
a little bit helpless ♪
♪ And I'm lying like
a child in your arms ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Every now and then I
get a little bit angry ♪
♪ And I know I've got
to get out and cry ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Every now and then I get
a little bit terrified ♪
♪ But then I see the
look in your eyes ♪
♪ Turn around, bright eyes ♪
♪ Every now and
then I fall apart ♪
♪ Turn around, bright eyes ♪
♪ Every now and
then I fall apart ♪
♪ And I need you now tonight ♪
♪ And I need you
more than ever ♪
♪ And if you only
hold me tight ♪
♪ We'll be holding on forever ♪
♪ And we'll only be
makin' it right ♪
♪ 'Cause we'll never be wrong ♪
♪ Together we can take it
to the end of the line ♪
♪ Your love is like a shadow
on me all of the time ♪
♪ All of the time ♪
♪ I don't know what to do ♪
♪ And I'm always in the dark ♪
♪ We're living in a powder
keg and givin' off sparks ♪
♪ I really need you tonight ♪
♪ Forever's gonna
start tonight ♪
♪ Once upon a time, I
was falling in love ♪
♪ But now I'm only
falling apart ♪
♪ There's nothing I can do, a
total eclipse of the heart ♪
I just wanted to call you.
I want to talk to you.
I can't believe I left the
way I did the other night.
I just feel so terrible.
I just...
I don't know how I could
do anything I'd done.
I don't know how I missed
out on our life together.
I just... I don't wanna
leave it on a phone message.
So could you please, please?
Please, please, please,
please call me back.
Is this the worst audience ever?
I mean, I just wanna yell
at them and say, "Wake up!
This is a live performance.
What, are you bored?
This is breast, and
rhinestones, and joy!"
Oh, God.
Can you help me with
my shoes, please?
How'd you do this
before I was here?
For 30 years, how'd you
make all your quick changes?
Oh, I'm glad you feel
so necessary, Jodie.
I mean, that's
important. That's good.
Do you hear where we're at?
Can you help me
with my necklace?
No.
No, I wanna see you
get ready by yourself.
I wanna see what would happen
to you if I didn't help.
Really?
Okay, now you're
stressing me out.
Good.
You're always behind, too.
Oh, that is bullshit.
Well, good luck.
Well, you know what?
We have plenty of time,
so I'm actually not
even worried about this.
Well, I'm slightly concerned.
I mean, with the wings, it's
gonna be a little tight.
Okay, well, then just
keep goin'. Stop talking.
Oh, my God. Stop yelling at me.
I'm gonna get anxious!
I'm not even yelling.
Okay, where are my clip-ons?
I don't know.
- Did you take them?
- No.
Ugh. Would you please help me
- with my damn wings?
- Nope.
You should have thought of
this pointless challenge
before the show, so
I was ready for it.
Well, here's your
warning for tomorrow.
- Okay.
- This is good.
This is character building!
Just what I need is, a lesson
in character from a 19-year-old.
I got it, got it. I got it.
Yeah, I got it.
Good! I'm glad you can get
into your costumes alone.
Shelly, come on.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, no!
The music is changing.
Jodie, we have to go.
You're a real asshole,
you know that?
Hey.
May I have Ida take
a look at that?
Oh, no.
They'll probably
dock me again, right?
Yeah, probably.
Do you know how much
longer you're gonna be?
Oh. I don't know.
Not long.
Well, it doesn't
have to be perfect.
There's only a few shows left.
You know, I was thinkin'...
I mean, you, more than anyone,
the end of show might
be kind of upsetting.
Yeah.
Do you know what's next?
Nope.
You?
Probably gonna stay here.
You know, work with the circus.
Oh, yeah, that's
right. Full schedule.
Yeah.
I mean, it's a much easier gig
for the money than the R.D.
So, that's nice.
Oh, that's lucky. I mean,
you'll still be contributing
to your pension and
getting health insurance.
Yeah.
Um, okay.
I just wanted to check on you.
You know...
if it means anything,
you're a real legend,
Shell, you know?
Okay.
Hey, Eddie.
Yeah?
Wanna have dinner with
me one night this week?
You wanna have dinner with me?
Yeah.
I mean, well, um, I
mean, yeah, of course.
That'd be nice.
Great.
- Okay, great.
- Yeah.
- Hi, Eddie.
- Hey.
- I'm here.
Hey.
- It's okay.
- Hey, I'm sorry I'm late.
No, you're not.
Just, you know,
debating dresses.
I mean, I probably
shouldn't tell you that.
Oh, funny story.
I didn't have time
to get my nails done,
so I went to the drugstore,
and right next to
my nail files...
- your favorite.
- Oh, thank you.
That's so... thank you,
that's so thoughtful.
Yeah.
I don't, uh,
I don't have anything for you.
It's okay.
You look nice.
Thank you.
Do I look nice?
Yeah. Sorry.
Yeah, you look... you
look really beautiful.
Oh, thank you.
But, well, you always
look beautiful.
Aw, thanks, Eddie.
Yeah. It's rare that I actually
get to see you in
a dress, not, uh,
one of those rhinestone
bustier things, you know?
I mean, with your
breasts hangin' out.
Well, I wouldn't say hanging.
No, no, no.
But you do, though. You
look really beautiful.
Even all covered up.
- Maybe we should order.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, let's order.
So, how's Hannah?
Hmm.
She's just about to
finish up school.
Wow. Wow.
You know, I wondered
for such a long time,
you know, where she was,
and what she was up to.
If she, uh, looked
at all like me.
Oh, well. She doesn't.
No. I know.
- Thank God.
- Hmm. Mm.
- What?
What'd you say?
Well, I... I mean, I met her.
- What?
- Yeah, I met her
in your dressing
room the other night.
What? You introduced
yourself? You met her?
Well, I didn't say...
I didn't say who I was.
I just, you know, she
asked me what my name was.
I said Eddie.
- Thank God.
- Yeah.
So, is she still
living with the Kellys?
Well, I mean,
they're in college.
Yeah.
I always thought
that was gonna be a,
like, a temporary solution.
Well, you're not
really in her life,
so I don't understand why
it's any of your business.
No. I'm just curious.
Hmm. Well...
She's best friends
with Becky and Theo,
and Lisa had all the
time in the world
to devote to her
kids, so, you know?
Could you have gotten a sitter?
I made it work, and
that's what matters.
Well, I was just...
I was just thinking
maybe, you know,
you could have gotten
a job where you worked
the hours she was at school.
I mean, you didn't have
to stay with the show.
- Of course I did!
- Mm-hmm.
Worked at a supermarket, or
waited tables, or retail.
There's lots of
retail jobs, you know?
I just can't win.
I mean, God, this is what
women have to deal with.
You know, all the time, people
are told... they're told,
"You have to do this,
you have to do that",
and they'll do the thing
that you didn't want to do,
take the road that
you should have taken.
It's so fucking confusing.
And, Jesus, and,
you know, how...
Yeah.
How are you saying any
of this when, really,
you were never there?
Where were you?
We weren't even
in a relationship.
Well, what do you want now?
You wanna be her father
now, all of a sudden?
No.
That's not what I meant.
What do you want with me, Eddie?
I just wanna be your friend.
Oh, God! Oh, my God,
- this is so embarrassing.
- What?
Why did I even come?
- Oh, my God, this is a bad idea.
- Shelly. What?
This is the worst fuckin' idea.
Christ! And, like you're in
any position to judge me.
Like that's what a friend does?
I didn't mean to
sound like that.
I love the show.
I love it.
I feel so good about
myself in this show.
And you, and Mary-Anne, and
Hannah can't understand.
But the costumes, the sets,
being bathed in that
light night after night.
Feeling seen. Feeling beautiful.
That is powerful.
And I can't imagine
my life without it.
I just think it's
wild that, you know,
I'm the one who's been on
the stage all these years.
That I'm the one
people come for.
That I'm the one on the poster!
And you, you, Eddie, are
gonna go on to this show
or that show and the producers
will just place you elsewhere
because you know how
to read a lighting cue.
You just tell someone
to push a damn button!
And you're gonna be just fine.
And I just have to disappear.
Well, you know what?
I have no regrets.
None.
Eat your meat.
There you go.
You know, when my
grandparents...
Pearl and Bob, retired...
from the stationery business...
they drove around the Southwest
doing square dancing
competitions.
That's cute.
We should do that. You and me.
I thought you
weren't gonna retire.
We could pick up
flouncy skirts and...
Shell, I fucked up a little.
I lost my shirt.
So what are you gonna do?
Well, I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
I...
I don't...
I can't even...
I mean, I would... can I...
I can't even... I
can't fucking even ask.
I can't ask you.
I can't even do it.
You have to stay here?
Yeah, just... I, um...
I've been taking night shifts
and showering in
the locker room,
and I've been sleeping in my
car for the last couple weeks.
What? You didn't tell me!
I promise you...
I promise you I'll be out
of your hair really fast.
It's okay.
Fuck.
If you're a Capricorn
or an Aquarius,
please follow me.
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Carpe diem, and the
clock keeps singin' ♪
♪ No, you can't go back,
so I live by minutes ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Carpe diem, fuckin'
up, busy givin' ♪
♪ Ain't life is safe, ain't
life worth livin', no ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
What's your name?
- Shelly Gardner.
- Just need the first.
Oh, sorry.
How tall are you?
5'7".
Age?
Oh, a gentleman never
asks a lady her age.
36.
Sorry, I lied.
I'm 42.
But this house is huge.
I mean, distance helps.
- Ah.
- Oh, gosh, I'm sorry.
I'm so nervous.
I've been on the Razzle
Dazzle for so very long
and...
I just haven't
auditioned in a while.
- But it's exciting.
- Yeah.
You have an act prepared?
I do. I'm a dancer.
Music?
Yeah.
I gave it to the maestro.
Okay.
♪ We're running with the
shadows of the night ♪
♪ So, baby, take my hand,
you'll be all right ♪
♪ Surrender all your
dreams to me tonight ♪
♪ They'll come true in the end ♪
♪ You said, oh, girl,
it's a cold world ♪
♪ When you keep it
all to yourself ♪
♪ I said you can't
hide on the inside ♪
♪ All the pain
you've ever felt ♪
♪ Ransom my heart, but,
baby, don't look back ♪
♪ 'Cause we got nobody else ♪
♪ We're running with the
shadows of the night ♪
♪ So, baby, take my hand,
you'll be all right ♪
♪ Surrender all your
dreams to me tonight... ♪
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
That's it?
Yeah, uh, we get the idea.
Thank you, Sherry.
Shelly.
Thank you, Shelly.
You didn't like it?
Not what we're looking for.
What are you lookin' for?
Just a different kind of vibe.
Okay, well, like what?
I actually have a very
versatile background.
Uh, you've been with
the Razzle Dazzle
for many years, huh?
Yeah. I mean, before that.
Just tell me what
you're interested in
and I'll give it to you.
I mean, you're
lookin' for dancers.
I'm a dancer. I'm an
experienced dancer!
We're looking for dance acts
that are either acrobatic or...
sexy.
Oh, well, I can do that.
Um, how about a...
Salome Dance of the Seven
Veils kind of thing?
Is that something
you'd be interested in?
It's gonna be a no for today.
I mean, you can just write
somebody off like that?
This is how it works?
This is how auditioning works!
Thank you. Bye, Sherry. Next!
I worked really hard.
Please?
Please, I worked
really, really hard.
You know what?
I can tell you worked
really hard, and I'm sorry.
It's just... if you were
a really good dancer,
it would be different.
But your technique isn't great.
Okay? You were obviously
hired at the Razzle Dazzle
because you were beautiful
and young a long time ago.
I mean, this isn't
news to you, is it?
Maybe if you'd had some training
or you'd been with a
company in New York,
you might have an argument here.
But, I mean, let's be honest.
You were hired
because you were sexy
and you were young.
I don't know how to
help you if that's...
if you don't understand
that's not what you're
selling anymore, baby.
Next.
So is this what sexy girls do?
Is this sexy enough for ya?
Next, please!
Is this what young
and sexy girls
- do so easily?
- Goodbye.
Oh, is that sexy? Yeah?
Oh, my.
Shell, come on, let's go.
Get her out of here.
- Shell?
- Who's she?
Shell, come on, let's go.
- Shell, come on, let's...
- Let go of me!
I'm beautiful.
I'm 57.
And I'm beautiful,
you son of a bitch!
Thank you.
- Next.
- Shell.
Go do your audition.
You're missing your audition!
I don't care about it!
You know, you
should have told me
a hundred years ago to
quit this stupid bullshit!
- What?
- God!
You saw it happening.
You saw me losing Hannah!
You didn't even say
anything! You were there!
- What? Look...
- Yes!
We didn't know
what was going on!
Shell, I... look, we didn't
know what was going on with you.
Yes, you did.
You and Jodie want
me to be your mother,
but I already have a daughter.
- I have one!
- No, Shell, look, we love you.
- We...
- I don't love you!
I don't care!
I don't care! Look,
what do I have to show
for the last 30
years of my life!
I don't even get to keep
a piece of my costume!
Shell, where are you going?
I don't know. And I
don't have to tell you!
No, I know. The only
reason... I can drive you...
Shell, you shouldn't be driving!
I'm not going home!
Fuckin'... fuck you!
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck.
Fuckin'!
I know this is probably weird
leaving on a voicemail,
but I just thought
maybe we could just remember
this one thing I read somewhere.
You know, our mothers are
not saints or saviors,
just regular people
doin' the best they can
with the tools they have.
I know that's not
a great excuse,
but I just want you to know
that I love you,
however imperfect
that might sound.
That's just...
I just wanted you to know that.
And that life is full
of contradictions.
And, you know, this
probably sounds crazy,
I've always only wanted
the best for you.
I've always been with you
and I just wanted
you to be safe.
Safe and happy,
and fulfilled, and
follow your dreams.
Just be you.
I love you.
Places, please.
This is your places
call for the last time.
To the very last showgirls.
To the very last showgirls!
Places, please.
This is your places
call for the last time.
This is your places call
for the final performance
of The Razzle Dazzle.
Mom!
Hannah?
What are you doing here?
- Hey.
- You're lucky.
You're probably never gonna
leave this theater, huh?
Yeah, you're right.
Probably not.
Your ghost is probably
gonna haunt this theater.
Yeah, I never
thought about that.
I can't believe this is
gonna be the last time
I set foot on that stage.
I know.
You know,
I think I'm gonna go
to Hannah's graduation.
Yeah.
- I might even move there.
- Really? Wow.
Yeah.
Or I could stay here
and maybe get a job
with Annette, cocktailing.
Cute outfits.
Well, not like this one.
Yeah.
Well, one last chance
to give 'em hell.
Ha.
Shelly.
You look great, Shell.
♪ Just like a rose ♪
♪ Red in its glow ♪
♪ Watch her as she sways ♪
♪ Just like a rose ♪
♪ She'll cut you a thought ♪
♪ She's beautiful that way ♪
♪ Hold your cards close ♪
♪ Know when to fold ♪
♪ Keep that poker face ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ And get back at bay ♪
♪ When she knocks you down ♪
♪ She's beautiful that way ♪
♪ I know it hurts ♪
♪ For what it's worth ♪
♪ But you have to know ♪
♪ Summer would go ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Spin, baby, spin ♪
♪ The night always falls ♪
♪ At least you had your day ♪
♪ Now the light shines
on some other pearl ♪
♪ Who's beautiful that way ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ She's beautiful ♪
♪ That way ♪