(SLOW SUSPENSEFUL
MUSIC PLAYING)
(PROJECTOR WHIRRING)
MAN: That's my little girl!
You're gonna be the star
of the church one day.
Do you think so?
MAN: If that's what you want.
I wanna be just like you, Daddy.
MAN: Then you'll
have to work hard.
I will. I'll do
whatever it takes.
MAN: Good. What
do we always say?
- I will not accept a life...
- MAN: Take your time.
Preach it like you mean
it or it won't come true.
(SIGHS)
I will not accept a
life I do not deserve.
MAN: That's right, Maxine.
Very good.
(METAL CREAKING)
(CREAKING STOPS)
Good morning.
So, Maxine.
Your agent tells us you're
quite a popular name
in adult film and entertainment.
- Is that correct?
- Yes, ma'am.
I'm curious.
Did you always want to
be in that line of work?
I always wanted to be famous.
So if you don't mind me asking,
why come here and do this?
Well, I've always had a
larger vision for myself.
Realistically, porn can
only take me so far.
I'm gonna be 33
years old pretty soon
and in hardcore,
women age like bread, not wine.
I'm not where I want to be yet.
I want the good life.
I figure acting is acting.
I can do just as good of a job
as any of those other
blondes out there.
Is that your real accent?
Yes, ma'am.
Let's give it a
try then, shall we?
Maxine Minx, Puritan II, mark.
If you need to read off
the sides we gave you
- just go ahead, all right?
- I know the lines.
"Veronica walks
in to her perfect
"1950s suburban home.
"Something isn't
right. It never was.
"She turns to the camera,
and through her trauma
"addresses the lens directly."
It may sound hard to
believe, but it's true.
I've seen the devil
stalking me like a
specter from the past,
haunting my dreams, (SNIFFLES)
my nightmares.
(SNIFFLES) I can feel
his power inside of me
transforming into
something vengeful,
something evil,
forcing me to do terrible,
awful, murderous things.
Whatever horror happened
here 300 years ago,
it's not over.
Satan has come back
to make me pay for
my greatest sin.
The sin of living.
WOMAN: Nicely done.
(EXHALES) Thank
you. (SNIFFLES)
(MAXINE SNIFFLING)
(MAXINE BREATHES DEEPLY)
Do you mind taking your top off
so we can see your breasts?
- Yeah, sure. (SNIFFLES)
- (ZIPPER UNZIPS)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Y'all might as well go home
because I just
fucking nailed that.
♪ I got to have a shot ♪
♪ For what you got
is Oh, so sweet ♪
♪ You got to make it hot ♪
♪ Like a boomerang
I need a repeat ♪
- ♪ Gimme all your lovin' ♪
- (ENGINE STARTS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
♪ Gimme all your lovin' ♪
♪ Don't let up Until
we're through ♪
(TIRES SCREECHING)
♪ You got to whip it up ♪
♪ And hit me Like
a ton of lead ♪
RONALD REAGAN: Don't
let anyone tell you
that America's best
days are behind her.
The gunman surrendered
just a short...
Drug bust here netted more than
$200 million worth of cocaine.
MAN 2: It sounds
like the scene
from an old-time horror movie
but with a modern twist.
MAN 3: At first, Los
Angeles Police thought
that the murder of a young woman
was an isolated act of
violence, but since then
they've come to believe
it was connected
to a wide-ranging
series of assaults
by a killer who's become known
- as The Night Stalker.
- The Night Stalker.
- Night Stalker.
MAN 4: is still being
sought by authorities.
WOMAN: The fact of the matter
is Hollywood sells sin.
MAN 5: Certain kinds
of creative expressions
have the potential
to serve as a medium
for evil spirits
to work through.
MAN 6: Authorities in
the film and music scene
are frightened by this and
other recent court cases.
I bought the Purple Rain
album for our 11-year-old.
I didn't know that
"Darling Nikki" was on it
and I felt that it
was inappropriate.
DEE: My name is Dee Snider. I
have been asked to come here
to present my views on, quote...
"The subject of the content
of certain sound recordings
"and suggestions that
recording packages be labeled
"to provide a warning to
prospective purchasers
"of sexually explicit
"or other potentially
offensive content."
♪ You got to move it up ♪
♪ And use it Like
a schoolboy would ♪
♪ You got to pack it up ♪
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
♪ Baby, work it like
A new boy should ♪
♪ Gimme all your lovin' ♪
♪ All your hugs
And kisses too ♪
♪ Gimme all your lovin' ♪
♪ Don't let up Until
we're through ♪
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(WOMAN MOANING)
Oh! Oh, God, yeah!
- (WOMAN CONTINUES MOANING)
- (MAN PANTING)
Hey, Maxine!
Stay focused, Amber.
We're almost done.
AMBER: (SIGHS) You said
that three positions ago.
As soon as Frankie Love
here decides he can bust,
we'll be ready for
you, all right?
- I'm trying, man.
- AMBER: Yes! Yeah!
(AMBER CONTINUES MOANING)
REPORTER: (ON TV)
Arcadia Police
responded to the gruesome scene
to discover yet another
victim of The Night Stalker,
the evil and seemingly random
nature of these slayings
have many Los Angeles
residents wondering
- just who could be next.
- (MUSIC FADES OUT)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
AMBER: Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
It should not be that
hard to fuck me. (SIGHS)
I was supposed to be in
Toluca Lake an hour ago.
And where does Shep
find these amateurs?
(SIGHS)
You wanna hit a party
in the hills tonight?
Gonna be loads of rich guys.
- Can't. I'm at Show World.
- (SCOFFS)
Buzzkill. All you
ever do is work.
Gotta make hay while
the sun shines.
I'm not country like you.
I'll find the best
plastic surgeon
on Rodeo Drive to
tighten my hay.
It won't be cheap.
It will be when the
surgeon's my husband.
Good luck out there.
♪ I'll satisfy your every
need And every fantasy ♪
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(SLOW SUSPENSEFUL
MUSIC PLAYING)
(SNORTS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MEN WHISTLING)
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
- (HORN HONKING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
- Yeah?
- WOMAN: I have your amazing agent
Teddy Night, Esquire for you.
- Okay.
- One moment.
- (SIRENS WAILING DISTANTLY)
- (OBJECTS CLATTERING)
- MAN: (ON PHONE) Maxi!
- Yeah?
How you doing, baby girl?
MAXINE: Uh, I'm running late.
Looking for my
outfit for tonight.
MAN: Do you want the good
news or the bad news?
MAXINE: The bad.
You didn't get the Lizzy
Borden music video.
They loved your look
but they said you
weren't a big enough name
outside of porn.
MAXINE: How am I supposed
to build a name for myself
if no one ever
gives me a chance?
I know. I know.
It's a catch-22.
It's prejudice is what it is.
I fucked on film and
now Hollywood wants me
to wear a Scarlet X for
the rest of my life.
You're preaching to the choir,
but you know what
I always say...
- "Everybody loves...
- "Everyone loves
- an underdog."
That's exactly right.
You want to hear the good news?
(SIGHS) Yeah, what is it?
- (WOMAN MOANING)
- (UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
♪ Well, I'm off my rocker ♪
♪ I fell out of my tree ♪
Name five celebrities
who got their start
in horror movies.
There's Jamie Lee
Curtis, John Travolta,
Demi Moore, Brooke
Shields, and...
Maxine-fucking-Minx.
I got it.
- No shit?
- Puritan II. I fucking got it.
Look, Puritan is
a future classic
as far as ultra-violent
satanic possession movies go.
Not exactly Terms of Endearment,
but in 30 years, we'll see
which one has more fans.
Elizabeth Bender is a
very underrated director.
My agent thinks it's gonna
make me a crossover star.
Like Marilyn Chambers.
Mmm, no. She's not a star.
Brooke Shields is a star.
Mmm, Brooke Shields
didn't do porn.
So?
She still got naked
and now she's in a
fucking Muppet movie.
True.
This is gonna be my head
soon, Leon. Just you watch.
LEON: I'll organize
the pizza and champagne
for America's new scream queen.
That's why I like you.
Oh.
You like me because
I'm the only guy
who isn't trying to fuck you.
(OBSESSION BY
ANIMOTION PLAYING)
Ass Sandwich...
(SIRENS WAILING)
Hi.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
♪ You are an obsession
You are an obsession ♪
♪ I cannot sleep ♪
♪ I am your possession
I am your possession ♪
♪ Unopened at your feet ♪
♪ There's no balance ♪
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ No equality ♪
♪ Be still I will
not accept defeat ♪
♪ I will have you
Yes, I will have you ♪
♪ I will find a way
And I will have you ♪
♪ Like a butterfly
A wild butterfly ♪
♪ I will collect you
and capture you ♪
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(COIN CLANKING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(CREAKING)
(CREAKING CONTINUES)
(TENSE MUSIC BUILDS)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey, thanks for waiting.
I don't like walking
out here alone at night
with that fricking
Night Stalker guy
on the loose.
You see about it on the news?
They're saying
it's devil worship.
I don't know.
It's all way too close for
comfort, if you ask me.
Then again, I guess
nobody would've
ever heard of Elizabeth Short
if it wasn't for the
Black Dahlia, you know?
I know a killer after-hours spot
in the hills, if
you're interested.
- No, I gotta get up early.
- (SIGHS)
I hate going to
parties by myself.
Ooh, let me get a
hot dog real quick
so nobody sees me eat.
How come you're waking up early?
I have a fitting for a film.
Oh, yeah? Guy-girl
or girl-girl?
A real movie.
No kidding?
I didn't know you could act.
Congrats.
I'm just dying for some
good news like that
- of my own, you know?
- It'll come.
- You just gotta work hard.
- Yeah.
I got a friend who's
in straight pictures.
It pays for shit
compared to fuck flicks.
Not if you're at the top.
What kind of movie is it?
Horror.
Honey.
You're not going to the
top in no horror movie.
You sure you don't
want to tag along?
The house is
absolutely fabulous.
It's right under
the Hollywood sign.
I hear you gotta take
a gondola to get there.
Real cosmopolitan shit.
(MAXINE CHUCKLES)
Okay. Your loss.
Be careful walking home.
- I can handle myself.
- Mmm-hmm.
So said every dead
girl in Hollywood.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MEN YELLING)
REPORTER: (ON TV) Authorities
still have no leads
to the identity of the
satanic serial killer
terrorizing Los Angeles.
Police are advising
all residents
to lock their windows and doors,
travel in groups
and refrain from taking
any unnecessary trips
outside at nighttime.
(STEAM HISSING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(SIGHS) Fuck.
(SIGHS)
(SIREN APPROACHING)
- You can run.
- (GATE RATTLING)
And you can hide.
But you'll never get away.
(INTENSE MUSIC BUILDS)
- Drop it!
- (SHUSHES)
Buster.
What were you gonna do, huh?
Nothing. I...
I was just playing around.
Well, we're playing now.
Strip.
What?
Strip naked.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
On your knees.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WHIMPERING)
Suck.
(GAGGING)
(SLOW TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(CONTINUES GAGGING)
(GAGS, COUGHS)
- On the ground.
- (COUGHING)
Face down, ass up.
Do you know what happened
to the last person
who tried to kill me?
I crushed her fucking head.
- (BUSTER SCREAMING IN PAIN)
- (SQUELCHING)
- (SCREAMING IN PAIN)
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS PLAYING)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(LEON SNORING)
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
(MAXINE GROANS SOFTLY)
(MAXINE GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(SIRENS WAILING DISTANTLY)
(MAXINE MOANING
IN PLEASURE ON TV)
(CONTINUES MOANING)
LEON: What's that?
MAXINE: Nothing.
(DOOR SHUTS)
LEON: You good?
MAXINE: Yeah, I'm fine.
LEON: All right.
I'm gonna head home.
MAXINE: Okay.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR SHUTS)
(SIRENS WAILING DISTANTLY)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING
ON MUSIC PLAYER)
Before we go any further,
money talks and bullshit walks.
Now you asked me
to find that girl,
which I did,
but whatever sick shit
you got planned next,
that's more than
we bargained for,
so if you still need
my help out here,
the price has gone up.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(STATIC CRACKLING)
(SLOW SUSPENSEFUL
MUSIC PLAYING)
(TABBY AND AMBER
SOBBING DISTANTLY)
CONTINUE SOBBING)
(TABBY AND AMBER BREATHING
HEAVILY, SOBBING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SOBBING)
TABBY: (MUFFLED)
No! No, no, no.
Please! Please! Please!
(TABBY SOBBING)
(MUFFLED) Oh, my God! Please!
Please, I didn't do anything.
(MUFFLED) I'll do
anything you want.
Please, just let me go!
(SOBBING)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS, WHIMPERS)
(SOBBING)
(GRUNTING)
- (STATIC CRACKLING)
- (SCREAMING)
(MUSIC STOPS PLAYING)
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
(REPORTER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ON RADIO)
WOMAN: Okay.
So I'm gonna be making
a lifecast of your head
for the end of the movie.
Ever had one done before?
Uh, no.
There's nothing
to it. (EXHALES)
All you have to do is sit
still for ten minutes.
That's a pretty bitchin'
scar. How'd you get it?
I got shot.
Dang. Who shot you?
It's a long story.
All right.
I'm gonna put this
over your head now
to make the mold.
(SQUELCHING)
Like I said, it'll take
about 10 minutes to set.
I'm gonna run. I'm
gonna get more bandages.
- Sit tight.
- (TICKING)
Remember to breathe.
I'll be right back.
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(CONTINUES BREATHING DEEPLY)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MOANING)
You'll end up just like me.
(CONTINUES BREATHING DEEPLY)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHIMPERING SOFTLY)
(WHIMPERING)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING FOR AIR)
Hey, hey!
- Are you okay?
- (BREATHING HEAVILY)
WOMAN: Breathe. Calm down.
- Breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
- (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Breathe. Come on.
- Breathe.
- (BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SLOW SUSPENSEFUL
MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT POLICE
RADIO CHATTER)
Good morning, detectives.
Here you go.
Well, we got two
bodies, both female.
A couple of homos cruising
Judy Garland's grave
found them floating
in the duck pond.
It's pretty gnarly stuff.
We were thinking it could
be The Night Stalker again.
Thinking or hoping?
Jesus.
Fresh meat.
They haven't been
here very long.
I'd say five or six
hours at the most.
Pretty girls.
- I hate to see it.
- (CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
Looks like they did that
with a fucking cattle prod.
Here.
(CORONER GRUNTS)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
He marked them both.
(SIGHS)
(SNIFFS)
Miss Minx?
(SIGHS)
I was told to give you this.
It's your copy of the
script and a prep schedule.
And Liz, the director,
wants you back on the
lot today for a meeting.
Just a word of warning, she
can be pretty frightening.
I've seen her blow a
gasket more than once.
- Okay.
- Uh, I love your work,
by the way.
(ENGINE STARTS, REVS)
(SLOW SUSPENSEFUL
MUSIC PLAYING)
(COIN CLINKING)
(LINE RINGING)
PROTESTORS: (CHANTING)
No more smut!
- No more smut!
- (HORNS HONKING)
No more smut! No more smut!
(LINE CONNECTS)
Who is this?
MAN: Unless you want
to find yourself
rotting away back in
some Texas jailhouse,
you will meet me
on the 34th floor
of the Bonaventure
Hotel in one hour...
Miss Miller.
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
(TELEPHONE BEEPING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS)
Hell of a view, don't you think?
A long way from the
Howard Johnson's,
I can tell you that.
Nowhere to hide from up here.
Oh, say, ain't you that
dirty movie actress?
Why, you look a whole
lot taller in person.
I guess I've only ever seen
you lying on your back.
John Labat.
Charmed to make
your acquaintance.
- What do you want?
- Oh.
Easy, tiger.
Don't go shooting
the messenger now.
I'm just the dick.
Private detective
hired to find you.
By who?
Well, that right there,
that's privileged information.
My employer would prefer
to reveal it his self.
He's got a... how
do I say this?
A flair for the
dramatic, so to speak.
Is everything all
right over here?
Oh, yeah. We're
just fine, darling.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Say, you want
something to drink?
I'm on an expense account.
No?
I guess we'll just take the bill
when you get a chance.
Wayne Gilroy,
Bobby-Lynne Parker,
R.J. Nichols,
Lorraine Day, and
Jackson Hollis.
Hearing those names bring
up any memories for you?
What about Howard
and Pearl Douglas?
You know they never did
catch who murdered them.
See, the past ain't
finished with you, Maxine.
It's gonna keep
knocking at your door
until you open up and let it in.
Thank you.
I'm not saying I
had anything to do
with what happened
to those people.
But even if I did,
which I didn't,
there's no way anyone
can pin it on me.
Are you absolutely
certain of that?
(CHUCKLES)
Tell me.
Does it weigh on you?
As a Christian, I mean?
That you survived, and
then your friends didn't.
Now I'm an atheist myself,
but I reckon that that
kind of guilt... (EXHALES)
that would just
crush me to pieces.
But I guess it's
not show friends.
It's show business,
now isn't it?
How much you want?
Oh, no. This
ain't about money.
Everything's about money.
For a couple of whores
like you and me, maybe so.
Not my employer,
nope. Mmm-mmm.
You can't buy your way
out of retribution.
There's a little soiree tonight
at this address.
It has been requested
that you attend.
If I don't?
Well, how does
that old saying go?
"You'll never work
in this town again."
Honestly, I don't
really care what you do.
My check's gonna
clear either way,
but I wouldn't recommend it.
My employer is a
very powerful man.
Don't play chicken with him.
I would hate to see
that lost movie of yours
wind up all over
the nightly news.
Contrary to popular belief,
there is such a
thing as bad press.
Maxine Minx?
Yeah?
I'm Detective Williams.
This is Detective Torres, LAPD.
Do you have time
for a quick chat?
Why?
Oh, we just want to
find out if you've seen
some people we're looking for.
Could we come inside?
We won't take but five minutes.
I get it. You're in show biz.
You know what? I'm just
gonna cut to the chase.
Have you, uh...
Do you know these girls?
Amber James, Tabby Martin.
We understand they're
work colleagues of yours,
for lack of a better word.
We also know that you're
one of the last people
to have seen them.
Did something happen?
Any information you have
could be really helpful.
They are your
friends, aren't they?
(KEYS JANGLING)
I don't talk to police.
Hmm. You fucked
that up, not me.
- What do you mean?
- All that bullshit bravado.
(CHUCKLES) No wonder you never
made it as an actor. (SIGHS)
I thought I was
pretty convincing.
WILLIAMS: Oh, please.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING ON TV)
(WOMAN SCREAMING ON TV)
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
(ALLIGATOR SNARLING ON TV)
Is there a way to find
out who made this tape?
- Why, what's on it?
- None of your business.
There's nothing that'll
tell you who recorded it
or where it was duped,
but the tape was
made by Quantegy.
Not a popular brand.
Usually, you see
Japanese companies
like Sony, Fuji or TDK nowadays.
I can check some old order forms
and call around
to see what region it's
still being sold in.
- Best I can think of.
- Thanks.
Yeah, no problem.
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
(WOMAN SCREAMING ON TV)
REPORTER: (ON
RADIO) The survivor
of the brutal attack last night
believes it to have
been The Night Stalker
who is responsible.
Authorities are following
all witness testimonies
in hopes of zeroing in
on the identity of this
vicious serial killer...
(SCREAMING AND
TIRES SCREECHING)
who has already claimed
the lives of eight victims
- in the Los Angeles area.
-  (CAR HONKS)
Can I help you?
MAXINE: I'm here to
see Elizabeth Bender.
I'm Maxine Minx.
Yes, you are.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(TIRES SCREECH)
Quite a pathetic
scene, isn't it?
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Angry people are
so easy to lead.
Jump in. Let's take a ride.
Fascinating that something
can look so believable
when in reality,
it's all a facade.
The producers don't want
you in this picture.
They say it's too controversial.
Do you believe that?
Cowards placating the
moral outcry of censors,
worrying their
satanic horror movie
might be too controversial
if it had a porn star in it.
I stuck my neck
out defending you.
We saw hundreds of women
for the role of Veronica.
None of them had what you had.
What you said in the
audition, it was special.
Raw. Real.
Ruthless.
Are you ruthless?
Yes, ma'am.
Well, that makes two of us.
I'm an artist.
This town is prejudiced
against artists.
Scared of its own shadow
when it comes to
upsetting the status quo.
But I say, if the
pearl-clutching
moral majority types are
gonna protest your work,
you might as well make
it bloody mean something.
Your character, Veronica, is
a powder keg ready to blow.
A killer, but not a villain.
She's Clint Eastwood meets
Charlie-fucking-Bronson
and that's what
will set this apart
from all the other
sequels out there.
I want to show that beneath
the technicolor
sheen of the 1950's,
things were just as
rotten as they are today.
A B-movie with A-ideas.
Could be the defining
role of your career,
which is why I need to know
you're willing to do
whatever it takes.
I am.
As if your life depended on it.
It does.
Very well.
We'll prove them
all wrong together
in a beautiful
fucking bloodbath.
Here we are.
Do you know what this is?
It's the motel from Psycho.
They filmed a sequel
here a few years back,
if you can believe it.
A serial killer disguised
as an old woman.
America was too prudish
to ever see it coming.
Some things never change.
It's quite the reminder.
People can protest
all they like.
If they'd look in the mirror,
they'd realize we all have
demons staring back at us.
I'd like you to visit
the set tomorrow.
I'm shooting the flashbacks.
Molly Bennett, who plays Clara
in the original, will be there.
I think it'd be nice
for you to meet her.
She can show you the
ropes, so to speak.
(CROWS CAWING)
I don't mean to
be disrespectful,
but this isn't a stag film.
It's a major motion picture.
Home video may have
been responsible
for much of The
Puritan's success,
but we're not some
video nasty anymore.
- We're theatrical now...
- (EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
and they don't show stag
films on 900 screens.
Are you listening to me?
Yeah.
I'll be there.
Do you want a bit
of free advice?
Look around you.
You've made it to the
belly of the beast.
Congratulations. Very
few come this far.
To stay here, you must
make it your obsession.
Eliminate all other distractions
because if you take
your eye off that prize
for even a moment, the
beast will spit you
right back out
where you came from.
It may never get a
taste for you again.
♪ American top 40 ♪
- ♪ Casey's coast to coast ♪
- (INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
MAN: (ON RADIO) John
Parr's title song
from the movie
St. Elmo's Fire,
a song that, this week,
is the number-one
song in the U.S.A.
♪ But maybe sometime
If you feel the pain ♪
♪ You'll find
You're all alone ♪
♪ Everything has changed ♪
♪ Play the game ♪
♪ You know you can't
quit Until it's won ♪
♪ Soldier on ♪
♪ Only you can do
what must be done ♪
JOHN: Yeah, just think
of me like the paparazzi.
Wherever you go, there I am.
♪ You're a lot like me ♪
JOHN: You can't
outrun the past
no matter how hard you try.
♪ And you're tryin'
To break free ♪
- (SHOUTING IN PAIN)
- ♪ I can see a new horizon ♪
♪ Underneath the blazin' sky ♪
MAXINE: Get in my way again,
and you're fucking dead!
You hear me?
♪ Gonna be your
man In motion ♪
♪ All I need's This
pair of wheels ♪
JOHN: You'll pay for this!
Now it's personal!
You're gonna lose
more than your job!
- (ENGINE STARTS, REVS)
- I'm gonna see to it!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
♪ Burnin' up ♪
♪ Don't know just how
far That I can go ♪
I need to see Teddy.
You haven't got an appointment.
Mr. Night is on a
very important call.
No, I can get you
the bearer bonds.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS)
I just need access
to your junkyard
for a couple of hours.
- That's it.
- We need to talk.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What
are you doing downtown?
You didn't get
shitcanned, did you?
I am so sorry, Mr. Night.
She just rushed right past me.
You're my lawyer, right?
Entertainment lawyer, yes.
So if I tell you something,
we've got confidentiality?
(DOOR SHUTS)
Frankie, I gotta call you back.
Technically, yes.
Why?
What'd you do?
(TEDDY GRUNTS SOFTLY)
How long we been
working together?
I discovered you on the street.
I put you in the
movies, didn't I?
Why didn't you
come to me sooner?
Okay, okay, okay. Relax.
Leave it with me.
You hear from that
detective again,
you tell him to call your agent.
I'm in charge of
this negotiation now.
I've brokered a lot more
than motion pictures in my time.
Trust me.
Nobody is more passionate
about your career than I am.
I'll go to jail over it,
that's how passionate I am.
This guy thinks he's
the big bad wolf?
Wrong. I'm the big
bad wolf and nobody
is gonna get in the
way of your big break.
Now, all you gotta worry about
is being undeniable
in that film.
That's most important
right now, capisce?
Stand up tall.
Be strong.
Yeah, you're Maxine Minx.
Go home. Learn your lines.
Keep your mouth shut.
You don't know nothing.
Teddy's got this.
(SNORTING)
- (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
- (SNIFFING)
(SNIFFS)
(MAN ON TV WHISTLING)
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
Can I help you?
Look, I ain't in that
kind of business no more.
This is just a video store,
and we're closing soon.
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(GLOVE SQUEAKING)
(TENSE MUSIC BUILDS)
(GASPS)
- (GASPS)
- (UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(LEON GRUNTING IN PAIN)
(GROANING IN PAIN)
(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
(LEON COUGHING)
- (KNIFE SLASHES)
- (LEON SCREAMING IN PAIN)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MUSIC BUILDS)
(MUSIC STOPS PLAYING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GLOVES SQUEAKING)
JOHN: Not a lot of
men in your position
got the stomach
to go all the way.
You certainly are willing
to do the hard yards.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
(TELEPHONE CONTINUES RINGING)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
(FOOTSTEPS
APPROACHING RAPIDLY)
Yeah?
WOMAN: Hold for Teddy Night.
- Okay.
- (LINE SWITCHES)
TEDDY: So I did some digging.
The number you
gave me for the P.I
forwards to an answering service
in Louisiana.
I checked it out for a
business name and address,
but it's unlisted.
Get this.
The Bonaventure Hotel has
no record of any guest
by the name of John Labat.
- He's no amateur.
-  (SIRENS APPROACHING)
- How you feeling?
- Better.
I'm going by the set today.
Good. Remember,
keep it by the book over there.
Don't be late. You never
get a second chance
to make a first impression,
especially in Hollywood.
- Just ask Ed McMahon.
-  (SIRENS CONTINUE WAILING)
Teddy, let me call you back.
( PRISONER OF YOUR EYES
BY JUDAS PRIEST PLAYING)
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
♪ When I saw your face ♪
♪ I became a prisoner
Of your eyes ♪
♪ And I would do
Just anything ♪
♪ To stay and be with you ♪
♪ You know there are times ♪
♪ When I let myself wonder ♪
♪ As I was going under ♪
♪ You pulled me
Back to earth ♪
♪ Don't you hear me crying? ♪
♪ Take me in your arms again ♪
♪ Tell me that you're trying ♪
♪ Or is our love a lie? ♪
WILLIAMS: I need to
show you something.
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
They were found yesterday,
dumped at Hollywood
Memorial Park Cemetery.
TORRES: You've heard of
The Night Stalker, right?
Okay, well, if you know anything
about this satanic shit,
we need to hear about it
because this killer's
still out there.
Look, we don't think
The Night Stalker
committed these
crimes, but whoever did
is setting the bodies
up to look that way,
and you're the common
denominator. Why?
TORRES: If I knew three people
who were murdered in three days,
I'd be pretty scared.
Are you scared, Maxine?
Because if I was scared,
I'd ask for help.
- You can't help me.
- Why not?
TORRES: Now what
are you hiding?
How come you act like
you don't want us
to find out who did this?
It's pissing me off.
You really want us
to take a closer look
at some of the individuals
you're doing business with?
Because actions
have consequences
and you ain't some
barefoot bitch
in a bus station now, right?
Now, I think you got
a lot to lose here,
so you better watch
your fucking step.
All right, let's
pump the brakes.
Maxine, we don't care
what kind of
partying you're into
or what kind of
tricks you're turning.
We're not vice.
We're not narcotics.
We are homicide.
And the only thing that we
care about are these bodies
and making sure we don't
find any more of them.
You Hollywood girls,
you're so desperate
to become famous,
you don't even realize
how easy it is to
become infamous.
- (WILLIAMS SIGHS)
- TORRES: It could be you
on one of these slabs, Maxine.
But it's not.
Can I go? I'm gonna
be late for work.
- TORRES: What?
- (DOOR OPENS)
You didn't like that
performance either?
WILLIAMS: Hey! Hold up!
I know you don't think
you can trust me,
but all I want to see is
this sick freak behind bars,
- hand to God.
- What am I supposed to do?
You're supposed to help me
save the next girl's life.
Please, Maxine.
Maybe she should save herself.
I did.
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
ELIZABETH: Cut!
(BELL RINGING)
The blood's wrong.
Kensington Gore.
It looks like a
bad Hammer picture.
- I need a valium.
- Sorry I'm late. I was...
Don't.
Hearing you blame something
will only irritate me more.
The most precious thing we
have in life is our time.
We never have enough,
especially on a production.
If you waste mine
again, you're out.
I'll have the second-best
girl on the Concorde tonight
frothing at the mouth
to take your place.
Is that clear enough?
Right then. Follow me.
MOLLY: Oh.
- How was it, Liz?
- Disappointing, frankly.
Even with all these
extravagant resources,
one thing remains the same.
You want something done right,
you gotta do it yourself.
(RUBBING HANDS)
Molly Bennett, meet Maxine Minx,
my latest fascination.
Oh, pleased to meet you.
Ah, sorry. (CHUCKLES)
We've all got blood
on our hands now.
Right, let's take it from
after the bite, shall we?
(BELL RINGING)
(SIGHS)
Okay, look. Here's the truth.
Liz is a genius and a mentor.
Just do whatever
she asks of you.
Don't get on her bad side,
and don't overthink the acting.
Just do what she says and
you'll get loads of jobs.
She's very loyal to
the people she trusts.
Look at me.
I was quite literally
burnt to a crisp
in the last film,
and here I am, resurrected.
A working actor.
Maybe not a household
name just yet,
but at least my health
insurance won't expire.
Plus, my charred corpse's scream
has been immortalized
in cinema history.
How many girls from
a council estate
in North Yorkshire can say that?
(INAUDIBLE)
(EXHALES)
Don't worry.
I know what you're
going through.
I was in your shoes once. I
realize how scary it can be.
You've got a memorable
face and a great bod.
You'll take to horror
like a duck to water.
Uh, I've gotta go
get cleaned up.
I was invited to a
big party in the hills
for some out-of-town producer.
See you around.
Yeah.
- Thanks.
- Of course!
Girls gotta look out for one
another in this business.
Nice to meet you, Nadine.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(HORSE GRUNTING)
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
I told you not to play
chicken, didn't I?
Now let's try and do this
without making a scene.
It's time to pay for your sins.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(PANTING)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(JOHN GRUNTING)
(PANTS, GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTH PANTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PANTING, WHEEZING)
(BIRDS CAWING)
- (MAXINE BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(FLOORBOARD CREAKING)
(CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
- SECURITY GUARD: Excuse me.
- (GASPS)
You can't be up there.
I do apologize.
(STAMMERS)
I guess my morbid curiosity
must've gotten the best of me.
A lot of famous killings
happened inside this house.
- Brutal murders and whatnot.
- (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Can I see your pass?
I don't know what I
did with it. (CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLING) I am a lost ball
in the high weeds today.
Maybe you can help
straighten me out.
Hey, how about you and me
take a walk on down to the gate
and we can make this right?
I used to work in
security myself.
- Very important job.
- (SOFT CREAKING)
SECURITY GUARD:
(CHUCKLING) Okay.
(INDISTINCT POLICE
RADIO CHATTER)
What?
Maxine.
I don't like it.
- No, the cream one.
- Okay. Yes, ma'am.
(ELIZABETH INHALES SHARPLY)
It took me a long time
to get where I am today.
Puritan II isn't just a sequel.
It's my opportunity to prove
I have a meaningful
voice in this industry
and I can't afford to have
anyone mess that up for me.
I understand. I'll
do whatever you say.
Take the weekend.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Have fun. Let loose.
Because on Monday,
the real work starts
and I'll be expecting
your absolute best.
PROTESTORS: (CHANTING)
No more smut!
No more smut! No more smut!
- Okay, man. Okay.
- SECURITY GUARD: Keep moving.
ELIZABETH: Oh, Maxine.
Whatever's going on in your life
that's interfering
with this picture,
I don't care what it takes.
Squash it.
I intend to.
(WELCOME TO THE
PLEASUREDOME PLAYING)
(DOGS BARKING)
(MAXINE SNORTING)
♪ Who-ha, who-ha ♪
♪ Ha ♪
♪ The animals are
Winding me up ♪
♪ The jungle call
The jungle call ♪
♪ Who-ha, who-ha ♪
♪ In Xanadu did Kublai Khan
A pleasure dome erect ♪
♪ Moving on keep
moving on Yeah ♪
♪ Moving at one
million miles An hour ♪
♪ Using my power I
sell it by the hour ♪
♪ I have it so I market it ♪
♪ You really can't
afford it Yeah ♪
♪ Really can't afford it ♪
♪ Shooting stars never stop ♪
♪ Even when they
reach the top ♪
♪ Shooting stars never stop ♪
♪ Even when They
reach the top ♪
♪ There goes a supernova ♪
♪ What a pushover, yeah ♪
♪ What a pushover We're
a long way from home ♪
♪ Welcome to the Pleasure
dome On our way home ♪
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
Do you know why people come to
The Big Easy to work with me?
Because I... (CHUCKLES)
am the best at what I do.
I got a reputation,
see? I can find anyone
anywhere, no matter how badly
they want to stay hidden.
I know how criminals think.
I'm one myself.
(TUBELIGHT FLICKERING)
Yeah, the only difference
between you and me, Maxine,
is I don't pretend not to be.
Oh, shit.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
MAXINE: Time to
pay for your sins.
MAN: Lights out, bro.
(GASPS)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
(GRUNTING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
You do got the devil in you.
I thought you were an atheist?
(SPITS)
Fuck you, bitch.
(WHIRRING)
Oh, no, no. Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't do this.
This ain't fair.
I only work for the man.
Killing me won't stop
nothing. Let's talk!
Come on, you're gonna
need my help, Maxine.
- This isn't over.
- Yes, it is.
Oh, no, no. This
ain't my cause.
I could be bought.
Anything you want!
Anything at all!
Oh, no, no, please!
Please, turn it off!
(CRYING) I don't
want to die in here!
Our Father who art in
Heaven, hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come.
Thy will be done
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive those
who trespass against us
and deliver us from evil.
(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
- (GLASS SHATTERING)
- (SCREAMING STOPS)
(METAL CRUNCHING)
(HORN DISTORTS, STOPS)
(DOGS BARKING)
- Get lost.
- (DOGS CONTINUE BARKING)
We'll clean up the mess.
Thanks.
What are agents for?
(DOGS BARKING)
(DOGS GROWLING)
(MUSIC FADES OUT)
(SHOWER STOPS RUNNING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(ENVELOPE RUSTLING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Tragically, another
female victim
of The Night Stalker
has been discovered
in Monterey Park.
Public demand for this killer
to be brought to justice
has a record number of LAPD
on duty around the city.
Residents living
in fear are praying
that someone out there
will come forward
to finally put a stop to
these vicious murders.
- What am I supposed to do?
- WILLIAMS: You're supposed
to help me save the
next girl's life.
(SIREN WAILING DISTANTLY)
Wanna hit a party in
the hills tonight?
Gonna be loads of rich guys.
I know a killer after-hours spot
in the hills if
you're interested.
I was invited to a
big party in the hills
with some out-of-town producer.
(SCREAMING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
We should take her.
Let's give it a beat.
Let's see what she does first.
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(MUSIC FADES OUT)
(SLOW SUSPENSEFUL
MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(VCR CLICKING, WHIRRING)
(VCR STOPS WHIRRING, CLICKS)
MAN: (ON VIDEO)
That's my little girl!
There's nobody else like you.
You're gonna be the star
of the church one day.
MAXINE: Do you think so?
MAN: If that's what you want.
MAXINE: I wanna be
just like you, Daddy.
MAN: Then you'll
have to work hard.
MAXINE: I will. I'll
do whatever it takes.
MAN: Good. What
do we always say?
MAXINE: I will not
accept a life...
MAN: Take your time.
Preach it like you mean
it or it won't come true.
I will not accept a
life I do not deserve.
MAN: That's right, Maxine.
Very good.
- (EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
- (STATIC CRACKLING)
- (VCR CLICKS)
- (STATIC STOPS CRACKLING)
I knew you'd come.
It has taken me
years to find you.
I missed you so much.
You've been lost for
far too long, darling.
Let me take you home.
(STATIC CRACKLING)
I'm making a film...
(PROTESTORS CHANTING)
- and you...
- PROTESTORS: No more smut!
- My beautiful little Maxine...
Are the star!
Well, don't you see?
Hollywood stole you from me
like so many other
poor children.
Satanists have been
propagating sex and violence
throughout our
homes for years now!
Weaponizing the television set,
brainwashing our youth,
turning them into deviants.
But we'll put a stop
to them together.
I, and many other
grieving parents like me
have come forth to expose
the devil once and for all!
Satan is inside of
you, my darling,
but I can take him out.
It'll be the climax of the film!
(SLOW DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- (MAXINE GASPING)
- (MAN GRUNTING)
- (MAXINE CONTINUES GASPING)
- (MAN CONTINUES GRUNTING)
(MUSIC FADES OUT)
WOMAN: Do you mind
taking your top off
so we can see your breasts?
(STATIC CRACKLING)
MAXINE: Y'all should
cast me in this movie.
ELIZABETH: Oh,
really? Why is that?
(SLOW DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Because I'm a star.
Ain't nobody else like me.
The whole world's
gonna know my name.
(LIGHTS POWERING ON)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MAXINE CONTINUES
BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Don't be frightened.
(MUFFLED GASPING)
I'm gonna give you
what you always wanted.
You'll be more famous
than anything Hollywood
could conjure.
Fame that will never end.
I tried to help your friends,
but they wouldn't
accept God's love.
So they were punished
by his wrath.
But not you.
You will be saved.
Are we rolling?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Tonight
I document an exorcism,
a form of miracle for
the whole world to see.
Ezekiel 16:14...
"Your fame went forth
among the nations
"on account of your beauty,
"for it was perfect
because of My splendor
"which I bestowed on you,"
declares the Lord God.
Evidence of your possession
shall finally reveal Hollywood
as the cult it is.
Luring children
into lives of sin.
The Devil is real
and he deserves no place on
the screens in our homes.
I have come to save
all lost children!
(EXHALES)
(WHISPERING) Play
along with Daddy now.
It's your big scene.
(GRUNTS)
Admit...
possession!
Confess!
Denounce your life of sin
and ask to be saved.
Only then shall you receive
divine intervention.
For if not...
you shall be marked
with the sign of the beast,
so that the devil
may never hide amongst us.
- The choice is yours.
- (MAXINE BREATHING HEAVILY)
What do you say?
(MAXINE WHIMPERING)
TORRES: Hold it, motherfucker!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Everybody to the side
of the house now!
I'm not fucking around, Padre!
(GUNSHOT)
Mass has ended!
Put your hands up!
Do not respect them!
Where were they when your
family members went missing?
They are complicit!
They are the devils!
Only the Lord keeps
watch over you
both now and forever!
Fight for Him! Fight
for your families!
To the death!
- Hey!
- (GUNSHOTS)
(GRUNTS IN PAIN)
(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
(GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
- (GRUNTS)
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
Cover me! I gotta reload!
(GRUNTING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (MAXINE SCREAMS)
(MUFFLED SHOUTING)
(GROANS IN PAIN)
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
(MAN SCREAMS IN PAIN)
(PANTING)
I'm going up the hill
after the leader!
- Wait for me!
- Come on.
(GROANS IN PAIN, SCREAMS)
Maxine, stay here!
Backup's on the way!
So am I.
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GUNSHOTS IN DISTANCE)
(DOG BARKS DISTANTLY)
(MAXINE GRUNTING, PANTING)
TORRES: Freeze! Drop the
gun! WILLIAMS: Drop it!
- (TORRES GRUNTS)
- WILLIAMS: No!
(GUNSHOT)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(PANTING)
Hang in there. Breathe.
You're okay. Just
hang in there.
You're gonna make it.
Maxine! Over here.
Come over here.
All right, stay with him.
Put pressure on the wound.
(TORRES GRUNTS IN PAIN)
WILLIAMS: I'm
going to get him.
(TORRES WHEEZING)
30 years in this city, I
never been up here before.
(CONTINUES WHEEZING)
I wanted to be an
actor once, too.
(GUNSHOTS IN DISTANCE)
(SLOW SUSPENSEFUL
MUSIC PLAYING)
(WILLIAMS WHIMPERING)
- (TENSE STING PLAYING)
- I got him!
(PANTING)
I told you I'd get him!
(SCREAMS, GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
It was all for you.
I tried to give you
what you wanted.
To be just like your daddy.
But I created a monster.
Forgive me.
Failing a child
- is the greatest sin of all.
- (HELICOPTER HOVERING)
OFFICER: (OVER LOUDSPEAKER)
This is the Los Angeles
Police Department.
We have you surrounded.
Drop the weapon.
MAN: You're a vision
in this light.
A beautiful shining star.
OFFICER: (OVER LOUDSPEAKER)
I repeat, drop your weapon.
This is your last chance.
It's over, Maxine.
Step away from the
sign, drop the weapon
and put your hands up.
REPORTER: (ON TV) We
interrupt this program
to bring you breaking news.
The horrifying saga
finally comes to an end.
The man previously known
as The Night Stalker
was apprehended by
citizens last night
bringing an end to
a year-long manhunt
for the suspected serial killer.
More on that later
in our program.
We are also joined
tonight by Maxine Minx,
star of the upcoming
film, The Puritan II
who joins us now
with her attorney
and our own Dianne Mattingly.
Maxine, you have become
quite a celebrity
outside of the movie business...
by taking down a serial
murderer of your own.
Who happened to be your father.
Isn't that right?
Why, yes, Dianne. It was
a harrowing experience.
I'm just so grateful to
be sitting here with you.
I've gotta thank God for
orchestrating this all.
CROWD: (CHANTING)
Maxine! Maxine! Maxine!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Maxine, over here!
- Maxine, you look incredible.
- Thank you.
How does it feel knowing that
after all you've been through,
you're in one of the
biggest movies in America?
It's hard to put into words.
There are reports that
you sold your life rights
and that the Maxine Minx story
will be going into
production soon
with Elizabeth Bender directing.
Is there anything you
want to tell the people
at home watching you tonight?
Any words of encouragement
for young girls
trying to make it
big in Hollywood?
Never give up.
It's hard work.
You've gotta be willing
to do whatever it takes.
(SLOW DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
There's a phrase my
daddy always used.
(HELICOPTER HOVERING)
Say it with me now.
- I will not accept...
- a life I do not deserve.
- A life I do not deserve.
You didn't fail me, Daddy.
You gave me just what I needed.
Divine intervention.
(MUSIC FADES OUT)
♪ There's no business ♪
♪ Like show business ♪
♪ Like no business ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ Everything about it ♪
♪ Is appealing ♪
♪ Everything that traffic ♪
- ♪ Will allow ♪
-  (SNIFFS)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Yeah.
They're ready for
you, Miss Minx.
Okay, thanks.
(SNIFFS)
(SNIFFING)
You're a fucking movie star.
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
Thank you.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
ELIZABETH: Right,
before we begin,
let's take a moment to
remember Molly Bennett.
She was the original member
of our Puritan family
and she'll be dearly missed.
All right, thank you everyone.
It's back to work.
Just like a Hitchcock blonde.
How does it feel
being someone else?
Good.
Quite the turn of events.
Tragic, really.
Molly was never gonna make
it beyond the franchise.
She was good, but
she wasn't a star.
Right, we've got
one more setup left
of the dream sequence.
Come see your head.
It looks so real.
MAN: All right, we're
ready to give this a try.
Brilliant.
Let's lock it up!
Roll camera!
So now that everyone
knows your name,
any idea what you
want to do next?
You've certainly got
everyone's attention.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
I just never want it to end.
(BETTE DAVIS EYES BY
KIM CARNES PLAYING)
♪ Her hair is Harlow gold ♪
♪ Her lips sweet surprise ♪
♪ Her hands are never cold ♪
♪ She's got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ She'll turn her
music On you ♪
♪ You won't have
To think twice ♪
♪ She's pure As
New York snow ♪
♪ She got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ And she'll tease you ♪
♪ She'll unease you ♪
♪ All the better
Just to please you ♪
♪ She's precocious ♪
♪ And she knows just what it ♪
♪ Takes to make a pro blush ♪
♪ She got Greta Garbo
Standoff sighs ♪
♪ She's got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ She'll let you
Take her home ♪
♪ It whets her appetite ♪
♪ She'll lay you On a throne ♪
♪ She got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ She'll take A
tumble on you ♪
♪ Roll you Like
you were dice ♪
♪ Until you come up blue ♪
♪ She's got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ She'll expose you ♪
♪ When she snows you ♪
♪ Of your feet with The
crumbs she throws you ♪
♪ She's ferocious ♪
♪ And she knows just what it ♪
♪ Takes to make a pro blush ♪
♪ All the boys
Think she's a spy ♪
♪ She's got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ And she'll tease you ♪
♪ She'll unease you ♪
♪ All the better
Just to please you ♪
♪ She's precocious ♪
♪ And she knows just what it ♪
♪ Takes to make a pro blush ♪
♪ All the boys
Think she's a spy ♪
♪ She's got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ She'll tease you ♪
♪ She'll unease you ♪
♪ Just to please ya ♪
♪ She's got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ She'll expose you ♪
♪ When she snows you ♪
♪ She knows ya ♪
♪ She's got Bette Davis eyes ♪
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES OUT)
(STATIC CRACKLING)