[heavy breathing]
- Lutzner: Dearly beloved...
- Paul: Okay.
We are gathered here
today to join Paul Duerson
and Sofia Minor
in holy matrimony.
Do you take Paul to be your
lawfully-wedded husband?
Sofia: I do.
Paul: [VO] I hate it when
they show the ending first.
But I just couldn't help myself.
Lutzner: You may
kiss the bride.
Paul: [VO] Okay
guys, that's enough.
Back to the beginning.
[upbeat instrumental
music playing]
[upbeat music continues]
[doorbell rings]
- [lock clicks]
- [music stops]
[crickets chirping]
So, what do you think?
It was my dad's.
Fits perfect, huh?
How was the tour?
Saw you guys in San Francisco.
[whooshing noise]
Whoa-ho! Nice.
Don't do this. Just go.
[whispers] William...
Tonight is the night.
I'm proposing.
Bell: I told you...
the next time you came around,
I was calling the police.
You're killing me.
We have to talk with
you about something.
I didn't want to do this.
Who?
Me and Sofia. You
know, my girlfriend?
She's not your girlfriend.
Okay, listen.
I know you're a lonely guy.
Because your wife died.
And that's why Sofia does
those puzzles with you.
She does them with you
because she feels bad
that your wife died
of stomach cancer,
and you have no one to
do puzzles with anymore.
[soft tense music playing]
How do you know
about the puzzles?
- Is she here?
- No.
Oh... oh, I can wait.
It's not a problem.
- No, no, no.
- Paul: No, it's really not...
Listen, I really don't want to
have to call the cops, man, okay?
Just leave. Now.
You don't have to call them.
You don't have to. [chuckles]
You know, I could just sit
right... right in there.
Yeah.
- Okay.
High five.
Give it to me. I need it.
- [sighs heavily]
- I need it.
Bell: Okay, Paul.
You got big hands.
Bye.
Oh, fuck. Go!
[door slams shut, lock clicks]
[doorbell rings]
[sighs] Goddammit.
[sinister music rising]
Hey. Hey.
Paul: Why are you
acting this way?
Take it easy.
Don't be mad at me, Ladybug.
Bell: I'm not mad at you.
You're confused.
We've been through this
before. You don't know Sofia.
Paul: You're wrong.
You are wrong.
Bell: Okay, you know her.
- Give me the knife.
- You.
What?
You're Sofia.
Don't you... Don't!
Look, I'm unarmed.
Let me help.
Say you're Sofia.
- Okay, I'm Sofia.
- And you love me.
I'm Sofia, and I love you.
Now, give me the knife, Paul.
Stay there.
[tense music playing]
Yeah. Oh, my god. Here it is.
I have a ring.
It's really nice of you.
Will you marry me?
I don't know what to...
to say.
Put it on.
It's perfect.
[chuckles]
Give me the knife, Paul.
[singing softly] ♪ I am
broken My heart has spoken ♪
♪ You are broken, too ♪
♪ I'm afraid I'm depraved ♪
♪ But no one's
depraved Like you ♪
I freaking love that song.
I love it.
The wedding is going to be
at the Cassowary Tabernacle.
JH is my best man.
Pastor Tim Lutzner is
gonna perform the ceremony.
And... and, and...
I got this dagger.
Not this one.
It's a Rajput ceremonial
wedding dagger.
It's in Customs now,
but wait until you
see this thing.
I mean... we're gonna
look amazing up there.
I mean, for that alone.
[chuckles] What do you think?
You're pretty
stone-faced right now.
Okay, let's do it.
Really?
- You love me?
- Yes. I love you. Now...
now, please just
give me the knife.
- [blade slashing]
- [Bell groans]
[Paul grunts, sniffles]
[Bell groans]
[Bell wheezing]
Paul: Hmm.
[Bell groans in pain]
Who should we tell first?
My family or yours?
[Paul giggles]
♪ ["Bongo Rock" by The
Incredible Bongo Band playing] ♪
[song continues, muffled]
[indistinct, overlapping
news report chatter]
[chatter fades]
♪ ["No More 'I Love You's"
by Annie Lennox plays] ♪
[siren wailing]
♪ I used to be a lunatic
From the gracious days ♪
♪ I used to feel woebegone ♪
♪ And so restless nights ♪
[laughing]
♪ My aching heart would bleed ♪
♪ For you to see ♪
♪ Oh, but now ♪
♪ I don't find myself
bouncing home ♪
♪ Whistling buttonhole
tunes to make me cry ♪
Sofia: Okay, um... I'm ready.
Ready for my interview.
Rhodes: Who is DeVante Rhodes?
Sofia: Ah. Well...
he's the best point guard
in the game of basketball.
Rhodes: So he's hot.
Is that why you had your
people call me yesterday?
No. I don't even know
what a point guard does.
What else he say? He said
you were a trailblazer.
And I was like, "In what?"
[scoffs] I-I was
traded to the Nuggets.
[chuckles]
That's a really silly name
for a basketball team.
Okay, so you called me
up to make fun of me?
Well, you seemed... like fun.
And I like to have fun.
Is that why you wrote that song?
What song?
I kind of like that one.
[claps hands] It's
your turn. You're up.
- Rhodes: All right.
- Sofia: Move it.
[Sofia chuckles]
What's your favorite
song of mine?
I told you. "Girls
Just Want to Have Fun."
That's Cyndi Lauper.
You're confusing
your white singers.
It's embarrassing.
Oh, uh... "Like a Prayer."
Do I look like Madonna?
A little. Actually.
- [knocking on door]
- Kaylor: Sofia?
It's Kaylor.
Your assistant?
Sofia: I know who you
are, Kaylor. What's up?
William's here.
[gasps]
Who's, uh... who's William?
Sofia: He goes by Bell.
That doesn't answer my question.
Sofia: I'll be down in a sec.
Does he seem okay to you?
Kaylor: What do you mean?
Sofia: You know, is
he healthy, mentally?
Kaylor: Do you
mean, like, twitchy?
He seems fine.
Are you twitchy?
Hey, Sof.
Hey!
Hmm.
- Sofia: How's Abby?
- Oh, she's good. Thank you.
[chuckles] That's Rhodes.
- The Blazer?
- He's a Nugget now.
Come on, I wanna
show you something.
[belt clinking]
Kaylor: Have you met Waylon
up at the front booth?
- His wife makes the best chili.
- [suspenseful music playing]
- Rhodes: What the fuck?
- [birds chirping]
[Bell chatting indistinctly]
Sofia: Love it.
Ta-da!
Would you look at that.
Took me every bit
of the six months
- you were gone, too.
- Mm
Wow. Six months...
for this puzzle.
Shut up.
And here is our next challen...
You said I could choose.
There's a piece missing.
Yeah, I know. It's
driving me nuts.
I looked everywhere for it.
♪ [suspenseful music fades into
"Lovefool" by The Cardigans] ♪
♪ Dear, I fear We're
facing a problem ♪
♪ You love me no longer ♪
♪ I know and ♪
♪ Maybe there is
nothing That I can do ♪
♪ To make you do ♪
♪ Mama tells me I
shouldn't bother ♪
♪ That I ought just
stick To another man... ♪
[engine stops, car door opens]
[birds chirping]
Bell: Sorry I'm late.
I figured I'd get
the silent treatment.
Came with reinforcements.
[bottle clinks]
Here. You left it up here.
Not supposed to
have Coke this late.
Says who?
You.
Well... I won't
tell if you don't.
You ready?
[bottles clink]
Let's see.
You're upset because the Pirates
lost their third straight today.
That was a terrible game,
but that's not why I'm mad.
Drink.
Hmm. Okay.
Is it because I'm
going back to work?
And you were really
looking forward
to spending more time
with me this summer?
- You're not that cool.
- [chuckles]
You're afraid I
could get hurt again.
I just hate the whole
idea of a bodyguard.
It's like saying your life
is less important than hers.
He called again today.
- Who?
- You know who.
Next time he does,
hang up and call me.
He just seemed confused.
- [door opens, squeaks]
- [dog barking]
[distant shouting]
[siren wailing]
Paul: [VO] My dearest JH,
by the time you're reading this,
the best day of my life,
and therefore yours,
will be fast approaching.
So, by now, you should
have already picked up
my parcel from the post office.
You wrote down the
lock combination
when we last spoke
so you should be able
to let yourself in.
I don't want to put too
much in writing because...
[whispers] spies.
But I trust you're prepared
and remember the plan.
Oh, and please remember
to bring your eyepatch.
I love you so much, JH.
Sofia and I could not be happier
that you're joining
us on this journey.
Your best pal...
confidant, Paul.
[jaunty string music playing]
- [music fading]
- [overlapping news reports]
[sirens wailing]
Reporter:... escape from
Concord Park Institution
in Fresno has left two
dead and one injured.
Authorities tell us
that Paul Duerson
and Penelope Pascal are unarmed
and should be considered
extremely dangerous.
[phone ringing]
- Bell: I won't be long.
- Abby: But, Dad,
- I don't think...
- Bell: Everything's fine.
Stay here with Aunt
Eleanor and be nice. Okay?
- Abby: I'm always nice.
- Um-hmm.
- Be careful.
- I'm always careful.
I love you.
[laughing maniacally]
You got the trunk
and the clothes!
Yeah.
See?! I knew you could do it!
JH: Ah.
Is that what I think it is?
It finally came. You
wanna go to McDonald's?
[door opens, shuts]
[Penny panting]
JH: Hey, Paul. There's
a woman in the car.
Paul: That's Penny.
[Penny grunting]
- [sneezes]
- Paul: Bless you.
She's my PA.
JH: What's a PA?
[French accent] A
personal assistant.
Paul: She helps Sofia
and I with our schedules
because we're both so busy.
Penny: I help with tasks.
To organize holidays and
gatekeep from unwanted...
...uh...
Kli... Kli... Klingons?
- Yes, Paul?
- Clingers-on.
Klingons are something...
totally different.
Hey... hey, Paul. Maybe
I could be your PA.
Paul: You know, JH,
it's best not to go into
business with your friends.
Hey, I thought you went home.
What, uh... what happened?
Officer Parker:
Let's get you inside.
Bell?
Paul Duerson escaped from
Concord Park two hours ago.
Huh. [chuckles nervously]
Rhodes: Who the fuck
is this Paul Duerson?
[car horn blares]
What happens to your eye?
I lost it.
- In a sword fight.
- [Penny gasps]
No.
He had a worm. A parasite.
[chuckles]
JH: It's not funny.
[Paul chuckles]
It's a little funny.
Paul: All right,
Penny. You're up first,
then we'll drop you, JH.
[suspenseful music playing]
[knocks on door]
[door opening]
Can I help you?
Yes. Hello, mister.
My car is... is broke.
Can... can I use your telephone?
Well, I'm pretty good with cars.
Why don't I take a look at it?
Now, where's that accent from?
[door closes]
- Rhodes: Bell, right?
- Yeah.
Rhodes: You mind if I use
your phone real quick?
I'm gonna call a cab.
Sure, but they'll take forever
to get here. It's late.
The guest bedroom
should be made up.
[chuckles] Oh, yeah.
We were messing around.
And I... can't find
my clothes now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got you.
Had fun tonight?
Yeah, Sofia is crazy, man.
[box thuds]
So, this guy, um...
Paul Duerson.
Rhodes: Yeah.
How bad he get you?
Bell: Ruptured spleen.
Should have bled out.
He called the cops on himself.
[car door thudding outside]
[suspenseful music playing]
[car engine revs]
[phone ringing]
Yeah?
Wait, slow down.
Call the police. I'm coming.
[phone thuds]
Rhodes: What? What's
going on, man?
Bell: I never should
have left her.
Fuck!
Bell: Lock this behind me.
[locks clicking]
[sentimental music playing]
[chuckles]
Lu's on First, huh? [scoffs]
So, that's what this is.
What the fuck.
[mellow piano music playing]
Hey. Cute top.
Where'd you get that?
[Sofia chuckles]
Hey, look, it's cool
if you wanna... go.
Oh.
- That's it then?
- Sofia: Well, yeah.
'Cause Bell's here,
Waylon's out front.
Bell left.
Where'd he go?
[Officer Carter whistling]
[knocks on door]
Hello? Got a call!
Hello? [clears throat]
Uh, got a call.
Yes, there's a strange man here.
- Inside?
- Outside.
So, there's not a
man here-here, then?
No.
Is that out of the ordinary?
- For there to be a man outside?
- No.
This seems to be a
fairly busy block.
People walk.
People stroll.
Ms...?
Eleanor: The guy was
creepy, all right?
And it's late.
You think I'd call the
cops for no reason?
That him?
What?
Is that the man from outside?
I'm not a man.
[Officer Carter chuckles]
Eleanor: You think
this is funny?
No. But, uh...
everything seems to be okay now.
And I gotta get up early
for an audition, so...
An audition?
Musical. It's a black
box theater thing.
Okay. Look, if you really
want me to hang out here,
I can, uh, stay here
and keep you safe.
How about a cup of coffee?
Oh, we'd feel safer
if you protected us
from your car outside.
- [kettle whistling]
- Bicycle.
[Abby laughs]
What?
[kettle whistling]
Okay.
[chuckles]
Should we get started
on the new one?
Have you seen this movie?
Because it looks like a riot.
Something wrong?
No.
It looks like something's wrong.
Rhodes: You worked so
hard on this puzzle and...
we're just...
just gonna clean it all up?
Well yeah, that's
how puzzles work.
Yeah, finished with that one.
Are you crying?
Nah.
Okay.
I'm a puzzle.
What?
You built me up for a minute.
You made me...
feel nice and...
whole and comfortable, and...
now, you're finished with me?
I didn't say we were finished.
Yeah, but we're finished.
I can tell.
Just... put me back in my box.
Oo-kay. Um...
[slurping]
[car door closing,
engine receding]
[country music playing on radio]
Uh... okay.
[country music continues]
Hello?
- [electricity dying]
- [music fades]
[crickets chirping]
- Fuck.
- Sofia: Fuck.
This keeps happening.
They were supposed to
fix this shit weeks ago.
[lighter clicks]
Rhodes: Who is "they"?
Sofia: I don't know.
The... light people?
Rhodes: Okay. Where's
your circuit breaker?
Sofia: I don't know.
Rhodes: You don't know where
your circuit breaker is?
Sofia: Do you know where
the circuit breaker is?
This is your house.
Sofia: Well...
I have... many houses,
and many circuit breakers.
[scoffs]
What?
That was such a
Sofia thing to say.
Excuse me?
Talking about how many
circuit breakers you have
is a rich person thing to say.
You're rich, so you can't talk.
Rhodes: Rich...
is a state of mind.
[chuckles]
What does that mean?
Like this thing.
It was a gift from
Liberace. It's funny.
It's creepy.
And I didn't know
people gave out
these candle holders as gifts.
But I guess fancy
clothing designers do.
It's called a candelabra.
[clears throat] And
Liberace was a pianist,
you're thinking of Versace.
Again, a very
Sofia thing to say.
Waylon: Dammit.
Ah, fuck.
Come on.
Sofia: Where are you going?
Rhodes: To find your
circuit breaker.
[Sofia sighs] Is
there a problem here?
Actually, you know
what? I don't care.
I'm not doing this with you.
- [lighter clicks]
- Rhodes: Doing what?
Sofia: Digging any
deeper with you.
Rhodes: Yeah. No shit.
Sofia: It is a
little weird, though.
For you to be
so... how you are.
Rhodes: Like a
Black guy, you mean?
Sofia: Please. Come on.
You're nothing at all
what people say about
you. You're more of a...
[crickets chirping]
Rhodes: I'm not like
what whosays about me?
Whoever wrote that
list on your desk...
that's some real Ice Queen shit
to have just fucking
lying around.
And, where do I fit in?
How are you ever going
to find anything real?
- Sofia: Real?
- Yeah.
What is that even?
[sneezes]
Waylon: Who the fuck are you?
Sofia: I'm very sorry
your feelings were hurt,
but I kind of have other
things to worry about.
The psycho who tried to
kill me is on the loose.
He tried to kill Bell.
You weren't even home.
He thought he was stabbing me.
He wanted me dead! What
are you still doing here?
I don't need you to protect me.
Okay, yeah. 'Cause
you have armed guards
and a security system
from the future, right?
- Yeah, great point!
- Okay.
- You're not needed at all.
- Rhodes: All right, I'm out.
[Waylon groaning]
[coughing and groaning]
Oh, my balls!
I enjoy this American hat.
[playful music playing]
Uh-uh. Open sesame.
- [Taser buzzing]
- [Waylon screaming]
[giggling]
- [Waylon groans]
- [Penny mutters indistinctly]
[gasps, laughs]
[Waylon groaning]
[Penny screams]
[groans]
[grunting]
Waylon will call you a cab.
[Waylon groaning]
Waylon: [muffled] Help me!
Yee-haw!
[microwave smashing]
[crickets chirping]
Rhodes: Hey man, can
you open the gate?
Waylon?
[switch clicks]
Sofia: [groans] Ow! Shit!
[laughs]
Am I an idiot?
[suspenseful music playing]
[sliding door clicks]
Paul: Coo-coo.
Hello?
Rhodes?
[lighter rattles]
[lighter clicks]
[suspenseful music playing]
[kettle whistling]
[stove knob clicks]
[kettle's whistle dies]
[objects clank]
[tense music playing]
[lighter clicks]
[suspenseful music playing]
[switch clicks]
Hey, Ladybug.
[object thuds]
Ooh! I missed you a lot.
A lot. A lot.
[chuckles]
Mm.
I owe you an apology.
I am so sorry for
leaving, honey.
Get away from me.
- [unsettling music playing]
- I...
Baby, I...
Don't do...
I don't know what
I was thinking.
Mmm.
Hi. [chuckles]
- [grunts]
- [Paul groans]
Hey, wait a second.
Wait. I can explain, baby. Ow!
Paul: Enough with
the little oranges!
Ow! Those are hard!
Baby, wait a sec.
[grunts]
[glass shattering]
[panting]
That is such bad luck, Sofia!
[shouting] Get out of
my fucking house!!!
- [grunts]
- Paul: Sofia.
Sofia: Get out of here!
[tense music playing]
I'm trying. I'm trying!
[screaming]
[thudding]
[squeaking]
Abby: Did my dad ever tell
you about Paul Duerson?
Like, what happened to him?
I saw on MTV News that
his girlfriend collapsed
during a Sofia concert.
A stroke or something
during "Father May I."
Just, boom, dead at The Forum.
[car tires screech]
You want to know
what's also messed up?
I'm in the "Father
May I" music video
and it's always
projected behind Sofia
when she performs it.
So, maybe Paul Duerson's
girlfriend saw my face
- and just, like, died.
- [door opens]
- Hey.
- Abby: Hey, Dad.
Everyone okay?
Eleanor: I think the officer
might have scared him off.
Eleanor made him wait outside.
There was nobody out there.
Get dressed.
- Abby: Where we going?
- Bell: Police station.
He was supposed to be
keeping an eye out.
He was just there.
[ambient traffic noise]
Officer Carter: ♪ I just got an
Invitation through the mails ♪
♪ "Your presence requested
This evening, it's formal ♪
♪ A top hat, A white
tie and tails" ♪
♪ Nothing now could take
The wind out of my sails ♪
♪ Because I'm invited To
step out this evening ♪
♪ With top hat,
White tie and tails ♪
♪ Oh, I... ♪
[clears throat]
♪ Oh, I'm puttin'
On my top hat ♪
♪ Tyin' up my white tie
Brushin' off my tails ♪
♪ I'm steppin' out, my dear ♪
♪ To breathe an atmosphere
That simply reeks with class ♪
♪ And I trust that
You'll excuse my dust ♪
♪ When I step on the gas ♪
♪ For I'll be there
Puttin' down my top hat ♪
♪ Mussin' up my white tie ♪
♪ And dancin' in my tails ♪
[panting]
- [tense music playing]
- The heck?
- [bike squeaks]
- The fuck did my chain go?
Who the hell steals a chain
from a police officer's bike?
Unbelievable.
Fucking West Side...
- [chain rattles]
- [choking]
[groaning]
[neck snaps]
[car tires screech]
Abby: Is that the cop's?
Bell: Get in the car
and lock the doors.
[sinister music playing]
[gun cocks]
Abby: Dad?
May I have that gun, please?
His hand is cold.
Let go of her.
JH: Take us to
Sofia's house, please.
Paul is waiting for us.
- [gun thuds]
- Abby: Do you work for him?
JH: You should never go
into business with friends.
♪ ["Crimson and Clover" by Tommy
James & the Shondells playing] ♪
♪ Now I don't hardly know her ♪
♪ But I think I
could love her ♪
♪ Crimson and clover ♪
♪ Ah... ♪
♪ When she comes walking over ♪
♪ Now I've been
Waiting to show her ♪
♪ Crimson and clover ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Da-da, da-da, da-da ♪
♪ My, my, such a sweet thing ♪
♪ Da-da, da-da, da-da ♪
♪ I wanna do everything ♪
♪ What a beautiful feeling ♪
♪ Da-da, da-da, da-da ♪
♪ Crimson and clover ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
♪ Da-da, da-da, da-da ♪
I killed someone.
- [claps softly]
- [Paul scoffs]
Ow. Ow!
Paul: [as Hannibal
Lecter] Hello, Clarice.
[normally] We've got a long,
long night ahead of us.
[chuckles]
Listen. I know
you're super upset.
I know you're upset
that I left you.
But I really needed
some time to focus on me
before I could focus on us.
But now, I'm ready
to be yours forever.
And I mean... forever.
- Paul...
- Paul: And ever.
And ever, and ever,
and ever, and ever.
- Paul.
- And ever, and ever.
Call me Paul.
Paul.
I love it when you
call me by my name.
Okay. Um... listen.
You're confused. All right?
You're in the middle
of a psychotic...
um...
They told me what
happened to you.
At my show, and I am so sorry.
Nobody should have
to go through that.
Okay?
But this is not the answer.
You're mad about the venue...
- Oh, my God. The venue?
- Aren't you?
[scoffs]
The Cassowary Tabernacle?
What?
The church we're
getting married at?
It's important to me.
We're getting married?
- Of course. [chuckles]
- Sofia: Oh, God.
What, are you having
second thoughts?
Look, this snuck up on us,
and it's totally normal to
have feelings like this.
But I mean, you
knew all of this.
- Um...
- Are you feeling okay?
Sofia: Um...
Okay, well, uh...
You gonna let me out then?
Of course.
Sofia: Yeah, now? [chuckles]
Show you around the house.
Show you the Jacuzzi.
Paul: You're hilarious, Sofia.
Like I don't know where
the Jacuzzi is. [scoffs]
I've been here like a
bazillion times. [chuckles]
[chuckles]
♪ ["Lovefool" by The Cardigans
playing quietly over radio] ♪
Will you please just take
the bag off her head.
JH: No.
Why are you doing this?
I'm not supposed to say.
Paul's a real great planner,
and he don't want
me to ruin anything.
So, you just do whatever
he tells you to?
Is that it?
He's the only person who ever
treated me like a person.
Well, he's gotten you
into a lot of trouble.
Let them go.
We'll sort it out.
Pull over here.
[crickets chirping]
Get out.
Find the nearest
house. Call the police.
Not them.
You.
Turn this song up.
Drive off and I'll kill him.
- [car door closes]
- It's okay.
Abby: Where's he taking him?
- Eleanor: He'll be okay.
- ♪... reach a solution ♪
♪ I will end up
Lost in confusion ♪
♪ I don't care If
you really care ♪
♪ As long as you don't go ♪
♪ So I cry and I
pray And I beg ♪
Don't do this.
I'm sorry.
- [gunshot]
- ♪ Fool me fool me ♪
♪ Go on and fool me ♪
♪ Love me, love me
Pretend that you love me ♪
♪ Leave me, leave me Just
say that you need me ♪
♪ So I cry ♪
♪ And I beg for you to ♪
♪ Love me love me Say
that you love me ♪
- You can take the bag off now.
- ♪ Leave me, leave me ♪
♪ Just say that you need me ♪
♪ I can't care 'bout
Anything but you ♪
Paul: I have a
surprise for you.
Don't move a muscle.
[shushing]
[whispering] Penny.
This is Penny. She's
a big fan of yours.
We met on the inside.
It was totally platonic.
She's great. She's
from Nice en France.
Spelled like "nice."
Nice.
Ha! Hilarious, Sofia. Truly.
[laughs] Truly. Uh, uh...
Penny plays the piano
and sings, just like you.
Oh... mon dieu. We
could be a... a duet.
[gasps]
Paul: See? Friends already!
Look at that. Perfect!
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
♪ ["Borderline" by The
Flaming Lips playing] ♪
♪ Something in the
way You love me ♪
♪ Won't let me be ♪
♪ I don't want to
be Your prisoner ♪
♪ So baby Won't
you set me free? ♪
♪ Stop playin' with my heart
Finish what you start ♪
♪ When you make my
love Come down ♪
♪ If you want me let me
know Baby let it show ♪
♪ Come on now
Don't fool around ♪
[instrumental break]
♪ Something in your eyes ♪
♪ Is makin' such a fool of me ♪
♪ When you hold me in
your arms You love me ♪
♪ 'Til I just can't see ♪
♪ Just... ♪
♪ Try to understand ♪
♪ I've given all I can ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
The best of me ♪
♪ Borderline ♪
♪ Feels like I'm Goin'
to lose my mind ♪
♪ You just keep on
pushin' My love ♪
♪ Over the borderline ♪
[discordant instrumental break]
- [doorbell rings]
- [music fades]
[footsteps approaching]
You made it!
[claps, exclaims]
Whoo!
Welcome to the cocktail hour,
where drinks and hors
d'oeuvres will be served
before the shuttle
takes us to the church.
[sniffles]
JH, put the gun away.
What kind of way is that
to treat our guests?
Our guests!
[yelling] Oh!
How do I look?
Hi, Abby.
[chuckles]
Uh, kids. Okay.
Come on. Don't be scared.
Please remember to
sign the guest book.
Penny: It's nice.
Huh?
I am sorry, I borrowed some...
some clothes from your closet.
But it fits, no? It's good.
I am very excitement
for tonight.
Yes.
Um... Paul told me
you are in love.
[whispering] I know
this is not truth.
I know. But, you know,
as... as they say, um...
Uh...
Paul... Paul's elevator does
not reach the top floor.
[giggles] You know? Americans!
I've never heard that
expression before.
Hmm.
But is... is this...
this is why I like Paul.
You know? He entertains me.
Watching him is like
watching a good movie.
So, he tells me, he
is to marry Sofia.
But...
he needs my help.
[chuckles] I think, "Oui,
merci, s'il vous plaît.
I would like to be in
this movie very much."
[chuckles]
Coo-coo.
This yours. Take it.
[chuckles]
It's nice, huh?
You know, you...
you have a wonderful, um...
skin and body. You have...
a great body.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
- Thanks.
- Penny: But...
uh, with honesty, I... I thought
you would be more beautiful.
Yes, is... is a big
disappointment for me.
All right. Well...
why don't you get
my makeup? Um-hmm.
Yeah, it's in my bathroom,
left of the sink.
Oh, um... and this...
will fix your face?
[imitating French accent]
Yes, it will fix my face.
Okay. [chuckles] Okay.
Ah-ah...
Sofia. [chuckles]
[Penny giggles]
Okay. Be back soon.
[footsteps departing]
[door opens and closes]
[door squeaks]
[tense music playing]
[approaching footsteps]
[door opens]
[door squeaks]
[grunts]
[body thuds]
[gasps]
- [guitar clatters]
- Fuck!
Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
Uh... okay.
[Paul humming]
May I offer you a
glass of champagne?
I'm kidding. Of course
you can't drink.
[chuckles and
snorts] Evil, right?
You keep calling me.
I do.
Why?
Well, we wanted you
to be our flower girl.
JH picked out the dress.
[muffled thudding]
What's that?
Huh. Would you?
Leaky pipes, I guess.
[thudding continues]
Abby: Paul?
Whew. Yes, flower girl?
Is someone in the trunk?
Man: Please help me.
I'm in here. Hello?
Yes, flower girl.
Can we let him out?
Well... we were supposed
to wait until later,
but, uh... sure, why not?
Get to it.
[claps and rub hands]
[man whimpering] Help me.
[trunk lid squeaks]
Pastor Lutzner.
Paul?
[groans]
[grunts]
[chuckles]
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is Pastor Tim Lutzner
of the Cassowary Tabernacle.
Please help yourself to
champagne and first aid.
Abby: You put a
priest in a box?
No, I put a pastor in a box.
We're Protestant.
Wake up, wake up,
wake up, wake up.
Hmm. Oh, thank god. Okay.
Hi.
Sorry I left you.
I'm sorry I hit you in
the face with a guitar.
[scoffs]
Was it on purpose?
No.
Guy thinks he's
marrying you tonight.
I know. He bought
me a wedding dress.
It's blue.
It's fucked up.
I know.
[Penny grunts]
[Sofia screams]
Jesus.
[choking]
Let go, you crazy bitch!
[grunts]
- [piano thuds]
- [tambourine rattles]
[panting]
[coughs, wheezes]
♪ [playing "It's All Coming
Back To Me" by Celine Dion] ♪
[continues playing]
Duet, please.
What?
No.
Penny: Du...
...et.
[Penny chuckles softly]
♪ [Penny plays "It's All Coming
Back To Me" by Celine Dion] ♪
I didn't even write this song.
I know. 'Cause
this song is good.
- Come on.
- All right. [clears throat]
["It's All Coming Back To
Me" by Celine Dion on piano]
Yeah. Yeah.
[singing beautifully]
♪ There were nights ♪
♪ When the wind was so cold ♪
♪ That my body froze in bed ♪
♪ If I just listened to it
Right outside the window ♪
♪ There were days when
The sun was so cruel ♪
♪ All the tears
turned to dust ♪
♪ And I just knew my eyes
Were drying up forever ♪
♪ I finished crying In the
instant that you left ♪
♪ And I can't remember
Where or when or how ♪
♪ And I banished every memory
You and I had ever made... ♪
[notes played on piano]
♪ But when you
touch me Like this ♪
♪ And you hold me like that ♪
♪ I just have to admit ♪
♪ That it's all
Coming back to me ♪
♪ When I touch you like this ♪
♪ And I hold you like that ♪
♪ It's so hard to believe ♪
♪ That it's all
Coming back to me ♪
[fire crackling]
[clock ticking]
♪ There were moments of gold ♪
♪ And there were
Flashes of light ♪
♪ There were things
I'd never do again ♪
♪ But then they
Always seemed right ♪
♪ There were nights
Of endless pleasure ♪
♪ It was more than
Any laws allow... ♪
♪ Baby! Baby! If I
kiss you like this ♪
♪ And if you whisper
Like that... ♪
- You are flat!
- [grunts]
Sofia: Fuck! What the
fuck is wrong with you?!
- [Penny grunts]
- [glass shatters]
[both groaning]
Sofia: Stop!
- [Penny yells]
- [Sofia grunts]
[Penny laughs]
Oh! Oh, no. Are you okay?
[laughs maniacally]
[dramatic music playing]
[screams]
[dramatic music continues]
[Sofia yelps]
[Sofia strains]
[groaning]
[Penny screams]
[screams]
- [Sofia yells]
- [Penny screams]
[lighter clicks]
[dramatic music continues]
Do it!
Sofia doesn't light
people on fire.
- [lighter clicks]
- [Penny growls]
[panting]
Fuck.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Come on. [panting]
[quietly] Okay. Okay. Okay.
[grunts]
[dramatic music resumes]
[coughing]
[Sofia grunting]
[sneezes]
God. Bless. You!
[Penny groans]
- [Sofia groans]
- [Penny grunts]
[yelling and screaming]
[panting]
[laughs]
Yes!
Come on! Light me on fire!
Come on, Sofia!
[laughs maniacally]
[screaming]
- [fire blazes]
- [Sofia panting]
[Penny continues screaming]
[Sofia whimpers]
[panting]
[coughs, pants]
Oh, fuck.
[fire extinguisher clangs]
Wh... what could they
be doing up there?
[scoffs]
Pas... Pastor Lutzner,
do you have any...?
- Lutzner: Paul?
- Yes?
What are you trying
to achieve here?
Just a partnership
based on mutual
admiration and respect.
Lutzner: It's not real.
You see that, don't you?
None of it is real.
Paul?
She's probably just
figuring out her dress.
Last-minute dress alterations.
Yeah, I'm sure it's
just last-minute kinks
with the dress, right?
Girls will be girls,
Pastor Lutzner.
You might not know about
that, but girls will be girls.
JH: Should... should
I go check on them?
No. No, no. I'll go.
I'll go. It's fine.
Saw a little girl
here when I snuck in.
Black girl. Ten or eleven.
Okay, okay. Um...
Fuck.
You stay here.
I'll be right back.
I'll be right back. Okay.
[groans]
Honey? Everything
okay in here?
You re...
Oh my god, I'm so sorry.
You're just the most beautiful
thing I've ever seen.
Why aren't you ready?
And where's Penny?
[sniffing]
[unsettling instrumental
music playing]
Is there something
wrong with the dress?
I'm...
I so... understand.
This is really scary.
But I adore you, Ladybug.
From your head all the
way down to your toes.
Sofia: Abby! Abby!
Hey!
You're supposed to
be getting ready.
Who are you?
How awesome is this, huh?
- [blade sings]
- Rajput warriors
are gifted this on
their wedding day.
It's sharp on both sides.
To protect you from
your enemies...
and your friends...
whoever came in the
way of your happiness.
But I won't let anyone...
come in the way
of our happiness.
Yo, what the fuck are
you talking about?
I love you.
Are you okay? You're okay.
Where's your dad?
[gunshot]
[crickets chirping]
You dead?
["Lovefool" playing quietly
in distance over radio]
Kaylor: Hello?
Hello?
Are you okay?
[coughs]
Kaylor: Are you okay?
Taylor?
Kaylor.
What happened to your head?
[Bell sighs]
We should really get
you to a hospital.
I need a car.
[car horn chirps]
You have a Porsche?
It's so fast.
[tires screech]
Guess I'm walking.
[suspenseful synth
music playing]
"Welcome to Paul
and Sofia wedding."
Father Tim Lutzner. Tim...
Lutzner. Motherfucker!
- ♪ ["Sweet Baby Jesus" by the Mondo
Boys playing] ♪ - ♪ Sweet baby Jesus ♪
♪ Won't you come ♪
♪ See me get married ♪
♪ To my love ♪
♪ Sweet baby Jesus ♪
♪ I see you watchin' ♪
♪ From above ♪
♪ Sweet baby Jesus... ♪
Let's get all units to
Cassowary Tabernacle.
I hate the fucking Hills.
♪ ... I see you watching ♪
♪ Sweet Jesus... ♪
- [door closes]
- [music stops]
Okay. Everybody ready?
Great. Let's do it.
[exclaims excitedly]
Flower girl, you look great.
What are you doing?
What?
Please take a seat.
It's about to start.
Ma'am, today's not about you.
Thank you.
Shouldn't you be up there?
I don't know.
JH: Uh, Paul?
Paul: Uh, JH?
Ar... aren't you marrying Sofia?
Of course.
Uh, Sofia is...
JH...
you've been one
hell of a best man.
I got it from here.
Okay? Your job's done.
Flower girl, get
back there, please.
[claps]
Get some hustle. Hustle.
Okay, great.
Hit it, JH.
[radio clicks]
[romantic music
plays through stereo]
Throw the... throw the flowers.
[door opens]
[wedding march playing]
Dad!
[quietly] Don't upset him.
He gets violent
when he's confused.
I'm in a wedding dress, man.
I think he's pretty
fucking confused.
[chuckles softly]
Thank you.
For your kindness
and graciousness.
I'll treat her right.
[whispering] And I'm sorry
my hands are so sweaty.
Hey, you mind if I
greet the guests?
Oh, of course. Just, um...
would you sit on my side?
It's empty.
[zipper unzips]
It's great to see you.
Thanks for coming.
Everything's gonna be okay.
The big one has a gun.
I know. He shot me
in the head with it.
Dearly beloved, we are
gathered here today
to join Paul Duerson and this...
person...
in holy matrimony.
- Uh, hey, Paul?
- [shushes]
Down, JH.
JH: That's not Sofia.
What are you talking about?
He's a man.
And he's Black.
And he don't look
nothing like her.
There's Sofia.
Don't listen to him.
Baby, it's me. I'm here.
I'm Sofia.
Pastor Lutzner...
you can continue.
If anyone present believes
these two persons should not
be joined in holy matrimony,
speak now or forever
hold their peace.
I do. I... I... object.
[tense music playing]
No. No. You don't have to.
And it's my fault
we're all here.
So, I should be the
one up there with you.
Not him, Paul.
You do look
beautiful, by the way.
Thank you.
You know, being with me is
not all it's cracked up to be.
But hey, you're the only person
who's ever wanted to marry me.
So fuck it, let's do
it. Let's get married.
[upbeat music playing]
- Paul: Ma'am?
- Yeah?
I told you to sit
down and be quiet.
Today is not
about you. Please?
For the rest of us? Thank you.
[Paul clears throat]
Paul: I'm so sorry.
You can skip ahead to the
good stuff. We're ready.
Lutzner: The good stuff?
Yeah. You know, the kissing.
Lutzner: Um, all right.
Do you, Paul,
take... Your name?
[both] Sofia.
Lutzner: Do you,
Paul, take Sofia to be
your lawfully-wedded wife?
I do.
Lutzner: And do you,
Sofia, take Paul
to be your
lawfully-wedded husband?
I do. [clears throat]
Well... in the presence
of family and friends,
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Hey, shouldn't we do something?
Let him have it.
It's all he wanted.
♪ Sweet baby Jesus ♪
♪ I'm alive ♪
♪ I'm awake ♪
♪ Dear Jesus above ♪
♪ I see you watchin' ♪
♪ Sweet Jesus ♪
♪ From a tower up above ♪
♪ Sweet baby Jesus ♪
♪ I'm alive ♪
[song continues]
[tense music playing]
No!
[Rhodes gasps]
[Sofia breathing heavily]
[knife sings]
No!
[screams]
[gurgling]
[dramatic instrumental
music playing]
Sofia...
[sniffles]
I'm sorry.
It's over, Paul.
I really love it when
you call me by name.
Are you okay?
Don't move!
- Bell: Let her go.
- JH: Hey, Paul.
I got myself in a
hostage situation.
Please let her go.
You! Dr... drop that knife.
Do it.
Just take it easy.
Now kick it over here.
Just... let her go and
you guys can leave, okay?
You don't need her.
JH: I might.
For... for leverage.
You don't want this
on your conscience.
I don't think I
got one of those.
Weddings are supposed to be fun!
[Rhodes screams]
- [slashing]
- [gurgling]
Oh my God.
Jesus Christ.
[JH thuds]
[panting]
I don't think I
meant to do that.
I don't think... I don't
think I meant to do that.
What the fuck?
♪ ["Atlantis" by
Donovan rising] ♪
♪ ...let us rejoice and
let us sing and dance ♪
♪ And ring in the new ♪
♪ Hail, Atlantis... ♪
♪ Way down below the ocean ♪
♪ Where I wanna be ♪
♪ She may be ♪
♪ Way down below the ocean ♪
♪ Where I wanna be ♪
♪ She may be ♪
♪ Way down below the ocean ♪
♪ Where I wanna be ♪
♪ She may be... ♪
[instrumental break]
♪ Way down below the ocean ♪
♪ Where I wanna be ♪
♪ She may be... ♪
♪ Way down below the ocean ♪
- ♪ Where I wanna be ♪
- ♪ She may be... ♪
So, hotshot. Should we
give this thing a try?
It'll never work out.
Why not?
I'm a married man.
- [Sofia exclaims]
- [Rhodes winces]
I'm so sorry.
Bell: Hey, I want you to
know that you were right.
I can't be doing this
anymore. It's too dangerous.
You think?
[Bell chuckles]
What are you going
to do for work?
Something that gets me
home to you in one piece.
You mean something that
doesn't get you stabbed
or shot in the head?
Or me covered in blood?
Yeah.
Dad, this is
freaking disgusting.
[laughs]
[car engine revs]
You know, I've never been
in a limousine before.
Drop us off at the Hilton where
we have the penthouse suite.
And in the morning... Maui.
[sighs] What a night.
What a night.
♪ ["Lean Into Life"
by Petey playing] ♪
♪ One night ♪
♪ I had a thought ♪
♪ What if we ordered
Anything we want ♪
♪ We quit our jobs
We went outside ♪
♪ No one could tell us
How to live our lives ♪
♪ One night, I took a drug ♪
♪ I gave three hundred
Uninvited hugs ♪
♪ You went to bed
I hit the floor ♪
♪ I don't think that we
should Get together anymore ♪
[instrumental break]
♪ One night Came and went ♪
♪ Spent lots of money,
It was money well spent ♪
♪ I took on some credit
card, Credit card debt ♪
♪ On a night that
didn't Mean nothing ♪
♪ A night I'll
probably forget ♪
♪ One night, I had a feeling ♪
♪ Bust through a wall
Cut through the ceiling ♪
♪ 27 Club and I'm still
Fucking breathing ♪
♪ I'm hyperventilating in
A building full of people ♪
[instrumental break]
♪ It's beginning
To feel like I've ♪
♪ Been training my
whole life For nothing ♪
♪ I've been meaning to
Tell you something ♪
♪ You gotta lean into
life Just a little ♪
♪ I think I'm breaking
My own heart ♪
♪ I think I'm making
My own self sick ♪
♪ At the thought
Of getting sick ♪
♪ I don't leave any more ♪
♪ Did I leave My
keys in the door? ♪
♪ It was so peaceful before ♪
♪ Come on buddy, you gotta
Lean into life a bit ♪
♪ You gotta callus
up Them hands ♪
♪ And get some dirt
Under them fingertips ♪
♪ I, ah, don't think it's skin
And papier-mâché ornaments ♪
♪ Another Christmas Eve And
you're still bumming out ♪
♪ About the same shit ♪
♪ Come on my friend ♪
♪ yeah You're really
going through it ♪
♪ You got all this free time, ♪
♪ No fucking idea
What to do with it ♪
♪ Sounds an awful lot to me ♪
♪ Like you like talking
About your bootstraps ♪
♪ Go to hell, I am the devil ♪
♪ Trying to claw
My way to heaven ♪
[instrumental break]
♪ I am regretful We
had our weekend ♪
♪ Filled with cocaine
And Essentia ♪
♪ It was fun and now I
can't really remember ♪
♪ And yeah we wonder why We
can't reach our potential ♪
♪ I am regretful Yeah my
head is in the gutter ♪
♪ Do we really need to
sin To love each other ♪
♪ Another psycho I'll get
Fucked up then recover ♪
♪ I just want to be A
better older brother ♪
♪ My head is in the gutter ♪
♪ It's beginning
to Feel like I've ♪
♪ Been training my
whole life For nothing ♪
♪ I've been meaning to
Tell you something ♪
♪ You gotta lean into
life, Just a little ♪
♪ I think I'm breaking
My own heart ♪
♪ I think I'm making
My own self sick ♪
♪ At the thought
Of getting sick ♪
♪ I don't leave any more ♪
♪ Did I leave my
keys In the door? ♪
♪ It was so peaceful before ♪
[song fades]