Stand aside. Let us pass.
Buntin, you landlord bastard!
Her beautiful eyes
were a terrible curse
Three days in his grave
She ran off with his purse
Lads, that bloody landlord
Buntin's on his way in.
All hell's breaking loose.
Buntin?
I hope they kill him.
Would you look at
that bastard, Joe?
Landlord!
You're a sinner!
Between your lungs, there's
neither heart nor spirit,
but the lump of your own
swollen money bag.
He'll never get over that one, Joe.
You're a blight on this country
that never belonged to you.
Out, you robber!
Joe, come on.
Are you hurt?
Take me home to my sons.
Back!
Stand still, you ugly animal.
Whoa, you ugly...
Damn you.
The hell with you.
Colm!
What?
Will you look at our little brother?
He can't keep hold of his ass.
Sweetheart of a child.
Slaving away.
Is it not enough, Joseph,
you plowed all
that muck down there?
My ambition's a little grander
than yours, a couple of lazy cows.
Ambition, is it? To break your
back on land that isn't your own?
It belongs to the
landlord Christie.
Hold your face up, lad.
Come on.
Give us something we can aim at.
Shag off, the pair of you.
There's a goat over there.
Go improve your love life.
Come on now, Joseph. Just a
nosebleed's all we're asking.
I've no wish to fight you.
Try pummelling me,
you arrogant son of a bitch.
Get him!
Watch him.
He's riled up now.
Hold still now.
Stand up, Joseph.
Lads, your father's been damaged.
You're here, Joe.
Da!
He took on the enemy
with his own bare hands.
Fifty of them.
Armed and with hideous guns.
Yeah, and your father,
he walloped them all.
One by one, the whole lot of them.
And I killed off a fair share
myself, to tell you the truth.
Quiet, Danty Duff, for once.
Humble as I am, I'll keep that part
of the story for another time.
How are you feeling now, Da?
My soul is departing
from me, Joseph.
Don't you talk that way.
I'll talk any way I please.
I'm dying, I tell you.
You can't die.
We need you here, Da.
Need me? What for?
Her beautiful eyes
were a terrible curse
Da?
God bless your soul.
Poor Joe Donnelly.
We'd be as well to sell off a thing
or two now that the old man's gone.
Is that any way to keen over
the death of our father?
Misery's a personal matter, Joseph.
We don't need any
instruction, thanks.
He's left us with a huge
debt of rent on the land.
We'll begin to settle our debts
when we harvest the land.
Grow the potatoes and pick them
yourself, Joseph, you ambitious boy.
You son of a...
Joseph!
Saints preserve us!
We thought you'd died, Da.
I did, son.
I passed away.
But you're talking to us, Da,
and your eyes are looking about.
I was as dead as a stone,
I tell you.
Now shut your mouth
before I die again.
Come here.
I've come back to
tell you something.
You're an especially odd boy.
You came back from the dead
to tell me that I'm odd?
You have all kinds of oddities
clattering around in your brain.
So had I when I was
as young as you.
But dreams, my boy, in this
poor corner of the world,
end up in a glass of ale.
Not my dreams.
I'll work my own land someday.
Without land a man is nothing.
Land is a man's very own soul.
Yeah.
A miracle, that's
what you're looking for.
And by God, if you manage it,
your old da will be smiling
down on you from heaven above.
Her beautiful eyes
God bless your soul, Joe Donnelly.
For the second time.
God rest your soul, Da.
Say nothing to them, lads.
This country's ours.
They don't exist.
What dead man is this?
You needn't answer,
but hear these words.
I represent Mr. Daniel Christie,
who by right of law owns this land
and all improvements upon it.
Rent on this property
has not been paid.
The warning's been given thrice.
Keep walking, lads. Our
father's being buried today.
Bastards are burning our house!
That will do.
Where is this landlord Christie?
I want justice for what he's done.
There's nothing I like better
than the glow of murder
in a young fella's eyes.
It has a terrible go of rust on it.
I've only killed
chickens and pigs till now.
He's a pig and a chicken all in
one, the same Daniel Christie.
Here now, give him
a proper taste of death.
Yeah, landlords!
Captain Moonlight.
Don't you be
pretending you know what
Captain Moonlight means,
'cause you don't.
It's the code, the rebel code.
Now you've heard it,
keep it to yourself.
Don't breathe it to a living
soul, you understand now?
Yeah. Yeah.
Captain Moonlight, Joseph.
Off to kill your landlord?
Blow the bastard's head off.
Don't be afraid to kill him.
Assassinate the bastard.
Joseph, it was too good
to be kept a secret, son.
Would you know which end of the gun
to point at the gentleman's ear?
He'll shoot himself in
the balls, I'll wager,
and come hobbling home in tears!
Goodbye, Colm.
Goodbye, Paddy.
Goodbye, Joseph.
We'll see you at your wake.
God bless all in this house.
God bless you, son.
Down from the north, are you?
Or perhaps the east?
West of here maybe?
South?
I prefer to keep my business
to myself, if you please.
Very wise, very wise, very wise.
God bless you, every one.
God bless you, sir.
Whiskey for everyone.
Great, great.
How are you, sir, tonight?
Oppressed.
That's the word for me.
I live in a house
that's stuffy and dull.
And worse, I've a wife
who forbids me to drink.
I crave adventure, boys.
If I had wings,
I'd fly to the stars.
Your good health, sir.
To your good health, sir.
To your health, Mr. Christie.
Liven up, lad.
You're too young to be
brooding in your ale.
What places you in this
small chapter of the world?
He's keeping himself
to himself, that one.
Then it's one of two things,
enterprise or love.
It isn't love,
rest assured of that.
Then you're a man of
business, like myself.
But I warn you,
it's brought me nothing but misery.
I'm lost in a fog
of commerce and compromise.
I'd trade it all away
for 15 minutes of freedom.
Freedom is a rare thing
in these parts.
It is.
It is, indeed.
Indeed, it is.
To a long and happy life,
Mr. Christie.
God bless you, lad.
Why should I expire?
For the fire of any eye
Though foolish men you slay
For thee I shall not die
Your beauty and your name
will never conquer me
What have I done?
Hello,
souls of the departed.
What a disappointment
I must seem to you all.
Here we are.
I recognize these hedges
by their dullness.
Oh, woman high of fame
Though men have died for thee
This is a difficult murder.
Good evening, Mr. Christie.
Take the horse.
Shannon, I saw you
galloping in the fields.
Dignity, Shannon. Dignity.
A lady must always be civilized
even when she rides.
No one saw me riding, Mother.
I saw you.
Yes, Mother.
"A lady must always be civilized."
She never leaves us alone,
does she?
No, she doesn't.
There, go on, good girl.
Somebody there?
Stay right where you are.
Don't flutter an eyelid
or I'll stab you.
I'll stab you through.
Father!
Jesus!
Father! Father!
Father, help! Help!
I've been all but raped
and slaughtered.
What is it?
In the stables.
What's all the fuss about?
It's the devil himself.
Mr. Daniel Christie.
Look!
Yes?
I'm Joseph Donnelly
of the family Donnelly
that you pushed off our land.
What in the name of God
are you talking about?
Prepare to pay for your crimes.
No!
Father!
Good Lord Jesus!
Captain Moonlight.
Shannon, come back.
Quickly! Find Mr. Chase
and bring him here. Go!
Shannon, come inside.
Shannon, turn around.
Look how black his
fingers are, Mother.
Never mind his fingers.
He's a lowborn blatherskite of filth.
If he's so worthless, then why are
you bothering to dress his wounds?
Our duty is to
restore him to full health
so he can hear his own neck crack
when he dangles from
the hangman's noose.
Turn away, Shannon, and protect
the innocence of your eyes.
Of all the days to intrude
upon our peaceful life.
The ladies are coming by
this afternoon for tea.
I'm feeling very sick
all of a sudden.
Mind yourself, Shannon,
those ladies are models
of manners and behavior.
Nothing happened.
Nothing happened, indeed.
A poor misguided robin
has broken a windowpane.
What a manufactured lie.
I was dusting the liquor cabinet.
As if a bottle in your vicinity
stood long enough to gather dust.
Go upstairs...
Mary, Mary, Mary Nell
Do you hear
your wedding bell?
Will he love you, Mary Nell?
Time and time alone will tell
You're having a dream. This
isn't really happening. No.
I want my land.
Whatever became of
the man I married?
Some other man's replaced him
and goes about with his name.
A murderous insurgent
under your own roof.
How horrible.
He's as ugly as sin and
the most vicious creature
I've ever set eyes upon.
Did you get a look at him, Shannon?
A peek.
Shannon, what is your collar doing?
It's choking me.
Well, do it up. Better to
choke than to be vulgar.
I hear a noise.
Let us hope it is Stephen Chase.
We've come for your
prisoner, Mr. Christie.
Good afternoon, Mrs. Christie.
Good afternoon, ladies.
Speak of the sun
and we see its rays.
Oh, my goodness,
we were so frightened.
Now, now, keep calm.
You're safe and protected.
Go back to your
sinful card playing.
Hello, Shannon.
Hello, Stephen.
My, how handsome he is.
He's a brilliant young man.
He was educated at Trinity.
Of course!
He manages all my husband's
business affairs.
Your daughter's
certainly a very lucky girl.
Yes, indeed.
Shannon, the ladies and I would
like you to play the piano.
No.
I beg your pardon?
Come play something, Shannon.
Something fanciful and nice.
She plays beautifully.
Shannon, good gracious, child.
It's band music, Mother.
Band music?
It's very modern.
It's from America.
Shannon, stay back.
Careful, boy, your life's
worth little as it is.
You're the bastard
that burned my father's house.
I've burned many houses in the line
of duty. Am I meant to remember yours?
Maybe you'll remember this.
Pistols, tomorrow at dawn.
Get him upstairs.
Go on!
Come, ladies. Let us resume our
pleasantries in the parlor.
Come here.
You, too, Shannon.
What's buzzing around inside that
head of yours, my little monkey?
The day's been disrupted, Father.
Heaven forbid.
I'm running away.
Excuse me.
There's something in here I need.
Perhaps you're wondering
why I'm running away.
I'll tell you.
I'm running away
because I'm modern.
I'm modern and I'm
going to a modern place.
You're not the only
one who's trapped.
If I stay here, my mother will turn me
into one of her stuffy old friends.
No, thank you. I'm a little
more interesting than that.
I'm very smart and very modern.
That's all you
need to know about me.
Boy, here.
Have a look at this.
Look!
You can't read, can you?
How pathetic.
"Land," it says.
Land?
"Wanted, strong,
healthy men and women.
"Every resident of
the United States
"is entitled to 160 acres of land."
They've got so much of it,
they give it away for free.
Noland is given away
in any part of the world.
In America it is,
and I'm going there.
I'm going to have
a place of my own.
I'll have horses on it
and I'll raise them,
and I will ride
them any way I please.
What do you need more land for?
You own half of Ireland as it is.
They took it, your people did.
I didn't take it.
You just live here
all fancied up on rent
and broken backs.
Boy, you said you wanted land.
If that's what you want,
then come with me.
Great ships sail out
of Dublin and Liverpool,
but a woman dare
not travel alone. No.
You're brave. You shoot men.
You step on their necks.
When I saw that, I realized you
could be very useful to me.
Useful, could I?
Yes.
You could be my serving boy.
I see.
I see, I could
polish your boots for you.
They will need
a polish now and then.
Aye.
Aye, they would, and I could
make you a cup of tea.
When teatime calls for it.
Yes.
I'll throw the tea in your
face and piss on your boots
before I serve the likes of you.
Get out.
No.
I'll pay you threepence a day.
Get out!
I've an appointment in the morning
and I'm going to honor it.
You'll never win
this duel with Stephen.
We've all seen you handle a gun.
Boy, I am giving you your freedom.
I'm not going to a distant world.
I'm of Ireland and I'll
stay in Ireland till I die.
That's in about five hours.
These weapons belonged
to my father's father.
His father's father was an ass.
I've asked to serve as your
second in this barbarism.
I appreciate that, sir.
Choose one of those things.
You had a good breakfast
this morning, did you?
It was grand, sir.
Thank you.
Good, good.
Count away, 15 paces.
One, two...
This way, son.
Fog! My life is one
long mollifying fog.
The land I hold I inherited.
It manages itself
with a foggy logic of its own.
Son, I was up thinking
about you all night long.
I knew nothing of your family
or their eviction.
I'm sorry for their pain.
I understand why
you came to murder me.
Thirteen...
And I don't blame you
for it at all.
Fourteen...
Fifteen!
Turn, each man, and fire!
I can't see anything!
I can!
Boy, boy, come away from there.
Shannon, get out of the way.
Assess your stupidity, lad.
Get away from me, woman.
As you wish.
Wait!
Shannon!
Shannon, don't!
Goodbye, Stephen!
Goodbye?
Don't shoot!
No! No! No!
Shannon!
Shannon! Don't!
No!
I saved your neck.
You remember that.
Thank you, boy.
Don't call me boy.
Sugar.
Two.
You might display some gratitude
considering the price I paid
for your passage.
I paid, let me remind you.
Good afternoon.
Forgive me if I'm intruding.
But I wonder if you'd enjoy a
gentle stroll around the deck.
She's drinking her tea now.
There's no need to
state the obvious, boy.
My name's McGuire
from Boston, Massachusetts.
You're American?
Irish-born, I went back
for personal reasons.
A stroll would be delightful,
Mr. McGuire.
Parasol.
In my imagination, America is
a wonderfully modern place.
Am I right?
Modern as modern can be.
The people, the
culture, the industry.
What about the land?
I beg your pardon?
Land. This girl's
got it in her head
they're giving land away for free.
That's true. Oklahoma territory.
The West's opening up.
I told you, boy.
Can't be good land.
It's the finest in the world.
Seeds flourish in it.
The cattle that grow upon it
are fat as elephants.
How do you get it, Mr. McGuire?
Is it there when
you step off the boat?
No. You have to
travel 1,000 miles or so.
When you get there, you'll have
to run for the land in a race.
A race?
Don't lose time in Boston.
As soon as you can, purchase
horses, a wagon and supplies.
Have I upset you?
I didn't expect it
to be so complicated.
We're very fortunate. Any difficulty
can be overcome with money.
Excuse me, I'd like to speak
to Mr. McGuire alone.
Mr. McGuire, I do have money,
but it's in the form of spoons.
Spoons?
Ancient spoons made of silver.
I'd planned to sell them
when I arrived in Boston.
I can recommend a couple of shops
that'll treat you honestly.
I'm very much obliged to you, sir.
Pleasure's mine.
Thank you.
May I ask what you are doing
sitting at my table?
I'm eating your chocolate cake.
I see. And what have you done
with my father's necktie?
I flung it into the sea.
It was gagging my throat.
You're just upset
because everything
I told you about is
turning out to be true.
"Cows as fat as elephants."
I know what that man's after.
I think you should
cover your ankles.
America.
I'm here, I've made it.
I've arrived, Joseph.
Beg your pardon.
United States of America flag.
You're an American today.
Your great friend,
Mr. McGuire, has vanished.
for one American dollar?
There he is!
Mr. McGuire!
Over here!
There you are.
Hey, mister, you Irish?
I can take you to the ward boss.
Need work? Need lodging? There's
people that hate you if you're Irish.
You can't get nothing
without the ward boss.
He's the biggest man in Boston.
Go fleece somebody else, boy.
I know the games of these shysters.
Come on, Miss Christie.
I'll find you a suitable hotel.
Cab!
Thank goodness for Mr. McGuire.
Take Miss Christie
here to a decent hotel.
Well, you've certainly upheld
your end of the bargain.
Good luck, Shannon.
Good luck, Joseph.
Hey, McGuire.
Yes?
Welcome back.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! My spoons, my spoons.
They're taking my spoons.
Joseph, Mr. McGuire
stole my spoons.
No, please! Those are mine.
He stole them from me.
Joseph! Please. Joseph, that
dead man, he stole my spoons.
My bag.
They're taking everything.
Now I have nothing.
Come away, Shannon, we have to go.
I have nothing now.
I have no money.
God is punishing me, Joseph.
I stole those spoons from my
mother the morning I ran away.
Hey, you!
You! Stand still!
I didn't do nothing.
Who's this man, the ward boss?
That's him there,
fighting in the fancy clothes.
Mike Kelly, his name is.
Shannon, you should
stand back over there.
Don't shield me, Joseph.
It's only a boxing match.
What?
I'm sorry, Mike.
Mike isn't happy when he loses.
You distracted me.
You weren't concentrating.
A scrappy Connemara man?
Fresh off the boat?
Follow me.
Not you, woman.
You just cost me part of a tooth.
If he gets to go, then I get to go.
I'm Mike Kelly.
Who is this bit of a
snip anyway, your wife?
Certainly not.
Then who are you
coming into my club?
She's...
I'm...
My sister.
Tell me she isn't
a pain in the ass.
Sister? Our blood's not even
the same temperature.
Shannon.
These people, Shannon,
are my kind of people.
And my kind doesn't like your kind.
In fact, they hate
everything about you.
Now, for some reason or other,
I'm willing to lie for you.
Or we could tell them you're a
rich Protestant. Might be sporting.
No, Joseph.
My brother.
Good.
What do you call yourself?
Joseph Donnelly.
Well, Donnelly, let's put you
on the road to citizenship.
We'll get you working and get
you voting when the time comes.
See how the system works here, lad?
Yeah.
Stop it.
Don't.
Leave me alone.
Get away or I'll claw your eyes out.
Don't. No.
I said, leave me alone.
Excuse me, Mr. Kelly.
Leave me alone.
I won't ask you again.
No. Get away!
I'll ask you to
leave this lady alone.
Go ahead and ask.
I've no wish to fight you.
He's no wish to fight me...
All right, hold him.
No, he's mine.
He's mine alone.
Get him, Joseph!
Okay, okay.
Well, now.
You knocked the piss out of the man
who knocked the piss out of me.
I'm not sure how I feel about that.
Dermody.
Yes, sir, Mr. Kelly.
Time to make the rounds. We'll take
this scrapper and the girl here
and lodge them at Molly Kay's.
Grab the luggage.
Yes, sir.
Come on.
Pete, get a match going these
fellas can bet on, will you? I'll be back.
Hey, Mike, what the hell you doing?
All depends.
Good to see you, lads.
This is it, here we are.
Good day to you, Mr. Kelly.
How are you, man?
Molly!
It's just as unpleasant
for me as it is for you.
Got a brother and sister,
Molly, need a room.
You're in luck. We had a
suicide just this morning.
How are you, Bridget?
Hello, Mike.
Any gentlemen up here, girls?
No.
Make an announcement, Dermody.
Ward boss!
I give you another year.
You're not campaigning, Mike.
Relax, Molly. Politics is more
important to these men than sex.
And I'm the Virgin Mary.
God forgive you, Molly.
Not likely, Mike.
Come on.
Is that Jimmy Dunne, I see? I was
chatting with your wife today, Jimmy.
Don't tell me wife, Mike.
And here is the bath, but
don't linger in it too long.
It's the only one in the house.
This is your room here.
Ours?
You're not suggesting
that we share this room?
I don't care what you do in it
as long as you pay me $1 a week.
There must be some mistake.
We need two rooms.
I've only got the one.
Well, that's not good enough.
Mike, what have you sent me?
You're not listening!
Shannon! Molly, the room is fine.
We'll take it gratefully.
Your sister was spoilt, I'd say.
Shannon?
Shannon, are you awake?
No, sound asleep.
I think I like America.
Do you now?
Aye.
We've only been here a day.
Look at the welcome we've got.
Would you like a room?
Here you go.
Would you like a job?
Why, here you go.
How about some land?
Well, get a horse and help yourself.
So, now you believe me
about the land, do you?
If they're throwing it away,
I wouldn't mind a piece of it.
Maybe this is my destiny.
On his deathbed, my father told me
he'd be watching me from up above.
I wonder now if his spirit might
be near, guiding me along.
If he bumps into
Mr. McGuire up there,
tell him I want my spoons back.
Imagine me,
Joseph Donnelly, standing
on my own plot of land.
What would I plant, I wonder, what?
Oats? Corn?
Potatoes?
God, no, not potatoes.
Maybe wheat.
Wheat.
Shannon, I'm dreaming of it now.
Great fields of wheat
as far as the eye can see.
Oklahoma land was my idea,
you blathering fool!
"Maybe this is my destiny."
If it weren't for me, farm boy,
you wouldn't even be here.
If it weren't for me, Miss High and
Mighty, you'd have died in the street!
Give me back my pillow.
Not in 100 years.
This book is irritating me.
Do you actually think
you're fooling me, Daniel?
Would you prefer I proclaim my
independence and drink in the open?
No.
I like the system we've got.
How can she be so cruel?
Not to send us any word.
She's in America, Nora.
She's been writing to me
for some time now.
You hid these from me?
At Shannon's request.
Read them now,
though they may not
bring you comfort.
Nora!
Death to the landlord.
Burn the house to the ground.
Burn it down.
Captain Moonlight.
Get out of the house, Nora!
The letters.
Leave the letters alone, Nora.
My baby!
Come with me.
Stephen, we're over here.
Quickly, come this way.
All of your life
collected and destroyed.
I'm truly sorry for your loss.
Does this mean we're finished?
Are we impoverished now?
No, sir.
You still have your land
and your holdings.
This is no longer
the Ireland of my birth.
Our daughter's fallen into perilous
ruin, Daniel. We must go to her now.
Shannon?
She's been in Boston
these many months.
Then we shall find her there.
You over there, keep working.
You don't work, you don't get paid.
Get those chickens plucked.
Get to work.
I think the prettiest
girl in this factory
with the prettiest eyes and the
prettiest red hair is Joseph's sister.
If you don't mind
me saying so, Joseph.
Say what you like, lad.
But I warn you, that redhead
has a bite that stings.
Get to work.
Get your filthy hands
off me, you ugly animal.
That'll cost you a day's wage.
Go ahead.
Insult me again.
Pig.
There goes tomorrow.
Done?
Take Friday as well, you spineless
little fraction of a man.
Bite, lads. Bite!
What are you looking at?
I'm just trying to figure out
what you're doing there.
It's obvious what I'm doing,
I'm cleaning my clothes.
I see.
Do you ever wonder why it
takes you so long, Shannon?
My clothes, if you notice,
if you look about,
are washed and hung.
Done.
Your talent astounds me, Joseph.
Move over.
If you want to clean your clothes,
you have to get your hands wet.
First, you place the board like so.
You take the soap in your right
hand, the clothes in the left.
You brush the soap across
the clothes twice. Like so.
Then you plunge and scrub.
You plunge and scrub.
Plunge and scrub
and plunge and scrub.
And plunge and scrub and lift.
And if it's still not clean,
then you go again.
You plunge and scrub.
You keep plunging and scrubbing
till all your plunging
and scrubbing is done.
Thirty, 40, 45, 50.
You could be a banker, Joseph,
with your ability to count.
A compliment.
Thank you, Shannon.
Don't suppose you've calculated
what the journey will cost.
If I barter, I can get a
buckboard for under $25.
It's the harness that's costly.
Bit, frame...
Frame, collar, reins.
Very impressive.
How much have you saved, Shannon?
Are you still praying you'll make
it to the Oklahoma land race?
I'll get there.
What a corker.
You're a corker, Shannon.
Why don't you go back to Ireland?
Write your parents for money.
They'll forgive you
for your petty foolishness.
America may not be exactly
what I thought it would be.
But if I went back
to Ireland, I wouldn't...
What?
Wouldn't what?
I said I'll get there and
I'll get there. By myself.
You'll need supplies.
Of course.
Food, clothes.
Ammunition, gun.
Whenever I think of guns,
I remember Stephen Chase.
You're lucky to be rid
of that piss-headed snob.
He wasn't so bad, Joseph.
You didn't know him as well as I did.
I knew him well enough.
Me, he adored.
He worshiped me.
There wasn't a puddle of mud
he didn't lay his coat upon
for me to walk across.
Are you facing east?
I'm facing east.
All right.
Almost ready.
Thanks be to Jesus.
Light!
I'm in.
Good night, Shannon.
Joseph?
What?
Am I beautiful at all?
I've never seen anything like
you in all my living life.
Good.
Let's have another boxing
match. We need another challenger.
This man has not
been defeated tonight.
Will anyone box him?
Any challengers? You, sir, you can
beat him. You got the face of a winner.
I'll fight him!
Joseph!
No! No. Joseph,
there's rules in this club.
Toe the line and all that. You got
to wait till I signal, Joseph.
Toe the line, gentlemen!
No kicking, no biting, no gouging!
You're facing the wrong way!
Fight me here, farmer!
Your foot on the line.
Right.
Toe the line. Toe the line.
Get away.
Come on, you're yella!
Come on!
Come on, scrapper.
Stop it.
You won, Joseph. Stop it.
What a fight.
I knew you had it in you.
Girls, next up, the burleycue.
What do you call yourself again?
Joseph Donnelly.
That's right. Joseph Donnelly. You
clobbered that fella's brains out.
I discovered this fella,
fresh off the boat.
Gordon, get this scrapper
something to smoke.
Who's your boy there, Kelly?
A new-fangled style
of fighting he's got.
He's slippery, all right.
Joseph, shake hands with Mr. D'Arcy
Bourke, member of the City Council.
I'll shake your hand, Mr. Bourke,
but I'm not in a friendly mood.
I came here to fight.
There's fight left in me yet.
He's a lively one, Kelly.
Would you box an Italian
if I scared one up?
I'll box any man
you put in front of me.
Mike, Mike, Mike!
Jesus Christ, Dermody, when's
your voice gonna change?
We've got another pug, Mike.
Bring him on.
And I'll put money on you.
Place your bets, gentlemen.
The boy's got an appetite, Kelly.
Toe the line, gentlemen.
Joseph.
It's nothing.
I'm feeling grand tonight.
Steady now, you rogue.
Joseph.
Oh, my God, what happened?
Help me get him into bed.
Joseph, you're covered in blood.
What happened to you?
He's been prizefighting,
but he'll survive.
He had a charge of gunpowder
in him that needed to go off.
And who might you be?
I'm Grace.
I work at the Social Club.
I did well tonight, didn't I?
You beat them all, Joseph.
But don't talk now.
Get some sleep.
I need to talk to you.
You're his sister, right?
What sort of man is he? Besides
tough and handsome as a devil.
He's extremely moody.
I believe that. Full of spit, isn't he?
And passion?
No, not really, no.
He's fairly dull.
Dull? I don't know what
sort of men you're used to,
but he's anything but dull.
And the build on him.
Me and the girls got swollen
eyes from gawking at his bum.
Goodbye, Grace.
Would you tell him I...
Nice to meet you.
I just want...
Good night, Grace.
That was Grace.
So she said.
She dances in the burleycue.
Yes, well, never mind her now.
Just lay there.
No, Joseph, lie still.
Lie still.
Look in my boot down there.
$4. That's more than plucking
chickens in a month.
I'll have my horse-and-buggy
money before the winter comes,
and it won't be
from plucking chickens.
There are other ways to
get to Oklahoma, Joseph.
You should have heard them,
Shannon, cheering me on.
It was grand.
Toe the line, gentlemen.
Too slow.
You come to the body,
you come to the face.
And you move out of the way.
When he's coming around,
you get out of the way.
They just stand there,
look at them.
Come on! Come on!
Come on now!
Hello there, Joseph.
Hello, Cara.
All done up like a gentleman.
How do you do, ladies?
Shannon.
Joseph.
He's a handsome catch,
that Joseph Donnelly is.
If he can keep his
knuckles up all night,
imagine what his willie can do.
Shoes, secondhand shoes, madam.
Would you look at that!
Look at the sleeves
all billowed out.
From Paris, France, it says.
So beautiful and modern.
Excuse me!
Well, excuse me.
Even her poodle's putting on airs.
Look, Shannon,
there's your famous brother.
Good grief, he's bought
himself another hat.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Bye, Olive.
Hello, Shannon.
Hello, Joseph.
What do you think?
Do you like it?
Like my hat?
No. Not at all.
I'll get some other opinions.
Do you like my hat?
It's a fine hat, Mr. Donnelly,
and a fine fight
last night as well.
Glad you enjoyed it, Connor.
So I left her there
pulling up her knickers.
Hold on a second.
Here he comes.
There's my boy,
looking fit and dandy.
How are you, scrapper?
Never better, Mike.
Hello, lads.
Mr. Bourke would
like a word with you.
Joseph Donnelly, still undefeated.
He's a rascal of a holy terror.
That he is.
That's a long-legged
piece of strawberry tart.
Mind your mouth, Mr. Bourke.
Now, Donnelly, you don't
talk to Mr. Bourke that way.
Let it go, Kelly.
This is business and the
boy's our stock in trade.
Now, listen to me, lad. There's
a man I want you to box.
He's a goddamn Italian and I
want you to spill his blood.
I'll box and I'll win.
But your boys don't
own me, Mr. Bourke.
I box for myself, alone.
What do you think you're doing
pissing against the wind?
D'Arcy Bourke is a
powerful man in Boston,
a man whose connections I need.
I'm not gonna kiss
the back of his trousers
just 'cause the rest of you do.
You like your suit?
Well, do you?
You like having
a roof over your head?
I'm your bread and butter, lad.
Cross me and you're nothing,
nothing but an ignorant mick.
You do what you're told or I'll
throw you out in the street,
and every door you knock on
will be slammed in your face.
Do you understand?
Aye.
Good.
It's gonna be a grand
fight, Mr. Bourke.
Good, that's what I like to hear.
Shannon?
I'm drunk, Joseph.
How can you be drunk?
You just left my sight.
She's working her way
through a jigger of rye.
When I finish it, I may or
may not have another one.
Well, Shannon, you came
to America to be modern.
I'm glad everything's working out.
You have changed, Mr. Donnelly.
Improved, you mean.
Nope. Changed.
Look at all those silly hats.
You'll never get to Oklahoma.
You've spent all your money.
At the rate I'm going,
they'll bring the land to me.
You have turned into a snob.
Joseph?
Joseph!
Excuse me, drunkard.
Hello, Grace.
Hello, Joseph, will I be seeing
you in church tomorrow morn?
Sounds divine and holy, Grace.
We can share a pew, me and you.
Toodle-oo.
Same to you.
She's got an awfully large
chest to be going to church.
Shannon, all chests are equal
in the eyes of the Lord.
She goes into the confession box,
she'll never come out,
the little tramp.
Grace isn't a tramp. She's
a dancer in the burleycue.
That isn't dancing. That's
kicking her knickers up.
I suspect if you asked her to,
she'd kick her knickers off.
Maybe she would.
Has she?
Let me see.
I'm trying to remember.
Think hard. If there's any
brain left in your head.
Look at you. They're making a fool of
you, the ward boss and his friends.
They respect me.
They do not.
They don't respect you.
Enough.
You're money in their pockets
and nothing more, Joseph.
I said that's enough, Shannon.
You let them pickle you
like a piece of pork.
They're just using you.
I said, that's enough out of you.
No, put me down!
No! No!
Tell me.
Tell me you like my hat.
You're not wearing a hat.
Say it. Say you like my hat.
Say it.
Why can't you say it, Shannon?
Why can't you say you like my hat?
Why can't you say you like my suit?
I've earned this.
I've done well.
Don't touch me, Joseph.
Why don't you go fondle that
slut with the runaway tits,
if she isn't stuffing
her face with pie.
You're jealous of me. I made more
money than you and you're jealous.
I can make money as fast as you can.
You just watch me, scrapper.
Shannon?
Shannon!
Why don't you shag her
and get it over with?
She's my sister.
And I'm your mother.
Joseph!
Every time your gentleman leaves,
I want you to tidy your room,
do you hear me?
Molly?
I don't want to
have to say that again.
Joseph, Mike Kelly's
looking for you.
Molly, where's Shannon?
Tonight's the fight, the big fight.
She didn't come home
from work today.
The club is crawling with eyeties.
Molly, have you seen her?
No, I have not.
She's there.
Shannon is there.
Where?
Joseph,
show them how it's done, lad.
Joseph, for Ireland!
Shannon, stop this.
Where's your dignity, woman?
You mind your business, Joseph.
You get your brains smashed in
every night. What's the difference?
There's a world of difference!
Come on, Donnelly, these eyeties
are tearing the place apart.
Forget it!
Get in there and box. I've
got $100 bet on you tonight.
Kiss it goodbye, Mr. Bourke.
I'll make it $200, and I'll
split the winnings with you.
$200,Joseph!
What?
Did you not hear me? I said I'll
split the winnings with you!
No.
Joseph.
Donnelly!
Take it.
Take it?
I thought you
didn't want me to fight.
But it's so much money.
You boxed for nickels before.
This is a fortune.
Joseph! Joseph!
I'll match that offer.
Don't let your stubborn
pride get in the way.
You'll have it.
You'll have Oklahoma!
You'll never have to
fight for them again.
This'll get us out of here.
Us?
Well, you.
I mean you.
Come on, let's show them.
Joseph, damage the dago.
You hear me?
Keep back, will you?
Get back, come on.
Come on, lad.
This is a fight to the finish,
gentlemen. A fight to the finish.
Side betting's allowed and a
knockdown terminates a round.
Come to scratch, gentlemen.
Come on, scrapper!
Keep your left up.
Yes! Go!
Joseph!
Kelly, I smell victory.
I'd enjoy it even more
with a little strawberry tart.
Mr. Bourke would like some company.
I'm not especially
attracted to Mr. Bourke.
You came to me for help.
Let's show some manners.
Come to scratch!
What the hell's he doing, Kelly?
Get your hands off her.
There's too much
money at stake here.
Filthy pig.
Joseph! No!
Get back to scratch!
You wanna forfeit?
Shannon?
Put him down!
Shannon!
Joseph!
You're losing me money, you coward!
Get back in there and fight.
You're gonna forfeit.
Move over.
Go on, Joe, get up, Joe.
Joseph!
No.
Get up, Joseph.
Get up.
Come on, get up. Get up!
I bet more money than you've got.
Get up!
He's out.
Joseph.
My God, I'm sorry.
You, get off. Shut your mouth.
Get this loser out of my club.
Did you tell them we're in
Jefferson Court? Number 6 Jefferson Court.
Make sure they hear you.
In the south end.
Her family has come from Ireland.
They're here in Boston.
They're offering a reward.
Have you seen a girl like that?
Find her.
Do your job.
Must I do everything for you?
We found her, and here
she is right over here.
We'll never get anything out of
these people. They're drunks.
If you see the girl, her
family is in Jefferson Court.
Number 6 Jefferson Court.
Joseph, what happened to you?
Shannon?
Shannon.
Do come in, scrapper.
That's our money.
We earned it.
There isn't a penny here
doesn't originate with me.
Get him out.
Don't touch her.
You're done, scrapper.
You won't work here,
box here, nothing here.
You coppers, beat it.
Get him up.
Too bad, but I saw it coming the first
time you walked in off the boat.
No. Leave him.
No!
Leave...
Molly Kay, these two are banished.
You shelter them even a night,
I'll shut this whorehouse down.
Come on.
It's too cold, Joseph.
Hey!
Do you need help, sir?
Get out of here.
We haven't eaten for three days.
I'll work for food.
I don't hire Irish.
For the love of God, we
haven't eaten for three days.
I said I don't hire Irish.
Now, get out of here.
Joseph, we can't keep
wandering like this.
I know.
It's been so long, too many days.
We can't keep doing this.
I think this house is empty.
Look.
A tree.
Food.
There's food here.
Joseph, look at us.
I never thought it
would turn out like this.
Coming all this way for land.
Shannon.
Sit down.
Sit down at this beautiful table.
No, we can't. We're burglars.
Please? Please.
I want you to pretend.
Sit down.
I'll serve you.
Tonight, I want you to dine.
No, Joseph, don't serve me.
Just sit down.
Sit down with me.
Let's pretend
that this house is ours.
That you are my husband
and I'm your wife.
Sit down.
Joseph, did you ever wonder what that
land you dreamed of looked like?
Aye.
Mine was a green pasture with tall
grass that rolled just a little bit.
Mine had a stream
running through it.
Perhaps some trees.
Rich, dark soil.
No rocks to pick out of the ground.
A green pasture and a stream.
They will complement
each other, no?
They would.
The one, in fact,
depends upon the other.
Pretend
you love me.
I pretend I love you.
I pretend I love you, too.
What was that?
Who's there?
Get the hell out of my house.
No!
Shannon.
Police. Police!
Get the police!
Help!
Help! This girl needs help.
Will you let us in?
Is this the Christie's?
Shannon.
Just let us in.
Quickly, fetch a doctor.
Yes, sir.
Step aside. You'll infect
her with your filthy hands.
What did you expect? That you
could climb to her station?
A gunshot.
God, look at her.
Will she be all right?
She will now.
The wound is in the shoulder.
I have to clean it.
Shannon, I...
You're safe now.
This house.
You're gonna be fine.
Take care of her.
Mr. Christie, Mr. Christie,
here's the doctor.
Something terrible has happened.
What is it, Doctor?
Your daughter, Mr. Christie.
Shannon?
She's here?
What's happened to her?
She's all clear! Let's get
the mud cleaned out here.
Hey, Mick, after you drop that tie
off, let's get after these rocks!
Come on. Let's get some
goddamn work done here.
Fill up that wheelbarrow!
Move it.
Fire in the hole.
Come on, boys, find yourself some cover.
We got fire in the hole.
Hey, you, fire in the hole!
Joseph.
Water!
Anybody need water?
Water?
Look at that. All them wagons
headed for the Oklahoma territory.
I'd be going with them
if I was as young as you.
Doesn't interest me.
I had a woman once.
But she don't want me
'cause I had no money.
That's America. Unless you
are rich, you are nobody.
I should never have
come to this place.
Forget the women, boys. You got
a job of work ahead of you.
Da, is that you?
Joseph!
You look like you're not
doing too well, my boy.
I missed you, Da.
"A man is nothing
without land, " they say.
Land is a man's own soul.
I'll work my own land someday.
If you manage it, by God,
your old da will be smiling down
on you from heaven above.
Stay where you are, boys.
We're just stopping for water.
Look, it's the pioneers.
No, they go to Oklahoma,
I think, for the free land.
They just wasting time. There
ain't enough land to go around.
One in 100 will stake a claim.
The rest of them,
they just dreaming.
Think they gonna
get some free land.
Hey, Irish!
Mick, where do you
think you're going?
I was on the wrong road.
There now!
Coming through!
Farmers, ranchers, homesteaders,
this well driller is an example of
modern American industry
at its finest.
Come up and have a look.
It's not gonna bite you,
it's just modern, that's all.
You may find land tomorrow,
but you won't survive in the
wilderness, not without water.
Folks, each quarter
section is marked.
You run for land, remove the marker
and drive in your own stake.
The race begins tomorrow at noon.
Again, each quarter
section is marked.
Where can I get a horse?
You're a little late, cowboy.
The pickings are slim.
Now, this here horse is broke.
That horse there, green broke.
Know the difference?
I think I can see it.
A broke horse is
a dependable horse.
A green broke horse, he's faster.
That sounds good.
The faster the better.
No telling what he'll do, though.
Hell, you could end up in Canada
on that green-broke son of a bitch.
Stand back.
I think I'll take
the dependable horse.
I would.
You go out there and get you
a good piece of land
tomorrow, now, Joseph.
Thank you, Ralph.
I'm cursed.
Oh, Lord, I'm cursed.
Mother, the clothes
will never come clean
if you don't get your hands wet.
There's no order in
this godforsaken place.
Here, take the soap
and you plunge and scrub.
Plunge and scrub?
Like so.
Nora? Nora! Nora!
I've been shot.
Shot?
Well, shot at anyway.
By the cavalry.
We crossed the starting line
and we broke the law.
Daniel Christie, I will not
have you riding tomorrow
in that vulgarity of a race!
The Wild West suits me, Nora.
There's no telling what I might do.
Shannon!
Shannon, I found it.
Twenty miles straight west of here.
It's paradise itself.
You will love it, Shannon. The
earth is dry and dusty here.
But where we'll live,
there's a winding stream,
and the grass on the gentle hills around
it grows high and rich and green.
It's the plot of land
you've dreamed of.
Excuse me, Stephen.
Are you cross with me, Shannon?
Of course I am. We were doing
this together, I thought.
I couldn't take you with me today.
It was too dangerous.
I don't mind a little
danger now and then.
Shannon, stop this childishness.
Are we not here,
your parents and I,
amongst all these people
because you wanted this?
Tomorrow we'll ride as one,
together, side by side.
We'll claim our land and then we'll
marry and finally settle down.
You do want to settle down,
don't you, Shannon?
Yes.
Yes, I want to settle down.
There now.
That's better.
I hate to see you angry.
It isn't your nature to be so.
Hello, Shannon.
I wondered if I'd see you here.
I suspected that I might.
Not I. I saw you living back
in Boston all this while.
You look well.
I'm here with my family.
We came by train.
I came by train myself.
You'll be running in the
race tomorrow, I presume.
I always said I'd get my land.
I even bought a horse,
a fine horse.
Well.
Time takes care of everything,
doesn't it, Joseph?
Everything's worked out
as it should have,
don't you agree?
Yeah.
Good luck tomorrow, Joseph.
Aye.
Best of luck to you, Shannon.
Shannon Christie?
You never gave up.
You knew what you
wanted back in Ireland.
And look at you.
Here you are.
You're a corker, Shannon.
What a corker you are.
Beautiful country, isn't it, boy?
I found the perfect piece
of land for Shannon and me,
almost the picture of what she
described. The land of her dreams.
Congratulations.
Just what the hell
are you doing here?
You bring her to me bleeding, and
now you think you can talk to her?
Stay away from her, do you hear me?
There'll be a lot of confusion
in the race tomorrow, lad.
Someone could get shot.
Her beautiful eyes
Were a terrible curse
Three days in his grave
She ran off with his purse
They've got their land
all picked out,
the pair of them.
The land of her dreams.
All those months I was
trying to forget about her.
I was laying down the very
track that brought her here.
And to hell with everyone.
I'm gonna get my land.
That's my thought for the night.
Tomorrow I ride for me, me alone.
And my horse.
Sweet Mary Jesus
and all the saints preserve us.
That there was the oldest
horse lever saw in my life.
It's almost noon. We're
gonna miss the photograph.
All right.
You ready?
Stay with him, Joseph!
I sold him that horse.
Don't let him bluff you, cowboy!
We're breaking the law, Nora.
I don't like you taking charge of
the business side of our life.
You do, too.
Now listen up.
This stake goes into
the ground over there.
That's your job.
I'll tell you when.
I, meanwhile, will run the
horse around in circles.
He's got to look all sweaty and
tired, even dead would be good.
Got it?
Yes.
But we don't
really need all of this.
It's scary out here, Daniel.
We'll do fine.
Pretend we're starting out in
life instead of ending up.
You want to buy
a good pair of spurs?
Sorry.
The race is that way, lad.
Forget the horse, lad,
and find yourself a donkey.
Joseph?
Take him by the bit.
Shannon?
Hey, where the hell are you going?
Shoot him!
Fire!
That way!
I've no wish to fight you.
Go! Go!
Lord, protect us.
Daniel, here they come.
Stand by, partner, and pretend
you're out of breath.
Pretend? My heart's
up here in my nose!
Oh, my God, Nora!
This is thrilling.
Nora? Now, Nora! Now!
There it is.
Come on.
Come on, Shannon. Hurry.
Come on!
Stephen! Stephen!
Shannon, getup.
Grab the reins.
Are you all right, Shannon?
Are you all right?
Go, Joseph. Go!
Ride.
Go get your land.
You're not in Ireland anymore,
you arrogant bastard!
Damn it, Shannon. Do you
want your land or don't you?
This land is mine.
Mine by destiny.
Go ahead, Joseph!
Claim it!
Shannon!
Claim it?
Stephen!
Look out, Joseph!
No! Joseph!
Oh, my God! Joseph!
Joseph!
Shannon?
Joseph.
Don't touch him.
Get away, Stephen.
Shannon, listen to me.
Shannon...
Leave!
Joseph? Joseph.
Joseph, look at me.
Look at me.
No, don't move.
Stay still.
Shannon.
Don't do this.
You've made your choice.
Joseph, look at me.
Look at me.
I feel myself dying.
No. No, you stay looking at my eyes.
Look at my eyes, Joseph.
Shannon?
No, you're not dying.
Look!
You've got your land.
But all the land in the world
means nothing to me without you.
Joseph...
I tried to prove myself to you,
but I know nothing
of books or alphabets
or sun or moon or...
All I know
is Joseph loves Shannon.
That's all that matters to me.
Hey, Shannon.
Joseph, Joseph, no.
Shannon.
No, no, stay with me.
Stay.
Joseph, no!
No. Joseph, look at me. Joseph!
Joseph, please.
Please don't leave me.
Please don't leave me alone.
Joseph, Joseph, no!
Joseph! Joseph, no!
No!
Please.
No. Please come back, please.
Don't leave me.
This is our dream together.
I don't want this without you.
I loved you.
I loved you from the
first time I saw you.
I often wondered about that.
How? Joseph.
You died.
You died!
Aye.
You can be sure
I won't be dying twice.