Relax.
We're going to begin.
Help me!
He won't let me go!
Can't you
please help me?
He won't let me go!
Cynthia?
Look at this one.
Larry.
You can leave.
The door is open.
I can't let you out.
Only you can.
When you're ready.
Don't talk to him!
Larry, you are in control here.
He has no power over you.
You just have to see.
Oh!
Larry, it's okay.
We'll try again next time, okay?
Larry, we're back.
Breathe.
Okay, it's okay.
You're safe.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
He was...
He was my...
I know.
That's all the time
we have for today.
But you are welcome to stay
as long as you like.
Someone digging around
in your mind
can be very disorienting.
Takes a lot out of you.
Just right there.
Um, I'll be right back.
Chamomile, right?
-Okay.
Hey, are you okay?
-Yeah.
-So what happened? He was, like,
blocking a memory
or something, right?
Can you find out what
phys ed teachers
Larry had between grades
four and twelve?
-Yeah.
-A coach maybe,
balding,
yellow and blue should be
the school colors.
How, how does that
happen in real life?
You've heard the saying
mind over body, right?
So what my mother just did
in there not only felt real,
but to her mind, it was real.
That's why we have
to be careful.
She, has she ever
done that to you?
No, no. Um...
I think she's afraid of
what she might see.
She should promote it.
Maybe at the hospital.
I work there.
She could help a lot of people.
Larry, the rules are there
to protect her.
To the outside world,
she's just a therapist.
That's it. Nothing out of the
ordinary. Standard practice.
-I know.
-Okay?
Have you ever tried it?
Like, is it passed down?
Well, I've been training,
but nothing yet.
Both my parents did have
the ability, though.
They learned to master
it together.
It's kind of how they found
each other, actually. Yeah.
Your dad did it too?
I'll be right back, okay? Take
as much time as you need.
- Hi.
Can I help you?
Hey. I need to speak
to Cynthia Winstone.
I don't think she's
expecting anyone.
I don't have much time. I need
to speak with her now, please.
I need help.
Okay, okay. Come in
from the rain.
Are you with someone?
Like a parent, or...
My dad's coming, but I need
to talk to Cynthia.
I, I heard she can help me.
I left my dad at the
grocery store.
I stole this from him so he's
going to know where I am.
I need to see her before
he gets here.
Okay, okay, come on.
Just around here.
Listen, you can tell me
if you're in danger.
I am.
Do you need me to
call the police?
No, no police. I just need
to speak to her.
Those look painful. Can I ask
what happened?
We have a procedure.
I can't let you speak to her
without at least doing
an assessment.
-Yep.
-Okay.
What's your name?
Riley Harris.
And how old are you?
Fourteen.
And how did you find out
about Cynthia?
A woman named Agatha
told my dad
that she could help
someone like me.
What do you mean,
someone like you?
I see things.
What kind of things?
A thing.
Can you describe
it to me?
It's... dark,
like a person,
but... not.
It stares at me like
a starving dog.
Does it speak to you, Riley?
Yes.
It always says the same thing.
Is it here right now?
Can you point to it?
Where did you get
those scars, Riley?
Riley?
It's here.
It's standing right behind me.
I can feel it.
It's hungry.
Jordan, who's at the--
Hey, Riley!
-Riley!
-No!
-Sir...
-Daddy, I need her help.
-We can talk about this.
-We don't need your help.
Come on, let's go.
No, let me talk to her!
We don't
need your help.
She can help us!
I need her help!
Sir.
Let's... Come here, go.
I'm sorry for the intrusion.
Get in the truck.
I just don't
understand.
I mean, she was terrified,
Mom, her arms.
I mean, her dad's obviously
hiding something.
She said some woman named
Agatha told her about us.
Agatha Baker, maybe?
Would she do that?
I don't know.
Mom.
You've been a little distant
throughout this whole thing.
I mean, what's going on?
Should we call the police, or...
No, they don't need
the police involved.
Why? I mean, something's
happening to that girl.
There's nothing we
can do for her.
Neither can the police.
There are some things
that are just
beyond help.
Can you be straight with me
for a second?
I mean, what even happened
back there?
I saw something.
What? What do you mean?
There is something
attached to that girl,
something terrible.
Okay.
Well, if you actually saw it,
doesn't that mean we can help,
you can help her?
You know why you
do screenings
before I meet with
any clients, right?
Yeah, Mom, I know.
Why?
To decide their
psychological needs.
If they have a willing interest
in alternative therapy,
we decide if we're going to do
blind hypnosis or therapy.
It's to protect them.
And to protect us.
Mom, if you actually
saw something
then you're the only person
who can help that girl.
I'm not going to open this
up to whatever it is
that's attached to that girl!
She had sores on her arm!
I saw it!
She needs us, Mom!
I don't care!
Well, Dad would have helped.
Okay, well, that is why your dad
is not here anymore.
Safe to enter?
Yeah, weapons are holstered.
Whatcha doing?
I'm researching Larry's
past coaches.
He had four, but this guy's
the only bald one.
Good. You send that to me?
Yeah, it's already
in your inbox.
Can we talk about today calmly?
I don't know, you tell me.
Okay.
Today scared me.
It reminded me of your father.
You know, that woman
that he tried to help,
it wasn't much different
than this.
She also had an entity
latched on to her,
and he just couldn't let it go.
Because he cared about people.
That's what made him him.
I don't blame him for that.
He took on a lot of pain
and suffering.
Too much.
Whatever was attached
to that girl today,
it isn't what we deal with.
Mom, you've become so scared
to look inside people.
You barely do it to
any of the patients.
You won't even do it to me.
I didn't need to look
inside that girl today
to see what was attached to her.
That makes it dangerous.
Yeah, which is more
reason to help her.
No, it is more reason not to.
Say that I try, then what?
I tell her father that
his daughter
has an entity attached to her,
so he can turn on us like
everyone did in Elmsboro?
We don't know these people.
Okay, we can't trust them.
I don't know if you remember
how horrible it got,
but after we moved,
I swore I would never let
that happen again.
The world believes in science,
not spirit.
One day when you can see,
I hope you have the sense
to know when to help
and when to protect yourself.
Okay?
Okay.
Daddy?
What's the occasion?
What?
Saturday morning,
up before 9 a.m.?
What have you done
with my daughter?
I have a life outside these
four walls, Mother.
Yeah, so what's up?
Nothing, I think I'm just going
to park with some friends.
-For what?
-Drinking, drugs, unprotected
sex. The usual.
Oh, you're still mad at me.
No, Mom. It's Saturday
and I'm 17.
I want to do something
that doesn't involve
depressed people. Is that okay?
Yeah. I mean, but I'm
not depressed.
I know. And I love you, but I
see you enough. Okay?
Bye.
Okay, well, be home for dinner.
Sushi Saturday.
I will.
Oh, I'm so thrilled you're here.
Okay, what can I get you?
Milk, coffee, ooh, would
you like a smoothie?
Uh...
Ooh, water. I can get you
a glass of water.
Alright, here we go.
I could order in.
That's okay. I don't
want to take up
too much of your time.
Oh, I've got nothing but time.
No one really visits me.
I was hoping your mother
was coming, too.
No, no, she's, she's having
a solo day at home.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Are you, are you still looking
to follow in her footsteps?
Mm, sometimes, yeah. Uh...
Big shoes to fill, so...
Such a talented woman.
So you have a couple
of questions, or...
Yes, I hope that's okay.
I just wanted to ask you,
we had somebody show up
at the house yesterday.
Yeah.
It was a bit of a scene,
to be honest.
I'm hoping you can help me
make some sense of it.
A scene. Sounds spicy.
Um, I'm not sure
how I could help,
but please, ask away.
Sure. Does the name Riley Harris
mean anything to you?
Uh, no, I don't think so.
Darn, should it?
Maybe her father?
She mentioned she heard
you speaking to him,
suggesting my mother might
be able to help her.
Oh, maybe, maybe Randall Harris
from Kenilworth.
Okay.
I've had him restore some of my
mother's old furniture.
Great woodworker, and cheap.
And what can you
tell me about him?
Oh, not much. He's polite,
you know,
serious most of the time.
Works out of his house,
in his garage mostly,
you know, making tables
or whatever.
Newly single.
So...
His wife passed away last year.
Okay, what from?
I just know the girl
took it pretty hard.
What makes you say that?
I don't think it's
my place to say.
Agatha, I'm really
concerned about her.
Anything you know
might be able to help.
I saw some scars on her.
Randall said they were
self-inflicted,
so I gave him your
mother's card, right.
But of course, I didn't say
what she really does,
just that she's great
with trauma
and that she can help
in that totally normal
kind of therapy way.
Could you tell me
where his shop is?
Yeah, I have his card
somewhere around here.
Let me get it.
Doug Ferry. He's probably
in his sixties now.
Cynthia, unless you can
give me a legitimate reason
why we should suspect this man,
I'm not going to start digging
around in this guy's past.
You know, I can't explain, but I
don't even need to know.
When you have time,
whenever,
he may be worth looking into.
I get it.
You're good at getting hunches,
but you never give me a reason,
a source, nothing.
You could just be picking names
out of a newspaper.
You know that's not true.
Take it or leave it, John.
See if he has anything
on his record.
Okay, guy's got a record.
What do you want me
to do with this, Cynthia?
I just know that he
is a terrible man.
Just keep an eye on him.
I got a lot of shitty people
to keep an eye on.
Call me when you have
an actual lead.
Prescott, come in.
Go for Prescott.
I'm sending you a name
and address.
Can we send a car
to run surveillance?
Copy that.
Anything we're looking
for specifically?
Just a hunch.
I have never felt
an entity this strong.
I can't help her.
I'm not risking it.
I'm not doing it.
Can I help you?
Sorry, you scared me.
Can I ask why you're
looking at my house?
Yes, sorry.
I was at the house yesterday
with Riley.
Yeah. No, I recognize you.
I was just wondering if we could
talk for a minute, or...
You know, it's not a great time.
I got a client in the shed.
Okay, I can wait.
It's important, so...
Look, I get it,
but my daughter doesn't
need to see a shrink.
You're wasting your time here.
I appreciate you coming out,
but I got things under control,
thanks.
No, no. I was thinking
she needs someone
with a different skill set
than a shrink.
You know, someone who can, um...
see what she sees.
What does she see exactly?
What did she tell you?
Enough to get an idea of
what she's going through.
You don't know us, or what
we've been through,
so I recommend you mind
your own business, alright?
Okay, can I speak
with her directly?
She's not here.
I'm trying to help.
Holy shit.
What the fuck am I doing?
Riley.
Riley, I'm just here
to talk to you.
It's okay, you can come out.
It's Jordan. We met yesterday.
Come on, he can't keep you
locked down here like this.
Riley.
He doesn't
lock me down here.
He locks them down here.
Who's them?
Hello, what --
Jordan?
Jordan.
Hello?
-Hello?
-Hi, Cynthia.
Hi, Agatha. How are you?
Oh, still not
getting out much,
but staying positive
and motivated
and ready to break
out of my shell.
That's good.
I was actually just
phoning to see if Jordan
ended up speaking
with Mr. Harris.
I'm sorry, Mr. Harris?
I'm not sure who you mean.
Randall, Randall Harris.
She stopped by earlier today
asking about his,
his daughter. I just hope,
hoped I was helpful.
It was really nice to see her.
What daughter, Agatha?
What did she say?
Um.
Oh, um, I'm. I'm sorry.
Maybe just have her call me.
Agatha.
Tell me what she said.
Well, she said there was a girl
that stopped by your house
last night,
and she just wanted
to speak with her.
I, I didn't think there
was an issue.
When did this happen?
This morning.
Shit. What is the address?
I can't really remember,
but I know where it is.
Okay, great. I'm on my way over.
Be outside.
Sorry, you're
coming over?
Oh my god!
Help!
Randall?
Password.
Randall, people know where I am.
What's the password?
I swear to God, I just came here
to help your daughter, okay?
Yeah, but you can't help her,
all right? No one can.
We've tried talking to people,
and it always ends up
the same way,
Child Services trying to take
my daughter from me.
No, that's not who
my mom is, okay.
She, she can help.
I don't need you filling her
head full of fucking lies.
Randall, it's the truth.
She has an ability,
and she can help.
I know she can.
No one can help my daughter.
No one could help
my wife either.
Randall, look,
I promise you that we can
find out what it wants
and we can get it
to leave you both.
I promise.
We know what it wants.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
She needs to feed it,
or it'll feed on her.
Riley?
Riley.
Sorry.
Riley, good job.
Okay.
Good job.
Go upstairs for me, okay.
Okay. Thank you, Jordan.
Go on, go ahead. Good job.
Hey, it's
Jordan, leave a message.
If people still do that.
Oh, hello. Hi.
So what are we doing?
I don't get out much.
This is kind of exciting.
I think that Jordan
might be in trouble.
Because of Randall?
Oh, come on.
Okay, well, you can
drive like a maniac,
but absolutely no texting
at the wheel.
See, look, she's fine.
"Just hanging out with friends,
Mom, don't wait up."
What?
She's...
It's not like her.
We had plans.
Grown daughter doesn't want
to spend Saturday night
with her mom? Shocking.
Dad.
Alright, hurry up. Get, get her
in the truck, alright?
Look, we need to sink the car
and get out of here.
We're running out of time.
Can't we just see if her mom
can help?
She is different
from the others.
People will be looking for her,
and if they find her, they will
take you for me forever.
Is that what you want?
Are we going to Brookers Lake?
Do you have everything you need?
Yeah, I just need
to grab my backpack.
Alright, hurry up.
Hey, hey.
Don't go to the basement.
We'll feed it together
before I leave, okay?
Go. Hurry up.
Come on.
Fuck.
Kill me.
No, don't say that.
We're going to get out
of this, okay?
Ow!
Okay.
Riley.
Did she really see it?
Yeah, yeah, Riley.
And if you let me out, then
I can take you to her.
She can help us, okay?
You can't get my dad
in trouble, okay?
He's just trying to protect me.
If your mom can make me better,
my dad can be a good person
again. I promise you.
I know. I know, Riley, okay.
Come on, please.
Thank you.
I'll try to keep him
busy outside.
Oh, shit, Riley!
Come on, come on,
come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Oh!
No, no, no, no.
God, come on, come on, come on!
Ready? Okay.
Oh, fuck!
I'll go get help.
Oh!
Randall.
You don't have to do this, okay?
She needs help.
We can help her.
You shouldn't have come here.
Dad, Dad, Dad, stop!
Riley, stay out of this.
You heard what she said.
She can help us.
You can't keep hurting people!
I don't want to do this anymore.
Riley, Riley, move, okay?
Daddy--
-Move out of the way.
No, you don't kill people.
You said!
Riley, move!
Riley. Riley?
Riley. Come on, breathe!
Riley
Riley, come on!
No, don't, don't!
Riley!
Riley, Riley.
Oh.
Help me, somebody!
No. No!
No, no, no, no, no, Riley.
Baby. Riley, Riley, Riley.
No!
Okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's okay.
Fuck!
Jordan! Jordan! Baby!
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
It's going to be fine.
We're just finishing up
with her.
They shouldn't be much longer.
Did they find the girl
at the house?
Yeah, they did. Um...
They brought her body to
Commongrove Hospital.
Staff's pretty shaken up.
I guess some of them
knew Riley Harris
from when her mother was sick.
You should know,
forensics is finding remains
at the house.
This guy's been doing it
for a while.
Jordan's lucky to have escaped.
Randall, and Randall,
did they, have they found him?
No sign. I bet he's three
counties away by now.
But we've run his plates,
and we've gotten every precinct
in area out searching.
We'll find him.
Hold tight.
I mean, this probably
isn't the time. But,
I thought you should know,
your hunch about the coach
may have been right.
We just brought Doug Ferry
in for questioning.
I can't say much, but
surveillance shows
some cause for concern.
One more time.
How'd you get these
sores on your arms?
Oh, he attacked me
so friction from struggling,
I guess.
This was after
he fired the rifle?
Yeah, I punched him
in the throat
and I escaped.
I know you're tired, Jordan.
We're just trying to
make sense of this.
I've told you everything.
Last word is forensics found
remains in the backyard
under the woodshed.
This is one of the most
horrific crime scenes
we have ever encountered,
Jordan.
You're our best way
of finding this guy.
Is there anything at all that
you're not telling us?
Anything?
I think I need to go home.
Please.
Okay.
We'll have a car stationed
outside of your
house tonight, okay?
Jordan.
Hey, baby.
Hey, you're okay.
Mom, I'm not okay.
Okay, let's go home.
Please, Agatha,
you really don't have to.
No, I insist. I am here to help.
What, what can I do?
Tea, coffee?
Tea would be good.
Tea, okay.
Mom, I'm sorry. I didn't
know what I was--
Jordan, I told you.
I said that we cannot open
ourselves up to this.
I know, Mom, but I couldn't
just let her go.
And look what happened!
I cannot believe you.
Mom, I'm seeing it.
No, you have been through
a traumatic experience.
She died in my arms, Mom.
I watched it leave her.
And I can feel it, okay?
I would sense it
if it was there.
Mom, I need you to look
inside me, okay?
I need you to see
that it's there.
Jordan.
I know why
you're afraid to look.
You're afraid of seeing Dad.
We share the same trauma,
and it doesn't matter
if you look or not.
It's not going to stop.
Look at my arm, Mom.
This is real!
You're a coward.
You're afraid of something
in her mind.
Oh. A smart woman
once told me
that the only way to overcome
fear is to face it.
You've spent so many years
trying to help other people
that you've never
helped yourself.
Whatever trauma you're afraid
of seeing inside her,
you've already been
through worse.
Sounds like she needs you now.
Agatha, I don't know
how this will go,
so if you see me struggling,
wake me up.
Agatha.
Oh. Oh, sorry. Yes.
You've done this to me,
but I have never seen you
do it to someone else.
Did you hear me?
Yes. Wake you up if you're
struggling. Got it.
Thank you.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
This won't be pleasant.
If an entity has attached
itself to you,
it will be the weakest
part of your mind
where you hold the most pain.
I need to go there to find it.
Okay.
I love you, Mom.
I love you too.
Okay, now breathe.
Just do whatever
you can to relax.
Right, relax. Okay.
Mom?
Do you want to come
inside with me?
It's okay, you don't have to.
Oh, honey, it's okay.
It's going to be okay.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Cynthia, Cynthia, wake up.
Cynthia, wake up!
Ah!
A shake would have sufficed.
I'm so sorry.
I panicked.
Oh.
She's asleep.
Probably for a while.
Poor kid.
Thank you for being here.
I appreciate it.
Is there any way you could
stick around for a bit longer?
I need to do something,
and I just,
I don't want her to be alone
if she wakes up.
Oh, yeah, I can. I can.
I can do that.
I can, I'll just read.
Okay. Well, there's an officer
stationed outside
if you need anything.
Call me if she wakes up,
Okay.
Larry.
Doctor Winstone, what
are you doing here?
Hey, um, I know I shouldn't
be here
talking to you out of session,
but I really need your help.
I know you can't share
patient information,
but I just need to know
the doctor
who dealt with a woman
with the last name Harris.
She passed away here last year.
I would not ask you if
I wasn't desperate.
-Harris, right?
-Yes.
Oh, yeah, I remember this.
Samantha Harris.
Really? You remember her?
Mm-hmm, yeah, it was like
a really big deal here.
Like a flesh eating disease,
really upsetting.
Doctor Whitaker was the lead,
but he retired.
Is there any way you could
get me his number?
I have a client who
may be dealing with an illness
similar to one of your patients,
Samantha Harris.
You have a client showing
the same symptoms?
Yes. You remember her?
What can you tell me about her?
Well, not much, as it's
patient confidentiality.
Please. My client
is getting worse,
and you are the only
person that has
any experience with this.
I know we work
in different fields,
but I'm asking you
doctor to doctor.
She's running out of time,
and I need to help her.
The disease she had
was unique, aggressive.
She was a humanitarian nurse,
long stretches overseas.
She came in with her husband
and her daughter.
She was deteriorating
so quickly.
After two weeks,
her hair fell out,
then her teeth, her nails.
It was like she was rotting.
But not just on the outside,
on the inside, too,
from her bones to
her organs, just...
Did she say anything to you
about what she thought
it could be?
About three weeks in,
she could see
that I was distraught,
and I was.
I was a mess.
Not in 40 years had I seen
anything like it.
I was about to lose her, and I
didn't even know what it was.
So this night, near the end,
she asked me to come close
and she whispers,
Something has me.
It's here with us right now.
It's hungry.
I can show you.
She reached out
her hand and she said,
"Don't be scared. It's worse
if you're afraid."
I could feel it pulling,
every part of my body being
sucked towards her.
It defied any scientific theory
I could come up with.
She needed me to see
that this was beyond
anything the medicine
could help.
It was her way of saying
thank you for trying.
After that, I couldn't
go back in.
Her daughter stayed with her
for the final days.
She held her hand
till she passed.
Do you believe that something
was with her?
I hope you understand why I
can't answer that, Cynthia.
But I'll tell you this.
If your client is suffering from
the same symptoms,
then she's better off being
helped by someone like you
than someone like me.
Feed me!
No, no.
Cynthia?
Oh.
Mom?
Oh, oh.
Agatha?
Agatha.
Agatha, wake up.
Hey, hey, hey. Wake up. Okay.
There you go. Okay.
Are you okay?
Ow.
Agatha, what happened?
Look at me.
What happened?
There's somebody, somebody...
Somebody was here. Somebody.
Jordan! Jordan!
Jordan!
No!
She's gone! She's gone!
She's gone!
Assistance needed at the
Winstone house!
I'm so sorry, Cynthia.
I get the police. This is
not your fault.
I just, we, we just need
to find her.
We have everyone
we can looking.
Local news, phone alerts,
everything.
We'll find her.
Hey, don't move! Don't move!
Randall, come on. You don't
have to do this.
You know, I didn't mean for
her to get hurt. I'm sorry.
This isn't about her.
Or you, not anymore.
This is about it.
You held her when she died.
And now it's inside you.
And now,
no one's going to be
around when you die.
So it can starve,
or it can go back to wherever
the fuck it came from.
No. No!
Let me out!
I'm sorry!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, come on, please!
I'm so sorry!
Starve.
I think we shouldjust
try to stay positive.
Anything?
The team is almost
done at the house,
and I have a few more questions
and then you can head home.
Yeah, I'm not going home.
We need to be out
there searching.
We are searching. We just
need you close in case--
I am not sitting around when
my daughter is out there.
Cynthia, please just--
Wait here.
What's going on?
It's him, he just pulled up.
What?
It's Randall Harris.
He's turned himself in.
And the girl?
Where is she?! Randall!
Where is my daughter?!
Where is she?!
Just let me talk to him.
I'm sorry, I can't
let you do that.
Please, John, you know me.
You know I can get
through to people.
Don't ask me to do that, okay?
It's so against protocol.
I don't give fuck about
your protocol.
This is my daughter.
John, just get me in the room.
Minutes from now, we could
know where she is.
But if I don't talk to him,
we might not ever find her.
You are making this decision.
You know I can do this.
Just trust me.
I'm sorry.
God.
Please, please.
What's going on with him?
Remember the two Sawyer kids
that went missing last year?
What about them?
I think we just found them.
You're not going to have
long in there.
Please don't let me regret this.
Where is she?
It won't hurt anyone else.
It stops now, okay?
Fine.
No, no, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Help! Somebody help! Help me!
Deeper.
No.
Leave!
Show me, Randall!
Show me where she is!
No, you have to leave her.
Get out of my head!
No.
No, you can't find her.
You have to leave her.
She has to die.
She has to die. Listen to me.
What is it? What just happened?
He buried her in the woods.
What? Where?
Leave her! It'll keep going!
Where are you--
I have to go.
They'll call you a cab.
Put the word out. We're looking
for wooded areas
in the direction Randall
was driving from.
I want search parties
to organize now.
I'm coming with you.
Let's go.
Fucking hell.
Feed me.
Where are we going?
I don't know.
I just know it's this way.
Find me Cynthia Winstone's
plates. I want an APB out.
She went east. Find me any
wooded areas in that direction.
There, we're close.
I remember this.
If you think
she's here,
shouldn't we call the police
and let them know?
The police cannot help her.
Can we?
I don't know, but we
have to try.
I want units searching
any the entrances
to forested areas.
Look for fresh tire tracks,
and any sign of Cynthia's car.
Copy that.
We have units on route.
We're almost there.
What are we gonna find?
When we get there,
I need you to trust me.
Yeah.
Whatever I can do to help.
You're a good friend, Agatha.
There.
Take it.
Sorry, she's--
Yes, Agatha, dig! Dig!
Okay, okay, okay.
Hey, Dispatch,
looks like there's
some fresh tire tracks.
We're going to check it out.
Come in, Otis?
Go for Otis.
A unit found
fresh tire tracks
and a broken gate
near Brookers Lake.
They're heading in
to investigate.
Send me the location.
I'm on my way.
I just need to take
a little break.
She's still here,
I can feel her.
Jordan! Jordan! Jordan!
Is she?
Jordan, Jordan, baby, wake up.
Jordan.
She's alive, but she's weak.
This thing must have known
that she was dying.
It's been aggressive.
Oh my god, we got to get
her out of here.
Hey!
No, no, shh! She doesn't
have much time.
Okay, I need to do this here.
Do what?
You remember when
I said to trust me?
-Yeah.
-Okay, now is that time.
The police cannot find us.
Okay? I need you to go, and
get them away from here.
-Away?
-Yes, I don't know what they'll
do if they find her like this,
but if they separate us,
I can't help her.
Please.
Okay, yeah.
Okay, go.
Hey! You, over, over here!
We're over here!
Over here! Help!
This way!
Over here!
Baby, baby, wake up.
Mom?
I'm here, I'm here.
Just stay with me, okay?
Okay. I'm coming.
No, you stay here.
Oh, oh!
Just a second.
Oh, hey, guys.
Where is she?
Oh, yeah, I don't know.
I was just kind of hoping
she was out this way.
Go back to the car, see
if you can find tracks.
Oh, no, no, no. She's,
she's not that way.
She's not that way.
Come on, let's go.
Okay.
Where is she?
She sent us in circles.
Oh, please. He's exaggerating.
What are you not telling us?
Well, there is this one thing.
In grade 11, I tried acid.
Horrible, horrible.
Put her in the back.
Wait! Do you want to know
who sold it to me?
It was my uncle!
Mom.
Leave her alone.
Take me.
Feed me.
Ah!
Where are you?!
Feed me.
You're hungry. We get it.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Cynthia.
Cynthia, wake up.
No, Otis, not now.
Ah!
No!
Cynthia!
Just keep looking.
Whatever you're doing,
hurry it up.
Mom? Mom, wake up.
Why didn't that work?
Please. Please.
Take me, and leave her alone.
Just leave her alone.
Hey.
Feed on this.
Jordan!
Come here, we have
to kill it.
We can't leave. We have
to kill it here, now.
Hurry. Grab something.
Jordan!
Jordan, baby. Baby?
Okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay,
it's over, it's over.
Okay, oh, baby.
It's okay.
-Mom!
-Okay.
Okay.
I saw him, Mom, I saw him.
I know, baby. I know.
I saw dad.
It's okay. It's over,
it's over, baby.
It's okay. You're okay.
You're okay.
It's over.
Over here!
We found her! Get EMS here now!
Call it in!
Get EMS here.
Thank you.
Oh, baby. Baby, it's okay.
Thank you. Thank you, Mom.
Hey, hey, get the shovels.
We need to clear this out.
Found her,
send EMS.
She's alive.
You're okay, baby. It's okay.
How are you feeling today?
Okay.
Only if you're ready, okay?
I am so proud of you.
Now you do me.
No, no way
I'm ready for that.
I'm so proud.
Your father would be so proud.