There, Mommy!
- Look there!
- Here, to me!
Mm. Thank you.
Thank you.
You know, Josh, the name of these
isn't pommes in America, it's...
French...
- Hmm?
- Uh, fries.
- Fries!
- Pass it to me, dumbass!
Over here!
Your papa, he always said
that in America, the French
fries are way better.
I'm not very sure about that.
I'm not very sure.
Uh-uh.
And who eats that one?
Hm. For papa, way
up high in heaven.
Hey, come on, pop.
It's time to put on sunscreen.
Give it to me.
I got it, I got it.
To me, here. Come on.
I got it.
Come on. I'm open.
Not there!
Boys, calm down!
- Hey!
- What the fuck?
Lady...
Shit, dude.
Man, are you okay?
Get up, man.
I'm sorry.
FOUR YEARS LATER
- Now she won't even call me.
- Really?
I mean, I kind of get
it. I wouldn't call you either.
- Forget about it. Just call her.
- I don't know if I can...
Ah.
Come on!
We have an appointment.
Ms. Wulf,
this is Eral Güney,
the journalist for the
investigative network Clarativ.
I'm calling again because
I have new material
concerning what happened
to you in Afghanistan.
I know you don't wanna
talk about it anymore,
but it would really help
with my investigation
if you could just watch a video.
I've sent it to you via email.
Do you recognize anyone
there? I look forward...
Josh?
You've gotta be by Mommy,
okay? I don't wanna lose you.
When we're in America, will
I get a baseball glove?
- Yeah, sure.
- Will I get a room too?
- Your own, yeah.
- And a PS5?
Nice try.
No way, little man.
Good morning. Please
have your passports ready.
All metal items
out of your pockets, please.
Place them in the trays. Thanks.
Smartphones in
here, please. Jackets separate.
All metal items
out of your pockets, please.
Next, please.
May I take a
look in the backpack?
- Of course.
- Okay.
Okay, next please.
Deutsch? English?
English.
- Okay.
- I'm interviewing to get an H-1 work visa.
- Sara and Joshua Wulf.
- Okay.
Hey, buddy. You're
American. How are you?
- Hm?
- Hey, how are you?
- He's shy.
- All right. You're checked in.
This is your number in the line.
They'll call you when they're ready.
B86.
When you're asked,
"How are you?"
you just need to say
you're fine, that's all.
Yeah, but what if
I'm not actually?
Either way.
The Americans don't actually wanna
know how you're doing in that moment.
That's why you just say,
"Fine." Simple as that.
There.
Did my papa also know any
German or only English?
Only English.
If your papa tried to,
he'd sound super funny.
You know how?
Are we also living near
where my papa used to live?
Yeah, really close.
B117, counter six.
Can you please sit down?
- Josh!
- I wanna play hide and seek!
Josh! What are you
doing? Josh! Sorry, sorry.
- But I wanna play hide-and-seek!
- Stop! Cut it out.
Come on. We'll speak
to someone. Yeah?
Excuse us. I think
we were forgotten.
- B-93.
- It all runs via the computer system.
I've got a little boy here with me,
and it's already been three hours.
There's a playground
down the hall.
A PlayStation!
Can I stay here, Mommy? Please?
Okay, but not too long, or we'll
miss our number when they call.
Yeah, but I'll just be here when
you're ready. Please, Mommy.
Well, okay,
for ten minutes.
But no whining when I
come to get you. Deal?
Deal!
I'm just gonna go get a coffee.
B93, counter six.
Josh?
We don't have time to
play hide-and-seek now.
Josh!
Josh, this isn't
funny. It's our turn.
Joshua!
Josh?
Josh!
Deutsch?
- English?
- English. English.
- What's the problem?
- I...
I can't find my boy. I left
him in the playroom there.
Could be that he's just
playing hide and seek.
- Can we please just open these doors?
- Would you please stay here?
Most likely he went to
the hall or the bathroom.
No, he didn't. Can we
please just open the doors?
- Why did you leave your boy by himself?
- I...
It was just a few seconds. He
was right here in the playroom...
For one, I'm not authorized
to open this door.
And for two, and
this is important,
the Americans don't mess
around with stuff like this.
So please come with me a moment.
I... I want to speak to
someone who can help me.
What seems
to be the problem?
Mr. Kynch, I'm sorry. She,
um, caused a disturbance.
Okay, I'll handle it.
Thank you very much.
Eric Kynch, Regional
Security Officer.
Sara Wulf.
- Gunnery Sergeant Donovan.
- Ma'am.
- You've lost your son, right?
- Yeah.
- What's his name?
- Josh. He's six years old.
- In these offices? Here?
- Yeah.
Please look around.
Josh?
You don't need to worry, Ms.
Wulf. If any place is safe, it's here.
- How long was your boy at the playroom?
- I don't know. Maybe five minutes?
We'd been here for so
long, he was super fidgety.
Shit, how
could I just walk away?
I have a daughter, Aileen.
She's eight.
Of course... sometimes you
just need five minutes.
You can't blame yourself here.
We'll find your son, miss.
Thank you.
A child
is missing. Six years old.
His name is Josh. Please
report to the information desk.
A child is missing.
I've got no other ideas
where he could've gone to.
Well, did he
somehow get outside?
No, this place doesn't
have a second exit.
If he'd've somehow made it to the front
desk, we'd have heard about it by now.
I'll check anyway.
I...
I may have an idea.
A man and a woman were here,
and they exchanged a bag.
I'm aware how this sounds,
but she went through this door,
and the man gave me a weird look.
They both looked like they
had something to hide.
What if those two took
Josh into this wing?
Please, can you
just open this door?
Can't do that.
High-security area.
What if those two people are
somehow involved? You've got a kid.
You know what can happen to children.
- What's going on?
- Can we speak somewhere? Privately?
Yeah.
Special Forces
training. Combat experience.
So you're a veteran.
Thank you for your service.
- When were you in Afghanistan?
- Up through 2017.
Could you maybe just tell
me what happened to Josh?
You applied for a visa
for you and your son.
But only you checked
in this morning.
What?
Are you serious? Of
course we both checked in.
That's not what it says on here.
The list is wrong. We both
checked in here this morning.
Someone did see him, people spoke
to him, like the guy at the front.
I spoke to the service
manager. Nobody saw him.
You were at the security
check. You saw him!
I didn't see a child, ma'am.
Really? You mean to tell
me he wasn't here with me?
That is how it looks, Ms. Wulf.
Okay, there are cameras everywhere.
Wh... What about surveillance videos?
I checked them already. Only
you can be seen in the footage.
That's not true. So let me
take a look at these videos.
Are you calling
me a liar, ma'am?
Sergeant. Please.
Okay.
So this is pointless, I want
to speak to the German police.
Sure, yeah. They were
informed already.
Hello. This is Eric Kynch. Ms.
Wulf would like to have a word.
- Schirmer.
- Okay.
They want me to think
it's in my head,
but I came here with my
baby boy early this morning.
They want me to believe
he was never here.
Could you please come here?
Ms. Wulf, we've been
informed about the situation at hand.
But we're not authorized to
enter the consulate building.
Which means what?
The consulate's
considered an exterritorial area.
Yeah, I know that. But,
so, w... what then?
The German authorities
have no jurisdiction there.
Basically, it's the same
as American territory.
Come out for now. We've always
collaborated very well...
But if I do go out, they
won't let me come back in!
And I won't be allowed
to see my son again!
Ms. Wulf,
you have to calm down.
Two of my colleagues will meet you
at the entrance in ten minutes.
Ms. Wulf, I promise that we'll
continue to cooperate with you.
Hey!
- Ms. Wulf, calm down, please.
- I won't go without my son!
I've got no idea about what happened
to your son. But he wasn't here!
Ms. Wulf, please! Please!
Okay?
Okay.
It's okay.
You're under a lot of
stress. I get that. I do.
But I'm asking you,
please stay in this room
until the German
police pick you up.
The sergeant here
will keep you company.
Have a good rest of
your day with us.
Please sit down, ma'am.
Copy.
Stay here. Don't move.
- Hello?
- Hi. It's me, Mom. Hi.
- Sara?
- I'm at the US Consulate in Frankfurt.
- You have to help me. Josh is missing.
- What?
You've gotta make contact
with the press and police.
They kidnapped Josh. Now
they're covering their tracks.
Are you there?
Sara, you're taking
your pills, right?
Mom, please. What's
one gotta do with the other?
I'm fine. You know I'm fine.
Why would you say that?
Can you put someone from the
consulate on the phone, please?
I already told
you, Mom. It's...
Listen. I know it is hard for
you, but you have to calm down.
Please tell me what
happened. Where's Josh? Sara!
Oh my God, the level 10 is so
hard, it's impossible to beat.
I had two hours to beat it,
and I still couldn't beat it.
Sergeant.
Please take your break now.
I'll take the next shift.
Any issues?
No. We're all good.
Good.
Josh?
Help!
Be quiet.
Okay.
English, Deutsch?
English. English.
Sit there.
Did you see a boy here?
About this tall, black hair.
What?
Jewelry in a plastic bag?
Who are you? How
come you're here?
Miss?
Miss!
I'm not here. I'm not here.
The things you requested.
Are you all right?
No.
No fresh fruit again?
Honey, I can't
live on that junk.
I'll talk to
the guest supervisor.
Thank you.
What's this about a
boy you're looking for?
My son went missing
two hours ago.
And I believe he was taken. From
the play room in the visitor area.
So go speak to, like, security.
I think someone here from the
consulate has something to do with it.
Have you seen a little boy here?
No.
I wasn't here either.
How did you make it here
from the visitor area?
There are cameras, security doors,
security personnel everywhere here.
I'm trained for
this kind of thing.
So what are you? A
freakin' special agent?
I was a soldier
Hm.
- Take care.
- I can help you.
I'm someone who knows
their way around.
I've been here for
months already.
You need to stay here. I can help
out. Maybe even find your son.
If you help find me a
way out of this place.
I remember that. A
skirmish in a hospital, right?
Yeah. An American and German
recon team ran into an ambush.
Eight killed.
Sara Wulf was the only survivor and
was heavily wounded by shrapnel.
Trained in hand-to-hand
combat. Is she special forces?
Retired. She was in a Bundeswehr
unit called "Fernspäher."
Reconnaissance. Trained in stealth,
infiltration and extraction.
I think she's harmless.
Delusional perhaps,
but harmless.
Still, we can't let a special forces
soldier roam free on our premises.
Ms. Consul General, we...
we raise an official alarm,
she'll be reported, put in jail, she'll
get a criminal record, won't get a job.
It ain't easy to get back on your
feet after what she's been through.
She's just a scared mother.
Find her. But keep it quiet.
Yes, ma'am.
- Yes, sir.
- Where is she?
I'm sorry. I don't
have her on the monitors.
I'm Sara, by the way.
Irina.
Please, don't.
I'm always playing it
this loud, no one'll hear.
Can you access
the Internet here?
No. They took my SIM
card away from me.
There's some
ultra-lame intranet,
and the Wi-Fi's triple
secured, WPA3, no SSID.
I majored in computer science.
But you're a political refugee?
Of a sort, yeah.
You must be under protection,
why do you need my help?
You're not a prisoner.
I am, though. I'm not allowed
to leave the consulate.
What prompted you to attack me?
You ask a lot of
questions. So...
Have we got a deal?
Yeah, okay. Deal.
No, it's fine. Just
get me out of here.
What else is in this building?
Storage rooms, guest apartments.
But no one's here, I'd have seen.
And in the other buildings?
I'm at the gym once in a
while and the cafeteria.
But only with an escort.
You need a key card to go anywhere.
I've also walked by some...
offices and training rooms too.
There's a daycare for the
kids of the employees.
And there's a tunnel to the
warehouse. A massive storage space.
Tons of stuff is sent to other
American embassies from there.
Then we'll
go to the warehouse.
- What are you looking at?
- Nothing.
Let's go.
Why go to the warehouse?
Well, it's the only way to smuggle
somebody out of this place.
I hope they didn't
already move Josh.
Who's they?
The two I saw who
exchanged a bag.
The woman went into
this building here.
And I bet my boy's disappearance
is connected to her.
Son kidnapped in the
consulate. Secret exchanges.
Makes total sense. For real.
- Just show me the way.
- I told you we need a key card.
Okay, copy that.
- Fuck. Did you kill him?
- Of course not. Just help me.
Hurry. Help me!
He'll wake up soon. His foot.
Okay, okay.
This way.
You're like a
badass fighting machine.
Make sure it's clear.
It's too simple.
They should be going
wild now. Close the door.
Search parties, exits blocked.
They should've seen
us on the monitors
and that the
camera's been broken.
There's something wrong.
Are you sure this is the
way to the warehouse?
Absolutely.
Someone's coming. Quick!
What is it?
Nothing.
If you've got issues or
whatever, just tell me now, okay?
Okay.
You think
there's a kid in here?
Sara, seriously, why would
anyone kidnap your son?
You're not gonna be able to
search the entire consulate.
Do you know how huge it is?
Hello?
Come on, please.
The last truck left
shorty after one o'clock.
Josh went missing around 2 p.m.
They can't have
moved him out yet.
The next one leaves in an hour.
Okay, I'll post up here.
And what about me?
We'll smuggle you out
on the next truck.
What is it?
Wait a minute.
What's the matter with
you? You can't just...
Wow.
Oh, yeah.
So this is what it's
all about. Drugs.
We've gotta move.
No. No! I'm staying put, man.
- I'm getting out of here.
- We're changing course.
- You promised me. We made a deal!
- Sh!
Diplomatic luggage
doesn't go through customs.
That can't be a coincidence.
The drugs, the exchange.
Josh must have seen something.
- I gotta talk to head of security.
- How am I supposed to get out of here?
There's no way anymore.
The fuck?
They need to clear this up, it'll
be chaos here if you leave now.
- But...
- It's my boy.
- I've gotta find him, I'm sorry!
- Come on this story makes no sense!
Maybe he wasn't really here.
This is his Playmobile figurine.
He was here.
And you feel that
proves something?
I do.
He was here.
Sorry, Sara.
But right now you
seem like a psycho.
Good luck.
- You're getting me out of here!
- I have to find my son!
No, this is bullshit!
Your son is not...
- Fucking don't touch me. Your son isn't...
- I've seen it, and I know it.
Not so fast. Who are you?
A rich girl being
persecuted? I don't buy it.
You're being a psycho.
Who is it?
I'm coming.
What are you doing? Stop! Stop!
Sara!
Sara! Help me!
Sara! Sara, help me!
Sara, watch out!
They wanted me dead, man!
If so, they'd've done it.
They were kidnapping you.
Irina, who were those men?
What's the thumb drive holding?
I have to
get out of here.
There are two injured men in
there. They tried to kidnap Iri...
I really am sorry.
Sorry.
I'll
clear the apartment.
Ms. Wulf.
I'm General Consul
Deborah Allen.
Are you all right?
My son was here today
with me, he's missing now.
They're claiming my
son was never here.
I found a bag of drugs.
Two men attempted to make off
with the woman in the
apartment for guests. Irina.
The thing with Josh must be...
What is it?
Your mother called us
this afternoon, Ms. Wulf.
- She's very worried about you.
- My mother?
She says that you have
post-traumatic stress disorder
with psychotic episodes
and even delusions.
You've received
inpatient treatment.
The cause was probably
your injury in Afghanistan.
Your son's father was
killed there too, wasn't he?
What's happening here
isn't related to my issues.
Please, time is of the essence.
We've gotta find my son
fast. Please let me go.
Ms. Wulf, you were
in our custody,
and you managed to break out.
Then you beat up an armed
guard in the hallway.
And as for these supposed
kidnappers, there's no evidence.
Nobody has seen them.
- Sure, but Irina can prove that she...
- I'm sorry, but...
now we only have a single
occupied apartment,
and the woman who is living
there is not named Irina.
What?
Sergeant Donovan
talked to our guest.
This person wasn't aware of an attempted
kidnapping, and she doesn't know you.
That isn't right.
Donovan is lying.
There are cameras and videos.
I wanna see the videos.
We've spoken
to a psychologist.
Sometimes our brain
plays tricks on us
when it doesn't process
traumatic experiences thoroughly.
Your mother said that you had a prior
incident where you attacked someone?
A long time ago, yeah.
I received pills. I
was given treatment.
I'm doing all right.
I don't wanna discuss whose
fault it is, Ms. Wulf,
all I want to do is to
get you the help you need.
Try to remember.
Maybe something
happened to Josh?
No.
Maybe there was some
incident, and you're suppressing it?
- No.
- Or did you lose him somewhere earlier?
Josh?
No. No. I came
here with him this morning.
I kept him in my sight
all day, he was with me.
For real. I'm not
imagining this.
You've been given a sedative
that may still be in effect.
I'm not imagining
this. Please let me go!
Tomorrow morning, German
authorities will pick you up
and take you to a hospital, where
everything else will be resolved.
Please let me go, let me go!
I'm not imagining anything!
I came here today with Josh. I did. Josh!
He was here, I didn't just imagine it.
See that a nurse
checks on her later on.
Yes, ma'am.
Josh.
It's a cover-up here.
What?
The assistant to the security
chief, Donovan, interrogated me.
I didn't tell him
we found drugs.
Your kidnappers and all that,
he didn't wanna hear it.
He walked back to the
apartment with me.
It was all put back.
Everything in place.
They didn't find
this though, luckily.
Your mind is fine.
Something's amiss here.
So come on.
- How do I know if you're real?
- Come on, of course I'm real.
They said I imagined you. They
said they never heard of you.
I wasn't sure if
I could trust you.
Irina isn't my real name.
It's Kira Wolkowa.
We were one of the richest
families in Belarus.
My father was a criminal.
Just money laundering,
but still, he was a criminal.
Like almost everyone
else in the government.
Then my father switched parties, which
obviously terrified the authorities.
So they snuffed him out.
And if I hadn't made it to
the US embassy in Minsk,
I would've been the
next one they killed.
This thumb drive is where
the evidence is stored.
And those people want it back.
But why Frankfurt?
The CIA got me out
of the embassy.
And I should've gone
straight to the US, but...
it didn't happen.
I'm stuck here.
For month after month,
it's excuse after excuse.
Two days ago, Donovan came and
asked me to hand over my passport,
and that's when I knew
something wasn't right.
Someone let these
men into the embassy.
I'm who they wanted.
But they showed me the
surveillance videos and...
I was by myself,
speaking to no one.
You don't believe
I'm real? Okay.
- Then this isn't real, right?
- What's the matter with you?
It's nothing. It's
not real, right?
Come on, stop it.
Welcome back.
Window. There are cameras
everywhere in the hallways.
Are you sure
that it's safer outside?
No.
- Great.
- Come on now.
I don't know
what's going on here
or how the drugs and the kidnappers
are connected to Josh, but...
I bet Donovan's a part of this.
Yeah, but how do
we find that guy?
We've gotta find who owns the
bag. The only lead we've got.
Can you...
The Bilateral Economics
Conference will resume in five minutes.
Participants, please
come to Auditorium 1.
Security.
Great plan, Sara.
Fuck.
The title of this next slide,
"Connecting Businesses to Global Markets."
It isn't just a statement.
It's a commitment.
DM.
I posted to the consulate's intranet.
Hopefully they'll get back to us soon.
Hey, what's the matter?
What if they're
right, and I'm wrong?
Don't be silly.
I thought I had it
under control with the pills.
But I've got flashbacks again.
All those images
are coming back.
Gaslighting.
My ex did it to me.
He kept me in his
grip from day one.
And he... convinced me of
things that weren't true.
Till I couldn't be positive
what was real... or fake.
I mean, I know it's
not the same, but...
Here, just snap this
against your wrist.
It helped me to feel it
when times got tough.
Come on. Do it right.
Aah!
Thanks.
So, what's your plan?
When this is all over?
Off to Boston. Opposition
members have a community there.
Between those folks and
the evidence I've got,
we could likely free
a few more dissidents.
We got asylum there
for my mother.
But it's been over a year
since we made contact.
And you?
What brings you to America?
A huge security firm
gave me a job over there.
Yeah.
Pay's good.
Prospects are better.
They, um... they
wanted female ex-soldiers.
It's a... a new beginning.
I just couldn't stand
it here anymore.
I barely even...
have time for Josh.
And we live with my mother.
Ouch.
Yeah.
Yeah. The woman does
her best, but...
I would also like, um...
Josh and his family
to know each other.
His father was American.
Was?
Died in battle.
In Afghanistan.
Well, I'm sorry.
In the hospital... I first
found out that I was...
I was pregnant.
Josh is my little miracle.
Or big one.
He replied.
No real name. He
wants to meet immediately.
Here?
Too dangerous. An open area.
Yeah, but where? The
cafeteria or something?
That'll work.
Sara. That was sarcastic,
you can't be... Wait!
- Where they'll least expect us.
- This is insane.
We'd have to pass through
the whole consulate.
We're not going
through the consulate.
Over here.
Fuck.
Call Donovan. I
have to pick up my daughter.
Yes, sir.
They're looking for you.
Everywhere.
Where's my son?
Brown hair, six-ish?
Name's Josh?
Give me the bag, and I'll
tell you where he is.
You don't know shit.
You just want the bag.
What? No.
Yeah. I can see you're lying.
The drugs must be worth, what?
A couple of hundred thousand?
So, if the bag doesn't
reach its destination,
you're gonna be in trouble.
- What do you want?
- Help me find my son.
I just told you
everything I know.
To be valuable for the
people who pay you,
you must have high
security clearance.
What are you? CIA? NSA?
Tech?
Yeah.
I need a floor plan
of the compound.
And a key card with all access.
- That's impossible.
- Is it?
You want the bag, you'll
think of something.
Uh...
Wait here. Twenty
minutes, then leave.
Not before.
Meet me at the men's
room down the hall.
I need to go wee-wee.
I need
to go wee-wee.
I need to go wee-wee.
You've got to be kidding me.
Mice crispies. Mice crispies.
Yeah?
Sir, we've
got a system failure.
Okay. We gotta go,
honey. Let's go.
Sorry, daddy's got to work.
- We have to clear our trays, Daddy.
- Not now.
Fuck.
That was close.
- We should've maybe talked to Kynch.
- Should've done what?
We don't know what's
happening here at all.
Do you have a plan for that?
I'll give it back
when this is all over.
I...
I thought it was
about the drugs.
The drugs have nothing to
do with Josh's kidnapping.
I'm back to square one.
We'll find your boy.
Yeah.
You're
fucking late. Come on.
I was able to deploy
malware on the server.
Now the IT support team is on
it. So you've got one hour max.
Then the cameras are back online.
- Floorplan, keycard.
- Key card. Yeah.
Warehouse.
- What is this?
- Uh, rec center.
And this?
NSA and CIA facilities.
Now, can I have my stuff?
- What are these?
- Detention cells.
I've never been there, but supposedly they
were decommissioned after the Iraq War.
Could somebody
hide a child there?
Do you really think the CIA kidnapped your
kid because of some secret conspiracy?
Sh!
- Now, I just want my stuff.
- What do you know about Donovan?
- Why?
- None of your business. So?
He's just a dumb jock
and wannabe influencer.
He crashed the system once
because he played an online game.
And he lied about it too.
Where is his office?
On the second floor,
in this building here.
Yeah. Yeah.
- You had it with you all along?
- "You had it with you...?"
Mean. All right.
I'll have to explain
how you got my card.
- Uh, where?
- Hold this.
Okay.
It's gonna look like you
put up a fierce fight.
What do you...
What do you think Donovan had
to do with Josh's disappearance?
Well, I hope that
we find some...
Oh, fuck!
Where should I meet
you? Office or Post One?
Goddamn!
Okay, what
are we looking for?
Anything to do with
the kidnappers or with Josh.
How's he have so much money?
Have a look at his emails.
I'll look for your name too.
Fuck.
- What are you doing?
- Looking through the system files.
Okay. This is...
Frame...
What the fuck?
But that's the firm in
the US I'll work for.
- Donovan got you the job.
- Looks that way.
MASSIVE FLASHBACKS PSYCHOTIC-LIKE
DISSOCIATIVE BEHAVIOR
He knew how you were doing.
He wanted you in the embassy.
Okay.
- The files about you were forwarded.
- To who?
No idea. That's
not a real name.
- Okay. I've gotta google the Consul.
- Wait!
He'll see it in
his search history.
Use this laptop here.
Yes, Ms. Consul General.
It seems to be a software problem.
It's got nothing to do with Sara
Wulf. She's still in the infirmary.
Sergeant Donovan checked on her.
The German authorities are picking
her up anytime now. All right.
- Any update?
- Nothing.
- Did you try to log in?
- I left my tablet in the office, sir.
- Well, go get it.
- Yes, sir.
- You think the Consul's a part of this?
- Yeah, definitely.
It must be a high-up person to
manipulate the video and sneak people in.
Look.
Born in Wiesbaden. Harvard.
There's nothing.
- Okay, fine. Eric...
- I'm on it.
Eric Kynch.
Consulate Frankfurt.
He was also a
soldier in Afghanistan.
Down, down, down. Wait.
"Regional Specialist in
Islamabad, Pakistan."
- I'm checking my mail.
- What? Why?
Searna Hotel, Islamabad.
That's Kynch.
What is this video?
It's related to our
deployment in Afghanistan.
It's where Evan was killed.
0175 165 89. Okay.
- They screen every call here!
- It doesn't matter.
- Who are you calling?
- The journalist who sent the video.
Clarativ, this is Güney.
- This is Sara Wulf. You sent me the video.
- Thank you for...
One of the men is Eric Kynch.
- Uh, that's correct.
- What do you know about him?
Okay, so, uh, Eric Kynch had to end
his military career because of injury.
His name pops up time and again
in connection with corruption,
but he's been
exonerated every time.
But now I have a new
source in Pakistan
who claims that
Kynch was responsible
for the ambush you walked
into in Afghanistan.
What?
Shit.
Sara, we've gotta go.
However, I'm still missing
one crucial identification.
Who's the man Kynch is
talking to in the video?
- I'm not sure.
- Sara, come on!
You can see him in the
mirror. Do you know him?
Uh, I... I can't make him out.
He... he's not really clear.
There's an enhanced screenshot.
- If I...
- Send it over. Yeah.
- Ms. Wulf? What is...
- Thanks.
- Shit, I can't open it. I can't open it.
- What's wrong?
I've got it. I've got it.
Okay, got it.
Fuck.
- Come on!
- Come on.
Come on.
Come on, come on. Now!
This way!
Backup! They're heading
to the cafeteria!
Move! Move!
Get out of the way!
Door.
- Elevator?
- Takes too long. This way.
Shit.
Fuck.
They went
through that door.
Clear! Let's go.
What happened
in Afghanistan?
There were two teams.
Us and the Americans.
And the first night
we were attacked.
We neutralized a few. In the end,
though, there were just too many.
When the helicopters finally
arrived, they were all dead.
Or, well, all except me
I've... I've asked...
I've asked myself why.
Why me and no one else?
Not just you.
You and Josh.
Here's the photo.
How do you suppose
Kynch is involved?
Sara?
Have you seen that man?
Get
out! It's an ambush.
Come on, move it!
- Clear!
- Move on there. Survey! Go!
Enemy down.
- We've gotta get to the warehouse.
- What? What for?
We have enough evidence now!
Donovan had you come here
and covered up my kidnapping.
Kynch is involved in your
past, we have no idea how.
But we have to
talk to the Consul.
Sara, this makes no sense!
Let's check the building where
they keep the detention cells.
And besides, what's
in the photo?
Sara!
- And?
- We lost them.
And I checked my tablet.
She found the emails.
She knows.
I'm sorry.
Watch out for that mirror.
What are we doing here?
You'll book the train to France.
In Paris, buy a plane
ticket to Mexico.
You've got a good chance of crossing
the border into the US from there.
They'll be leaving soon. Just
hide in the back of the truck.
I'm sorry, you...
- You said we'd...
- I know what Kynch did.
I figured out why I'm here.
It's too big, you have to go.
What about you?
I, uh, I'll be fine. Okay?
I'll be fine.
Go now.
Find your mother, okay?
- I'll distract them.
- Okay.
Okay.
Hey!
Stop! Who are you?
Hey, what's going on?
Hey!
I said, don't move!
Get out of the car! Now!
Stop or I'll shoot!
Stop, or I'll shoot!
Sara, stop! Stop right there!
Hey, stop! Don't move!
Come back here!
You can't be here!
You're under arrest.
Wait! Hey, you!
Hey! What's your problem?
Stop right there!
You just won't give up, will you?
Aah!
Fuck!
Where's Josh?
Tell me where he is!
- Tell me now!
- He's okay.
I have your son.
He's just fine.
You kidnapped my son, why?
You could've just
killed us outside.
Like some freak accident.
How d'you find out?
I saw the video.
In Islamabad,
you met with one of the members
of the Taliban who attacked us.
I can identify the man.
I'm the only surviving witness.
I found out that you revealed
our position to them.
What for?
I'd have left you alone, Sara.
But this journalist, he
put so much pressure on me.
Where's Josh?
Fucking talk!
I'm the only one
who knows where Josh is.
If you pull the trigger
now, he'll starve to death.
What do you wanna do now? My
people'll be here any minute.
I'll find Josh myself.
Josh?
Officer down!
Are you okay, sir?
We lost her. But she's
probably still on the compound.
Sir, we have to
trigger an alarm.
No, we will follow
daily protocol.
But according to regulations...
No, you will report directly
to me and no one else.
I repeat.
Explosion in building E.
That was her.
- Why isn't she on the cameras?
- She must have dodged them, sir.
- Yes, Ms. Consul General?
- What's going on, Mr. Kynch?
Well, th... there's
been an explosion.
Is that so? What about the attack
at the recreational center?
I... I'm sorry. There was a glitch
in the chain of command, I...
Stop bullshitting me.
And follow protocol.
Yes, ma'am. Fuck!
Go to code red! Shoot on sight!
Go!
Please
follow emergency procedures.
Head to your nearest assembly point
and await further instructions.
Attention.
This is an emergency.
Clear!
Come!
All right, everybody!
- Clear.
- To your right.
All right.
Everybody, keep it moving.
I want to go home.
Aileen?
- I'm Sara. I'm here to pick...
- How do you know my name?
- What happened to your face?
- Oh.
I'm a friend of your father's.
He asked me to pick you up.
I must not go with strangers.
Yeah, you're right.
But I'm not a stranger.
I'm a friend, promise.
See? Your father gave me this.
Mr. Rabbit!
Come on.
Go, go!
This is a safe room.
My daddy told me all about it.
You're a very smart girl.
Post One.
Section A is cleared.
Team Alpha, move to section C.
You shouldn't be in the safe
room. The compound is being evacuated.
Sir, it's for you.
Eric Kynch?
♪ Miss
Mary Mack, Mack, Mack ♪
♪ All dressed in
black, black, black ♪
Sara?
I explained that I
was babysitting her.
Can I speak to my girl?
Sweetie? Your dad.
- Daddy?
- Hey, little bug, you all right?
Yeah. Are you coming to get me?
No, I'm sorry, little bug.
Daddy's gotta work a little longer.
Sara is gonna take care of you.
I'll pick you up soon, okay?
Okay. Love you.
I love you
too, little bug.
What do you want?
I want my son returned.
- Ms. Wulf...
- And I want you to confess.
I'm not having fun anymore.
This door is ten centimeters
thick, reinforced steel.
If you wanna blow it up, you're
gonna risk killing your daughter.
- You'll be too slow drilling.
- For what?
Because we'll run out of oxygen.
If you call this room again,
better show me my son's face.
Sara?
Copy.
She's turned off the air supply.
- Can we turn it back on?
- No.
These units are completely
self-sufficient.
There has to be some
other way to get back in!
- Do you wanna play another game?
- Yeah.
Okay. I spy with my
little eye something that is...
red.
What's going on here, Eric?
- Why is this happening?
- Everything is going to be all right.
Don't you worry. It's okay.
I spy with
my little eye...
something... that is...
green.
The blanket?
No.
That box?
Are you okay?
I'm... very tired.
Come, lie down.
Sara?
Where's my son?
Sara, please let
the girl go free.
Have you got a clue what
they're keeping from you here?
Do you know about
Eric Kynch's past?
- W... Why did she say your name?
- I have no idea.
- He's corrupt.
- What's going on?
She's delusional.
Eight deaths the
man's responsible for.
And he knows I am the only
one who can incriminate him.
That's why he wants me buried.
Sara, please, just
come outside for now.
You can't possibly
want the girl to die.
I wanna speak to him now.
How?
Are you serious?
What are you saying?
You would watch me kill your
daughter before you go to prison?
She's done nothing wrong
here. But you wanna kill her?
I know... that you're not
capable of that, Sara.
You're not a murderer.
The lantern?
What?
I spy with your little
eye... the lantern.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
Are you alright?
I was just thinking
about my son.
We love to play that game too.
What's his name?
His name is Josh. He's a
little younger than you.
And where is he now?
I don't know.
Come on, sweetie.
- Where are we going?
- You're going home.
I'll let Aileen go free.
But I wanna talk to you.
Just the two of us, here.
Okay, Sara.
Clear the area.
All right. Everybody fall back.
Fall back.
More!
Thank you, Ms. Wulf.
Will you now please
come out as well?
No.
I want Kynch to come in.
That's what we planned.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
You... will never release
Josh while I'm still alive.
Regardless of whether I
promise to stay quiet.
Just tell them
that I put up too
much resistance.
And as soon as you walk through that
door, I'll shut off the air supply again.
That... wouldn't surprise
anyone given my condition.
Just promise me you'll
bring Josh to my mother.
Please promise me that.
No!
Please.
Please, let Josh and me go free.
I'm sure you know
I can't do that.
Why take my boy away?
Why go through all the effort?
Please, Kynch, you
owe me an answer.
I made a fucking mistake.
A big one too.
I underestimated you. "She's a
fighter, she doesn't give up."
Everyone who knew you said that.
I didn't think you'd succeed in
getting out of the visitors' building.
It all started to go wrong when
you witnessed the bag exchange.
An unfortunate coincidence,
but also my mistake.
I should've known about
Martello's side business.
That's why you broke
into another building,
which was never
part of the plan.
Still, I decided
not to interfere.
Even after you met Kira Wolkow, we
were still in control of the situation.
The abduction was supposed
to go down as planned.
But none of us were prepared for you
to eliminate two trained assassins
and stop the whole plan.
The whole fucking plan
went down the drain.
The kidnappers were let
in on your authority.
You made sure I'd be offered
the job in America so I'd come.
You stay
here. Do not move.
Sergeant, please
take your break now.
And you made sure
I'd be able to escape.
You wanted me to be on the
loose in the consulate.
We can't let a special forces
soldier roam free on our premises.
She's just a scared mother.
You knew I'd do
anything to find my son.
If someone like Kira were
simply to vanish from here,
it'd be too big to get off free.
They would ask too
many questions of you.
Yeah, but the loony tunes
ex-soldier running around loose?
Perfect scapegoat
for everything.
And then you could shoot the only
witness left from Afghanistan
while she's on the run.
Icing on the cake.
How much were you
paid for it? Huh?
To open the door to kidnappers?
How come you are
where you are, Sara?
Hm?
Because the Bundeswehr
took good care of you?
No, you ceased to properly
function, and they left you hanging.
Isn't that right?
I busted my ass for them!
Military college scholarship,
OCS with honors, and then... Bam!
One RCM hits your vehicle.
After six months, they say
you're all right again.
You can't even get out
of bed in the morning
'cause you are so
fucking depressed.
And they say, "Okay, get behind
a desk, that's where you belong."
"Career dead end,
take it or leave it."
Your family moves
every couple of years.
Your daughter's never
gonna have a proper home.
And they don't even give you enough money
to pay for her to go to college some day.
Fuck 'em!
I owe them nothing.
They owe me.
You know...
we're not so different, Sara.
I'm doing this for my family.
But my family you destroyed.
Josh has no father.
And you've already
murdered eight people.
I am sorry, Sara.
I thought I sold them
just useless intel.
I can't listen to
your whining. Get out.
I said out!
Guess you never do give
up the fight, Sara.
And that's why...
Motherfucker! I knew
I'd hate that part.
She got my gun!
- Are you hurt?
- Secure the door! Medic!
- It's an ambush!
- Move it!
- Clear! Get out, get out!
- Incoming!
Mommy?
Explosive in place.
Armed.
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One.
I made a fucking mistake.
A big one too.
I underestimated you. "She's a
fighter. She doesn't give up."
Everyone who knew you said that.
But I didn't think you'd succeed in
getting out of the visitors' building
and stop the whole plan.
The whole fucking plan
went down the drain.
The kidnappers
were let in on your authority.
And you made sure I'd
be able to escape.
You wanted me to be on the
loose in the consulate.
Stop!
Get on the ground!
Where's the boy?
Please
don't give up now.
Mommy?
Her
condition is stable now.
We can take her
outside right away.
Mommy?
Give 'em a minute.
Hello, my darling.
How are you, Josh?
Fine.
Come here.
Mm.
EIGHT WEEKS LATER
Kynch is detained in the US.
The General Consul let me know.
And they found out that the
guy who helped us check in
was involved with the
whole thing as well.
And Martello? The tech guy?
Oh, he fled the same day.
It would appear he's hiding.
Okay, crazy.
Yeah.
How are you?
Yeah, good.
Doc says I'll be just fine.
Oh, I'm off. That's my ride.
All good. Well, I'll see you in a
bit. You have a good flight, yeah?
Thank you. Say hi
to your mother.
- I will. See you soon, psycho.
- See you.
Bye, Mom.
Take care of
yourself, okay? And of Josh.
I will. I promise.
You will.
I'll call you
when we've landed.
What is it, Mommy?
Just a helicopter, bud.
Are we leaving soon?
Yeah. So let's go.
♪ I got something
burning in my chest ♪
♪ An ocean made of
embers unexpressed ♪
♪ It's in my bloodstream, I ♪
♪ Think I'm ready
for a higher ground ♪
♪ Finding my reasons why ♪
♪ 'Cause I never
wanna slow down ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Yeah, I never
wanna slow down ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Think I'm ready
for a higher ground ♪
♪ Finding my reasons why ♪
♪ 'Cause I never
wanna slow down ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Think I'm ready
for a higher ground ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪