Elena.
I know this must seem like
the darkest day of your life.
I know you miss your mother
and even though
she's not here right now,
she'll always love you.
You understand that, don't you, darling?
Yes, Daddy.
But, I'm going to be around more.
I will always be here.
Promise?
I promise.
Traps his victims...
People still missing.
String of murders.
Vicious crime spree.
We're dedicating every...
...available resource...
...to hunt this man down.
A serial killer has...
...claimed yet another victim,
in what has become...
...the most vicious crime spree
in our city's history.
This unprecedented...
...series of violent murders has many...
...staying indoors...
...and living in fear.
Good morning.
Here's what we can share at this time.
The assailant traps his victims...
...in homes...
...businesses, or work places...
then kills them.
However, it appears
that he takes one victim
from each crime scene.
These people may still
be alive and held captive.
With over 50 people still missing...
...grieving families
are seeking answers...
...and authorities have begun a manhunt.
That's right people.
The latest in a string of murders.
The killer seems...
...to strike without
any pattern, which...
...makes it impossible for police...
...to track his moves with...
...is best described
as a predator without...
...boundaries. Targeting men, women,
children, young, old,
he does not discriminate.
The latest missing person
is no stranger to crime himself.
Arkin O'Brien is a...
...twice convicted thief
who was abducted shortly...
...after paramedics
responded to a 9-1-1 call.
O'Brien's wife, Lisa...
...recently reacted to the abduction.
Whoever's watching this.
Please, if you see this...
and you have him...
...please let him go.
Please...
...let him go.
We will hunt this man down.
We are on his trail and
we will bring him to justice.
Hey. Are you here?
Yeah, I'm not going to be able to
make it tonight, babe.
I gotta work till close.
I'll make it up to you though,
something real special.
Okay?
Who you talkin' to? Come on!
Let's go already!
All right?
Okay. You're off the hook.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I love you, babe.
I love you. I love you so much.
I love you, too.
Hey, Missy.
What are you doing?
Studying now. Brian bailed on me.
Good. Get dressed.
I'm taking you to a party.
Uh, I don't know.
I'm kind of tired.
I think I'm just gonna go to bed.
Yeah. Yeah, I got ya.
Look out your window.
I'll be down in five.
Thank you, Marcus.
We are now going live
to Nikki Johnson...
...reporting live at the scene...
...of the latest attacks.
A serial killer
has claimed yet another victim,
in what has become the most vicious
crime spree in our city's history.
This unprecedented series
of violent murders
has many staying indoors
and living in fear.
And now, with over 50 people
still missing grieving families...
...are seeking answers...
Did I pick the right shirt?
It's not about the shirt,
little brother.
It's about how you wear it.
All girls say that,
dude, and none of it is true.
Every detail counts.
I've been workin' on some lines...
- ...and I was thinkin' that if I...
- Okay, stop.
First off, don't call me dude.
Look, when you
wanna be with a woman
you don't walk up to her and say, hi,
I'd like to sleep with you.
You say, nice shoes.
Does that make sense?
Hmm.
Just try wearing some
confidence for a change.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Hey, Josh.
Nice shoes.
I can't believe your dad
let you out the house
- with that psycho on the loose.
- He didn't.
Really?
Where is this place, anyway?
It's private here.
Password to get in.
Which is what?
Nevermore.
Wow, this... really looks inviting.
This has to be it.
Okay, that's gotta be the door guy.
Go tell him the password.
Um...
...nevermore.
Nice shoes.
Stay down!
Stay here!
Get out of my way!
Move!
Move, bitch!
Whoa... whoa, whoa, whoa!
Fuck!
Stay down.
You gotta help me.
You gotta help, come on.
- You gotta help me.
- No!
Help me. You gotta help me.
- Move!
- Man, what happened?
- What is it?
- Brian?
Oh, shit. This way, over here.
Shit!
Oh, my God!
Elle! Elle!
Elle! Please! Oh, my God!
It won't stop!
Help me!
- Push on it, Missy! Push on it!
- Can you shut it off?!
No!
Push on it, Missy! Push on it!
No! No!
Look out!
Okay. What do we got here?
- I need you to stay calm.
- Where's my family?
- Where's my wife at?
- I need you to stay calm.
- My arm hurts bad.
- Pack it in...
...20 milligrams of Versidep...
...push 10 milligrams of morphine.
Right now.
Can you tell me your name?
Arkin.
Please note scratches on subject's
right arm are self-inflicted.
- Hold on to him please.
- 1... 2... 3...
Oh, fuck!
Hey, we need
some help in here right now!
Let's go! Over here, hold him down.
Hold his arm down.
Morphine, push 10 milligrams. Now!
Hey, you can't be in here
- Hey, come on. Step back.
- What the fuck is goin' on?
- Get out of here!
- Cuff him! Cuff him!
Whoa. Okay, okay.
Okay, easy guys.
Okay? Easy.
Get it off me! Get it off me!
Lisa.
I thought I'd never see you again.
You ain't that lucky.
What happened to you?
It's okay, baby. I've got you now.
You didn't have to get me flowers.
- I didn't.
- What's that say?
What's it say?
For the collection.
Get well soon,
can't wait to meet the family.
What's wrong?
What?
Listen to me.
Baby, you got to go to your moms.
- No.
- Go now.
- Don't tell anyone where you're going.
Don't even pack a bag.
- No, please.
- Go.
- Okay.
- Go, now.
I've got it from here, bud.
Have a good night.
Hello, Arkin.
I told you guys everything I know.
I'm not a cop.
Who are you?
My name's Lucello.
Yo, what the fuck are you doin'?
Relax. I'm here to help you.
I'm working for a man
whose daughter's gone missing.
Did you see her at the party?
Yeah.
Was she alive?
Last time I saw her.
Did he take her?
If you didn't find a body, then maybe.
He always takes one.
Her name's Elena.
I've got 48 hours tops
before she's dead.
I think you have a pretty good idea
where that man might be.
What makes you think
you're gonna find this guy
when the cops can't?
Because I am
willing to do things they won't.
I have assembled a team
and we are gonna find him and kill him.
What's the plan?
He's gonna lead us to
where Elena's being held.
What about the police?
They had their chance.
What this man deserves
is beyond the law.
She's all I have. Find her.
Sir, I've always been there for you.
She'll be home tonight.
Thank you, Lucello.
Lena.
Dad!
Daddy!
- Elena!
- Daddy!
I got you.
I got ya.
Hello?
Who's... who's out there?
Oh, my God.
Get away!
Get away from me!
Get away! Get away!
Please! Get... get...
Get away from me!
We're goin' in for the girl tonight.
And this man, Arkin O'Brien,
is our best chance
to bring her home alive.
Let's be clear about one thing.
I'll help you get there...
...but I will not go inside.
Understood.
You help us find Elena, you walk...
...we do the rest.
Now tell us what we need to know.
If you're gonna find this guy,
you gotta start at the beginning...
...when he threw me into that red trunk.
I cut my forearm
every time I got to 100.
When we turned right
or left I made distinct cuts.
Drive five miles under the speed limit,
stop fully at every stop sign,
don't gun the engine
through the yellows.
Follow my instructions...
I'll take you right to
where he took me. Right.
But you better be prepared, man.
Bring everything you've got.
Because if he... catches you,
he's gonna make you wish you were dead.
Left.
You're not gonna walk
in there like this is...
Sunday dinner because this is his house,
and he will cut your balls off
and feed them to you.
Stop.
This hotel has been
abandoned for years.
This is the place.
You're the expert.
Think you can get us in there?
I'll get you in then I'm outta here.
Oh, God.
Hello?
Watch your back in there.
It's built like a maze.
The whole place is rigged.
That's why you're leading us in.
What are you talkin' about?
That wasn't the fuckin' deal.
It's the same deal Arkin.
I'll kill the guy...
...but you've gotta help us find Elena.
What makes you think
I know where she's at?
Because you're the only person I know
to see the inside
of this hotel and live.
Ladies first.
Eat a dick.
Guard the door. Stay on the radio.
There's something moving in there.
No way, man.
Point that gun at my head.
No fuckin' way... I'm not goin'.
You already abandoned that girl once.
You gonna do it again?
At least give me something
to protect myself with.
Are you kiddin' me?
Nope.
Lin?
What?
Fuck!
What the fuck was that?
Are you okay?
His tongue's been chewed off.
His pupils are completely blown out.
This guy's been coked out of his mind.
He messes with 'em, jacks 'em up.
They don't do what he says,
he turns him into his dogs.
It's like a zombie.
He's not a zombie.
He's just a person
or what's left of him.
There's enough drugs here
to turn anyone into an animal.
Holy shit.
What is this place?
Okay, listen up.
Here's what we're gonna do.
One...
Shit. What the fuck?
Come here. Come on. This way.
Come on!
Fucked
Fuckin' shit!
Come on, guys!
Hold there.
I got a gun!
What the fuck?!
And, you.
This asshole! Fuckin' walked us
right into that fuckin' shit!
- Relax!
- My cell's worthless.
I'm not getting any signal down here.
We're gettin' jammed.
All right, the police will be
all over this place any second.
We're in a concrete tomb,
1o feet underground
in a part of the city
that rats won't even shit on.
Nobody's gonna hear us because
there's no one around to listen.
Okay?
All right, let's get movin'.
Stay close.
Who's out there?
I can hear you.
Please, let me out? Please?
I can... I can get you out,
but you have to be quiet. Okay?
Okay.
Who are you?
How did you get out?
Did... did he let you out?
He didn't let me out. I got out.
He did this to me.
I'm Elena. What's your name?
Abby.
Do you know your way around here?
Oh, no, no, no.
We can't leave this room.
No, no, no.
- Abby.
- We can't just go.
We can get out of here, okay?
Okay, come on.
Come on.
The footprints.
Look at the spacing.
Hands up!
Stop.
Please.
Stay back!
Please, help me.
What the fuck is this?!
Stop right there or we'll shoot!
I didn't make it.
What didn't you make?
The collection.
And neither will you!
Get back!
Where's Arkin?
Arkin? There.
You don't wanna go in there.
Oh...
...thanks.
We should keep moving.
Yeah.
He likes me, you know.
Wait? What do you mean he likes...
You'll never win.
- What?
- You have a hearing aid.
You're not strong enough,
you're at a disadvantage.
- You can't win.
- Shh. Be quiet.
You weren't even supposed to get out!
- Shh.
- He's testing me!
- Be quiet, okay?
- He's testing me again!
- Be quiet. He's gonna hear you.
- Get away from me!
Get away from me!
Help me. Please.
Help me.
Please.
Hey! Hey, up here!
Somebody help me!
You're at the bad end of good luck.
I told you,
you should have cut his heels.
Paz, put something right here
so he can't so he can't...
Paz, give it to me.
Kept you on a leash.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Love this shit man.
It hurts... hold his hands.
- Guys up!
- Stay down, you son of a bitch.
- Wally!
Hey! Help me!
Help me!
No win. He's picking
us off one by one.
If you want to live
you've got to start...
...listening to me
before he takes us apart
and hangs us on the wall
of his fucking gallery!
We've got to work together
and get the hell out of here.
I am not leaving without her.
If you haven't found her by now,
she's probably dead.
I have been watching over her
since she was a little girl.
I promised her father...
I know where she is...
...but you've got to get me out of here.
That way.
Are you sure?
Mm-hmmm.
No. No, no, no.
It's not Elena. It's Paz.
Where you goin'?
It's a trap.
He's trying to
lure us away from Elena.
You're just going to let Paz die?
My objective is Elena.
Dude, fuck your objective.
Can't you hear that?
Don't act like you don't give a fuck.
Help!
Stay with her. Stay with her.
Help me!
Help me! Help me!
In here!
Wait! No! Help!
Hey. Hey.
Get me down.
Can you get me down?
- Help, no, turn around.
- I got you. Okay?
I got you. Okay?
Get out of there! Come on!
That way.
Go. Go.
- Get me out!
- Elena.
Oh! Get it off!
- You.
- He's coming.
Get me out of this fucking thing!
Get me out of this thing!
Get it off!
Lucello.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It's okay. Okay? It's okay.
We're going to get you out of here.
Okay? Let's go. I'm here.
No. No, don't trust her.
No. She's crazy.
- Okay. Wait, wait, wait.
- No.
Look at me.
You're safe. You're safe.
- We gotta go now.
- Yes.
Come on. Let's go.
I think I know a way out.
Let's go. Come on.
How many shots you got left?
Two.
Give me the gun.
Not a chance.
We are on the third floor.
I'm leading us out
the way we came in.
We can't make it with
those things down there.
Look, man.
It's time for you to trust me.
Give me the gun.
If I would have wanted you dead
I wouldn't have saved
your ass back there.
You left me.
Look, there was nothin' I could do.
All right? I'm sorry.
There was nothin' I could do.
I can get us out of here
if you give me the fuckin' gun.
What the hell?
Did you just shoot somebody?
Shots fired attracts attention.
Sorry, dude.
Man down attracts cops.
Well played.
Gunshot on the upper
right side multiple suspects.
Gotta let them know
exactly where we're at.
We have shots fired!
I repeat, shots fired!
Need back up.
1167 Tracy lane,
the old Sargento Hotel.
Shots coming from the north tower.
Just need to hole up
not draw attention to ourselves
and wait for them to raid the joint.
Sounds simple enough.
What the fuck did you just do?
- Oh, God.
- He likes me, you know.
I told you.
They're here!
Shut up! Shut up!
You're all gonna die!
Shut the fuck up!
Let's go.
I can't.
Oh, my God.
Go. Now. Save her.
We're not leaving you like this.
Arkin...
...bring Elena home.
Go!
Go, now!
- Go!
- Okay. Okay.
Fuck.
Team in position.
Go, go, go!
Red team take your six.
Wait for my word.
Weapons tight.
What is it?
No, it's a trap!
Shit.
I tried to tell you.
Fuck you!
You're him, bro.
What are you doin', man?
Come on! Fuck you!
You piece of shit!
You remember me?
Huh?
Oh yeah. You remember me,
don't you?
Okay. Here I am, fucker.
Fuck you! Come on!
- Fuckin' cock!
- Come on inside this cage, bitch!
Come on. I'd love to fuckin'
have a piece of you!
Come on, man!
I'll fuckin' eat your heart!
I'll tear it out of your fuckin' throat!
Come on! Come on, you fuckin' pussy!
What kind of pussy are you?
Pussy, pussy.
Come here, you little pussy. Come on!
- No! No!
- What are you doin'?
Come and get me!
What are you gonna do?
You gonna kill me?
You come in here and do it.
- You come in here.
- No! No!
- What are you doing?
You come and do it!
No!
No! We gotta get out.
We gotta get... we gotta...
ls there a way out? See if you can
fit your hand through.
- Can you fit it through?
- Pull.
- Where's the fuckin' knife?
- It slides right here.
Grab the latch and pull it.
- I can't do it!
- Come on. Take it out.
Take it out.
I'm gonna try and get the knife
Slide it towards me.
Okay. Towards you.
- Almost got it.
- I've got it! I got it, I got it!
No! No, no, no.
Shit!
There's gotta be another way.
There's gotta be.
What are you doing? Stop it.
What are you doing?
I need you to step on my forearm.
I need you to re-break it.
- What?
Shit... shit, shit.
Just do it! We don't have much time!
Paz, please. Elena Somebody...
...just fuckin' do it!
Do it!
We need the fire department,
right now.
Fuck!
It's working. It's working.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Let me reset it.
Give me your arm.
Ready?
- Oh, fuck!
- We can't stay here.
We gotta go.
- You guys get... you guys go.
- We gotta go! Come on! Come on.
All right, you're good.
Come on... let's go. Careful, careful.
Drop down two floors.
Don't look down. Cut the rope.
Don't go all the way.
- Got it?
- Yeah, go.
Shit.
Keep movin'.
This way.
Oh, my God. What...
No!
Get up, Arkin. Get up.
Help us!
Help! We're in here!
We got people in there.
Don't die yet! Get up.
I ain't done with you!
Look at me.
Hurry up!
Open it!
Help us!
Bring in the saws.
Come on! Hurry!
Chief, the coroner's
stationed the bodies
at the south end of the parking lot.
We're waiting for the final count.
We haven't seen anything
like this since the late '60s
and it was at those Bowery murders.
- Do you remember?
- Oh, yeah.
Her father went crazy,
from ingesting all those
chemicals from taxidermy.
Slaughtered his whole family
and sat them
at the Thanksgiving table.
Well, not the whole family.
I believe the little boy...
All those insects
you're quite the collector.
There are 200 mile radius from where
we last saw each other.
There are 14 licensed entomologists
and you were number 12.
Your daddy ran a museum, didn't he?
Fucked you up real good.
Turn around.
Are you here to kill me?
No. That'd be too nice.
First I'm gonna make you
feel everything that I felt
and then I'm gonna kill you.
So that you can never hurt any...
Fuck you!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
You're on his turf now.
He didn't let me out. I got out.
Come on! Hurry!
Daddy! Daddy!
She's all I have. Find her.
What the fuck?
I'm not leaving without her!
Damn it!
Stay down bitch.
Wally!
What the fuck!
Don't get any ideas.
Go now! Go!
We're running out of time.
You're all gonna die!
Hey, Jeff. Can you take me
to your apartment?
What the fuck?
Get out of my way!