Uh...
Guy...
Hey!
What the hell are you doing up here?
The bathroom. I saw her.
There's something wrong.
You're a real little
peeping tom, aren't you?
Get back to your room.
She fell. She's hurt. Mrs. Baran!
I told you, there's something wrong.
And I told you to get back
to your room. Now go.
Nicole.
Is she dead?
I don't know. I didn't check.
Jesus, Guy!
Well, get her pills, for God's sake.
She's still alive.
Call 911. She needs a doctor.
Go get another teacher.
Move it!
I'm alive?
No.
You're dead, this is heaven,
and I'm the virgin Mary.
Can you swallow?
Yeah?
Here you go.
I don't want them to see me like this.
Did they say how long?
Erik...
What happened?
It's just her heart again.
Get the boy out of here.
Failure, despair, passivity,
rebelliousness, defeat...
Why?
Well-meaning people
may offer dozens of theories,
all of them boiling down to blaming you...
the parent.
You won't find those theories here
at the St. Anselm school for boys.
Poor little losers.
Aren't you glad you never did drugs?
You never did, right?
I think we should open with
the zero tolerance talk...
Then the room searches.
Parents eat that shit up!
Man, you'd have to be at the end
of your rope to wind up here.
We are here, dick head.
Front steps in 10 minutes
for the video shoot.
And take your books home
over the long weekend.
There'll be a test on Tuesday.
Miss Horner?
-I'll be in a better mood on Tuesday.
-Yes, ma'am.
Don't let Guy catch you.
He's occupied.
You see? He didn't resist the urge
to assist another mother.
What happened to your eyes?
I don't know what you
did to him last night,
but your husband was in
one of his moods again.
Thank you very much.
Nicole!
You shouldn't be seen with him.
They all know, Mia.
It's better if we act Normal.
That way, it won't look bad after.
Anyway, I only went over there
because the wife chooses
to sedate herself.
What if she notices they're gone?
Oh, please. That woman has enough
drugs over there to relax China.
Good morning, ladies!
Oh, God.
Are we ready for our close-ups?
I can't wait for this filming to be done.
It just gets everyone overexcited.
And your husband... forgive me...
how he expects us to handle more students
without having more staff...
Lovely seeing you last night.
Any time Estelle and I can
assist you two star-crossed...
Your eye, madam... is something
wrong with your eye?
Allergies.
Ah. I'm not surprised.
Well, if you don't quit for
yourself, think of us.
Second-hand smoke does kill, too, you know.
Not reliably.
Thanks.
-This is disgusting.
-Hey, you going to eat that?
I've got to eat it. I'm starving.
And then we thought we'd cut
to a talking head of you,
you know, consequences,
a system kids can believe in,
blah, blah, blah, then do
talks with some of the kids.
I once was lost, but now I'm found...
that classic boys' town stuff.
Success stories are our speciality here.
As a matter of fact, I have
a very extra ordinary...
We want to get some footage of
the pool once it's cleaned.
Can we get that, this weekend?
I'm a poor man, guys.
As much as I'd like to,
I can't afford to maintain a
pool all summer for show.
But, it's just...
young... young boys frolicking,
sound minds and sound bodies,
the clean Appalachian
Mountain air, that...
type of thing.
O.K. We'll skip it.
But we really want to shoot
the kitchen work crew.
Yeah, take a number.
Hopkins,
would you take this away? I'm not hungry.
Our chef's skill is not presentation.
I think you'll find it
tastes better than it looks.
It would have to.
Peas mushy. Pepper.
Guy...
You promised.
It's a sin to waste.
Aren't you the expert on sin?
No.
You are.
Mia.
No one's eating.
Well, don't encourage them.
Use your great moral force on my behalf.
Eat.
It's perfectly edible.
See?
Pick up your fork.
Just pick up your fork.
Pick it up.
Take some food and put it in your mouth.
That didn't kill you.
Now swallow.
Swallow it.
For God's sake, Guy.
Swallow it for once in your life.
Actually, I...
I'm afraid I'm quite hungry myself,
so if you're not going to finish it...
Mr. Katzman,
will you please tell the table proctors
that no student will be
allowed to leave this room
until every plate is clean.
Yes.
Thank you.
A child bride, gentlemen.
That's what I married, a child bride.
And each year, she grows
younger and younger.
She's worse than the boys she teachers.
You're not finished yet.
Eat.
Again.
You know, I think this might help.
Oh!
Look what I did.
Hopkins,
could you take this away, please?
Excuse me.
Wasn't that fun?
Don't you wish you had that on tape?
Bet you're just kicking
yourselves now, huh?
Excuse me.
I'm...
I'm sure Miss Horner will
keep something hot for you.
Mia?
Why do you make me do that to you?
Why?
You always do it.
And you always will.
No, no, no. Only when you misbehave.
Like that stunt you pulled on Sunday.
When you do things like that,
do you know how bad that makes me feel?
You should think about me sometimes.
I... just don't know you.
You know me, Mia.
The problem is, you just
don't understand me.
Isn't that right?
I know what my little nun likes.
I thought you weren't coming.
Hey. Go ahead, get in. Let's go.
They'll see.
Well, we want them to see.
They're our alibis.
Come on.
You take my bedroom. It's
down by the bathroom.
And stay here till she sees you, O.K.?
Ah, Nicole!
What a surprise!
Irving, it's Nicole!
Miss Horner, I should say,
now that you are the landlady.
I think about your poor mother every day.
Bijou!
Well, come in.
No, we can't today. We're just
here for the weekend.
But I would like you to meet
my principal, Mrs. Baran.
Hello.
Oh, how nice.
Welcome to Pittsburgh, Mrs. Baran,
and the entire Three Rivers area.
Oh, can you manage?
Irving!
Well, it must be the post office, then.
Half the people that work down there
aren't American any more, anyway.
I'll send you another check tomorrow.
I'll drop by for it.
Tomorrow night, say?
You can bring your house
guest, if you like.
She'll be busy.
You look more like your mother every day.
From behind, you can really see it.
I've been to see a lawyer,
and she tells me a divorce
would be very simple.
I could even keep the school.
I don't want to talk about
it on the phone, Guy.
All right.
I'm at Nicole's house.
Fine.
Yeah.
Well, tomorrow night is best.
We'll be out tomorrow.
All right.
After 8:00.
Fine. Goodbye.
Good for you.
It's good to get it over with.
Now we can get on with our evening.
I should take him off speed-dial.
One good drink oughta do it.
I can't do this.
He's never going to leave you alone.
Does he leave me alone?
If I give him the school...
If you give him the school,
he'll just sell it.
Then where will all the future
Lee Harvey Oswalds come from?
Anyway, it's not like he's
the one that won't let go.
What do you mean?
What I mean is,
you still want him,
or you wouldn't keep sleeping with him.
It's not love.
You don't love people
who treat you this way.
Where'd you get that, off a talk show?
You know, I'm not surprised
he likes to come to me
after he sleeps with you.
I don't care.
I hate him.
I don't feel anything.
You don't feel anything.
How about when he does this?
Hmm?
Do you feel anything
when he does this?
You don't feel anything?
He doesn't do that to me.
Don't you lie to me!
We're not going to get anywhere
if you start lying to me now.
I know. It's me. My fault.
It's not your fault.
I know. I...
Oh, just snap out of it. all right!
It's not your fault, O.K.?
It's his fault. He is who he is.
And he's going to keep being who he is
and doing what he does.
And he's going to do it
and do it and do it...
We're never going to
be free until he's dead.
He's my husband, Nicole.
Oh, yeah?
Well, last week he was happy to stand by
and watch you die.
Pull yourself together. You're
going to scare him away.
He always parks out there
so the neighbours won't notice him.
He'll be coming in through the back door.
You're going?
Yes. I'm going to the
neighbours to keep them busy.
I need 10 minutes.
O.K.?
Yeah.
Courage.
Make yourself one.
I want you to hear what I'm saying, Guy.
I'm serious.
Ooh!
Mia's serious.
Give me the goddamn drink.
It's for your own good.
I'll be a lot easier to handle
with some of this in me, right?
Right.
It's a little cloudy.
What?
Whatever.
Do you want to talk, or do you
want to stare at me all night?
The lawyer says I can get a divorce
and keep the school.
I inherited it before I got married.
You put me on the title.
You need me to sign a quit-claim deed.
He didn't mention that?
Tsk-tsk.
What's the matter?
Are you all right?
What?
What were we talking about?
The title.
You forgot I'm on the title.
I could buy you out.
I could get a loan.
You give me the school,
and I'll give you a divorce.
Frankly, I didn't have to get
married to have lousy sex.
No.
I did.
Come on, Mia.
Ooh.
Why don't you have a drink with me?
What did I ever do to you, Guy?
What did I do that's so wrong?
You try living with a fucking angel.
It's easier living with a dog.
I'm not your little dog, Guy.
You do something with your hair?
Yeah. You did something with your hair.
Let me make you feel good
like you know I can.
Isn't that nice?
You don't want to split up, do you?
You don't even love me.
But you can't let go.
What was that?
Something on TV.
Oh, you're so good, Bijou!
Now that was her alarm bark.
It... it's like her stranger bark,
only a little bit higher.
That doesn't sound very good,
that kind of noise, Irv.
Why don't I just turn
up the TV a little bit?
Their marriage is worth saving.
We just heard from Tim and Tracy
who have been married
for less than a year,
but have already
been separated five times.
Will they reconcile?
I'll find out.
-Don't you run away from me!
-Aah!
When is she coming back?
You feel that?
You feel it?
What did you do for feelings
before I came along, Mia?
You shouldn't get me mad.
It won't happen again.
Come here, Mia.
Have another drink, Guy.
You deserve it.
What are you doing to me?
Listen!
I don't know you that well.
I don't ever want you to come
back to Tennessee again!
That's the one...
has returned.
I hope that was an empty bottle, George.
You can't afford to waste good liquor.
Oh. Yeah.
I'm going to wait until this is in colour.
Liar! You haven't...
You little bitch!
You're trying to kill me!
Mia...
Help me.
Say you're sorry, Guy.
I love you.
How is he?
It wasn't quick like you said.
Yeah, or quiet.
Well,
it's attempted murder
now if he does wake up.
We have no choice.
Come on.
O.K, get out his wallet.
It's O.K. If your fingerprints are on it.
Check and see if there's
any gas station receipts.
There's nothing.
O.K, put it back.
Put it back.
Now,
go turn on the radio in
case there's more noise.
Uhh!
# But #
# in the arms of love #
# your embrace #
# fits me like a glove #
# in my world #
# You #
# took control of me #
# and I fell #
# in love #
# hopelessly... #
Aah!
Get the water bottle!
Is it over?
It's over.
Are you all right?
You're blaming yourself.
Don't.
For wanting him, I mean.
I was the same way.
Ohh! Oh, my God.
He tried to move. He was alive.
Nicole...
Let Irv help.
Look at them. It's too heavy.
Uh, Mrs. Baran...
This is Irv.
Hi.
Well, he's... he's good
at this kind of thing.
Allow me.
-No. It's fine.
-Please.
Bend your knees.
All right. Ready?
1, 2, 3...
O.K, your end in first, Irv.
What do you got in here?
Books.
O.K
Thanks, Irv.
Oh, wait!
I made a coffee cake for your trip!
Here. Oh.
Here.
-Let's go.
-Right.
Nice shape on that principal.
Hmm.
That Nicole's always been
a cold fish, though.
Yeah.
Bijou...
Bad dog.
You take mine. I'll take his.
-Let's stay together.
-Sure.
Oh, Jesus.
Attention, all units.
All units, accident on
the Pennsylvania turnpike.
Exit 12 is closed.
Units responding, please
give me your E.T.A.
E.M.T. is on their way. Over.
Move your vehicle right away.
Don't worry, we'll get
you out on the road
and out of this mess in no time.
Excuse me,
sir?
Yes, ma'am?
Can I help, officer?
No. Everything is fine.
Can I give the woman a lift?
I'm O.K. It's drivable.
It's not drivable.
You have a flat.
Oh.
Come on, Buddy, help
me get this going.
Sorry it's so heavy.
Pull it out straight.
Books, you know?
Let me help you with that.
Look, ma'am,
just return to your car, O.K?
I mean, there's nothing you're
gonna be able to do tonight.
Thanks a lot.
Uhh!
Push.
O.K.
All right. Come on.
Go get the lights.
Go.
All right.
Oh, my God.
O.K.
All right.
Shit.
Bastard.
All right, it's over. We better
get the hell out of here.
He'll never hurt us again.
What do we do now?
Wait for the body to surface.
They'll do an autopsy, maybe.
He was drunk. He fell in.
When will it come up?
Tomorrow, maybe.
Oh,
come on. You can't
pull that off.
Why hasn't he risen yet?
It'll happen.
Be patient.
I'm not going to be able to do this.
Well, I suggest you try.
It isn't like you burnt the toast, Mia.
You killed your husband.
It's a little off the chart demerit-wise,
understand?
You're so calm.
Look at you.
Your hair is done.
You've got make up on...
This is a day like any other day.
We did what we had to do, and it's done,
O.K.?
It was self-defence.
You've been taking it for too long now.
You finally said, 'fuck off.'
Good for you.
Fuck him.
Fuck them.
Everything but 'fuck you.'
Roughly.
Now, come on.
Places.
I desire.
Je desire.
They desire.
Ils desirent.
They desire...
Feminine.
Elles desirent.
Hey, Tad, over here!
Ms. Horner. While the cat's
away, the mice will...
Apparently.
Not at all.
Guy and I talked to a new supplier Friday.
Portions are smaller.
Is Dr. Baran here?
His car's back in the garage.
It was gone all weekend.
Excuse me?
Because, if he is, could
you ask him please,
if he's going to take
his classes tomorrow?
I can't possibly take on
any more... Mrs. Baran!
-Boys!
-You idiot.
What?
Why are you torturing her?
Isn't it obvious she
doesn't know where he is?
Miss Horner, please.
The students.
I don't blame you, though.
He could make an effort for your sakes...
Uh, for her sake.
You're drawing attention to yourself.
I'm allowed to brood.
My husband's disappeared.
You'll feel better when the body surfaces.
Yeah.
It always perks me up.
What do your saints say?
I'm brooding.
I'm not praying.
Lost your faith, huh?
I never really had
any to begin with, I guess.
Never believed in any of it...
God, the virgin Mary,
that life begins at 40,
and that people are all
just basically good inside.
Pretty soon, we'll be the Same person.
See how nice things turned out?
I'm going inside.
You know, it wasn't too smart
changing the food like that.
You never would have done
that if he was alive.
What's the point in killing him, then?
I like making it better for the boys.
Still, if it's all the Same with you,
I'd rather not hang for fried chicken.
Nicole, why did you kill him?
You could have left him.
You could have left here.
I was underestimated.
Stop looking at it.
People are watching us.
I can't stand it much longer.
Finally.
We're going to have to get
the net from the shed.
Who wants to go?
Me! Me! Me! Me!
Desantis?
Ohh!
What are we going to do now?
Now, we'll have to drain the pool.
I'll get it.
No!
-Why not?
-He's a child.
Go and see if you can find it!
There's something down there.
It's a lighter.
Hey, that's Dr. Baran's.
Remember the close-up when
he was playing with it?
Did you see anything else?
No.
All right, that's enough.
Go inside and change.
Now, take that up to Dr. Baran's office.
We'll have to drain the pool.
And refill it?
Well, that's up to Dr. Baran.
All right, everybody. That's enough.
Go on.
Go on inside and get ready
and go back to class. Go on.
Mia...
Mr. Gannon,
will you drain the pool?
I've got orders not to.
But my keys are in there.
Please?
Right away, please.
Here's the penis
and the scrotum,
that holds the testicles,
or testes, inside.
Now, when you're around 14...
maybe sooner, maybe later...
the testes start making a chemical
substance called a hormone.
It's this hormone that causes the changes.
It starts hair growing
here under your arms
and on your face.
Mr. Gannon,
what is it?
Something blocking the drain!
Since you want it done right away,
I can't help the noise.
You all know what sperm is?
Yes.
Go on, Mr. Nunez.
Atlantic...
Pacific...
Indian...
Arctic.
Arctic...
Class?
Atlantic...
Pacific...
Indian...
Arctic...
Mediterranean...
Gulf of Mexico...
And Caribbean.
Australian...
Hudson bay...
Baltic sea...
North sea...
English channel...
Irish sea...
Bering sea.
Mrs. Baran fainted! Let's go!
-Get a doctor.
-I'll go.
Doctor's very worried about you.
-He thinks this is serious.
-Where is the body?
Someone moved it. That's apparent.
-Someone saw us put it in?
-No.
Well, I don't know.
Maybe.
I've got to find him.
No. Mia, let's just stick
to our story. O.K?
It's even better like this
'cause we really don't know where he is.
He'll turn up.
If he doesn't, all the better. O.K?
-Did you take your heart medicine?
-No.
We've got to act naturally.
You have to start asking about Guy,
you know, be more concerned,
like you would be
if he was really missing.
Ohh! Ohh!
Ohh!
What?
His suit.
Oh, my God.
4 x 6 colour prints, please.
Could I have those in 20 minutes?
Ah! Dios mio!
Ask her.
Tell her if she sees anything to call us.
He's disappeared.
Vaya con dios,
O.K.?
Let's just get these and
get out of here, O.K?
Someone's watching us.
Someone with Guy's camera.
You need to eat, honey.
I'm not hungry.
Thank you.
He is dead, Mia.
He is dead. We killed him together.
You saw him die.
What about the pictures?
I think someone took them
before he was killed...
Right?
Who?
We'll find that out when
they start blackmailing us.
He's dead.
This is another thing.
Look, there's something
I haven't told you.
Open it.
It's from the school accounts.
That's why there's never any money there.
It was for Guy and me.
He told me someone stole it.
Well, I found it when I
was looking for the body.
You killed him for money?
Believe me. It wasn't the only reason.
There's $50,000 there, Mia.
We'll split it.
You can use it to pay for
your goddamn fried chicken.
I can go to the police.
I can tell them what we did.
What you did.
We both did it.
Well, I don't think they'll
see that as beneficial to me.
They'll say, 'the wife gets the school,
'the money he embezzled, her freedom.
'What did the other woman get?
Nothing.'
That's how they'll look at it.
I'll say we were lovers.
Well, you can take the
girl out of the convent.
I thought we had the Same reason.
We did have the Same reason.
I just had an extra one.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
I couldn't do it now.
If you hadn't found this,
you killed the one person
who could have told you where it was.
He said we were partners,
and then he acted alone.
Mia!
Hey.
Where you going?
I've got to go.
What are you talking about?
This.
It was under my door this morning.
It's over.
He's been found.
This is Sunbury.
This is 20 Miles from here.
Now, how would he get there?
I don't know.
Someone took him out of the pool
and dumped him in the river.
I don't know.
Hey, Mia, but I think we
should call the police first
and file a missing persons report.
I've got to go. It's him.
All right. I'll go with you.
No, I'll wait.
Fine.
Hold on.
You can wait in there.
No. I'll be fine.
Just...
don't let him forget me.
You're not going to light that are you?
You can light these?
In America?
Nah. I'm quitting.
Nicorette.
Excuse me.
My husband is missing.
I think this might be him.
How long?
Four days.
Have you filled out
a missing persons report?
No.
So, has he left before
without telling you?
The description fits.
Uh-huh.
O.K. John Doe, 180 pounds, 6-foot even.
That's right.
Describe his clothing.
The body was naked,
that's what it says here.
We don't always tell the press everything.
Well, I... I didn't see him
the day he disappeared.
Any jewellery?
A wedding ring. That's all.
He doesn't always wear that.
Can I just see the body?
Appendectomy scar?
No.
I see.
Hold on.
Howie?
I think we have Mrs. Doe here.
Hi.
You've got to prepare yourself.
The sand does a lot of damage.
Oh, my God.
Is that your husband, ma'am?
No.
Oh?
Poor kid.
Wasn't her husband. Never
saw him before in her life.
Excuse me?
Mrs. Baran?
Who are you?
Please, forgive me for intruding.
Come, sit down.
Coffee, please.
I... I saw you at the sheriff's station.
I got your name off the view request.
Shirley Vogel.
You're the police?
Cagney and Lacey.
That kind of thing.
You know, they met with me once?
Research stuff.
Nice girls.
I say 'girls.'
That O.K. With you?
Anyway...
Flash forward 10 years,
I'm on medical leave.
The big 'c.'
Air.
I'm sorry.
Ah, whatever.
I knew it was coming.
My family...
never two boobs in a coffin.
I'm sorry, but...
I don't know why you're here.
Remember your husband?
Uh... could I get some coffee, please?
You mean...
I'm sure he'll turn up.
Yeah. Wrapped around a pier apparently.
I mean, you drove all the way from...
That's very kind of you, but...
Who the hell am I, right?
I don't blame you.
Look, um...
I know a Guy in the
department in Hazelton.
I could call him, he'll
visit, get the details.
I don't want to make it official.
Suppose it's just intentional.
Here's your coffee.
Yeah. I know what you mean.
Men.
How do they sleep at night?
They have sex.
That's how they sleep at night.
He might be home already.
This place. Jesus.
It's no sizzler, is it?
He'll be furious if I've
gone to the police.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
Keep it private.
You know, once the boys get
their hooks into you...
You know, I couldn't afford you.
We run a school.
A school?
Then you can forget the police.
You can't afford that kind of publicity.
Look,
2, 3 days, I chase him down
to some girlfriend's house,
and I scare the shit out of him.
That wouldn't be easy.
Look, I...
I don't want money.
I mean, look at me. I'm...
chasing all over
Pennsylvania for lunch dates
with guys I couldn't stand 10 years ago.
Give me something to do.
You ever smoke?
No.
Yeah.
Well...
Look at this security system.
You know, what is this, a
piece of the true cross?
Aren't you hungry?
Oh.
I thought I should eat.
You know what your problem is?
You're feeling guilty.
No.
I'm not.
It's not your fault.
It's men.
Testosterone.
They should put it in bombs.
You want that?
Mrs. Baran would like me to help...
Informally.
Well, Ms. Vogel... or is it detective?
Detective.
Well, frankly, detective, I don't
think we need to overreact.
We've seen this before.
We have?
We, we, we. What is she, the school nurse?
When was the last time
you saw your husband?
Last Saturday.
He was asleep when we left at 7:00.
Nicole and I drove out to her duplex.
Oh, look!
This must be nice... when it's full.
Isn't it kinda dangerous
keeping it empty like this?
Yeah. Well, we lost some keys in there.
You know, I think we should
get back to our students.
They're on work crew this week.
Yeah. So I noticed.
Must save money, I bet, having
the kids keep up the place.
These older buildings.
So, none of his friends
know where he might be?
We haven't asked them.
You know, it's kind of awkward.
'Hey, my husband's disappeared,
have you seen him?' You know.
Her husband.
It wouldn't be awkward for me.
If it's O.K, Mrs. Baran,
maybe I could take a look
at his address book.
You know, detective,
I don't think we need to make
a Mountain out of a molehill.
Exactly. I mean can you imagine
this place crawling with police.
Wouldn't be the kind of thing you'd write
home in letter about, now, would it?
We'll tiptoe.
Would you be kind enough to
show me your husband's things?
Of course.
So nice meeting you, Ms. Horner.
Oh, this is lucky.
A phone bill.
Yeah. It came this morning.
May I?
Ah. This must be Ms. Horner.
Pittsburgh.
Earlier this month.
I... I call her there sometimes
when she goes there on weekends.
53 minutes.
72 minutes.
Girl talk.
Yeah.
This goes through Monday.
He didn't call you there over the weekend?
No.
What kind of car does your husband drive?
We have one car... the Cherokee.
How did you break the tail light?
I don't know.
It happened a while ago.
What was he wearing when he disappeared?
Um... His blue suit.
Could I see his closet?
Yes.
It's missing.
His blue suit...
And his belt...
with the silver buckle.
You just have to look and you know.
Good for you.
Place for everything,
and everything in its place.
I hope we're not too late.
There's video cameras out there.
Is that the news?
Oh, no. It's just some PR for the school.
Is that all, detective? I'm really tired.
Of course.
The address book?
It's in his office.
I'll find it.
Oh, um...
It's just one more thing.
That isn't the suit there, is it?
Mia,
you're needed to take Voss' classes.
Oh, detective, you're still here.
Yes, I was just wondering if...
this is the suit Dr. Baran
was wearing on Sunday.
No.
But close. He had two.
Well, maybe I'll go and speak with
some of the other teachers now.
Ms. Horner.
Mm-hmm.
Why did you bring her here?
I'm supposed to act concerned.
Anyway, it keeps the police away.
Fine.
That woman should wear a prosthesis.
I hate that in-your-face survivor crap.
I'm really tired, Nicole.
It's O.K. You did fine.
I heard you from the hallway.
Just don't see her alone any more.
Promise?
Can I get a print-out of that?
Yeah. You can get a dub of it, too.
Oh, this is some really cool stuff.
Total inside edition material.
Yeah. The magic hour tape.
This guy gives 'prick' a bad name.
What doesn't?
I want this one, too.
O.K, if x equals 4, then x minus 2 is?
-2.
-Great.
10 plus x, when x equals 3 is?
I'm talking to you.
Oh, um, 13.
Thank you.
Ahem.
All right, I want you to
review these equations,
continue to work them until I return.
And stay in your seats.
This is Ms. Horner.
Nicole, this is Lisa Campos.
Hello.
Ms. Campos is looking for Guy.
Well, I'm sure Mrs. Baran told you
that Dr. Baran is away on business.
You said you didn't know where he was.
Well...
Someone has to pay.
He said he would, but...
I thought it over.
I don't want to wait till
next month like he said.
Excuse me?
Ms. Campos is expecting.
Unto her a child will be born.
What does this have to do with Dr. Baran?
What do you think?
What makes you think that it's Guy's?
That's what he said. But come on,
I would know.
I don't sleep around.
And he said he'd pay.
I'm not putting it on my card.
I'm maxed out.
O.K.
Well...
So, you're absolutely certain
this is Dr. Baran's?
What does she have to say about it?
Abortion is murder.
Well, I'm going to have an
anaesthetic, for God's sake.
How much is this going to cost?
They want 650,
and that's a clinic.
I'm not holding anybody up here, you know?
I just want what he promised.
Besides...
It's your husband.
You don't want me to have his baby.
I wouldn't have come,
only he said you knew
about his girlfriends,
Mrs. Baran.
Thank you.
And tell him not to call
when he does get back, you know?
It's boundary time.
Incidentally, Ms. Campos...
When was the last time you saw Dr. Baran?
Sunday afternoon.
I dropped by.
He was real wired-up about something.
Figured you two had a fight.
Make him pay you back.
Anyway...
Goodbye.
You knew about her?
Yeah.
Since last fall.
Right after you came.
You should've told me about her.
Why would I want you
to be hurt like I was?
Somebody knows.
You know...
there was a big pile-up on the I-80.
And, uh,
technically, there
could've been a mistake.
I mean, does anyone else
use it for their travel?
No.
No one you can think of?
All they got was a list
of license plate numbers.
Technically, they could've
gotten a number wrong,
But it looks like that was his car.
There's no way to know
if he was actually driving the car or not.
I was just telling Mrs. Baran
I ran Dr. Baran's license
plate through the DMV.
That pile-up Monday evening on the I-80?
He was in it.
The report doesn't tell us much,
but his car's right
there on the print out.
It's one of 22.
Didn't you tell me it was an old dent?
Did I?
Let's say he left Sunday,
wearing one of the blue suits.
Couldn't he have been
heading to Pittsburgh?
We know, he stopped for gas
Sunday in Williamsport.
Oh?
Yes.
Mrs. Baran gave me his credit card
numbers on the phone this morning.
Anyway,
doesn't it look like he
was trying to see you?
Pittsburgh is a big town.
You're sure you didn't hear from
him any time after Saturday?
-Oh...
-That's not the kind of thing we'd forget.
Mia?
Dear, aren't you on room checks?
Oh, yeah. Excuse me.
Well, I'll be in touch.
I'm glad she didn't ask.
There weren't any charges on
the cards from Sunday on.
What are room checks?
Drug searches. Some of the
kids here used to use.
My son had a habit, years ago.
My husband and I looked
into this kind of place.
He's dead now.
Your husband?
Son.
I.V. drug users.
You know what happens to them nowadays.
But my ex is alive.
Isn't God quirky?
You got an ex?
Nothing official.
Mine thought he was God's gift to women.
Like that topped my list...
God, please send me something
that'll wear black nylon socks
to bed every night of his life.
My idea of heaven
is a place where they screw you barefoot.
You make me want to pass a hat for you.
Don't feel sorry for me.
I got him to leave.
Every cloud has a silver lining.
He was too dull to kill.
What about her?
She ever want to kill her husband?
Why would she do that?
Maybe she found out
you were sleeping with him.
Oh, that's so clever.
What'd you do, ask a faculty
member or any student?
I know. You read it
in the brochure, right?
So she knew?
Of course she knew. Ask her.
Come on, she's not a murderer.
She's an ex-nun for Christ's sake.
Yeah. Remember them?
They disappeared overnight
like dial phones.
What about you?
What if he wouldn't leave her?
Honey, if I couldn't get
a man to leave her,
I wouldn't kill him. I'd kill myself.
Well, he has left her...
Apparently.
One way or another.
Well...
Unless there's anything else...
Yeah, there is. Just one more thing.
Guy did it barefoot.
'Did, ' Ms. Horner?
Don't you mean 'does'?
Mrs. Baran?
It's dinner time, Erik.
You should go inside with the others.
Are you O.K.?
You know the rules, Erik.
Your table won't be able to
eat before you're there.
It's so much nicer here since he left.
I hope he never comes back.
Where did you find those?
I found them yesterday.
Give them to me.
They're good, though.
They're just a little rusty.
Give them to me!
Doesn't mean anything.
The pool was empty, and...
maybe he saw them at the bottom.
I didn't.
Did you?
If they were so plain to see...
Don't you see what it means?
Yeah. It means we overlooked them.
It means Guy's watching us.
He's alive.
He's dead,
and I'm not sorry.
And neither are you, if you're
really honest with yourself.
Killing him is a good thing...
like planting a tree.
Maybe there is a God.
What are you talking about?
I haven't believed for so long.
So when the pool was empty, I thought,
maybe there is a God.
And he knows what we did,
and he's coming for us.
It's not God, honey.
That's a lady detective with one breast.
You're always laughing at me.
So was Guy.
He must be laughing now.
I'm not laughing at you, Mia.
You are...
A little.
Inside.
It's lonely without God, isn't it?
It's just lonely...
Period.
They're filling the pool!
When's it going to be done?
Should be soon.
That's great.
We should have cancelled this.
Every thing's fine. Just calm down.
20 bucks they killed him.
Dykes.
And that would explain why
they're not all over you.
Thanks.
We really could use Dr.
Baran for these shots.
Well, he's still away on business.
So, we'll do without him.
I don't want to be in it.
O.K. It's parents' day,
and these are your parents.
Now, boys, you're happy,
but try not to look relieved.
O.K.?
Um...
I'm glad to see you, mom and dad, but,
boy, is this school great!
Moms,
one or two of you can look misty-eyed.
Who wants to be misty?
O.K. Here.
All right, you, and, uh...
You.
Don't overdo it.
Let's make sure everyone
has their numbers.
Number one?
O.K.
Is that Dr. Baran?
What are you talking about?
Up there on the second
floor, at the window.
Wait. I'll play it back.
Well, it's someone, that's for sure.
It's Guy.
Bless me, father, for I have sinned...
What are you doing?
I'm fasting and praying for our sins.
I want you to stop that...
And come inside.
You're not well.
Each time I go to sleep,
I have to kill him over and over.
No, Mia. Someone's playing a game with us.
Now, come inside.
You're ill.
It's holy water.
Come on.
What are you looking at?
Go inside!
Let's get out of here.
Go in!
Go!
Where's your heart medicine?
I'm sure it's there.
No. I think you're out.
I'll go to the pharmacy
and get it refilled.
You should take these.
Here. Go on.
You'll be out like a
light before I get back.
I want you to go, Nicole.
O.K.
No. I mean away.
Leave the school...
For good.
I'm sick of you.
If they only knew.
They will if you keep acting like this.
You know, the church can't save you now,
no matter how much you pay them off.
Look, I know you gave
that priest my money.
The money should go to
the people who love you.
It should go to the people you love.
They don't love you, Mia. They used you.
And now that you're scared,
you're using them, too.
Like you used me?
You're a good teacher, Nicole.
We should have paid you more.
You like playing the victim, don't you?
Get out!
Leave me alone!
Fine, if that's the way you want it,
but let me tell you one thing,
from one Saint to another...
you should keep right on praying.
Wear your knees out that way for a change.
Hello?
Oh.
Aah!
Who's there?
Get the water bottle!
Aah!
He's dead.
God forgive you...
Aah!
You're a lot tougher than I
thought, you little bitch.
Jesus, Guy.
Sucking on that douche-bag
hose for eight hours...
And that ride in the back...
I've still got a cold.
I don't care what the doctors say...
That fucking heart was made of iron.
I tried to reach you to call it off.
Call it off?
What for?
I wish I could have seen her face.
Some of those gags were great.
What are we going to do with
that goddamn detective now?
Snooping around.
She got hers.
You were supposed to call me.
I think you should find the body.
I'll show up tomorrow...
And you can break the news to me.
I'll be grief-stricken.
I think you should go.
Go?
Yeah.
Why?
Haven't you missed me?
Yeah.
That's better.
It's over.
So, let's celebrate.
O.K, but I...
I don't... you know...
I just... I don't want you to get caught.
I think you'd better...
Is this natural?
Huh?
I mean, the tub is full.
Hmm?
Shouldn't she be undressed?
Yeah, O.K.
Aah!
-I thought she was dead.
-I...
I thought she was.
I did.
It's over. Look,
she's not going to do anything.
-We'll think of something else.
-Lying bitch!
We'll do something different with her!
Just let her go!
-You're with her!
-No, I'm not!
-Yes, you are.
-No!
Mia, go!
You...
bitch!
Aah!
-No!
-Just you wait!
No! No!
Mia!
Don't you run from me!
I said stop!
No! No!
Come here!
Aah!
Let me see your face!
Was it a lonely week...
Or did you two keep each other company?
How does it feel, after all
these years of sainthood,
finding out we're perfectly matched?
You're just like me...
Soul mates.
-Aah!
Bitch.
Do you want to confess before you die?
Say, 'I'm sorry, Guy.'
Maybe I'll forgive you, even if God won't.
Fuck you!
You son of a bitch!
This is a week late, ass hole!
Aah!
Mia.
Oh, Jesus.
Mia, come on.
Aah!
This way it'll be easier
to claim self-defence.
You know, paramedics can work miracles.
One of us should go get one right away.
Oh, Mia.
I'm sorry.
Goodbye.