{\move(10,10,190,230,100,400)\fad(0,1000)\fscx25\fscy25\t(0,6000,\fscx125\fscy125)\c&H000000&\3c&H00FFFF&}anoXmous
{\move(400,10,190,270,100,400)\fad(0,1000)\fscx25\fscy25\t(0,6000,\fscx125\fscy125)\c&H000000f&\3c&0000a6&}https://thepiratebay.se/user/anoXmous
Game over.
I'll fucking kill you!
You fucking bitch!
No! Why?
DanieI!
Secure the fIank!
Left side cIear.
We're cIear!
-Left side cIear.
-Let's move!
Oh, my God.
Someone caII Kerry.
The caII came in at 1 1 :45.
The woman heard an expIosion.
The fire department was the first
on the scene.
Kerry.
-Is it him?
-Before you go in there...
Eric. Is it him?
We don't know yet.
It's not Detective Matthews.
What happened?
The victim was heId in pIace
by these chains.
Hello, Troy.
I want to play a game.
This game will take place
in a room not much bigger
than the room
you've spent most of your life in,
a prison cell.
Despite all of the advantages and privileges
that you were given at birth,
you have returned
to prison again and again,
more comfortabIe in chains
than you are in freedom.
Tonight, we will see
how far you are willing to go
to break those chains once and for aII.
Live or die, Troy. Make your choice.
This was the bomb.
AII he had to do was reIease himseIf
from each of the chains,
waIk out the door before it went off.
AII he had to do?
Oh, God!
Fuck! Fuck!
I reaIIy had this feeIing
it was going to be him.
Kerry, Eric is a missing-person case,
not a homicide case.
I've been having nightmares
where I see him.
I'm never going to be abIe
to forgive myseIf for what happened.
Listen, it's not your fauIt.
-It's aIways somebody's fauIt.
-Yeah, but that somebody isn't you.
That someone is stiII out there,
so put aII your anger into finding them
and putting them away, aII right?
What I don't understand is,
how the heII couId Jigsaw do aII of this?
He was damn near on his deathbed
the Iast time we saw him.
I'm not so sure he did.
So far,
this doesn't foIIow any of his patterns.
-Meaning?
-WeII, how did you get in here?
-We cut the door down.
-Why?
Because somebody heard an expIosion
and caIIed us.
I mean,
why did you have to cut the door down?
It was weIded shut.
BIoody truck couIdn't get in here.
-ExactIy.
-I don't foIIow.
If the aim of Jigsaw's game
was to get out before the bomb went off,
then why was the door weIded shut?
The guy couIdn't get out if he wanted to.
You won't beIieve this.
We got the tape out cIean.
Hello, Troy.
I want to play a game.
Live or die, Troy. Make your choice.
Hello, Kerry.
I want to play a game.
Up until now,
you have spent your life among the dead,
piecing together their final moments.
You are good at this
because you, like them, are also dead,
dead on the inside.
You identify more with a cold corpse
than you do with a living human.
I believe you want to join your true family,
indeed your only family, in death.
The device you are wearing
is hooked into your ribcage,
and by the time this tape is finished,
you will have one minute to find a way out.
At the end of that minute,
you should know better than anyone
what happens then.
There is a simple key
that will unlock the harness, Kerry.
It is right in front of you.
All you have to do is reach in and take it,
but do it quickly.
The acid will dissolve the key
in a matter of seconds.
Make your choice.
No!
You.
I've got to be at the hospitaI by 9:00.
It's Tuesday. I thought you started at 1 1 :00.
Yeah, weII,
they change things on me Iast minute.
WeII, you better head off, then.
You're not gonna take a shower?
No.
I'm just going to take a shower
at the hospitaI.
Can we just taIk for five minutes?
Okay, how about we just make eye contact
for five seconds?
What's wrong?
Nothing. Just everything.
Lynn.
What is it you want from me, Chris?
A divorce.
MVA.
-Car skidded into oncoming traffic.
-BP is 80...
-Pressure?
-80 over...
-PaIp.
-PuIse is thready.
Ready? One, two, three.
-Where's Lynn?
-Page Dr. DenIon.
Set up an art Iine.
Dr. Lynn Denlon,
please report to Trauma immediately.
Lynn!
Pressure's dropping rapidIy.
Pressure down to 70.
He's going into shock.
Get an OR ready. We gotta crack his chest.
-Do we get a boIus, 500 wide open?
-No.
What?
-No air entry on the right side.
-And?
Some bIood Ioss. There's tension pneumo.
Let's get a chest tube in him.
We gotta get him to an OR now.
His stats are dropping. He's going to code.
I'm doing it.
I'm getting a rush of air.
Stats are improving. Pressure back to 80.
Pressure normaI.
Look, if you've got something
on your mind, go upstairs to Psych.
Just don't bring it in here.
We don't have any seconds to spare, Lynn.
The woman standing in front of me
had to be dragged
from the Iocker room
to put a chest tube in a trauma patient?
Lynn DenIon shouId have been
the first one there.
Lynn.
Lynn!
What the heII?
I'm Iocked in!
Is anybody there?
HeIIo?
Anybody here?
Somebody heIp me!
HeIp! HeIp me!
HeIp!
Who are you? Who are you?
What is this?
What are you doing?
Are you gonna behave?
Let's go.
What is this pIace? What is this pIace?
What is this pIace?
Who are you? Who are you?
HeIIo, Dr. DenIon.
You may not remember me,
but I most certainIy remember you.
I was a guest at your hospitaI once.
Where am I?
Do you remember me?
I've seen you on teIevision.
Lawrence Gordon was your doctor.
I was his patient, and he was mine.
As you can see from that report,
my prognosis isn't good.
WouId you agree?
There's no preventative treatment
for what you have.
I remember you saying that
to me once before
in aImost the exact same tone.
Leave it to a doctor
to find such a coId, cIinicaI way
of saying I'm a dead man waIking.
Looking at me,
how Iong wouId you say I have Ieft?
I'd have to examine you.
Even then,
a frontaI-Iobe tumor is unpredictabIe.
The growth depends on the rate
of mitosis versus apoptosis...
I'm sorry, but is
aII this crude medicaI equipment around me
causing you to beIieve
that you're stiII inside a hospitaI?
No.
Then why are you speaking to me
in that graduate-schooI medicaI jargon?
Look at me!
Now, you Iook at me.
I asked you a simpIe question.
Based on your experience,
how Iong do you think I have Ieft?
It's not a simpIe answer.
Based on your fiIe, I'd say not Iong.
Death is a surprise party
unIess, of course,
you're aIready dead on the inside,
unIess you're the type of person
who swaIIows antidepressants
to hide the pain, huh?
Turns their back on their husband,
negIects their chiId,
who has every possibIe advantage in Iife
but chooses not to advance.
What do you want from me?
What do I want?
I want to pIay a game.
The ruIes of the game are simpIe.
The consequences
for breaking them are great.
Death.
You're being tested.
Your wiII is being tested,
your wiII to keep someone aIive.
Can you do that? Can you foIIow the ruIes
-and grant someone the gift of Iife?
-What is this? What is this? No, get it...
No! No! What is this?
What are you doing to me?
The device that you're wearing
is Iinked to my heart-rate monitor.
The second that heart-rate monitor
fIat-Iines or you move out of range,
an expIosion wiII go off in that coIIar.
Your Iife and my Iife
wiII end simuItaneousIy.
PIease, pIease don't do this to me.
I have a famiIy. I have a famiIy.
Let me give you the simpIe version.
You wiII keep him aIive, whatever it takes.
No excuses, no equivocations,
no crying.
What do you mean, keep him aIive?
Out there, on those screens,
we have another test subject.
A man.
He wiII face a series of tests.
You have to keep John aIive
untiI he makes it through.
If he compIetes aII of his tests,
and John is stiII breathing,
then I wiII remove your coIIar,
and you're free to go.
You're a vitaI piece of my puzzIe,
Dr. DenIon,
a criticaI part
of what couId be my finaI test.
Amanda, it's time to start our game.
HeIp!
HeIIo!
Is there anybody out there?
Hello, Jeff.
Over the past few years,
you have become a shell
of your former self,
consumed with hatred and vengeance,
vengeance against the drunk driver
who killed your only son,
vengeance against the killer
who, to your surprise and dismay,
was set free after a hasty trial.
Today, however,
it is you who will be put on trial.
To escape from where you are,
you will have to face a series of tests.
You wiII have to suffer
to move forward through each of them,
but with each one,
you will also have a chance,
a chance to forgive.
When you complete the tests,
I promise you,
you will finally come face to face
with the man responsible
for the loss of your child.
That will be your ultimate test.
Can you forgive him?
You better hurry, though.
ln two hours, the doors will lock,
and this place will become your tomb.
This is what you've been waiting for, Jeff.
Let the game begin.
HeIp!
You fucking kiIIed my son.
Don't you fucking beg.
Do you know who I am?
I'm your fucking teacher, you motherfucker.
This is what you fucking deserve.
Where is it?
What?
How many times?
How many times do I have to teII you
before you get it in your head?
I just wanted to sIeep with something.
No. No, you just nothing.
You don't touch things in DyIan's room,
okay?
I'm sorry, Daddy.
You know I Iove you, don't you?
What do you think Mommy wouId say
if she saw us Iike this?
I'm gonna go get ready for schooI.
Daddy!
HeIIo?
Hey!
AII right, John.
I need you to Iook at my nose.
Right here.
Look at my nose, pIease.
FoIIow my fIashIight.
TeII me if you feeI any pain, aII right?
That hurt?
It's begun.
He's out of the box.
So?
My 20-second anaIysis
without any medicaI equipment
is that his brain's herniating.
He needs to go to the hospitaI
and have an operation
to decompress his brain.
Come here.
-No, reaIIy. Come here.
-What?
-Come here.
-No.
-Let me ask you something.
-Oh, God!
Did I bring John to you,
or did I bring your seIf-centered ass
to him?
Now, you better start
fucking paying attention.
No one's going to any hospitaI.
I can't perform miracIes.
You're... You're giving him painkiIIers.
For a tumor Iike this,
he needs steroids, Prednisone.
Oh, good, yeah.
Maybe we couId try
some corticoid steroids,
you know, Iike Dexamethasone.
Why don't you fucking teII me something
that I don't know, you stupid cunt?
The onIy pIace that he can get those drugs
is in a hospitaI,
or eIse he's gonna die.
You are not a good Iistener.
I think you missed the part that if he dies,
you die.
You're asking me to do the impossibIe.
I'm not asking you. He is.
He chose you.
-Not me.
-Amanda!
Our doctor can't do
what's being asked of her
if you're threatening her.
The ruIes of our game
have been made very cIear.
You need to abide by those ruIes.
Sorry.
Amanda! Amanda, I need your heIp.
Amanda, he needs oxygen.
Oxygen, Amanda!
Put the mask on his face.
I need you to hoId him down.
Tip his head to the side. You got it?
What are you doing?
Ativan? Do you have Ativan?
No!
Back off! Back off! Back off! Back off!
Stay with me, John.
You're aImost through this.
Stay with me. We're aImost done with this.
Was that enough for you?
Are you ready to go to the hospitaI now?
He needs to have an operation.
-Okay.
But we do it here.
-We do it here.
-What?
What do you need?
I need anesthetic for a procedure Iike this.
Anesthetic, what eIse?
Even with an anesthetic...
A power driII.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
PIease, pIease, Iease, Iet me go.
PIease, why...
Why are you doing this to me?
Don't... Don't kiII me, okay? PIease!
Wait. Key, key, key. Okay, come on.
Fuck!
-God!
-Fuck!
Okay.
PIease, pIease, I'm so coId.
I can't feeI my arms. PIease.
Welcome to your first test, Jeff.
For the past three years,
you've cursed the name
of all those you thought were responsible
for the death of your son.
You fantasize those accountable will pay.
Well, you will find a woman
in front of you chained in place.
This will prevent her from running,
much Iike she did
on the day your son was hit.
Her name is Denica Scott.
She was the onIy witness present
at the scene of your son's untimely demise.
If not for her own self-absorption
and cowardice,
she could have brought
your son's killer to justice.
Now it is you
who has a chance to bring her to justice.
You alone can grant her the gift of life
before she freezes to death.
Behind the pipes on the back wall,
you will find the key
that will free her and bring you
one step closer to the man
responsible for the loss of your child.
Will you claim the key
to save only yourself?
You have to heIp me!
Or can you find it within you
to save another?
Make your choice.
No!
I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything to you!
That's exactIy it. You didn't do anything.
I'm fucking dying. PIease...
He died
in my arms.
My eight-year-oId son died in my arms.
I made a mistake.
I'm so sorry.
I'm human.
I'm human, just Iike your son was, okay?
Look at me.
I said, Iook at me. Look...
Oh, my God.
It's so coId.
Oh, God!
Amanda, if you reaIIy care about John,
you won't Iet me do this to him.
You're a smart woman,
and you know what's right for him.
I'm sorry.
I know it's hard to concentrate
when you're surrounded by so many things
you couId kiII me with,
Iike this ax I saw you Iooking at.
Take it.
PIease, it's yours.
Come on.
I'd go for the neck,
but I'm not the brain surgeon.
Just do it quietIy
so John doesn't hear me die.
Otherwise, he's IikeIy to get upset,
rip off his heart-rate monitor. Boom.
Then you just have to find the sensor
and disarm it
so you can waIk more
than 30 feet out that door
without the coIIar detonating,
or you couId try and take
the coIIar off yourseIf,
but that couId be tricky.
The sIightest knock
in the wrong pIace couId trigger it.
I shouId know.
I buiIt it.
So do you have everything you need?
I have the instruments
to cut someone open.
I don't have the tooIs to save a Iife.
You'd be surprised
what tooIs can save a Iife.
Hello, Amanda.
You don't know me, but I know you.
I want to play a game.
There's only one key to open the device.
It's in the stomach of your dead cellmate.
Look around, Amanda.
Know that I'm not playing.
Live or die.
Make your choice.
CongratuIations. You are stiII aIive.
Most people are so ungrateful to be alive,
but not you, not anymore.
Amanda, do not be afraid.
Your life has just begun.
He made it through the freezer room.
He tried to save her.
There are some things
I need you to do for me.
In my desk, in the center drawer,
an enveIope
with your name on it.
She's gonna do a procedure on you.
-Yeah?
-To reIieve the pressure on your brain...
-...and heIp with the headaches.
I can't do this.
Amanda, you can.
You can.
You're stronger now,
and I beIieve in you.
You chose her 'cause she's the best, right?
That's one reason I chose her.
Damn it!
HeIIo?
HeIp me, pIease!
PIease, heIp me!
I'm in here!
PIease get me out of here!
HeIp me! I...
HeIIo?
I know you're there.
PIease! PIease heIp me!
I can hear you. PIease, answer me!
HeIp me!
PIease!
Get me out of here, pIease! PIease heIp me!
Get me out of here!
PIease!
Don't just stand there! HeIp me!
Jeff, when the judge
presiding over your case
sentenced your boy's murderer so lightly,
your soul never recovered.
Now you have the power to sentence
his soul straight to hell,
or you can forgive.
The key that will free him
is hidden inside your son's possessions,
possessions you have clung to
for far too long.
Now, if you flip the switch
on the incinerator underneath you,
a fire will cleanse you of this obsession
and destroy them all,
leaving only the key remaining.
It is also the key that will bring you closer
to the man accountabIe
for taking your child.
He doesn't have much time, Jeff.
Let the game begin.
PIease get me out of here. PIease!
What is that?
What's that sound?
I'm a criminaI court judge, for Christ's sake!
You can't do this to me!
You don't remember me?
WeII, maybe you remember
Timothy Young?
He was the driver who kiIIed my son.
You gave him six months!
Okay, aII right, we can taIk about your case.
ObviousIy you want answers.
I can't give them to you Iike this.
Does this hurt?
You give more for fucking parking tickets!
Listen to me.
I can see that you're in a great deaI of pain,
but there are ways
that we can have his sentence extended.
I can heIp you!
It's too Iate!
They Iet him go!
Don't become what he is!
Don't become a kiIIer!
PIease, I have a son, too.
Where are you going?
You gotta heIp me!
I'm so sorry!
Oh, God.
You're kiIIing me!
Don't do this to me! I'm gonna die!
Fuck you!
Fuck you, you...
You gotta heIp me!
Shut the fuck up.
HeIp!
Come on!
He made it through the second test.
The judge is aIive.
Faster than I expected.
AII right, John, I need you
to keep your head to the side
and keep stiII.
What's going on here is that your brain
is pushing against your skuII.
I'm gonna try to reIieve the pressure
by cutting away a IittIe bit of your skuII.
It shouId heIp you with your headaches
and drasticaIIy improve your motor skiIIs.
Do you understand?
AII too weII.
AII right, you're gonna feeI
some sIight discomfort.
Are you gonna give him
a generaI anesthetic?
For a procedure Iike this,
the patient needs to be fuIIy aIert.
Okay.
Amanda, I need you here.
Amanda.
AII right, John,
you're gonna feeI some pressure.
Let's cIip this, stop the bIeeding.
FiII that syringe
with aIcohoI from that bowI.
Hurry.
AII right, John,
I need you to keep your mouth cIosed.
You're gonna hear a Iot of noise.
-John, how you doing?
-Never better.
AII right.
AII right, you're gonna hear a Iot of ringing.
I need you to stay very stiII.
Here I go.
AII right, John, I'm gonna remove the skuII.
He's stabiIized.
John, I need you to raise your hand
and fIex your fingers.
John?
John, raise your hand.
John, can you hear me?
What's happening?
John.
What's happening to him?
What's happening?
What's wrong?
Why isn't he moving?
Do something!
PIease.
Stay with me, John.
Good.
-I Iove you.
Breathe! Breathe, damn it! Breathe, John.
I Iove...
Breathe.
I...
I Iove you.
You wiII give everything to me.
Every ceII in your body.
Is that understood?
Yes.
The marks on your arms,
they're from another Iife.
We'II Ieave that Iife behind.
When you go down that corridor,
there is no turning back.
Do you understand that?
Yes.
Then start with this.
Go.
Who is that?
Who's in there?
I'll kill you, you motherfucker!
Put his Ieft Ieg in the shackIe.
It's time to start our game.
What's that?
SIow my heart rate, reIax my muscIes.
It's time.
CIose the door behind you.
He can't hear you.
He doesn't even know you're there.
Amanda.
Put it away.
Trust me.
Leave us aIone.
Now.
You fucking freak.
I apoIogize for her behavior.
She swims in my sea.
In the end, she wiII be the cIosest
I've ever come to a connection,
to being understood,
but her emotion is aIso her weakness.
Adam.
Come here. I'm gonna heIp you.
I'm gonna heIp you.
I'm gonna free you.
I'm so sorry about your son, Jeff,
but Iet me teII you something that I...
That I know for sure.
No sentence I gave him, not 500 years,
not even death, nothing,
wiII take your pain away,
and vengeance doesn't soIve anything.
It onIy makes the pain greater, Jeff.
What the... What the fuck?
Somebody heIp me!
What the fuck?
HeIp.
What the... What the fuck are you doing?
PIease heIp me.
Hello, Jeff.
If you are listening to this,
that means that the confrontation
you so long dreamed of
is finally unfolding.
Do something!
In your head, he is a cipher,
a symbol of your life changing,
a symbol of death.
I present him to you now
as a simple human being.
His name is Timothy Young.
He's 27 years old,
a medicaI student
with a mother and a father
just like you,
a man whose life also changed
the day your son died.
That day, he made a terrible mistake.
You believe he didn't pay for that mistake,
and now is your chance to make him pay.
The device Timothy is strapped to
is my personal favorite.
I caII it the rack.
The human body is a miraculous creation.
Ever wonder how far the arm can twist?
This device is going to start twisting.
There is a chance he might live,
though, with your help.
PIease.
To your right is a box.
At the back of the box is a key.
It's tied to the trigger of a shotgun.
The question you have to ask yourself
is this.
-Are you willing...
-Have mercy!
...to take a buIIet for the man
who killed your son?
Does "Do unto others
as you would have them do unto you"
apply here, Jeff?
Make your choice.
My God.
You've got to heIp him, Jeff!
Fuck!
PIease stop! Stop! Stop! PIease stop!
Jeff!
Just standing there,
you're an accompIice to murder.
Are you a murderer?
I've wanted to kiII him every day.
-Oh, my God!
-For three years, I wanted to kiII you.
Yeah, maybe I am.
-You'II Iose your famiIy.
-Oh, my God!
-Your wife, your daughter.
-Oh, God!
Fuck!
Oh, God.
Okay.
HoId on, son.
HoId on. Don't give up.
Come on, son.
Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God!
Son.
Got the key.
HeIp me!
-HeIp me!
-Stop!
I forgive him!
I forgive him! No!
No!
God!
God damn you!
Don't you think it wouId be wise
to engage me in conversation
for your own sake?
I asked you to teII me about your husband.
-It's Iike we're strangers now.
-And?
The Iast time I saw him,
we were so disconnected,
but now
I'd give anything in the worId
to see my husband.
Matrimony's aIways fascinated me.
Husbands bareIy abIe to Iook at their wives,
wives on their backs
in moteI rooms with perfect strangers,
peopIe who bear chiIdren
onIy to negIect them.
"TiII death do us part," indeed.
I don't know what you think you know,
but my marriage
has survived more suffering
than someone Iike you couId ever grasp.
Suffering?
You haven't seen anything yet.
Someone Iike me? Who am I?
A monster.
A murderer.
I don't condone murder,
and I despise murderers.
PIease.
PIease, Iet me go.
We're fine, Amanda. We don't need you.
I said, we're fine.
If you make it through this, Lynn,
you're going to thank me one day
just as Amanda did.
PIease, Iet me go.
I saved your Iife.
Maybe my Iife isn't the one
you were saving after aII.
TeII me about your daughter.
I understand she's quite a IittIe athIete.
-Or we couId taIk about your son.
-What did you say?
Why are you Iiving with the dead
when you have such a beautifuI famiIy?
A husband who's indeed aIone,
a daughter who needs her mother,
patients who need a competent physician
who Iooks them in the eye
and treats them Iike human beings?
He's compIeted the third test.
CongratuIations, Lynn. You're free to go.
Yeah, but he's not aII the way out yet.
Undo her coIIar, Amanda, and Iet her go.
No, he's not finished. He's not aII the way.
Amanda, Lynn is more important
than you know.
UnIock her coIIar, and Iet her go.
I said no.
-Amanda, there are ruIes.
-I said no!
She doesn't deserve to go free.
-You promised.
-I didn't promise you shit.
Amanda, even with that gun,
it is Lynn who hoIds your Iife in her hands.
Fuck you. You give her controI over me?
Fuck you!
I won't teII anyone. I promise I won't.
PIease, I have a famiIy.
Shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up!
And stop fucking moving around!
And what about the other test subjects
that we Ieft aIive?
-Game over.
-I'II fucking kiII you!
-What about them?
-Is that how you feIt about them?
Is that how you feIt about Eric Matthews?
-Eric Matthews.
-Oh, my God! Let me go.
I'II teII you how I feIt about Eric Matthews.
DanieI!
-Fuck!
-DanieI!
DanieI?
Fuck!
Where's my son?
-Where is he, you junkie bitch?
-Fuck you.
Where is he?
TeII me where he is.
-TeII me where he is.
-Right fucking here.
You bitch!
You're nothing, bitch!
You're nothing!
You're not Jigsaw.
You're not Jigsaw, bitch!
You hear me?
You're nothing!
You're not Jigsaw, bitch.
I'II fucking kiII you!
No!
That's right. I'm a murderer.
He took my Iife from me,
so I just returned the fucking favor.
No, Amanda, that's what you thought,
but I know different.
-You Ieft him for dead, didn't you?
-Just stop fucking with me.
But I cIeaned up your mistakes,
and I forgave you for them.
Let me go! PIease!
What you do is no different than murder.
You torture peopIe. You watch them die.
But now you're begging me
not to kiII this worthIess bitch
on the grounds of some game?
You're waIking us
toward a precipice, Amanda.
-Step back.
-It's buIIshit.
Nobody changes. It's aII a Iie.
If you faiI in this, we aII faiI.
Succeed, and we aII succeed.
It's a Iie!
I'II teII you, she hasn't changed
because nobody fucking changes.
Nobody is reborn. It's aII buIIshit!
It's aII a fucking Iie,
and I'm just a pawn in your stupid games.
I don't mean anything to you.
No, you mean everything to me.
Fuck you!
Our fates are Iinked.
I've tried to heIp you, Amanda.
So heIp me! Fix me!
Fix me, motherfucker!
I'm standing right here.
Why is she so important to you?
She's not important to me.
-She's important to you.
-She's not important to me.
I beg you to reconsider that.
This is your Iast chance, Amanda.
She's nothing.
Your time's running out.
Now, you think about what you're doing.
Think about everything that you've done.
You think about what you promised me.
Think about our dreams.
You think about tomorrow.
Lynn?
Jeff! Jeff!
Lynn.
-Lynn.
-Jeff.
You just destroyed four Iives.
You just murdered Jeff's wife.
Baby.
Amanda.
It's okay.
This was your test,
your game.
What do I want?
I want to pIay a game.
You're being tested.
Your wiII is being tested,
your wiII to keep someone aIive.
Can you do that? Can you foIIow the ruIes
and grant someone the gift of Iife?
I was testing you. I took you in.
You wiII give everything to me.
Yes.
Every ceII in your body.
I selected you for the honor
of carrying on my life's work,
but you didn't.
That's right.
I'm a murderer.
I despise murderers.
You didn't test anyone's wiII to Iive.
Game over.
Instead you took away their only chance.
Your games were unwinnable,
your subjects, merely victims.
You.
There is no turning back.
Do you understand that?
In my desperation,
I decided to give you one last chance,
so I put everything in place.
You chose her 'cause she's the best, right?
That's one reason I chose her.
You didn't know that Lynn and Jeff
were husband and wife.
I had to keep that from you
for the purposes of my game.
I had to leave out the ruined marriage,
the cheating wife,
the vengeful husband,
the neglected daughter,
and I let you make your own choices.
I wanted you to succeed.
Amanda.
Put it away.
Trust me.
Even with that gun,
it is Lynn who hoIds your Iife in her hands.
She's not important to me.
I beg you to reconsider that.
UnIock her coIIar, and Iet her go.
I said no.
The ruIes of our game
have been made very cIear.
You need to abide by those ruIes.
You couIdn't.
God.
Game over.
You haven't Iearned anything tonight,
have you?
Your rage and your vengeance
wiII onIy hurt the ones you Iove.
KiIIing me wiII onIy add to your misery.
It wiII not bring back your son.
Think of your daughter, Jeff.
She needs you now more than ever.
You can't kiII me, Jeff.
Your wife's dying, Jeff.
Her time's running out.
Jeff, do not miscaIcuIate.
Your fate is in my hands.
Your wife's fate is in my hands.
I Iove you.
I'm taking you home, okay?
Though you may not see any threat,
there are threats aII around you.
Jeff, if you try to move your wife,
she wiII die.
I can have an ambuIance here
in four minutes.
WouId you Iike to take your wife
out of here tonight?
WouId you Iike to take her to safety?
-Stay.
-Stand and face me, Jeff.
-Stay with me, pIease.
-Right now.
WouId you Iike to get your Iife back?
WouId you, Jeff?
We can make that happen.
Which is it, Jeff?
Come on, yes or no?
Yes.
-What do you want?
-One finaI test.
The ruIes are simpIe.
Over on that tabIe,
there's a host of vicious impIements,
which you can use
to exact your pound of fIesh,
to take your vengeance,
to induIge your obsession,
or you can choose
to put your vengeance aside,
and you can forgive.
You can forgive me for the pain
that I've caused you and your wife tonight.
-Jeff.
-Which is it gonna be, Jeff?
Honey, don't do it.
Jeff...
It's up to you.
-I need you.
-Live or die, Jeff?
Make our choice.
I forgive you.
Jeff...
Jeff. Jeff!
Jeff, no.
I forgive you.
Hello, Jeff.
I made this tape as an insurance policy,
if you will.
Jeff!
And if you're listening to it,
then it's time to coIIect.
I was your final test of forgiveness,
and if you are listening to this,
then you failed.
Now you must pay the price,
the price for living for nothing
but vengeance.
Now I will give you something to live for.
I told you that you couldn't kill me, Jeff,
but I didn't tell you why,
and the answer is simple.
I am the person responsible
for the loss of your child.
I am the only person
who knows where your daughter is.
She onIy has a Iimited suppIy of air, Jeff,
and if you want to get her back,
you'll have to play a game.
Jeff!
© anoXmous
@ https://thepiratebay.se/user/anoXmous