Public Enemies
It is the fourth year of the great depression
For John Dillinger, Alvi Karpis and baby face Nelson
It is the golden age of bank robbery¡­
All right, get out of there.
Let's go.
All the way down and take a seat.
Let's go. Stop your dragging. Let's go! Move!
Let's go. Let's go.
Line up! Line up!
Move! Move! Right turn!
Stay with me!
Keep your head down!
Line up!
Everybody ready? Come on.
Get off me!
Come on.
Now march us to the changing rooms
Go. Let's go.
Line up!
l know you.
You just got paroled out of here. You didn't last very long.
When was that?
Eight weeks ago.
Did nine years.
John. John Dillinger.
That's right.
My friends call me John.
But a son-of-a-bitch screw like you better address me as
Mr. Dillinger.
Open it! Open it or l'll blow you in half.
Against the wall.
Take your clothes off, now!
You did it, kid.
Sure did, Walter.
Give me the goddamn jacket.
Red !
Come on. Hurry up!
Get undressed. Take your clothes off.
Come on.
You eyeballing me, you son of a bitch?
Cut it out, Shouse!
Shouse!
Lockdown !
Bring them in from the yard !
There they are!
Walter! Come on.
Walter Dietrich's dead 'cause of you.
The bastard guard wouldn't do what he was told, Johnny.
Homer?
Just let him have it, Johnny.
Pete?
lt's up to you.
How far is the farm?
3.2 miles.
We're ready!
Okay. Let's go!
Burn these, okay, honey?
Thanks for getting us out, Red.
lt was Johnny's plan.
Yeah, but thanks.
Take me with you, mister.
l can't, darling. l'm sorry.
Welcome back, Pete.
Let's go to Chicago and make some money.
Floyd, halt!
Melvin, look out!
Pretty Boy Floyd, you are under arrest.
lt's Charles. Charles Floyd.
Who are you?
Melvin Purvis, Bureau of lnvestigation.
Where is your friend, Harry Campbell?
l believe you've killed me.
So you can go rot in hell.
Sport.
Red, call Oscar.
Okay.
Hi, there, doll.
Let's switch out the shorts.
We gonna use Berman?
Yeah. Get a Plymouth and an Essex.
Where the other gals?
You get a hold of Marty?
Sure did.
How you doing, Mr. Johnny?
Doing great, Sport.
The main spring's too tight on this one. Jammed twice.
l cut off one coil.
And it rides up and to the right.
l widen port.
Hi, Red.
Hi, Harry.
Harry, this is Pete. Pete, this is Harry Berman.
Hi, Pete. How you doing?
So, what do we got? Got a couple of nice straight eights.
Bored them out. Rebuilt the carburetors myself.
These are some really fast cars.
Perfect work cars for a couple of gentlemen.
Johnny, how are you?
Good.
Marty
tell me that me and my boys are okay.
As long as you stay in East Chicago,
you're in safe haven, any time you want.
Extra cake's in here.
Thanks.
Hey, Anna.
l opened up in Chicago on Halsted now. Come by and see the girls.
How are you?
On the floor! Now! Now! Do it! Do it! On the floor, now! Now!
Let's play a game, Mr. President. lt's called Spin the Dial.
You, hands up! Come on. And, you, sit down !
On the floor!
Relax, pops.
Open it up.
Empty it! Move, move! Shut up!
lt's one of these.
You can be a dead hero or a live coward.
Get it open.
You, hands up. Come on !
Empty it! All of it!
Hey, sit down !
Push it to me!
And don't move!
We got company!
Move out of there!
You can put it away. Not here for your money. Here for the bank's money.
l said, move it out of there!
What for?
Come here, sister. Let's take a ride.
Get down !
Beat it.
You, too, sister.
Come here.
There you go, doll. Something to remember me by.
You know, when l'm not doing this, l'm a scout for the movies.
Really?
Join hands.
We'll freeze here!
No. You'll worm your way out of there in about 1 0 minutes.
Why do we need this?
Because criminals flee in fast automobiles across state lines,
thereby defeating local jurisdiction
because there is no federal police force to stop them.
By my tally, your Bureau wants to spend more taxpayers' dollars catching crooks
than what the crooks you catch stole in the first place.
Well, that's ridiculous. The Bureau has apprehended kidnappers and bank robbers
who have stolen up to and in excess of. . .
Really? How many have you apprehended?
We have arrested and arraigned 213 wanted felons.
No, l mean you, Director Hoover. How many?
Well, as Director, l administer.
How many have you arrested personally?
l have never arrested anybody.
You've never arrested anybody.
Well, of course not. l am an administrator.
With no field experience.
You are shockingly unqualified, aren't you, sir?
You have never personally conducted
a criminal investigation in the field in your life.
l think you're a front.
l think your prowess as a lawman is a myth
created from the hoopla of headlines by Mr. Suydam, your publicist there.
Crimebusters, G-men, you're setting yourself up as a czar?
That's running wild in my estimation.
A crime is what runs wild.
lf this country requires a Bureau such as yours,
l question whether you are the person fit to run it.
Well, l will not be judged by a kangaroo court of venal politicians.
Your appropriation increase is denied.
Feed the following to Walter Winchell.
McKellar is a Neanderthal, and he is on a personal vendetta to destroy me.
We will not contest him in his committee room.
We will fight him on the front page.
Where is John Dillinger?
Agent Purvis, congratulations.
Thank you, sir.
May l ask why?
They're ready for him.
This is Henry Suydam. He is our expert in press relations.
Congratulations for Pretty Boy Floyd,
for which you have my personal gratitude.
Second, you are, as of this moment,
the Special Agent in Charge of the Chicago field office.
Are you up to that task, Agent Purvis?
Absolutely, sir.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
Today, l am declaring the United States of America's first War on Crime.
And l'd like to introduce one of our finest G-men, Agent Melvin Purvis.
Agent Purvis will be in charge of the field office in Chicago,
the center of the crime wave sweeping America.
His task will be to get Public Enemy Number One, John Dillinger.
Say a few words, would you?
Mr. Purvis, how did you run down Pretty Boy Floyd?
Through an apple orchard.
Mr. Tolson, when he's done, you tell him if he needs anything,
you'll get it for him.
And tell him he may call me J. E.
Yeah, but people say John Dillinger's a lot smarter and a lot tougher.
Well, nevertheless, we will get him.
What makes you so sure?
We have two things Dillinger does not.
What are they?
The Bureau's modern techniques of fighting crime scientifically
and the visionary leadership of our Director, J. Edgar Hoover.
The broad over there is looking at me.
She likes me.
How you doing, sweetheart?
Alvin. Good to see you.
How you doing?
Homer. Pete.
Me, Freddy and Doc are looking to snatch a fellow.
He's a Saint Paul banker, Ed Bremer. We need a few more hands.
l don't like kidnapping.
Well, robbing banks is getting tougher.
The public don't like kidnapping.
Who gives a damn what the public likes?
l do. l hide out among them.
We gotta care what they think.
We also got a mail train we're looking at, too.
By the way, if somebody was to get pinched, who knows their way around?
Syndicate lawyer named Piquett, Louis Piquett. We all use him.
What's it all about, this train?
Needs two or three more real right guys to stick it up.
Be ready in a couple of months.
About $1 ,700,000. lt's a Federal Reserve shipment.
lt's the kind of score you go away on after.
Where you gonna go?
l don't know. Brazil, Cuba. l like Varadero Beach.
What about you?
No plans.
Yeah, well, you ought to.
What we're doing won't last forever.
We're having too good a time today.
We ain't thinking about tomorrow.
Keep me in mind on the train, would you? All right. Thanks.
You know how much they made taking that Hamm Brewery guy?
$1 00,000.
Simmer down, Homer.
Come on, fellas. Let's go to the bar.
l got three broads convinced l own the place.
See you.
ls Homer staying steady enough?
Homer's fine.
One rule l learned from Walter Dietrich,
never work with people who are desperate.
Yeah, well, l got a rule, too. Stay away from the women.
Without women, it's like back in the stir.
That's why they invented whores.
Hey, hey, Anna.
How are you doing, big boy?
Who's this?
Veronica.
Veronica, Red.
Hi, Johnny.
Hey, Anna.
l don't know why you gave that fellow the go-by,
but l'm awful glad you did.
What's your name?
Billie Frechette.
Can l buy you a drink?
Okay.
You got a name?
Yeah. Jack.
You dance, Jack?
l don't know how.
Come on.
How come you don't know how to dance?
Frechette.
That French?
On my father's side. There's an "e" at the end.
This is a two-step.
Daddy's French. What's on the other side?
My mama's a Menominee lndian, okay?
Most men don't like that.
l ain't most men.
Yeah?
And l've been a dice girl, and l check coats at the Steuben Club.
And what do you do?
l'm catching up.
Meeting somebody like you,
dark and beautiful,
like that bird in that song.
Blackbird, bye-bye
No one here can love
Or understand me
You cold?
What is it exactly you do for a living?
l'm John Dillinger. l rob banks.
That's where all these people here put their money.
Why did you tell me that?
You could have made up a story.
l'm not gonna lie to you.
That's a serious thing to say to a girl you just met.
l know you.
Well, l don't know you.
l haven't been anyplace.
Well, some of the places I've been ain't so hot.
Where l'm going is a whole lot better.
Want to come along?
Boy, you are in a hurry!
lf you were looking at what l'm looking at, you'd be in a hurry, too.
Well,
it's me they're looking at this time.
You're beautiful.
They're looking at me because they're not used to
having a girl in their restaurant in a $3 dress.
Listen, doll.
That's 'cause they're all about where people come from.
The only thing that's important is where somebody's going.
Where are you going?
Anywhere l want.
Let's get out of here.
Hey, Johnny!
Go wait for me outside.
Gil.
Ever since l got out, l've been working for Frank Nitti.
These guys are connected to everybody all over the country now.
He looks like a barber.
Phil D'Andrea. Every time l read about one of your bank jobs
where you give the customers back their money, you crack me up.
You need anything, ask Gilbert.
Gilbert knows how to find me.
Thank you.
Where'd that girl go?
l don't know, sir. She jumped in a cab and took off.
This is Lowell Thomas.
From West Virginia comes accusations
by the Carnegie Coal company of Red influence
on the United Mine Workers' strike.
Meanwhile, in Racine, Wisconsin, after raiding the American Trust Bank,
PubIic Enemy Number One John Dillinger
roams the wilds pursued by the hounds of justice.
And in Geneva, the League of Nations
voted the USSR full membership.
According to the bank teller, Barbara Patzke,
this is John Dillinger's coat.
lt's made by Shragge Quality out of St. Louis.
Price, $35, windproof 32-ounce wool. Top stitching.
Thank you, Agent Baum.
Agents in our offices across the country
are identifying every store in the United States that sold this overcoat.
Then we will cross-reference every Dillinger associate at locales where that coat was sold.
He was in a place.
He got cold. He bought a coat.
Unless he was traveling through,
he was being harbored nearby.
lf he returns, we will be there.
lt is by such methods that our Bureau will get John Dillinger.
Now, Doris, would you please contact
the Chicago area telephone exchange supervisors. There are six.
Request appointments for Carter Baum and myself.
Gentlemen,
shortly you will be provided Thompson submachine guns, BARs
and a .351 Winchester semi-automatic rifle.
We are pursuing hardened killers. They will be dangerous.
And those of you who aren't prepared for that should go.
And if you are going to go, please go now.
This is a phone call conversation from a car dealership from 27 minutes ago.
Harry Berman.
When you drop it, leave the keys on the floorboard.
I got a DeSoto.
Okay.
lnterior's no good.
How did we get to Berman?
Off the Dillinger coat.
The coat was bought in Cicero, lllinois,
a few doors down from Berman's dealership.
Now, we know Berman. He's been supplying cars to the Syndicate since Capone.
When Dillinger bought that coat,
he must have been at Berman's switching cars.
As soon as they call to drop the DeSoto, we'll tail it.
l want men on this around the clock.
May l check your coat, sir?
Yes, thank you.
You ran out on me.
You left me standing on the sidewalk.
lf you're gonna be my girl,
you're gonna have to swear to me that you'll never ever do that again.
Hey, l'm not your girl.
Brown overcoat.
And l'm not gonna say that.
l'm waiting.
So am l.
"l'm never gonna run out on you ever again." Say the words.
No.
My coat.
Well, l ain't ever gonna run out on you, and that's a promise.
Well, l want to run out of here, so, lady...
Hit the road, sport. Keep the tip.
You ain't getting other people's hats and coats no more neither.
Why'd you do that?
'Cause you're with me now.
l don't know anything about you.
l was raised on a farm in Mooresville, lndiana.
My mama died when l was three.
My daddy beat the hell out of me 'cause he didn't know no better way to raise me.
l like baseball, movies, good clothes, fast cars, whiskey and you.
What else you need to know?
Have a seat.
You been living here long?
Yeah.
Since yesterday.
Hey.
l got you something.
When l was a girl,
we went to live on the reservation in Flandreau
'cause my daddy died.
ln Flandreau, nothing ever happened.
And when l was 13, l went to live in Milwaukee with my Aunt lnes.
We had a lot of Indian friends,
and we went around to churches and put on plays.
And nothing exciting ever happened there, either.
So I haven't been anywhere or done anything except come to Chicago
and try to make my way.
You're all packed.
Well, baby,
l'm gonna take you with me.
And you're gonna start a whole new exciting kind of life.
And what do you want?
Everything.
Right now.
Purvis.
Berman dropped the DeSoto at Sherone Apartments 20 minutes ago.
Men go in and out of an apartment rented to a Miss Vi Scott.
They carry heavy suitcases. One of them looks like Dillinger.
Where are your men?
ln cars on Clarendon and Wilson Avenue.
Blocking vehicles? The alley?
Who has a line of sight on the DeSoto to you?
Are they aware that we are here? Any rapid movements?
No.
Carter,
you keep an eye on the DeSoto from there.
Barton, you're with me.
Yes?
l'm Special Agent Melvin Purvis, Miss Scott.
Are you here by yourself?
No. l'm here with my fiance.
And what is your fiance's name?
Leonard McHenry.
May we come in?
Well, please.
l'm perfectly safe, but come on in.
Something wrong?
You have identification?
Yeah, sure.
Honey, would you get my driver's license? lt's in my jacket pocket.
Sure.
l know you.
You're. . .
You're Melvin Purvis. Right?
Yeah. l seen your picture.
And what do you do for a living, Leonard?
l travel in ladies' shoes.
Show him, honey.
Cute, huh?
Well, you enjoy the rest of your dinner, Mr. McHenry.
Thanks.
Good night.
No one in or out. l'll get the others. You stay here.
You watch that door from right there.
Get the men from Sheridan.
Bureau of lnvestigation. What's your name?
You wanna know my name?
Come on.
Baum, you keep an eye on the alley.
Barton?
Barton.
Where is he?
They're headed east!
Who was in the blocking car?
That was us.
We heard gunfire so we came here.
Who was it? Dillinger?
The man we let get away wasn't John Dillinger.
That was Baby Face Nelson.
Get on the floor! Now! Go!
Y'all get up against that wall.
This is a stick-up! Up!
Put them up! Up!
Down on the floor, now! Down !
Put them up! Come on. Put them up!
This is a stick-up!
Let's go. Come on. Up!
Where l can see them, up!
Customers, stay calm. Don't move.
Hey! You ! Up!Hands up!
Move! Empty it!
John Dillinger held up a bank for $74,000 while you failed to arrest Nelson.
Sir, l take full responsibility.
And l would like to make a request.
That we transfer men with special qualifications
to augment the staff here in Chicago.
There are some former Texas and Oklahoma lawmen
currently with the Bureau in Dallas.
l thought you understood what l'm building.
A modern force of professional young men of the best sort.
l'm afraid our type cannot get the job done.
Excuse me, l cannot hear you.
Our type cannot get the job done.
l cannot hear you.
Without qualified help,
l would have to resign this appointment.
Otherwise, l am leading my men to slaughter.
Mr. Tolson will call you, Agent Purvis.
Did he say what he looked like?
Didn't say.
You gentlemen need any help?
Thank you, no.
How you doing?
l'm doing all right.
Agent Winstead?
That's right.
lt's a pleasure.
Welcome to Chicago. We have a lot of work to do here on Mr. Dillinger.
Put Johnny Patton down front on the other four tracks.
lt's hot out, right?
Yes, Frank.
Ever since those pricks shot me, l can't get warm.
What?
Some people from Chicago over there.
Johnny.
What do you say we meet you in Tucson around the 25th?
Okay.
All right.
l heard one today. lndiana paper,
"Wanted, John Dillinger, dead or dead."
l think we wore out the Midwest for a while.
What?
Come out to the Colonial tonight. lt's our joint. Be my guest.
The best steaks in Miami.
You're not gonna take our picture, are you?
No pictures.
All right. We'll be there.
Thank you for taking me on this trip.
You going somewhere, doll? Am l?
No. Don't kid a kidder.
Then don't play me for a fool.
We both know l end up back checking coats at the Steuben Club,
one way or the other.
What does that mean?
You don't think past today or tomorrow.
And eventually, they will catch you or kill you
and l don't want to be there when that happens.
Who gave you a crystal ball?
l don't need one.
Ask Homer.
Ask Homer what?
And his goddamn joke, "dead or dead."
You ain't going nowhere, you hear me?
l'm gonna die an old man in your arms.
We're too good for them.
They ain't tough enough, smart enough or fast enough.
l hit any bank l want any time.
They got to be at every bank all the time.
That's why we're on top of the world.
Ain't nobody lay a glove on us.
No.
l ain't going nowhere. Neither are you.
What do you got to say about that?
Hi, folks.
Afternoon. Got a reservation for a Mr. and Mrs. Frank Sullivan.
l can send up some sandwiches and beer if you like.
That'd be swell.
Some friends of mine should be here already,
a J.C. Davies and a Mr. Clark?
Out shopping, l believe.
l'll let them know you're in when they get back.
Okey-doke.
The elevator's right down that way.
Thank you very much.
You look like you could use some company.
How's about me and my friend Prince Albert come and pay you a visit?
Get on in here, both of you.
Johnny! Johnny!
Put some clothes on, miss.
What the hell happened, boys?
There was a fire in the hotel.
Firemen found our guns. They called the cops.
Where they taking you?
We're getting shanghaied to Ohio.
Where's Billie?
Your girl's been put on a bus back to Chicago.
We ain't holding her.
Right this way.
Well,
here's the man who killed Pretty Boy Floyd.
Damn good thing he was pretty, 'cause he sure wasn't Whiz Kid Floyd.
Tell me something, Mr. Purvis.
That fellow, the one who got killed at the Sherone Apartments,
the newspaper said you found him alive.
lt's the eyes, ain't it?
They look at you right before they go.
And then they just drift away into nothing.
That'll keep you up nights.
And what keeps you up nights, Mr. Dillinger?
Coffee.
You act like a confident man, Mr. Purvis.
You got a few qualities.
Probably pretty good from a distance,
especially when you got the fellow outnumbered.
But up close, toe to toe,
when somebody's about to die right here, right now,
l'm used to that.
What about you?
Goodbye, Mr. Dillinger.
l'll see you down the road.
No, you will not.
The only way that you will leave a jail cell
is when we take you out to execute you.
Well, we'll see about that.
You ought to get yourself another line of work, Melvin.
Hey, l was just kidding.
l believe l'm gonna let you boys keep me here a while.
We'd like that, Johnny, but don't get too comfortable.
They're moving you.
Where to?
lndiana.
Why?
l have absolutely nothing l want to do in lndiana.
He's here.
Back up, fellas. Back up.
We'll take custody now. Take the manacles off.
Are you glad to see lndiana again?
About as glad as lndiana is to see me, l suppose.
Did you smuggle the guns into lndiana State Penitentiary
for the big break of September 26th?
Right now, you're too inquisitive, buddy.
Put your arm around Dillinger.
Hey, when was the last time you were in Mooresville?
Ten years ago.
l was a wild boy, and, well, l was foolish.
l held up a grocery store,
which l never should have done 'cause Mr. Morgan was a good man.
And they sentenced me to 10 years in the state penitentiary for a $50 theft.
When l was in prison, l met a lot of good fellows.
So sure, yeah,
l helped set up the break at Michigan City. Why not?
l stick with my pals and my pals stick with me.
Johnny, how long does it take you to go through a bank?
Oh, about one minute, 40 seconds.
Flat.
Let's go.
Mr. Johnny, your lawyer's here.
You come highly recommended by Alvin Karpis.
At the arraignment,
they're gonna try and transfer me to the state pen.
What can you do for me?
What's on your mind?
The electric chair.
Your Honor, are we to have an arraignment in accord with the laws of this nation
or is the State to be permitted to incite an atmosphere of prejudice?
The very air reeks with the bloody rancor of intolerant malice!
The clanging of shackles brings to our minds
the dungeons of the czars,
not the flag-bedecked liberty of an American courtroom.
l request the court to direct that those shackles be removed forthwith.
This is a very dangerous man, Your Honor.
And l'm responsible for the safeguarding of this prisoner.
Are you a lawyer? What right do you have to address this court?
All right. Remove the shackles from the prisoner.
Your Honor, we would like to relocate the prisoner.
Only lndiana State Penitentiary in Michigan City
can guarantee Dillinger will not escape.
Sheriff Holley?
l concur, Your Honor.
Sheriff Holley, l think this is a very nice jail you have right here.
What makes you think there's something wrong with it?
There's nothing wrong with my jail.
lt's the strongest jail in lndiana.
That's what l thought.
But of course, l don't want to embarrass Mrs. Holley.
l appreciate she's a woman and she's afraid of an escape.
Oh, no. l'm not afraid of an escape.
l can take care of John Dillinger or any other prisoner.
Okay.
Dillinger will stay here.
Thank you, Your Honor.
The defense will need four months to prepare itself.
lt should take 10 days.
To go to trial in 10 days would be a legal lynching of this lad.
There's a law against lynching.
There's a law against murder!
Then observe the law part.
Or just stand Dillinger up against a wall
and shoot him. Just shoot him.
Then there's no need to throw away the State's money on this mockery.
Calm down.
l apologize to the court.
Bob and l respect each other very much.
Watch out or he'll be putting his arm around you, too.
Trial starts in one month on March 12th.
Attaboy, counselor.
Open the gate.
Hey, Cahoon !
Come here a minute.
Come on, Sam.
You and me's going places.
Call Bryant.
Bryant?
Call Max.
l'll kill you if l have to. Don't think l won't.
Open up!
l'll plug him right here.
Open the gun safe. Go on. Open it up!
Lock up the warden.
That wasn't real, was it?
Let's go.
Put your hands up!
Which one of these here cars is the fastest?
That would be that Ford right there. lt's got the new V-8.
We're gonna take that one. Go on.
That's Sheriff Lillian Holley's personal car.
Good.
Mr. Youngblood, are we clear now?
We are.
Okay, then.
Oh, come on, buddy.
You gotta relax a little bit. Just take it easy.
Do you know the words to The Last Round-Up?
Get along, little dogies
Get aIong, get aIong
Get aIong, IittIe dogies Get aIong
Get aIong, IittIe dogies Get aIong, get aIong
I'm a-headed for the last round-up
How did he act? Was he jolly?
Yes. He sang part of the way.
While in Washington today, President Roosevelt said,
"John Dillinger is making a mockery
"of the system of justice in this country."
The passing of John J. McGraw, long-time manager of the New York Giants...
Hello.
Hey, doll, it's me.
Look, l can't talk long. You okay?
Yeah. l heard it on the radio. How about you?
Yeah, l'm fine. l'm fine.
Don't come to Chicago, Johnny.
What's that supposed to mean?
l promised l'd look after you, didn't l?
Yes.
Well, then that's what l'm gonna do.
You know that, don't you?
Yes.
Look, I think they're watching me.
l'm gonna come get you out of there and take care of you.
Baby, don't come to Chicago!
Say you know it.
Say it.
l know you will take care of me.
l love you.
Sooner or later,
she will go to him
or he is gonna come for her.
Say, Sport!
Mr. Johnny, you got to hold it right there.
Can't stay here no more, Mr. Johnny.
Says who?
Sport's only following orders. So am l.
They thought you might come here.
l don't get it.
Talk to your pal Gilbert.
About what?
You gotta talk to Gilbert Catena.
Come on. Come on, get out of here! Beat it! Scram !
The welcome mat was not out.
l kept hearing your name. Now, l'm going to ask you once.
And l just did.
Anybody see him come in?
l don't think so.
You want to know if we're armed?
We're armed.
Calm down.
Calm down. Calm down.
Hey, back to work.
What's the deal, Phil?
Look around. What do you see?
A whole bunch of telephones.
You see money.
Last month, there were independent wire services
letting bookies know who won the third race at Sportsman's Park,
300 of them nationwide. Now there's only one, ours.
On October 23rd, you robbed a bank in Greencastle, lndiana.
You got away with $74,802.
You thought that was a big score.
These phones make that every day.
And it keeps getting made, day after day after day,
a river of money, and it gets deeper and wider,
week in and week out, month in and month out, flowing right to us.
Unless the cops come through that door.
Which you pay them not to do.
Right.
Unless you're around.
Then they gotta come through that door no matter what.
What does that tell you?
l'm popular.
lt tells us you're bad for business.
So the Syndicate's got a new policy.
All the guys like you, Karpis, Nelson, Campbell,
we ain't laundering your money or bonds no more.
You ain't holing up in our whorehouses anymore.
No armorers, no doctors, no safe havens, no nothing. You get it?
Personally, you need something to tide you over?
Good luck to you.
Hamilton has a 34-year-old sister in Detroit. Arrest her.
Pick up all known Dillinger associates, doctors, family,
Pierpont's mother in lndianapolis,
Dillinger's family in Mooresville.
We suspect them of harboring.
But Hamilton's family has not had word from Red in years.
You convince them to get word.
Create informants, Agent Purvis.
The suspects are to be interrogated vigorously, grilled,
no obsolete notions of sentimentality.
We are in the modern age. We are making history.
Take direct, expedient action.
As they say in ltaly these days, "Take off the white gloves!"
Do we understand each other, Agent Purvis?
These are fine young men here. What's your name, son?
Harris.
G-men all over the country have picked up the gauntlet
flung down by the outlaws and the wanton murderers.
And these junior crime fighters here,
these Junior G-men, has, every one of them,
stopped some crime from occurring
and forestalled an entry into the black book of criminal deeds.
Today, l am rewarding them with these medals.
My friend Harris here is the first. Well done, son.
You can size up a score like nobody's business, Tommy.
You're a good egg.
But l don't like Baby Face Nelson.
You got Nelson all wrong, John. He thinks the world of you.
Hell, the whole country thinks you're a goddamn hero.
Where's the bank?
Sioux Falls.
Nelson says there's $800,000 in there.
Says he's got us a sweet little place to hole up
till after the heat blows over.
What's he here for?
John, we gotta all be friends, all right, or this ain't gonna work.
Red told you, after the bank, we bust out Pierpont and Makley.
lt'll take a lot of careful planning.
Yeah. So?
PubIic Enemy Number One, John Dillinger.
They may be sitting amongst you.
They may be in your row.
Turn to your right.
And turn to your left.
lf you see them, call the Bureau of lnvestigation or your local police.
After the bank,
we'll figure out if we can bust them out. Okay?
Okay.
"You don't work with people you don't know
"and you don't work when you're desperate."
Walter Dietrich. Remember that?
Walter forgot.
When you're desperate, that's when you got no choice.
l got one!
What are you doing? Get your hands up! Get your hands up!
Come on, sugar, let's go. Come on.
Where's all the damn money we came here for?
Come on.
Open the door.
What are you looking at, huh?
What are you looking at?
Tommy.
John, let's go!
Let's go! Get in the goddamn car!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
How'd you find this place?
Don't worry. Nobody will find us. Come on.
How much?
$46, 1 20.
That'd be less than $800,000. Am l right?
Am l right?
lt's $8,000 a man.
Leave me my share and get out.
We gotta cut loose from Nelson.
You gotta rest up a while.
No.
No. lf we don't get out of here first thing in the morning,
we're gonna wind up dead.
Only you're gonna make it.
God damn it, don't talk like that, Red.
No, Johnny. l got a feeling that my time is up.
And when your time is up, your time's up.
Red,
look here.
Tomorrow morning, Homer, you and me will go to Reno,
and everything will be fine.
Give me a shot.
l'll give you the shot if you tell me where the gang's holed up.
l don't know anything.
Where's Baby Face Nelson?
l don't know!
Where's Dillinger?
l wanna know where they are.
l don't know!
Tell me! Where are they?
The bullet entered the back of his head.
lt's resting over his right eye.
Do not interfere.
His brain is swelling ! He will be dead soon !
He's suffering and l need to sedate him !
Not yet.
lf you interfere, l will arrest you.
l don't know! Please, give me a shot! Oh, mother, please!
Tell me where he is!
l don't know!
All right.
Where? Tell me!
Little Bohemia.
Manitowish, Wisconsin.
Fuck you !
Give me a shot.
Little Bohemia. Manitowish, Wisconsin.
Sam, you drive up.
Madala and Clegg, you cut through the woods. Stay in the trees.
Come up on it from the south,
close enough to see if they're in the barroom there.
Rice, Rorer,
come up on it from the north. The kitchen is there.
You see if they're in what is probably the dining room. You stay in the trees.
And if he sees them in there?
We go in.
And if he doesn't?
We go in anyway.
There's too much real estate out here.
Too many ways for him to get out,
too few of us to block him in.
We need to blockade the roads behind us.
We need to wait for Cowley's group to surround him.
Mr. Purvis, this is not the way to do it.
l will not risk their escaping the Bureau again.
You and Hurt take the northeast corner where the road turns.
Cover that and the front. Campbell, Baum, you're with me.
Thanks, but we gotta go.
No, come on, stick around. Let's have a party.
We gotta work tomorrow. Aw, work's for mugs.
Get out of here!
You wanna see my James Cagney?
You wanna see my James Cagney act? Huh? Huh?
What do you see? What do you say? What do you know?
What's your name, doll? This your wife, you dumb egg?
Go ahead.
Stop that car!
Bureau of lnvestigation !
Fire!
Don't shoot!
Get on the floor!
Johnny!
Go!
Someone got out!
Is it Dillinger?
I think so!
Baum, you drive around the woods. You flank him!
Go.
Go!
Come on, Red, come on. Come on. We're getting out of here.
Hey, give me the keys to that car.
Have you...
All you bastards wear vests,
so I'm gonna give it to you high and I'm gonna give it to you low.
Carter?
Who was it? Dillinger?
Nelson.
Sir, there's somebody on the road.
Cowley! Did you see a car?
A Ford, yeah, it's going the other way.
Turn it around! Madala, get in. It's Nelson!
Get in, you dumb bastards! Get in!
Get in. Come on. Let's go. Come on.
Where'd you get the car?
I killed a Fed by the road.
Faster, Sam!
They're behind us. Let them have it, Homer!
Steady the car, God damn it!
Shit!
Homer! Homer!
Come on!
Have you never seen a man die before?
Hush up.
You gotta let go, John.
Bullshit.
And you gotta let Billie go, too.
I know you.
You've never let nobody down.
But this time,
you gotta go on.
You gotta let go.
Right now,
all of Dillinger's friends are dead.
He is out there.
He is alone.
And there will not be a better chance to run him down.
Yeah, but he could be anywhere.
He could be anywhere.
But he is not anywhere, because what he wants is right here.
What's she doing?
Still listening to the radio.
Sir, we have questioned a source, John Probasco.
We have information that leads us to believe that they're...
But Dillinger did aid law enforcement in one way.
He's cited as the reason Congress is considering the first national crime bill,
making criminal enterprise across state lines a federal offense.
Meanwhile, in Fargo, North Dakota...
We're building coast-to-coast.
We want it nice and quiet, and they bring this on us?
Frank, calm down. They rob banks. Right.
In one state, then another state, that's called interstate.
We're coast to coast. Wake up!
Now they can use these laws on us.
What time is it?
It's 4:00 a. m., Sunday morning. What's wrong?
I don't want to sleep.
Why?
Because I want all the time we got.
What if
we could get out of here altogether?
Where?
Like Cuba?
Maybe further.
Alvin's got this job. It's a big job, a lot of dough.
We could go away on it.
We grab a Pan Am Clipper to Caracas,
scoot on over to Rio for some fun in the sun,
slide off the map.
We could go dancing
and have a lot of laughs
any time we want.
Want to take that ride with me?
Yeah, I want to take that ride with you.
Where's the apartment?
Oakley and Potomac.
All right, the bartender's name is Larry Strong.
He'll give you the keys.
Who brought you? How did you get here?
A taxi. I took a taxi.
Let's go. Let's go, guys. Come on! Get her outside.
Where is he?
Where were you meeting? Where were you hiding out?
Answer him or they'll drop you in a black hole in Cook County.
Where is he?
I have to go to the bathroom.
Christ, look what you did.
Where were you supposed to meet him?
I can't hear you.
I can't hear you!
We were supposed to meet at our apartment.
Where?
On Addison.
What number?
1148.
When?
Right now.
Miss Roberts, can you reach Agent Purvis?
No. He's on his way back from Mooresville, Indiana.
He's going directly to Cook County Jail.
John Dillinger's holed up at 1148 Addison.
Where is he?
Well,
way the hell away from here by now, isn't he?
You wanted to know where he is, you dumb flatfoot.
Mr. Purvis, those men cannot treat a woman in this way.
You walked right past him on State Street.
You were too scared to look around.
He was at the curb in that black Buick.
You asked me how I got there, I told you I took a taxi,
and you believed me?
He dropped me off and was waiting for me.
And you walked right past him.
And when my Johnny finds out how you slapped around his girl,
you know what happens to you, fat boy?
Uncuff her.
Restroom is down the hall.
I can't stand up.
Miss Rogers.
Hello.
I'm Marty Zarkovich. I was told to call you, Mr. Nitti.
I think I can get her to play ball.
Make sure.
Yes, sir, Mr. Nitti.
What did they say, Anna?
They say they send me back to Romania.
You know what to do.
Can they fix deportation? Can they do that?
These guys can fix anything.
Okay.
I want guarantee.
If you aid us in apprehending John Dillinger,
I give you my word
I will do everything I can to influence Bureau of Immigration
to let you stay in America.
Not enough.
Well, that's all there is.
I want guarantee.
Well, you're not gonna get one.
I think you did this.
I think you told Immigration to pick me up and send me back to Romania.
How do you socialize with him?
We go out.
Maybe tomorrow night. Maybe not.
Maybe in a week, a month. Maybe never.
I will not guarantee what Immigration will do,
but I can guarantee what I will do.
If you do not cooperate,
you will be on a boat out of this country in 48 hours.
Do not play games with me.
Who is "we"?
Me, him, Polly Hamilton, one of my girls.
How will we know?
I call you on the day when I know.
Did you get in there? Did you see her?
Yes, I did.
She palmed me this note.
She told me what it said.
That's good advice.
What are you doing here?
Meeting people.
On Tuesday, it'll carry the payrolls for seven factories around Rockford.
There's two ways in, two ways out.
Doc cuts the telephone lines five minutes before.
Train arrives, you and I go in strong.
Harry handles the door and the safe.
Jimmy and Freddy drive.
What do you figure?
About $1,500,000 to $1,700,000.
$300,000 each.
Holy cow.
Yeah.
We pull this Tuesday, I'm gone Wednesday.
Yeah. Where? Cuba?
No.
No. Where I go, I'm gonna have to go a lot farther than Cuba.
Yeah.
Hi, Jimmy.
What do you say?
Polly, Jimmy's back!
I tell you what, doll.
How about you, Polly and me go out to a movie tonight?
Get in some refrigeration.
Where do you want to go?
Maybe the Marbro or the Biograph.
Jimmy's taking us to the picture show.
Mmm.
I'll go to the store later and make fried chicken for dinner.
Where you going?
Streetcar.
I gotta go downtown to get my waitressing license.
Hang on a minute. I'll take you. It's too damn hot in here.
Yeah?
Mr. Purvis. Anna Sage.
Afternoon, Miss Sage.
It is tonight!
Anna Sage will be with him
and will wear a white blouse over an orange skirt.
That is how we will know it is him.
He may have changed his appearance.
And we have not learned if he will go to the Marbro or the Biograph.
Two theaters?
That's right.
What's playing?
Excuse me?
What's playing at the Marbro? What's playing at the Biograph?
A Shirley Temple movie called Little Miss Marker is at the Marbro.
The Biograph is playing a gangster picture
starring Clark Gable, Manhattan Melodrama.
John Dillinger ain't going to a Shirley Temple movie.
Sergeants Zarkovich and O'Neill, from the East Chicago Police Department,
and Agent Winstead will be at the Biograph, as will I.
Now, Virgil Peterson, you will coordinate the Marbro.
He will be armed and extremely dangerous.
Is that it?
Yep.
I'll be right back.
Hold on.
I'll go in with you.
All right.
It might take 10 minutes.
I'll meet you outside.
I'd like to see Babe take one more swing this season.
But his leg is pretty sore. He takes a bit of batting practice, but not very much.
What's the score?
Cubs, 3-2, top of the 7th.
...that's why he's out of today's game.
The pitch is high. Ball one.
Broaca, the batter leading off for the Yankees,
did not see the ball very well.
What's going on?
Nothing yet.
They haven't shown up at the Marbro.
Blackie!
Jim!
Well, you old son of a gun!
I say, you're looking swell, Jim.
Let's get a load of this Dempsey-Firpo binge, shall we?
Yeah, yeah. But when will we get together again? Gee, it's been weeks!
Well, what about tomorrow night? Saturday?
I will light my cigar when he's coming out.
Zarkovich, O'Neill, you and your men
take the hat store right across from the theater.
Smith, Suran, Clegg, take two agents, you cover the rear alley.
And Rorer and Rice, you stay in the car with Reinecke to the north.
Clarence and I are gonna be in the doorway
30 feet south of the theater entrance.
Gerry, you're in the tan sedan just to the north of the entrance.
In case he walks north?
He ain't gonna walk north, Mr. Purvis.
He's gonna head south, cut through the alley back to her place.
Madala.
Hello, Gallagher.
Hello, Snow.
Must be something pretty important,
getting me in here in the middle of the game.
What do you want?
I want to do a little favor for a friend.
You're the governor. You can save his life.
He's guilty. The jury says so.
Goodbye, Blackie.
Goodbye, Jim.
I can't help it, Blackie.
I'm not gonna let you die.
I've got to commute you.
You think you're doing me a favor
by keeping me locked up in this filthy trap for the rest of my life?
No, thanks. Come on, warden, let's go.
So long, Blackie.
Kid, keep your chin up and your nose clean.
Die the way you lived, all of a sudden, that's the way to go.
Don't drag it out.
Living like that doesn't mean a thing.
What did he say?
I couldn't hear him.
You take care of this. I need to go call Washington.
How you doing, Billie?
I'm Special Agent Winstead.
If you've come here to ask me more damn questions...
"Where's this one or that one?"
I didn't come here for you to tell me something.
I came here to tell you something.
They say you're the man who shot him.
That's right. One of them.
So why are you coming here to see me?
To see the damage you've done?
No.
I came here because he asked me to.
When he went down, he said something.
I put my ear next to his mouth,
and what I think he said was this.
He said,
"Tell Billie for me,
"'Bye-bye, blackbird. "'
Thanks for watching
-=The Last Fantasy=-