[TYPEWRITER LOADING]
[TYPEWRITER CLACKING]
[WOMEN TALKING]
I've finished my play.
Well done.
Have you seen mummy?
Well, she'll be
in the drawing room, I expect.
I hope you're not going to be
getting under our feet today, Miss Briony.
We've got
a dinner for 10 to prepare.
Hello, pal.
I hear you're putting on a play.
Who told you?
Jungle drums.
Will you come and see it?
I'm not sure that would be quite
Why don't you let me read it?
You used to make me those
beautiful bound copies of all your stories.
I've kept them all.
I still want you to come.
Let's see.
I have to go now.
Mummy, I need you!
Stupendous. It's
stupendous, darling. Your first play.
Do you think so?
Do you think Leon will like it?
Well, of course he will.
The Trials of Arabella
by Briony Tallis
- Cee.
- Yes?
What do you think
it would feel like to be someone else?
Cooler, I should hope.
I'm worried about the play.
I'm sure it's a masterpiece.
But we only have
the afternoon to rehearse.
What if the twins can't act?
You have to be nice to them.
I wonder how'd you feel
if your mother had run off with
Mr. What's-His-Name
who reads the news on the wireless?
Perhaps I should have
written Leon a story.
If you write a story, you only
have to say the word "castle," and you could see
the towers and the woods
and the village below, but
in a play, it's
It all depends on other people.
- Cee.
- Yes?
Why don't you
talk to Robbie any more?
I do. We just move
in different circles. That's all.
[WHEELBARROW RATTLING]
Do we have to do a play?
Why do we have to?
It's to celebrate
my brother Leon's visit.
I hate plays.
JACKSON:
So do I.
How can you hate plays?
It's just showing off.
You'll be in this play
or you'll get a clout, and I'll tell the parents.
You're not allowed to clout us.
We're guests in this house.
And what did the parents say
we were to make ourselves?
- Well, Pierrot?
- Amenable.
- Jackson?
Amenable, that's right.
Now, Briony,
what's your play about?
Well, it's about how
love is all very well
but you have to be sensible.
- I suppose you're going to be Arabella.
- Well, not necessarily.
LOLA: In that case
do you mind if I play her?
PIERROT:
Lola was in the school play.
Do say yes. It'd be
the first decent thing to happen to me in months.
Well, yes. All right.
I suppose we should
start by reading it.
If you're going to be Arabella
then I'll be
the director, thank you very much.
Sorry.
I'm going to do the prologue.
"Prologue"
"This is the tale
of spontaneous Arabella"
"who ran away
with an extrinsic fellow."
"It grieved her parents
to see their firstborn"
"evanesce from her home
to go to Eastbourne."
[DOOR CREAKS]
Yes?
Nothing. Just thought I'd watch.
BRIONY:
Rehearsals are private, I'm afraid.
You can
see the play this evening.
I'll have to work then.
Well, I'm sorry, Danny.
JACKSON:
Can we go for a swim now?
Yes!
No, I don't
really think there's time!
PIERROT:
Cecilia will let us.
I'm sure a half-hour break
would do us all good.
PIERROT:
Cecilia? Cecilia!
Cecilia!
[BEE BUZZING]
[BUZZING]
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
Cecilia! Please,
can we go for a swim, Cecilia?
Yes, I don't see why not.
Don't go out of your depth!
Can you do me one
of your Bolshevik roll-ups?
Beautiful day.
I suppose so. Too hot for me.
- Are you enjoying your book?
- No, not really.
It gets better.
I prefer Fielding any day:
much more passionate.
Leon's coming down today,
did you know?
I heard a rumor.
He's bringing a friend with him.
It's Paul Marshall,
the chocolate millionaire.
Are the flowers for him?
Why shouldn't they be?
Leon says he's very charming.
Uh-huh.
The Old Man telephoned last night.
He says you're planning on being a doctor.
I'm thinking about it, yes.
Another six years of student life.
How else do you become a doctor?
You could get
a fellowship, now, couldn't you?
- I don't want to teach.
- With your First?
I said I'd pay your father back.
That's not what I meant at all.
- Let me help with that.
- No, I'm all right, thanks.
- Take the flowers. Take the flowers.
- I'm all right.
Oh, you idiot.
Do you realize that's probably
the most valuable thing we own?
Not anymore, it isn't.
Careful!
I'm...
[CAR HORN HONKING]
LEON:
Hello, Robbie!
No need to encourage him.
Cee?
Mother?
Where is everyone, Danny?
I don't know, sir.
Sir.
- LEON: Gasping for a drink.
- Sir?
- Will you have one?
- Rather.
- Whiskey?
- Please.
- Leon!
- Here she is.
Oh, I've missed you.
I've been going completely doolally up here.
This is my sister, Cecilia.
Paul Marshall.
I've heard
an awful lot about you.
Likewise.
Where are we putting him?
In the blue room.
Mother's lying down.
She's got one of her migraines.
I'm not surprised, with this heat.
It's the big room
next to the nursery.
Is the Old Man staying in town?
LEON: Looks like it.
Some sort of rush on at the Ministry.
[THUDDING]
So aren't we doing the play?
No.
Why not?
Don't ask me.
I don't like it here.
PAUL: There's always a problem
when a new brand comes about:
the remarketing,
the re-packaging, the re-shaping
even the re-flavoring
in some cases, or whole new technology.
I think our main challenge
is whether or not to launch the new Amo Bar.
The Army Amo.
Do you see? Pass the Amo?
[PAUL CHUCKLES]
My source at the Ministry
is very reliable
I used to
clean his shoes at Harrow.
Informs me we have a good chance
of including it
in the standard issue ration pack
which means that I'd have to
open at least three more factories.
more if they bring in conscription,
which I'd say is bound to happen
if Herr Hitler doesn't pipe down.
He's about as likely to do that
as buy shares
in Marks and Spencer's,
wouldn't you agree?
This isn't very good.
I make a cocktail
with crushed ice
rum and melted dark chocolate.
It's absolutely scrumptious.
Guess who we met
on the way in?
Robbie.
I told him to join us tonight.
Oh, Leon, you didn't.
So, Robbie,
the housekeeper's son
whose father
did a bunk 20 years ago
gets a scholarship
to the local grammar
the Old Man
puts him through Cambridge
goes up
at the same time as Cee
and for three years
she hardly speaks to him.
Wouldn't let him
within a mile of her Roedean chums.
Anyone got a cigarette?
I don't know what the hell
he's doing these days, messing about in flower beds.
As a matter of fact,
he's planning on doing a medical degree.
LEON:
And the Old Man said yes to that?
Look. I really think you should
go down to the lodge and ask him not to come.
Why?
Has something happened between you?
For God's sake.
When can we go home?
LOLA:
Soon.
We can't go home. It's a divorce.
How dare you say that?
Well, it's true!
You will never, ever
use that word again! Do you understand?
Now what are we going to do?
I'm always asking myself that.
My name is Paul Marshall.
You must be the cousins from the north.
- What are your names?
- Pierrot.
- Jackson.
- What marvelous names.
JACKSON:
Do you know our parents?
Well, I've read
about them in the paper.
What exactly
have you read about them?
Oh, you know:
the usual sort of nonsense.
I'll thank you not to
talk about this in front of the children.
Your parents
are absolutely wonderful people.
That's quite clear. And
they love you and think about you all the time.
Jolly nice slacks.
We went to see a show
and I got them at Liberty's.
What was the show?
Hamlet.
Ah, yes: "To be or not to be."
I like your shoes.
Duckers in the Turl.
They make a wooden thing, shaped like your foot.
Keep it forever.
PIERROT:
I'm starving. When's dinner?
Well, I might be able to help you there,
if you can guess what I do for a living.
- You've got a chocolate factory.
- Everyone knows that.
Then it wasn't a guess, was it?
There'll be one of these in every kit bag
of every soldier in the British Army.
Sugar casing, so that it won't melt.
JACKSON:
Why should they get free sweets?
Because they'll be
fighting for their country.
Our daddy says
there isn't going to be a war.
Your daddy is wrong.
Calling it the Army Amo.
Amo, amas, amat.
Top marks.
It's boring how
everything ends in "o:" "Polo" and "Aero."
And "Oxo" and "Brillo".
Sounds as if you don't want it.
Then I shall just have to
give it to your sister.
Bite it.
You have to bite it.
BRIONY: The Princess was well aware
of his remorseless wickedness
but that made it
no easier to overcome
the voluminous love
she felt in her heart for Sir Romulus.
The Princess knew instinctively
that the one with red hair
was not to be trusted.
As his young ward dived
again and again to the depths of the lake
in search of the enchanted chalice,
Sir Romulus twirled his luxuriant mustache.
Sir Romulus rode with his two companions,
northwards, drawing ever closer
to an effulgent sea.
So heroic in manner,
he appeared so valiant in word
[TYPEWRITER CLACKING]
no one could ever guess at the darkness
lurking in the black heart
of Sir Romulus Turnbull.
He was the most
dangerous man in the world.
"Dear Cecilia, I thought
I should write to apologize for my clumsy"
"and inconsiderate behavior."
[OPERA PLAYING]
"Forgive me if I seem strange but I'm..."
[CHUCKLING]
ROBBIE: Dear Cecilia,
you'd be forgiven for thinking me mad
the way I acted this afternoon.
The truth is, I feel rather
lightheaded and foolish in your presence, Cee
and I don't think
I can blame the heat.
"Will you forgive me?"
"Robbie."
Off out then?
Yes. Leon's asked me
to join them for dinner.
So that's why I've been
polishing silver all afternoon.
I'll think of you when
I see my face in the spoon.
You're not a bit
like your father, not in any way.
That's because
I'm all yours. I'll be late.
Your shirts
are hanging upstairs.
- Son.
- Yes?
Nothing.
Briony! Is that you?
Are you all right?
Do you think
you could do me a favor?
Could you run ahead
and give this to Cee? I
feel a bit of a fool,
handing it over, myself.
All right.
Briony.
Briony!
[PANTING]
I suppose he's
what you might call eligible.
Rather.
He certainly seems to
think he's the cat's pyjamas
which is odd, considering
he has pubic hair growing out of his ears.
I should imagine he'd give you
a lot of very noisy, boneheaded sons.
He's quite a good egg, actually.
You say that about everyone.
Leon!
Rummy, if it isn't my little sis!
I wrote you a play, Leon.
I wanted to do a play for you.
- The Trials Of Arabella.
- Well, there's still time.
- Doesn't have to be this evening.
- No, it's impossible.
- Briony.
- Tell you what. I'm good at voices.
You're even better.
So we'll read it out after dinner.
Briony, did you read this letter?
Yes, let's.
That's a wonderful idea.
Briony!
Here we are: my choc-tail.
I insist you try it.
Wasn't there an envelope?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Do you mind if I come in?
I've had the most appalling evening.
The twins have been
torturing me. Look.
How awful.
Chinese burns.
That's right.
They want to go home.
They think it's me that's keeping them here.
[SOBBING]
Lola.
Can I tell you something?
Something really terrible?
Yes, please.
What's the worst word
you can possibly imagine?
[BELL RINGING]
He's a sex maniac!
That's right.
- What's Cecilia going to do?
- I don't know.
You ought to call the police.
Do you think so?
He said
he thought about it all day long.
All you have to do
is show them the letter.
You won't tell anyone,
will you? Promise?
I promise.
Good. If he found out,
there's no knowing what he might do.
You're right.
You better tidy your face.
I've still got to change.
Thanks, Briony.
You're a real brick.
[MEN CHATTERING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[PANTING]
BRIONY:
Cecilia!
- It was a mistake.
- Briony read it.
My God, I'm so sorry.
It was the wrong version.
Yes.
- It was never meant to be read.
- No.
[CLOCK CHIMING]
What was in
the version I was meant to read?
I don't know.
It was more formal, less
- Anatomical?
- Yes.
It's been there for weeks,
and then this morning by the fountain...
I've never done
anything like that before.
And I was so angry
with you, and with myself
I thought if you went away
to medical school, then I'd be happy, but
I don't know how I could have
been so ignorant about myself, so...
so stupid.
You do know what
I'm talking about, don't you?
You knew before I did.
Why are you crying?
Don't you know?
Yes, I know exactly.
[SIGHING]
[BOTH PANTING]
Robbie.
Cecilia.
I love you.
[MOANING]
[DOOR OPENING]
Someone's come in.
Cecilia!
People were sitting out,
having dinner on the pavement.
It was always the view of my parents
that hot weather encouraged loose morals.
In high summer, my sister and I
were never allowed out of the house.
They thought the villagers
would be unnecessarily provoked.
What do you say, Cee?
Does the hot weather make you behave badly?
Good heavens, you're blushing.
It's just hot in here. That's all.
Lola, wipe that lipstick off.
You're far too young.
What about you, Briony?
What sins have you committed today?
I've done nothing wrong.
EMILY:
Have you seen the twins recently?
They didn't look very happy
the last time I saw them, poor little chaps.
BRIONY:
You know nothing about it.
EMILY: Briony. I can't imagine
what's got into you.
I've never known you to be so rude.
Well, they're not poor little chaps.
- Just look what they did to Lola.
- What are you talking about?
Jackson and Pierrot
bruised her arm, gave her Chinese burns.
I'm afraid she's quite right.
I had to pull them off her:
how I got my war wound.
The twins did that, Lola?
Yes, it all turned into a bit of
a wrestle, I'm afraid. Still, no harm done, eh, Lola?
EMILY: Would you go and
find these boys, please, Briony?
Tell them dinner's ready,
and where are their manners?
- Why do I have to go?
- Briony, you'll do as you're told
or you'll go straight to your room.
- BRIONY: It's a letter!
- Give it to me!
- BRIONY: They've run away.
- EMILY: Who has?
The twins.
"We are going to run away because
Lola is so horrid to us and we want to go home."
- "Also, there wasn't a play."
- Don't worry.
We'll send out some search parties.
They can't have gone far.
Cee, you come with me.
LEON:
Pierrot!
CECILIA:
Jackson!
PAUL:
Boys!
Jackson!
Pierrot!
[RUSTLING]
[SCREAMS]
[GASPS]
[SOBBING]
Lola? Are you all right?
I'm sorry. I didn't... I'm sorry.
Who was it?
I saw him.
It was him, wasn't it?
Yes, it was him.
Lola, who was it?
It was Robbie, wasn't it? Robbie?
You saw him?
Like you said, he's a sex maniac.
And you don't even know
what happened before dinner.
I caught him
attacking my sister in the library.
I don't know what he'd have done
if I hadn't come in.
You actually saw him?
Of course I did, plain as day.
He pushed me to the ground
and then he put his hands over my eyes.
I couldn't actually...
I never actually...
Listen. I've known him
my whole life, and I saw him.
Because I couldn't say for sure.
Well, I can and I will.
Call the police.
And she'll be needing a doctor, as well.
[LOLA SOBBING]
It's all right, dear.
It's all right now.
Is Robbie back yet?
I haven't seen him.
I know who it was.
You saw him, then?
Yes, I saw him.
Just as you see me?
I know it was him.
You know it was him? Or you saw him?
Yes, I did. I saw him.
With your own eyes?
Yes. I saw him.
I saw him with my own eyes.
Well done, darling.
[TYPEWRITER CLACKING]
My brother and I
found the two of them down by the lake.
POLICEMAN:
You didn't see anyone else?
I wouldn't necessarily believe
everything Briony tells you. She's rather fanciful.
When they went looking
I went up to my dad's.
I did, honest.
POLICEMAN:
Why was that?
To tell him all about it.
I know I shouldn't have opened it.
No, you should not
but at least
you've done the right thing now.
[SNORING]
[TAPPING PIANO KEY]
Sir, there is someone coming.
- Time you went to bed.
- But
Now.
[DOOR OPENING]
EMILY:
Cecilia!
You liars! Liars!
[GRACE WAILING]
[HARMONICA PLAYING]
I says to him, I says,
"You can sit down there, twiddling your thumbs"
"waiting to get
your head blown off, if you want to."
"I'm off out of it."
[SHUSHING]
[FLOOR CREAKING]
MAN:
Bonsoir, monsieur. Bonsoir?
[WHISPERING] Let me do this.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
[ALL PANTING]
What's his game?
He says he's got something for us.
Fucking hell!
[PANTS]
Come on, then.
How come a toff like you,
talks French and everything, ends up a private?
Not eligible for officers' training
if you join direct from prison.
You're pulling my tit.
No, I'm not.
They gave me a choice:
stay in prison or join the Army.
And for the record,
the last thing I am is a toff.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
I'm sorry I'm late. I got lost.
- Hello.
Should we sit down?
Yes, of course.
I'm sorry, I can't remember
Two. Thank you.
Where are you living?
A tiny flat in Balham. It's ghastly.
The landlady's
rude and horribly nosy.
You look the same
apart from the uniform, of course.
Yes, I'm sorry. I've got to
go back to the hospital in half an hour.
Oh, God, that...
- Sorry.
- No.
Have you been
in touch with your family?
No, I told you I wouldn't.
Leon waited outside the hospital last week.
I just pushed past him.
Cee, you don't owe me anything.
Robbie, didn't you read my letters?
Had I been allowed to visit you,
had they let me every day
I would have been there every day.
Yes but
If all we have
rests on a few moments
in a library three and a half years ago,
then I'm not sure
- I don't know if
- Robbie, look at me.
Look at me.
[WHISPERS]
Come back.
Come back to me.
ROBBIE:
Dearest Cecilia.
Cecilia.
A friend of mine
has a cottage by the coast.
He said we can borrow it
when you're next on leave.
White clapboard
with blue-painted window frames.
I hope this bus never comes.
Here.
Something
to think of while you're away.
I love you.
[SIGHS]
[PLANES DRONING]
Some poor sod's
going to catch a packet.
CECILIA: My darling, Briony
found my address somehow, and sent a letter.
The first surprise was
she didn't go up to Cambridge.
She's doing
nurse's training at my old hospital.
I think she may be doing this
as some kind of penance.
She says she's beginning to get
the full grasp of what she did and what it meant.
She wants to come and talk to me.
I love you.
I'll wait for you. Come back.
Come back to me.
ROBBIE:
Come back. Come back to me.
So where we going, guv?
I fucking hate those boots!
I hate them worse than
all the fucking Germans put together!
You'll have a job
getting back to England in your socks.
Come on, pal.
You should be getting dressed.
If I fell in, would you save me?
Of course.
[WATER SPLASHES]
Briony!
[GASPING]
[LAUGHS]
Thank you.
Thank you!
That's an incredibly
bloody stupid thing to do.
I wanted you to save me.
Don't you know
how easily you could have drowned?
You saved me.
Stupid child!
You could have killed us both.
Is that your idea of a joke?
I want to thank you
for saving my life.
I will be
eternally grateful to you.
ROBBIE:
The story can resume.
Our story can resume.
I will simply resume.
Jerry, come and
have a go at us in fucking South End
or better still, Trafalgar Square.
No one speaks
the fucking lingo out here.
You can't say, "Pass the biscuit"
or "Where's me hand grenade?"
They just shrug. Because
they hate us, too. I mean, that's the point.
We fight in France
and the French fucking hate us.
Make me Home Secretary.
I'll sort this out in a fucking minute.
We've got India and Africa, right?
Jerry can have France and Belgium
and wherever else they want.
Who's fucking ever been to Poland?
It's all about room, empire.
They want more empire:
Give them this shithole. We keep ours
and it's "Bob's your uncle"
and "Fanny's your fucking aunt"!
Think about it.
ROBBIE:
Dearest Cecilia, the story can resume
the one I had been
planning on, that evening walk.
I can become again
the man who once crossed the Surrey park
at dusk in my best suit,
swaggering on the promise of life.
The man who,
with the clarity of passion
made love to you in the library.
The story can resume.
I will return
find you, love you, marry you
and live without shame.
You can smell the sea.
Fuck me.
It's like
something out of the Bible.
Jesus Christ.
Come on. Get everybody
to clean this mess up now.
ROBBIE: We've just arrived, sir.
Can you tell us what we're supposed to be doing?
Nothing. Just wait.
ROBBIE:
Where are the ships?
A few made it in yesterday.
The Luftwaffe blew them to buggery.
We lost 3,000 men
when they sank the Lancastria.
High command, in its infinite wisdom,
is denying us air cover.
A disgrace, a fucking disaster.
No, Look. The thing is, you see,
I'm expected back, you see.
There's over 300,000 men on this beach, private.
You'll have to wait your turn.
Just be grateful you're not wounded.
I've orders
to leave the wounded behind.
No. Leave it, guv!
Never trust a sailor on dry land.
You're best off out of it.
[GUN FIRING]
That's not right.
Christ.
MAN:
Can you hear me, laddies?
I'm coming home!
[SINGING) Take from our souls
the strain and stress
And let our ordered
lives confess
The beauty of Thy peace
Breathe through
the heats of our desire
Thy coolness and Thy balm
Let sense be numb,
let flesh retire
Speak through
the earthquake, wind and fire
O still, small voice of calm
[PANTING]
[MEN WHOOPING]
Guv'nor
I have to get something to drink.
You need one. You're gray.
He's gone all gray, can you see?
There. Come on.
MAN:
All I want's a cup of tea now.
What the fuck are you doing?
MAN: I'm coming home!
Laddie, I'm coming home!
[MEN SINGING]
Fuck 'em all! Fuck 'em all!
The long and the short and the tall
Fuck all the sergeants and WO1s
Fuck all the corporals
and their bastard sons
'Cause we're
saying goodbye to them all
As back to
their billets they crawl
You'll get no promotion
this side of the ocean
So cheer up, my lads.
Fuck 'em all!
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Mike!
Hold up, guv.
Wait here.
Why don't you sit down?
It's so hot in here.
Take off your boots.
I have to get back. I promised her
to put things right
and she loves me.
She's waiting for me.
[ARTILLERY FIRING]
[EXPLOSION]
Oi!
Wait.
Hey. What have you done
with your boots?
Look. You're sure
you're feeling all right?
Never better.
Now I'm wondering whether
the beach really is the best place for dinner.
[BOMB EXPLODING]
I'm not sure. I don't recognize it.
I don't know. This'll do, down here.
No.
No. It's further on.
What is?
This place I know,
an old cottage with white clapboards
and blue-painted window frames.
Oh yes. Yeah, that's right.
That's where we're going.
It's close to here.
We're there. This is it.
Here we are, guv, down here.
That's all right, guv. That's right.
Get your head down. There you go.
[HUMMING]
Tuck yourself in. Keep yourself warm.
Chew on a bit of this.
But quiet like,
or they'll all be wanting some.
Try and get some sleep.
[SINGING]
ROBBIE:
Find you.
Love you.
Marry you.
And live without shame.
I love you.
Come back. Come back to me.
- A bit too much noise, guv'nor.
- What?
What noise?
You keep shouting.
Some of the lads
are getting a bit peeved.
What?
Christ. You look a bit rough.
The thing is,
I've decided to stay on for a bit.
I'm meeting someone
and I'm always keeping her waiting.
Now, listen. Listen to me, guv'nor.
I went out for
a Jimmy Riddle just now. Guess what I saw!
They're getting themselves
sorted out down on the beach.
The boats are back, and a geezer
from the Buffs is marching us down at 7:00.
We're away. We're off home, mate.
So get some more sleep,
and no more of your bleeding shouting.
All right?
I won't say a word.
Wake me before 7:00,
would you? Thanks so much.
You won't hear
another word from me. I promise.
Bed castors should be
lined up and pointing inwards.
I found three yesterday that weren't.
You know who you are.
Which of you were responsible
for putting away the blankets today?
I was, sister.
I don't suppose you can
tell us what you did wrong?
No, Sister.
Labels are folded
to the inside, are they not?
- Yes, sister.
- Do them again.
Nurse Tallis,
I'll see you in my office.
The rest of you are excused.
Is this job at all
important to you, Tallis?
Very important, sister.
Yesterday, you were
seconded to men's surgical.
When your patient came round
from his anesthetic, it seems the first thing he did
was ask for Briony.
Who might Briony be?
Well me, sister.
There is no Briony.
You are Tallis,
nurse Tallis. Is that understood?
Yes, sister.
There is no Briony.
MAN ON RADIO: This is
the BBC Home Service. Here is the news.
The BEF, with their French allies,
are fighting a desperate battle
in the northern zone
of the Western Front.
The Allied Forces have not
lost cohesion, and their morale is high.
The RAF continues to give
all the support in its power
to the Allied armies in
northeastern France and Belgium. Railways, roads
bridges and enemy troops
have been continuously attacked, yesterday...
[WOMEN CHATTERING]
Thanks. I never could
make the scissors work with my left hand.
Mummy always did it for me.
There. You're done.
Bother!
Night-night, Ponty.
Good night, Tallis.
Don't panic! It's only me.
Fiona, I almost
jumped out of my skin.
So this is where
you duck to after lights out.
I thought you might be
in the middle of some tempestuous romance.
Don't you freeze to death up here?
I love London.
Do you think all of this
will be bombed and just disappear?
No.
I don't know.
Do you write about Sister Drummond?
- Do you write about me?
- Sometimes.
Can I look?
I'd rather you didn't.
It's private.
I don't see any point
in writing a story
if you're not going to
let anyone read it.
It's not ready yet. It's unfinished.
What's it about?
It's complicated.
Yes?
It's just...
It's about a young girl, a young
and foolish girl, who sees something from
her bedroom window which
she doesn't understand, but she thinks she does.
I probably won't ever finish it.
I look at you, Tallis,
and you're so mysterious.
I've never been mysterious.
Do you know
what I decided tonight?
What?
I could never marry a man
who wasn't in the Royal Navy.
[SNIGGERING]
[SHUSHING]
Here we are. Cecilia Tallis.
I think this is her address.
Thank you.
Dear Cecilia. Please don't
throw this away without reading it.
As you'll have seen from the notepaper,
I'm here at St. Thomas'
doing my nurses' training.
I decided not to
take up my place at Cambridge.
Oh, God.
I decided I wanted to
make myself useful, do something practical.
It says in the newspaper,
the Army are making strategic withdrawals.
Yes, I saw that.
It's a euphemism for retreat.
No matter how hard I work,
no matter how long the hours
I can't escape from what I did
and what it meant
the full extent of which
I am only now beginning to grasp.
Cee, please
write and tell me we can meet.
Your sister, Briony.
So do you?
Do I what?
Have a secret fiance in France.
That's what everyone thinks.
No, of course not.
Imagine not knowing
if he'd ever come back.
I've never been in love.
What, never? Not even a crush?
Oh, I had a crush once,
when I was 10 or 11.
I jumped into a river
to see if he'd save me from drowning.
Now you're teasing me.
Oh, no. And he did save me.
But as soon as I told him I loved him,
the feeling sort of disappeared.
Something's happened.
[BELL RINGING]
NURSE:
Outside, quickly.
[CLAMORING]
[GROANING]
Robbie.
Excuse me.
Nurse Tallis, you speak
a little French, if I remember rightly.
Only school French, sister.
There's a soldier in Bed 13.
Go and sit with him for a minute. Hold his hand.
Off you go.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
Robbie?
Luc.
Luc Cornet.
Tallis.
- Tallis.
- Briony.
Je m'appelle Briony.
SISTER:
Stand up, Nurse Tallis.
Now go and wash
the blood off your face.
NARRATOR: The Navy has earned
our undying gratitude. The Army is undefeated.
Courage has brought them through
unconquered, their spirit unbowed.
This is the epic of Dunkirk
a name that will live forever
in the annals of warfare.
In the course of
a comprehensive tour
Queen Elizabeth is seen here
visiting a chocolate factory in the north of England.
The confectionary magnate
and friend of the British Army
Mr. Paul Marshall, gave the Queen
a tour of the Army Amo factory
with his lovely, soon-to-be-wed
fiancée, Miss Lola Quincey.
What a mouthwatering
couple they are.
Keep the Amo coming.
Our boys have a sweet tooth.
Secondly, for a remedy against sin,
and to avoid fornication
that such persons
as have not the gift of continence
might marry and keep themselves
undefiled members of Christ's body.
Thirdly, it was ordained,
for the mutual society, help and comfort
that the one ought to have the other.
I saw him.
Therefore
if any man can show any just cause
why they may not
be lawfully joined together
I know it was him.
...let him now speak
or forever hold his peace.
[GASPS]
I saw him.
I saw him with my own eyes.
[ORGAN PLAYING]
WOMAN:
Let the nursey through.
They're going
down to the country today.
Never been out of London before.
I hope they get a nice family.
They don't know
what they're in for with this lot.
Come on.
I'm looking for
Miss Tallis, Cecilia Tallis.
Is she in?
Tallis! Door!
I tried writing. You wouldn't answer.
I have to talk to you.
[DOOR CLOSING]
So you're a ward sister now?
Yes.
Thanks.
I want to go in front of a judge
and change my evidence, Cee.
Don't call me that.
Please don't call me that.
I know what I did was terrible.
I don't expect you to forgive me.
Oh, don't worry. I won't.
You're an unreliable witness.
They'll never reopen the case.
Well, at least I could
tell everyone else what I did.
I can go home and
explain to mummy and daddy and Leon
So what's stopping you?
Well, I wanted to see you first.
They don't want to
hear any more about it.
That unpleasantness is all
tidied away in the past, thank you very much.
But...
I'll be late. I'd better get moving.
Excuse me.
He sleeps so deeply.
What is she doing here?
She wanted to speak to me.
Oh, yes. What about?
The terrible thing I did.
Robbie. Darling.
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
I'll be quite honest with you.
I'm torn between
breaking your neck here
and taking you and
throwing you down the stairs.
Oh, God.
Do you have any idea
what it's like in jail? Of course, you don't.
Tell me, did it give you
pleasure to think of me inside?
- No.
- But you did nothing about it.
- Do you think I assaulted your cousin?
- No.
- Did you think it then?
Yes. But yes and no.
- And what's made you so certain now?
- Growing up.
- Growing up?
- I was 13.
How old do you have to be
to know the difference between right and wrong?
What are you? 18?
Do you have to be 18 before
you can bring yourself to own up to a lie?
There are soldiers of 18,
old enough to be left to die by the side of the road.
- Did you know that?
- Yes.
Five years ago
you didn't care about telling the truth.
You, all your family,
you just assumed that for all my education
I was still little better
than a servant, still not to be trusted!
Thanks to you, they were able to
close ranks and throw me to the fucking wolves!
- Robbie! Look at me.
- Don't!
Come back.
Come back to me.
CECILIA:
Briony.
There isn't much time.
Robbie has to report for duty
at 6:00, and he's got a train to catch
so sit down.
There are some things
you're going to do for us.
You'll go to your parents
as soon as you can
and you'll tell them
everything they need to know
to be convinced that
the evidence you gave was false.
You'll meet with
a solicitor, make a statement
have it signed, witnessed,
send copies to us. Is that clear?
Yes.
You'll write a detailed letter to me
explaining everything that happened
leading up to you saying
you saw me by the lake.
Try to include
whatever you can remember
of what Danny Hardman
was doing that night.
- Hardman?
- Yes.
It wasn't Danny Hardman.
It was Leon's friend, Marshall.
I don't believe you.
He's married Lola.
I've just come from their wedding.
Lola won't be able to
testify against him now.
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
He's immune.
I'm very, very sorry
for the terrible distress that I have caused.
I am very, very sorry.
ROBBIE:
Just do as we've asked of you.
Write it all down,
just the truth, no rhymes
no embellishments, no adjectives
and then leave us be.
I will, I promise.
[DOOR CLOSING]
BRIONY: I'm sorry.
Could we stop for a moment?
MAN: Of course.
Is something the matter?
I just need
a couple of minutes by myself.
[TAPE REWINDING]
...minutes by myself.
MAN:
Briony Tallis, your new novel
your twenty-first,
is called Atonement. It's...
Briony?
I'm sorry.
Could we stop for a moment?
Briony Tallis, I'd like to
talk now about your new novel, Atonement
which comes out in a few days
to coincide with your birthday.
It's your twenty-first novel
It's my last novel.
Oh, really? Are you retiring?
I'm dying.
My doctor tells me
I have something called "vascular dementia"
which is essentially
a continuous series of tiny strokes.
Your brain closes down.
Gradually you lose words. You lose your memory
which for a writer
is pretty much the point.
So that's why I could
finally write the book, I think. I had to.
And why, of course, it's my last novel.
Strangely enough
it would be just as accurate
to call it my first novel.
I wrote several drafts as far back as
my time at St. Thomas' Hospital during the war.
I just couldn't ever
find the way to do it.
Because the novel
is autobiographical... Is that right?
Yes, entirely. I haven't
changed any names, including my own.
And was that the problem?
No.
I had, for a very long time,
decided to tell the absolute truth
no rhymes, no embellishments.
And I think...
You've read the book.
You'll understand why.
I got first-hand accounts of
all the events I didn't personally witness
the conditions in prison,
the evacuation to Dunkirk, everything.
But the effect of
all this honesty was rather pitiless.
You see, I couldn't any longer
imagine what purpose would be served by it.
By what? Sorry. Served by honesty?
By honesty.
Or reality.
Because, in fact
I was too much of a coward to
go and see my sister in June, 1940.
I never made
that journey to Balham.
ROBBIE: Do you have
any idea what it's like in jail?
BRIONY: So the scene in which
I confess to them is imagined.
CECILIA:
He sleeps so deeply.
BRIONY:
Invented.
ROBBIE: How old do you have to be
to know the difference between right and wrong?
BRIONY: And, in fact,
could never have happened.
Because
Robbie Turner
died of septicemia at Bray-Dunes
on June the first, 1940
the last day of the evacuation.
Cheerio, pal.
And I was never able to
put things right with my sister, Cecilia
because she was killed
on the 15th of October, 1940
by the bomb that destroyed
the gas and water mains above Balham tube station.
[BOMBS EXPLODING]
So...
my sister and Robbie
were never able to have the time together
they both so longed for, and deserved
and which, ever since, I've...
ever since
I've always felt I prevented.
But what sense of hope
or satisfaction, could a reader
derive from an ending like that?
So, in the book, I wanted to give
Robbie and Cecilia what they lost out on in life.
I'd like to think
this isn't weakness or evasion
but a final act of kindness.
I gave them their happiness.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Resync by Orangeman
Downloaded from Opensubtitles.org