Guess what.
What?
I can't move.
Yeah, well, you don't have to.NYou're in a car.
Am I driving?
Like a pro.
Come on, wake up, you fuck.NCome on.
Did you try to help him get free?
Briefly.
Briefly?
When it came down to it, my lifeNwas more important to me than his.
Selfish, huh?
We found these...
...in your Spider.
Actually, I don't drive a SpiderNanymore.
Now I have a C8 Laviolette.
It's lighter, faster...
...swims better.
Right.
These three contain tracesNof ketamine...
...the same as we found in your bloodNand his.
This one had pure D-Tubocurarine,NDTC...
...which we only found in him.
Must've been somethingNhe took at the party.
No. DTC is not a party drug.
Along with the other stuff in his blood,Nit paralyzed his lungs.
Kevin Franks did not drown.
He had already stopped breathingNby the time you drove off the road.
He was breathingNwhen we went off the road.
How do you know?
He was making me come.
What? You were having sexNat 100 miles an hour?
Hundred and ten.NI must've hit a pothole.
Your friend, Dickie Pep...
...says he sold you 15 millilitersNof DTC last Thursday.
I don't know any Dickie Pep,Nbut he's lying.
Or you are.
Why would he lie?
You got him on some other chargeNand he's trying to deal his way out.
If he even exists.
You don't seem too upset by what'sNhappened.
Of course I am, I'm traumatized.
Who knows if I'll ever come again?
I want that cunt in jail.
We haven't got a case, Roy.
Well, just fucking make one. Please.
They'll order a psychiatric for bail.
I'll make sure we get somebodyNgood and tough.
Dr. Glass. I'm Henry Rose,NMiss Tramell's solicitor.
This is Catherine Tramell.
I shall be present duringNthe evaluation.
Well, that's fine by me.
I'll be asking fairly personal questions.NIf she doesn't mind your presence....
My client understands and agreesNI should be present for--
Maybe Dr. Glass is rightNand we should be alone for this.
I strongly advise youNnot to contemplate having--
So is this whereNwe're going to do it?
Mr. Rose told you the purposeNof this evaluation.
I'm applying for bail in a murder case.
The Crown wants to knowNif I'm a danger to myself or others.
You're the Crown's shrink,Nso you'll say I'm dangerous.
My shrink will say I'm not,Nand the judge will flip a coin.
Anything you tell me can be quotedNverbatim in testimony...
...and can affect your case.
You can quote me all you want.
Thank you.
Well, I see that you're a writer.
What do you write about?
Murder, sex, violence.
Do you ever write about yourself?
Not into autobiography.
Really? Why not?
Maybe I like to just sit back and getNother people to reveal themselves.
For instance,Nyou look a little divorced.
What makes you think I'm divorced?
The ring line hasn't faded.
You're very observant.
Yeah, but am I wrong?
Would it bother youNif you were wrong?
Would it bother you if I was right?
Tell me something you're afraid of.
Boredom.
Is that why you like to take risks?
I do like to take risks.
Like taking drugs and having sexNin a speeding car?
Like talking to meNwithout having your lawyer present?
Actually, that was your idea.
Like being on trial for murder? That'sNrisky. You could end up in prison.
Not if I'm innocent.
Innocent people end up in prisonNall the time.
Not rich, innocent people who areNrepresented by Henry Rose.
In that case, it isn't really excitingNunless you're guilty.
Oh, I bet you like to take risks,Ndon't you, Dr. Glass?
But I'm not the one who's on trialNfor murder.
Not yet.
Sorry, you're not allowedNto smoke in here.
You know what I like about you?
You enjoy being in control.
Like me.
Sorry, sir. Can't let you through here.
Well, I would say extremely intelligent.NGifted, accomplished.
Yet inside, I believe...
...she vacillates betweenNa feeling of godlike omnipotence...
...and a senseNthat she simply doesn't exist...
...which, of course, is intolerable.
Do you consider Miss Tramell to beNmentally impaired?
Not by legal definition, no. Not at all.
If released, is she likelyNto commit a violent crime?
I believe her behavior is drivenNby what we call a risk addiction.
A compulsive need to prove to herselfNthat she can take risks...
...and survive dangers others can't.
Especially the subsequent encountersNwith the police or the powers that be.
Why would a person do that?
The greater the risk, the greater theNproof of her omnipotence.
Her existence, really.
When you say she hasNa risk addiction...
...is this condition likely to getNworse?
All addiction is progressive.
The addict always needs to takeNgreater risks.
If other people are hurt or killed...
...as a result of her behavior,Nthat's not likely to stop her?
I think the only thingNthat'd stop her....
I suspect the only limit for herNwould be her own death.
Then she is a danger to herself.
Yes, I believe she is.
Nice work, Michael. Well done.
Dr. Glass, did Catherine TramellNkill Kevin Franks?
No, I can't make any comment, sorry.
Can you please tell us about the bail?
Dr. Michael Glass. What a big thingNyou are all of a sudden.
What are you doing here, Adam?NDon't say you're writing about Tramell.
A sexy, omnipotent killerNwith a Random House contract.
Why would I write that?
You don't know she's a killer.
No, but I hope she is, though.NI mean, I pray to God she is.
By the way, I hear you wereNbrilliant in there.
You're so lucid sometimes,Nit's just disgusting.
You thought about daytime television?
Denise always says you were bornNfor the small screen.
And how is my wife these days?NHaving fun?
Ex-wife, Michael. Ex-wife.
While we're chatting about killers...
...is there any chance of talking aboutNGeorge Cheslav?
Who told you about Cheslav?
Denise?
That's got to be any shrink's worstNnightmare.
A patient in your careNsuddenly runs amok...
...beats his girlfriend to deathNwith a brick.
That was seven years ago,Nwhy talk about it now?
Not quite seven, actually.NSeven in July.
But you talked to him twice a week.NHe never indicated he'd harm the girl?
I don't talk about my patients.
Cheslav's dead. Can't you talkNabout them when they're dead?
No, not even when they're dead.
Michael, what are you doing here?
What did you tell Adam TowersNabout George Cheslav?
Nothing.
Can you give us a minute?
He already knew.
Really? Because he said you told him.
No, all I said was--
If he writes about that, if he puts itNon his magazine cover--
He won't. You're just being paranoid.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Right. I didn't. I was treating a patientNthat killed his pregnant girlfriend.
End of story.NYou make sure he gets that.
Don't worry.
I'm up for the Douglas ChairNat the university.
You know what that means to me.NDo you think this is going to help?
I can't tell Adam what to write.
Why not?
Don't be stupid.
I think you're entitled to since you'veNbeen fucking him for over a year.
Do you think I didn't knowNwhen it started?
It's a pity you never asked yourselfNwhy it started.
How was the court caseNwith the mystery writer?
I hear she looks fabulous.
Also very intelligent.NPathological liar. Narcissistic.
Seductive, manipulative.
Do you think she killed the footballer?
I have no idea.
Everything she does is so perfectlyNcomposed.
It's designed to confuseNor confound you.
You never know what's truthNand what isn't. She's brilliant, really.
The masked psychotic. Your favorite.
I'm already working it into a paper:N"Risk Addiction and Omnipotence."
You're writing another already?
I'm writing two,Nbut this is the more interesting.
I'll catch you up.
Hello?
Glass? It's Roy Washburn.NAre you near a television set?
If you'll be quiet, I'll make aNstatement.
What happened?
The judge let her go.
Let her go? Why?
The guy who saidNhe sold her the DTC...
...the judge found out he'd perjuredNhimself in another case...
...and disqualified him as a witness.NBut I'll make you a bet.
What's that?
She'll do it again.
And soon.
Only this timeNI will fucking nail the bitch.
So we've been considering those whoNwish to control others...
...through their insecurity and theirNnarcissism.
To study NietzscheNpsychobiographically may seem naive.
Wasn't it Nietzsche's work itself,Nwhich...
...through deconstructive andNpost-structuralist readings...
...induced the death ofNpsychobiography?
Paul Portman said he might goNto Tavistock. I'm thinking I might go.
Just be patient.NStay where you are for about a year.
-But there's nothing holding me.N-Trust me.
You know Dr. Gerst?
Michael Glass.
It's a pleasure.
I saw your review of my book.
You didn't understand what I wasNsaying about the analytic field.
Towards the end you made one or twoNinteresting remarks.
Maybe one of these daysNwe can discuss it.
I'd be honored. Thank you very much.
"One or two interesting remarks"?
That was a compliment, Michelle.NDr. Gerst was very impressed.
And it appears that our MichaelNhas just been knighted.
Cheers.
Congratulations.
Excuse me. Dr. Glass?
I'm Peter Ristedes.NAdam Towers' assistant.
Urbane magazine.
Mind if I join you?
Adam asked me to see if you'd give usNa quote for the article he's writing.
I believe he mentioned it to you.
He didn't seem to thinkNyou'd want to talk to him.
I'll take that as a "no comment," then?
Dr. Glass?
Miss Tramell.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to talk to you.
About the evaluation.
Some of the things you said,NI've been thinking about them a lot.
I'm sorry you had to hear all that.
Got a minute?
Come through.
What you said about meNbeing addicted to risk...
...about having to do more and moreNdangerous things....
Well, after you said it...
...I realized I was...
...scared.
What exactly scared you?
For weeks before the accidentNI was having the same...
...fantasy over and over again.
I even wrote about it.
The woman's driving in the car,Nthe man's making her come.
She drives off the road,Nthe man's killed.
I feel like maybe I made it all happen.
That's why I'm here.
Are you saying you'd like toNgo into treatment?
Yeah.
Well, I think that's a very good idea.
I wouldn't be able to treat you, but l'dNbe happy to refer you to a colleague.
Why can't you treat me?
It's not advisable for a doctor who'sNdone a forensic evaluation...
...to then become that person'sNtherapist.
Why not?
Therapy requires a great deal of trust,Nwhich is difficult for most people.
It's best to start with a clean slate.
You mean you don't trust me.
What I said about you at the hearingNmust have seemed very negative.
I'm sure you've got feelings about that.
I'd be happy referring youNto another doctor.
This is Dr. Milena Gardosh.NShe has a clinic here in London.
You want to know the truth?
The reason I agreed to the evaluationNwas because I thought it would be fun.
I never....
I never talked to anyone who....
My patient's here.
What do I owe you?
You don't owe me anything.
But if you'd like to call Dr. Gardosh,NI'm sure she can help you.
I don't shop around.
Like you said,Ntrust is very hard to come by.
I was hoping I might find it with you.
Listen, why don't weNschedule another meeting.
And then we can talk about thisNwhen we're not so rushed.
You look different today. More relaxed.
The more nervous I am,Nthe more relaxed people think I am.
I wanted to talk about something youNbrought up last Wednesday.
You said before the accident...
...you had fantasies of sexualNexcitement and driving off the road.
Do you often have fantasies like that?
I have fantasies all the time.
Fantasies involving violence, death?
People die in my novels.
I have to think of new and interestingNways to kill them.
What happens whenNyou don't take risks?
I'm sorry, there's no smoking in here.NIt's a rule.
I don't like rules.
I have some of them,Nand that's one of them.
After the hearing...
...I was interviewed by a reporterNfrom Urbane magazine.
Adam Towers. He said he knew you.
Slightly. Why?
He told me about the Cheslav case.
I was impressed by what you did.
You knew Cheslav was dangerous.
Still you protected him.
You honored his confidentiality...
...even at risk to yourself.
Do you think you made the rightNdecision?
Or do you think you fucked up?
Given what I knew at the time,NI made the right decision.
So you still believe in confidentiality.
Within legal limits.NWhat exactly are you concerned with?
If I told youNthat I killed Kevin Franks...
...would you report me to the police?
No.
Anything that happened in the past,NI wouldn't discuss outside this room.
But if you told me you were going toNmurder someone specifically...
...and I thought you were serious...
...then, yes, I'd go to the police.
I might be manipulating youNto create risk for myself.
Do you want to talk aboutNwhat happened to Kevin?
No, not really.
I was just checking your policy.
So have you decided?
About taking me on as a patient.
Shooter had an ex-wife,Na drinking problem...
...a drug problem, a complicated sexNproblem he was barely aware of.
And a tremendous amount ofNfree-floating rage.
In short, he was a copNand a very good one.
On March 3rd....
The woman knelt nakedNat the foot of the bed.
Her back to him, her head on a pillow.
Shooter raked his fingers through herNblond hair and twisted it tight.
She groaned, her breath catching...
...as he suddenly yanked her hair likeNa rider pulling on a horse's mane.
The veins on his arms bulged asNhe roughly drew her onto him.
Do you rememberNthat cop Washburn?
T o him, the fact that I wasn't upsetNabout Kevin Franks...
...was proof that I must've killed him.
Then, when I wouldn't break down...
...he hit on me.
Hit on you?
Yeah.
He said that if I fucked him thingsNwould go easier.
Homicide copsNare usually smarter than that.
I knew one once, in San Francisco.
Nick Curran.
They called him Shooter.
We used to get in his carNand ride around...
...Listening to 911 calls on hisNscanner...
...then speed over.
Have you ever been to a murder sceneNright after it happened?
The body's still warm.
The watch is still ticking.
You can smell the blood.
We'd hang aroundNfor a while and then...
...go have sex in Nick's car.
Nick used to say:
"Death is always there.NIt's the only thing that's real."
Except maybe sex sometimes.
But only sometimes?
Well...
...I fucked this guy last night.
I fucked him for hours.
You know,Nwe did everything to each other.
The full screaming MastersNand Johnson's greatest hits.
But you know, a week from now,NI probably won't even remember him.
But, if I was with him when he died....
Now...
...I probably would never forget that.
Would l?
Were you ever with anyoneNwhen they died?
No.
Christ.
We still have 20 minutes left.
I feel like a cigarette.
See you tomorrow.
She just walked out?
How Lacanian.
For her, time's a weapon.
Everything's a weapon.NEverybody's an enemy.
Do you think she made it up aboutNthe policeman? Washburn?
I don't know. It's so hard to believeNanything she says.
She's trying to seduce you.
They always try to seduce you.
Yes, but this one's different, isn't it?
I don't know. More fun maybe.
Be careful, Michael.
By the way, I got a call from thatNreporter, Adam Towers.
What did he want?
I made everything sound boring.NI assured him he didn't have a story.
What if he calls others?NWhat if he calls Gerst?
Gerst won't talk to a popular magazineNreporter. Are you kidding?
Anyway, it was a successful paper.
Published, on this occasion,Nunder sole authorship.
Well, thank God for that.
Speaking of God, is Gerst coming?
We can only hope and pray.
That he comes or he doesn't?
I'm going for a smoke. Don't talk aboutNanything interesting till I get back.
How long have you lived here?
About six years, something like that.NSeven.
Hi, Dominic.
Hi, Milena.
Thank you.
The beauty aboutNantisocial behavior...
...is that it takes you away from otherNpeople, however briefly.
You're not an analyst.
I'm a writer.
Really? What do you write about?
Oh, the lurid, the sexual, the violent.
The basic instincts.
They're the most powerful,Naren't they?
Milena.
Oh, Michael.
I'm sorry, I didn't ask your name.
Catherine Tramell. Milena Gardosh.
Oh, you're Dr. Gardosh.
I've heard so many wonderful thingsNabout you.
Catherine.
There you are.
Milena, Dr. Glass.NI see you've met Catherine.
She's doing research for a novel aboutNan eminent psychoanalyst.
I thought she might enjoy an occasionNlike this.
Well, may I take your coats?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Would you put that in my pocket?
Certainly.
Catherine, come this way.
What's going on? What was GerstNthinking of, bringing her here?
I'm sure he's no idea who she is.
Where did he meet her?
She would have met him, believe me.
I can't stay here while I've gotNa patient here. I have to go.
I understand.
If you follow inter-subjectivity to itsNnatural end...
...aren't you asking who's the patientNand who's the doctor?
Those were my very words.
Very good.
Note that one for future reference.
Are you leaving because of me?
You must have known I'd be here.
Is that a problem?
I know some people who play tennisNwith their shrinks.
I'm sure you do.
Have sex with them. Sell them drugs.NWork on their screenplays.
But I don't do that.
I was upset about our session today.
I felt I owed you an apology.
That's why I came.
We can go into that tomorrow.
I've got a better idea.
How about I ditch everybodyNand we go somewhere for a drink.
I told you, I don't socialize with myNpatients.
Another one of your rules?
Don't you get kind of tired of them?
You know, that's the nightmareNof shrinkdom, doctor.
Too many answers,Ntoo many questions...
...nobody gets laid.
Okay, forget getting laid.
We'll just talk.
We'll talk tomorrow.
Michael. There you are.
Oh, my God. Did you see that womanNthat Gerst brought with him?
No.
Actually, I was just looking for you.
What, in there?
I was looking for your coat.NI thought we could go for a drink.
If that's all right?
Yeah. Great.
What's wrong?
Turn around.
What?
Oh, God!
Michael, it's Denise!NPlease pick up the phone! Please!
Michael, please pick up the phone!
Denise?
Hey, hey, hey. What's happened?
Thanks, guv.
Come in, Michael.
Hey, you okay?
Hey, what's going on?
It's okay, I'm here now. Okay?
Who lives here?
It's Adam's place.
Jesus.
What happened?
I don't know. The door was unlockedNand I just came in.
I just saw him lying there.
Have you called the police?
No. I was afraid.
Hello, Michael.
What are you doing here?
It's my wife. Well, my ex-wife.
She found him like that,Nthen she called me.
I see.
And how did she happen toNfind him like that?
They'd been seeing each other and....
Oh, really?
Since when?
It's why I moved out.
So I assume you weren'tNthe best of friends?
No.
Yet I saw you talking to himNafter the Tramell hearing.
It was just journalist stuff.
He was asking me questions aboutNTramell.
Do you think she killed him?
Who?
Denise? No.
No, not a chance.
I've known her for a long time.NShe could never do anything like that.
Listen, Roy, I've told my story twiceNover. Is it all right if I go home?
All right.
Oh, by the way...
...this yours?
No, I just found it on the floor.
How did it end up in the rubbish?
I stepped on it. It was leaking.NI just threw it away.
Can I go?
Yes, by all means.
I assume you know Adam TowersNwas killed.
Why would I know?
Because of Denise.
Denise?
Your wife. Your ex-wife.
I know who she is.NHow do you know her?
Adam introduced us a couple of times.
It was all very open. I knew about her,Nshe knew about me.
Knew what about you?
That I was seeing him too.
The Masters and Johnson guy.NThat was him.
So-- You were sleepingNwith Adam Towers?
Occasionally.
So, of course,NWashburn thinks I killed him.
Why would he think that?
I kill because I'm addicted to risk.NOr to prove that I exist.
I'm not sure which one it is.
I never said you killed anybody.
But you think I did.
You think I killed Kevin, and nowNyou're wondering if I killed Adam.
Why don't you just ask me?NOr is that too direct for you?
Did you kill him?
If I said I didn't,Nwould you believe me?
Depends.
On what?NThe quality of my performance?
You know what?NI'm glad Adam Towers is dead.
And you should be glad too.
If you're too uptight,NI'll be glad for you.
Whoever killed him did you a favor.
Favor?
If he'd written that article on Cheslav,Nit would've ruined your career.
You haven't told me if you killed him.NCan you put that out?
Put it out now or you can leave,Nokay?!
Is that better?
When you think about fucking me...
...and I know you do...
...how do you picture it, doctor?
Oh, I know you can't answer me,Nso just think it.
Do you want it straight up?
You on top?
Me on top?
Do you want it from behind...
...on your knees,Nmy face in the pillow?
Do you want to beat me up...
...just a little?
Not too hard.
Oh, a little harder than that.
Do you want to come in my mouth?
What if I told you that I masturbateNthinking about you?
That I make myself come...
...thinking about youNmaking yourself come.
I guess we're out of time for today.
I'm terminating therapy.
Send me the bill.
Miss Tramell, it's Dr. Glass here.
Listen, I'm concerned about how ourNsession ended today.
I'd like to talk throughNany misunderstandings...
...there might be between us.
As soon as you get this message,Nplease give me a--
Just call me when you can.
Evening, Dr. Glass.
Could I have a word?
Sure. Upstairs.
Is that German?
Can I get you anything?
No.
So here's a surprise.
Adam Towers had a girlfriendNbesides Denise.
Guess who.
Catherine Tramell.
You don't look surprised.
She's a private patient of mine.
I see. Since when?
Not long.
So your ex and your private patientNwere both screwing Adam Towers.
That's quite a coincidence.NDid they know each other?
I don't know. I don't think so.NDid you--?
Tramell's prints were all over Towers'Napartment, along with others.
But what's interesting is the last callNhe made was to her mobile phone...
...90 minutes before he died.
Her story is she was out walking allNthat time.
Two hours strolling around ClerkenwellNand nobody saw her, so....
Come on, Michael. Talk to me.
I can't tell you anything. Even if lNknew something, which I don't.
Franks was first. Towers second.NThere's bound to be a third.
This goes beyond confidentiality.
You've got a legal obligation to protectNa potential victim.
You can't lock somebody up becauseNyou think they might do something.
Why don't you tell me what you knowNabout this article...
...Towers was writing about youNand our old friend George Cheslav.
Who told youNhe was writing an article?
His editor.
He'd been very busy.NHe had a lot of information on you.
What, and you think I killed him...
...to stop him writingNsome stupid article?
No. But just for the record, why don'tNyou tell me how you spent last night.
Between, say,N7 p.m. and 2 in the morning.
You know, broad strokes.
I had patients until 8 p.m.
Then went to a partyNin Collingham Gardens.
I left there about 11 with a woman.
We came here and I was on my kneesNfucking her when Denise called.
On your knees, eh?
Sounds like your eveningNwas better than mine.
Could I get her name?NSo there are no loose ends.
Look, Michael, Adam TowersNwas fucking your ex-wife...
...and about to do the sameNto your career. I've got to ask.
Michelle Broadwin.
She's a psycho-pharmacologist atNVictoria Psychiatric Hospital.
Thank you.
I'll be in touch.
What does that mean?
I smell blood.
Yeah, not all of them, of course, but,Nyou know, some of them.
They're all so sanctimonious...
...so judgmental.
All my friends, they drink too much.NThey snort too much coke.
Miss Tramell,Nit's Dr. Glass here again.
I'm a little concernedNI haven't heard from you.
I was wondering whether you're okay.
Look, let me give youNmy home number. It's 0207....
Sorry, it really got to me and I don'tNknow why it seems to be doing that.
Why it's getting worse.NI mean, I was really excited.
You have no new messages.
The thing about Gerst is this:
The selection committeeNis just a formality.
This is the real interview.
Relax.
Be direct, candid.
But not too candid.
Very good time. They always get lostNon the way. Come in.
Meet my new Mughal painting.
Not another one.
An lndian goddess at peace. It has aNtranquility to it, don't you think?
I wonder what the males are doing,Nloitering so close to her?
It's obvious. They're worshiping her.
As they should.
Perhaps that's why she has eight armsNto fend them off.
Why don't you girls go outsideNwhile Dr. Glass and I have our chat.
Come. Come.
Come with me. You'll enjoy it.
So, Dr. Glass, I have a question:
Do you think I'm insane?
Pardon?
Nuts? Bonkers? Off my trolley?
No, not at all.
But I might be if I recommended youNfor the Douglas Chair.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
George Cheslav.
A major drug dealer, under your care,Nbrutally murders his girlfriend.
An inquiry is held...
...where Detective Roy Washburn...
...testifies that you actedNprofessionally at all times.
You're blameless.
That's right, I was.
However, after the trial...
...you experienced what we might termNan emotional meltdown:
Depression...
...occupational underachievement...
...marital problems...
...and questionable professionalNconduct...
...much discussed at dinner partiesNaround our great city.
I'm sorry?
Now you want my supportNfor the Douglas Chair.
No more Cheslavs, Michael.
No.
No more Cheslavs.
Catherine!
Sorry. All right.NSorry, I'm just looking for someone.
Not love. It's....
I don't know.
You have to terminate this therapy,Nright away.
Well, it's already done.NShe terminated it herself.
Good.
If she calls again, give her my number.
I'm a woman.
She'll relate to me differently.
What are you doing here?
Where she goes, I go.
Since when?
Since she started comingNto your office five days a week.
So, Adam Towers.NSeems his research has gone missing.
All his notebooks, audiotapes,Neven his hard drive.
Everything on George CheslavNand Michael Glass.
-You think Catherine has it?N-I know she does.
She ever tell you about themNwhen she's chatting on the couch?
You know I can't discuss that.
Come on. I've been very good to youNthese past few years.
I'm practically a psychopathNdelivery service.
I can't break privilege.
Pity. I have somethingNyou might like to know about.
Someone says you'd been lyingNat the Cheslav inquest.
Who?
You want me to break privilege?
Since you're a friend,Nit was your ex-wife.
Denise?
You want to sort her out.
Who knows, she might tell youNwhere Towers' notes went.
Someone's here.NDo you want us to say?
I'll be all right. Don't worry.
We'll see you later.
How you doing?
Okay.
Do you want a drink?
No, I have to go.
I'm meeting someoneNat the Atlantic Bar.
Denise, did you tell Towers thatNI lied at the Cheslav inquiry?
Of course, there's always an agenda.
No. I said you knew he was goingNto kill his girlfriend.
I didn't. That's a lie.
Yes, you did.
You kept saying how you knewNand should have gone to the police.
I didn't know. I sensed. And I told youNthat as my wife in confidence.
I didn't think you'd go and repeat itNin bed to some moron reporter.
Do you want to ruin my life, is that it?NYou want to ruin my practice?
Your life? Your practice?
Catherine was right,Neverything's always about you.
What about me? Adam's deadNand I'm a murder suspect.
Washburn keeps going on about meNnot cooperating, like I'm a liar.
I don't know where Adam's notes are.
I'm scared to go home. I'm scaredNto go out. I'm going out of my mind.
Be careful about Catherine.
Don't tell me what to do!
Just calm down.
Don't tell me to fucking calm down!
Hey, come on.
That's my wife, okay?NThis is a private conversation.
Get out of my way! Out of my way!
Denise. Oh, Denise!
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Come on, Denise. Look at me.
Call an ambulance!
Do it now!
Come on. Let's go.
Stay with me. Come on. Stay with me.
Come on. Stay with me.
You have a problem, Michael.
Witnesses say they saw you arguing.NShe was crying.
You grabbed her.NShe almost fell down.
Five minutes later,Nsomebody slits her throat.
Also, there are people here who thinkNyou killed Towers.
Towers? Didn't you speak to Michelle?
Yes. But now I'm hearing about thisNcigarette lighter with your prints on it.
I just picked that up.
And your ex is in a coma just as she'sNto say something inconvenient for you.
I was trying to save her life.
Look, I spoke to Towers' assistantNat Urbane magazine.
He expected Denise to say that youNperjured yourself at Cheslav's inquiry.
She wasn't going to say that.
What was she going to say?
Sorry, guv.
You wait there.
So....
Your ex and Catherine TramellNwere girl buddies. Did you know that?
What do you mean "girl buddies"?
According to Catherine,Nthey met through Towers and hit it off.
Denise told Catherine that Towers hadNbeen pressuring her...
...into saying that you'd perjuredNyourself.
But Denise wasn't having it.NShe was going to say you were clean.
You didn't know Cheslav was going toNkill his girlfriend, did you?
In fact, it cameNas a complete surprise, didn't it?
-Of course she's lying.N-How do you know?
Everything that comes out of her is aNlie. Even the truth's a lie with her.
It's her way of getting you to thinkNwhat she wants you to think.
That's her art. The art of mind-fucking.
She might be a talented writer.
When it comes to mind-fucking,Nshe's the all-time genius.
She really got to you, didn't she?
What do you mean?NWhat did she tell you about me?
Well, what is there to tell?
Don't play games with me.NShe can pull it off, you can't.
Where are you going?
Someplace else. UnlessNyou have evidence to charge me.
Do you?
I didn't think so.
He let you go, finally.
I was worried.
You lied to Washburn for me. Why?
I knew you hadn't hurt Denise.
How could you know that?
Because I know you.
And I know the cops were keeping youNjust to play some kind of game.
What, like getting meNto talk about you?
Yeah, but you wouldn't do that,Nbecause you're into confidentiality.
Why were you meeting with Denise?
Research for my novel.
Research.
About what?
About you.
And Cheslav, the masked psychotic.
The analyst in my book is obsessedNwith that sort of thing.
Washburn thinksNthat you slit Denise's throat.
Me? You're the one that hated her.
Maybe I'm acting outNyour unconscious impulses.
Stop it!
Do you think it's possible thatNyou want me to be the killer?
You know, how some guysNare into blonds...
...and some guys are into killers.
Isn't that what you're into?
Isn't that what turns you on?
Turns me on?
Isn't that why you're over here?
Okay.
I trust you.
You trust me.
Is there somewhere we can talk?
Over there.
Can I guess where you got it?
Let's find out what it is first.
It would be highly improper of me toNaccept any evidence in this fashion.
Fine.
It'll take me a few daysNto get it analyzed.
You'd have made a good cop, Michael.
You like the smell of blood.
Dr. Glass.
Hold on.
I was just thinking about you.
I might have moreNpsychiatric evaluations for you.
That's nice, but I'm busyNat the moment.
Oh, that's a pity.NYou were so good with Catherine.
She tells me you're very perceptive.
She's very perceptive herself.
I hope Detective Washburn isn't givingNyou cause for...
...concern?
What do you mean?
Well, given his past record.
What past record?
I want to talk to you.
Oh, so now you want to talk.
Look, this "Dirtiest Cop in London,"Nit doesn't mention him by name.
But this "Detective X,"Nis that Roy Washburn?
Is it Washburn?
Excuse me?
Yeah, it's him.
Are you sure?
Adam may have been a sloppy writer,Nbut he had excellent sources.
What about perjury, intimidation,Nfalsifying evidence. Is that true?
A policeman fabricating evidence.
But you have proof?
How about Kevin FranksNand the Case of the Killer Orgasm?
When I did Catherine Tramell'sNassessment, I read that report.
Those syringes found in the carNcontained DTC.
Yeah, well, who foundNthe syringes in the car?
But why would Washburn do that?
Adam thought he did it to set upNCatherine Tramell.
Why didn't he write about it?
That's the whole point.
He was going to.
Then he got killed.
I owe you an apology.NAbout Roy Washburn. I--
I don't like apologies.
I also don't like people stealing thingsNfrom my apartment.
The insulin? In case you haven't had itNanalyzed yet.
Insulin?
My friend's diabetic.
Let yourself out, doctor.
Hello, Michael.
What do you want?
I got the lab analysis back.
D-Tubocurarine. Funny that.
You're sure it's not insulin?
Insulin?
No.
Can I see the report?
You've got some trust issues there.NYou might want to work on that.
This isn't an officialNForensic Services report.
No. Because an unpreserved orNcontaminated chain of evidence...
...will be deemed inadmissibleNin a future trial, lnspector Clouseau.
So do you want to tell meNwhere you found it?
She's not worth it.
People are dyingNand I will have her for it.
If you stand in my way,NI'll have you as well.
I can fucking promise you that.
I've got something to show you.NGet in the car.
Get in!
Medical examiner's on his way.
Hello, guv.
Were you working that night?
No, I don't know.
Did you see or hearNanything suspicious yesterday?
Not yesterday. No.
-Nothing?N-No.
How long have you worked here?
Four months.
Four months?
Where were you before that?
Ted.
Hi, guv.
--remember I talked to Vice earlier andNthey said--
Fergie, give me a minute.
Let's go.
Who is he?
Richard Pepovic.NKnown to his friends as Dickie Pep.
You know him?
No.
Look at this.
Now, we'll have to wait for the labNresults, of course...
...but what's the betting he's oozingNTubocurarine?
Now do you want to tell meNwho gave you the sample?
You don't know she did it.
No.
But then again, maybe I killed him.
Isn't that what she's gonna tell you?
He had something on me,Nso I killed him.
Then I jerked him offNeven though he was dead...
...to make it look likeNthere was come everywhere...
...to make it look like it was her.
Look, Towers was right about me,NI put them away whatever it takes.
So, fine, don't trust me.
You know Catherine better than me.
If you have five secondsNwhen you're not dizzy...
...with the smell of her pussy,Nask yourself: Do you trust her?
Do you?
She's George Cheslav, times three.NWe both know it.
The question is:NHow do we put her away?
If you tell the courts that she's made aNdirect threat against someone....
But she hasn't.
If you say she did, and that got her putNon a psych ward...
...stopped her from killing again,Nwouldn't that be worth it?
Some kind of redemptionNfor Cheslav at last?
Look, I'm prejudiced.
Don't take my word for it.
Talk to this guy.
Listen to him.
Lieutenant Walker. It's Michael.
Look, thanks for talking to me.
It's just that I did an evaluationNof Miss Tramell....
Darkness had fallen and even beforeNthe buzzer sounded...
...Kelly knew it would be the doctor.
He'd come to accuse herNof more crimes.
They'd fight about thatNand then have sex...
...and everything would beNall right again.
Except it wouldn't be...
...if he didn't trust her.
Hi, handsome.
My new novel.
I'm anxious to hearNwhat you think about it.
I've been speakingNto Lieutenant Phil Walker...
...the San FranciscoNPolice Department.
Paranoid Phil.NNow there's a blast from the past.
He said you murdered a Johnny BozNand two detectives in San Francisco.
I was never even charged.
Grand jury said that Nick Curran'sNgirlfriend did it.
I'm going to take a Jacuzzi.NCare to join me?
All right, all right.NI killed Johnny Boz.
Why?
I didn't like him.
For the money.
To see if I could get away with it.
To show that deathNreally isn't very important.
Because I was bored.
And you know how I hate being bored.
What about Denise, huh?
Adam Towers?
Adam was insufferable.
And you are something special.
Adam was trying to ruin you justNout of spite, and I couldn't bear it.
This is wonderful.
Denise.
Denise.... Denise was good in bed.
Denise would have spoiledNeverything I'd accomplished...
...by killing Adam Towers.
God, you can't tell the truthNabout anything, can you?
You don't believe meNwhen I say I did it.
You don't believe meNwhen I say I didn't do it.
What is the pointNof talking to you, anyway?
Oh, come on.
Why don't you take your clothes offNand get in, huh?
This is worse than Cheslav, isn't it?
This time you knewNright from the start what I was.
And you let it happen again,Ndidn't you?
It's almost like youNkilled them yourself.
Who do you thinkNI'm going to kill next?
Come on.
You can figure it out.
Kelly met the analyst during her littleNstay at Holloway Prison.
His eyes wereNa beautiful shade of blue.
Did Kelly trust the doctor?
Did she mean itNwhen she told him she wanted help?
Even she wasn't sure.
If things went well,Nthen she meant it.
If not, she didn't.
That way, she'd be protected.
She remembered the first timeNshe met Irena...
...at the party in Bloomsbury.
She felt a deep affinityNfor the older woman.
As if the two of them leaning againstNthe wall, silently smoking....
The next time they saw each other...
...only broughtNthe two women even closer.
Even as Dr. Green watched themNthrough the window...
...Iooking for any sign of conspiracy.
Kelly found herself opening up,Ntrusting the older woman...
...revealing things about herself....
Yes, Kelly thought. She liked Irena.
She was trustworthy, intelligent,Nbeautiful, dignified.
It was a pityNKelly was going to have to kill her.
She dressed carefully.
She liked to be well-dressedNwhen she killed.
Killing Irena and telling Dr. GreenNshe was planning to do it...
... that was the riskiest thingNshe could do.
Come on, Milena.
Come on, Milena, answer the phone
It's Michael Glass here. Can you callNme as soon as you get this message?
As much as Kelly hated her shrink...
...she also loved him.
She took a last glance at herselfNin the mirror.
Irena deserved a good death.NAnd Kelly would give it to her.
Hello, this is Roy Washburn,Nplease leave a message.
Roy. It's Michael Glass.NCome as soon as you can.
23 Highgate Street. Hampstead.
I think Catherine is going to killNMilena Gardosh.
It was almost midnight by the timeNDr. Green got to Hampstead.
What is it?
Thank God.NListen, we don't have much time.
You're in danger.NShe's going to try and kill you.
What? Who's trying to kill me?
Catherine.
I thought I could help herNbut I was wrong.
I'll try and get her sectioned.NIt's the only thing that'll stop her.
I've already spoken to Catherine.
She's very upset. You terrified her.
I terrified her? She's a murderer.NShe's already admitted it.
For chrissake,Nyou had sex with your patient.
You assaulted her.NShe nearly drowned.
You've broken the law, not to mentionNthe ethical canon of our profession.
It wasn't like that.
Michael, listen to me, please.
You're not well.
You're the one who needs help.
I've spoken to Gerst...
...and he thinks that if you volunteerNfor a 28-day observation...
...you might be able to avoidNcriminal charges.
However, they will have toNrevoke your license.
I'm sorry.
She's right.
It's for your own good, Michael.
She asked meNto take over her treatment.
She's my patient now.
Please, don't.
You've no idea whatNyou're getting into.
Tell her the truth.
I'll make you tell her the truth.
God.
Come on.
She's right, you know.
You really do need help.
Bitch.
So, what's this about?
Protection.
Oh, yeah? From who?
Washburn.
Go ahead.
Kelly Lash kills lrena,NDr. Green's colleague.
No, I read your book.
So you just rushed right over hereNto save her?
It's just a story, doctor.NOr maybe I really am omnipotent.
Congratulations,Nthe control freak finally lets go.
This is what you wanted from the start,Nwasn't it? To ruin me, to fuck me up!
Feels good, doesn't it?
No more "l should've stopped CheslavNfrom killing his girlfriend."
No more whining over nothing.
-lt wasn't over nothing.N-Yes, it was.
Cheslav did not kill his girlfriend.
Washburn did.
Washburn?
What do you think Adam Towers wasNwriting about when he was killed?
You're lying.NYou're a lying fucking bitch.
Sure I am,Nif it makes it easier for you.
Why? Why would he killNthe girlfriend?
To nail Cheslav.
That's right.
Your seven years of hell.
Your meltdown.
Your divorce.
Just so your good friend RoyNcould nail a drug dealer.
Don't take it so hard.
Even OedipusNdidn't see his mother coming.
It's Roy Washburn.
Give me the gun. Give me the gun!
Fuck off!
Give me the gun! He knows I've gotNTowers' notes. He wants me dead.
Open the door!
He's going to kill meNand say you did it.
No. No, this is all fucked up.
You don't know what you're doing.NGive me the gun. He's going to kill me.
You--!
Go ahead, then, baby.
Whatever she told you, she's lying.
Kill her!
It's the only chance you've got.
Let go of the gun!
Clear the weapon!
-Stay still!N-Get off me!
Stop struggling! Stop struggling!
Stay down! I'm telling youNto stay down. Okay?! Stay down!
Get the cuffs on him.
-Call an ambulance!N-Keep still!
Call an ambulance!
Stay down!
Calm down! Calm down!
Nighttime! Nighttime!
You'll be home soon.
Hello, Michael.
I brought you a present.
I know you read an earlier draft.NBut you gave me a better ending.
So, thank you.
Would you like me to tell you the plot?
It's about an American.
A blond.
A novelist.
People around her just keep dying.
But the question is:
Who's killing them?
Is the beautiful blond novelistNa serial killer?
Or is it the crooked cop?
Her analyst isn't sure.
But he goes crazy trying to find out.
But that's just half the story.
There's a twist.
You see, the novelistNnever really killed anybody.
And neither did the cop.
The real killer all along...
...was the shrink.
Yeah, from the moment he saw her...
...he knew she was the smoke screenNhe was looking for.
His best opportunity to get even.
First...
...he'd deal with that scumbagNjournalist.
You see, you don't just go aroundNstealing another man's wife.
It's humiliating.
Not that she was a complete innocent.
That weekend slut.
Jesus, how could sheNlet that sleazebag touch her?
It's hurtful.
And there's some hurtsNyou don't just get over.
Jealousy.
Jealousy can make us do crazy things.
But getting away with it...
...that was genius.
"Unfit to stand trial. "
No prison for him,Njust a happy ending...
...in a quiet, sunlit, peacefulNpsychiatric institute.
Of course, that could all be a fiction.
He might really be insane.
Come back soon, baby.
I miss you.