Good morning, sweetheart.
I had to leave super early this
morning to drop off some saddles.
I hope I didn't wake you.
Could you take the horses
out if it stopped raining?
I'll be back home
in about an hour.
Come on. Let's go.
I was thinking, let's stay
home this weekend, huh?
Catch up on that to-do
list we keep putting off?
I promise I'll fix that
crack in the bedroom ceiling.
Hey, I just wanted to say
sorry about last night.
I was just drunk and
being insensitive.
Anyway, I'm back
home in half an hour
and I'm going to shower you with
kisses until you forgive me.
Kate. I'm sorry.
-I didn't mean to scare you.
-No. Sorry.
Let me just take out my...
What's the verdict?
You wanna come and
have a look with me?
I don't know. Do I?
Okay. Come on, Coop.
You see the dips? Those rafters
could collapse any day now.
Then you've got a real
mess on your hands.
How much to replace it?
Well, if you stick with the shingles,
you're looking at around $9,000.
Okay, let me think on it
and I'll get back to you.
No rush.
-Morning, Kate.
-Hi.
Hannah, why are you not dressed?
Could you be a little
polite and say hi to Kate?
Hi, Kate.
Hi, sweetheart.
Richard, honey,
Kate's here again.
I'm back in my office.
Sorry, I gotta get
this little one ready.
-Do you wanna just go on in?
-Yeah, of course. Thank you.
Come on, sweetie.
We got to hustle.
I'm coming, I'm
coming. Geez, Mom.
-Good morning.
-Hey.
Come in.
I'm trying to find a brief.
I hired a new assistant,
and it's not working out.
I don't know where
the hell anything is.
Please, sit.
Thanks.
Yeah, this is good.
So, your message said you needed
to discuss the roof. Is that right?
Yeah...
Randy came out to take a look and
unfortunately, we need a new one.
-Well, not surprised.
-I know. I know.
I thought that we had two years,
-you know, at least.
-How much?
How much?
9,000.
9,000. This is turning
into a bad joke.
No, but it's guaranteed
to last ten years.
He said at least ten years.
You know, I ran into
Kathy Dumont at the club.
She said you'd canceled her daughter's
riding lessons for the past six months.
Hilary Stafford told
me the same thing.
Look, I'm sorry you lost Patty,
but I can't continue to pour
money into a failing business,
especially 'cause we're
not married anymore.
And I never wanted that
farm in the first place.
If you can't make it work,
you're gonna have to sell it.
Bye, Richard.
Bye, Dad.
Bye. Nice to see you guys.
-Have fun.
-I'm late. Let's go.
Thanks.
I'm guessing you haven't
heard from Claire.
She showed up here last week.
Three o'clock in the morning and
she's pounding on the front door.
What did she want? I me...
What does she
always want? Money.
And it doesn't help that you continue
to give her anything she wants.
She's our daughter, Richard.
-What...
-We made promises
when we sat down with the
counselor, do you remember?
-We both made pledges not to enable...
-Yes. You know I tried.
-You know I tried...
-You never tried, Kate.
She'll show up and give you that smile and
you'll gladly pretend everything is fine.
It's not fine. Our
daughter is very sick.
He only barks when
you come home.
Are you feeding him enough?
-He's about to eat my hand off.
-Stop it. Come on, he's fine.
I missed you so much.
I missed you more.
What is going on
with your hair, Mom?
I could ask you the same thing.
Okay, well, I'm gonna call
and make you an appointment.
You really need to start
taking care of yourself again.
Why didn't you call me back?
It's a long story.
Speaking of, can I have your
iPad so I can check my messages?
Okay. Where were you?
A couple of Ryan's friends rented
a house down in Dewey Beach.
You didn't get my messages?
No, my phone died.
We just bought it.
-It broke already?
-Ryan threw it into the ocean
like a Hail Mary pass. Like...
Splash. Fish food.
Why did he do that?
'Cause he is a fuckface.
Don't worry, I got him back.
Before I left, I went into his
closet, and I gathered up all his shit
and I threw it over
the 21st bridge.
He is probably freaking
the fuck out right now.
Oh, my God. He totally is.
Mission accomplished.
Oh, Claire, come on.
Well, that's what happens when
you send dick pics to skanks
in front of your girlfriend.
Maybe you should
break up with him.
I am going. Sprinting.
But first, I need...
I need a phone, so
can we go to Verizon?
Yeah, let me put the horses
in and we can then ride over.
You hungry? You want
a grilled cheese?
I am starving.
So...
are you feeling good?
I'm clean, Mom. I'm good.
So happy you're here.
Are you getting jealous?
You wanna go for a swim
tomorrow down at Marsh Lake?
It'll be good for you.
Yeah, well, we'll see.
Remember when I was little, and I was
convinced a ghost lived in the lake?
Yes, of course I remember that.
You called her Ariel, right?
-No, Aurora.
-Aurora.
The ghost of Marsh Creek Lake.
So scary.
No, I got it.
Where's my stuff?
Oh, my God. What
happened to your face?
Stop fucking around,
Claire. I know you took it.
Ryan, I don't know what
you're talking about.
Do you have any idea how much fucking
trouble I'm in right now because of you?
There was a half a
fucking kilo in my bag.
Well, I told Jackie
that you stole it.
-So if you don't give it back...
-What?
-You told Jackie?
-...he's gonna come looking for you.
Ryan, what the fuck is
the matter with you?
Why the fuck would
you do that to me?
Because I'm fucking
scared, that's why.
-You know what Jackie's like.
-Ryan, do not tell him where I live.
Do not tell Jackie
where I fucking live!
Hey.
Hey, everything okay here?
I'm going out.
Go where?
Where are you going?
Honey? You okay?
Claire?
Claire? Claire?
Claire.
Stand up for me. Come
on, stand up for me.
There you go.
Okay. There you go.
Claire.
Honey, I need to talk
to you about last night.
I'm gonna go take a dip.
You can't keep avoiding this.
Okay.
Trip number 15. I think my
arms are gonna fall off.
I remember those days.
Tell me it gets easier.
Oh, God, no. Just you wait.
I'm just kidding.
Every day is a gift.
Okay, do you guys want me to
do a front flip or a backflip?
Backflip!
You guys have to promise me
you're not gonna try this.
You have to pinkie
promise, okay?
Let me see all of you.
-We pinkie promise.
-That's not a pinkie!
-Yes it is.
-Now, go!
Okay!
Three, two, one.
-Hey.
You know, an ad popped up
on my computer the other day
from Chester Community College.
Mom, an ad doesn't just
pop up on your computer.
It's there 'cause
you searched for it.
Well, it doesn't matter
how it got there.
What matters is that they
offer creative writing classes.
Why does that matter?
Well, because you should think
about going back to school.
And you're a great writer.
What have I written that makes
you think I'm such a great writer?
That short story you wrote
about the mother who loses
her child at the zoo.
What do you think it was about?
I think that, for me...
it was about regret.
That's not what I
intended it to be about.
So I guess it was a failure,
just like the rest of my life.
You know, I hate it when
you say things like that.
Hello, sweetheart.
How you doing?
I didn't realize you grew
up all the way out here.
Man, horses and green grass...
It's beautiful.
Just like you.
How'd you find me
out here, Jackie?
Hey.
Come on.
Man.
You know, for the life of me I do
not understand what you see in him,
'cause I see the
way you look at me.
I don't look at you
any way, Jackie.
No?
No.
Where's my shit?
I don't have it.
You don't have it?
I threw it away by
mistake and I'm sorry.
I didn't know your shit
was inside, Jackie.
-I didn't know.
-Fucking dumb bitch.
The fuck's wrong with you?
What'd you fucking do?
Hey! Leave her alone.
What?
What'd you say?
Fuck!
-Where you going? Come here.
-Jackie.
Come here.
Come here. What? What?
No, no, it's okay.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to hit you that hard.
Just breathe. You just
gotta breathe nice and slow.
Breathe nice and slow.
You're all right.
Hey! Get away from her!
Get the hell off of her.
You okay?
Come on.
What's going on here?
I'm really sorry, Ms. Garretson.
Hey, you must be Claire's mom.
I was just commentating on
how beautiful it is out here.
-The horses...
-Who are you?
I'm a close friend
of your daughter's.
Unfortunately, she...
Look, she betrayed my trust, and she took
something that didn't belong to her...
She didn't steal it.
-She threw it away.
-Shut up.
And it's put me in a very
bad spot with some people
I'd prefer not to be
in a bad spot with.
Stay away from him,
Mom! He's crazy!
Claire, why would you say that
-about a close friend?
-Hey!
-He's not my friend, Mom!
-You need to leave or I'm...
I'm gonna call the police.
Okay, but just so
we're all clear,
your junkie daughter
has two choices.
Give it back, or she
can pay me my money.
Get out of here.
Come on.
You fucking...
Bye, Claire!
Who the hell was that?
Remember when I said I threw
Ryan's stuff off the bridge?
-Well, there was something inside.
-You mean there were drugs inside.
I didn't know it then, Mom.
Honestly, I didn't know
when I threw it over.
That man knows where we live now,
Claire. What if he comes back?
-He won't.
-No, you don't know that.
Okay, I won't let him, Mom.
Goddamn it, Claire.
Really?
Mom.
Mom, let me explain.
Mom!
What's he doing here?
I thought you were running.
Ryan's in trouble because of me,
and he wanted me to come
here and apologize to you
-for bringing Jackie here earlier.
-I don't give a shit.
I just want him gone.
Well, that's why we're leaving.
We're gonna camp out for a few days.
You mean you're gonna
use for a few days?
No, Mom, we're gonna
camp out for a few days.
Okay.
Here, take this.
Narcan. You know what?
Take all of 'em
in case you OD again.
Mom, I need some money.
Claire, just... just leave.
Mom, I am leaving. I just need
some money for food and supplies.
Food and supplies? Do you
think I'm that stupid?
Ryan is in trouble
because of me, Mom.
-I'm not giving you money.
-It's serious this time.
-I made a pledge to your father...
-Oh, my God. The pledge!
The fucking pledge! You and
Dad and your fucking pledge!
I pledge allegiance to
neglect my daughter,
-not give a flying fuck about her!
-Not give a fuck, really?
-Mom, I need some money. Mom!
-I don't have any money!
It's all gone towards getting you
better and clearly it hasn't worked.
Mom, where are you going?
Mom, I am in trouble.
I need money, Mom.
Mom, I need help.
Mom, give me some money.
Mom, open the door!
Mom, open the door.
I need a check.
Are we really doing this again?
I'm just gonna cancel it anyway.
No, you won't. You
won't cancel the check.
Of course I'm gonna
cancel the check.
-No, you won't cancel it this time, Mom.
-There's nothing in there.
You've taken it all.
I have to beg your father for
money just to keep the farm.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Honey, are you hurt?
Ryan!
What?
Ryan, get the dog and put
him in the back of my car!
What are you doing?
I'm gonna take Cooper.
I'm gonna drive him so far away that he
will not be able to find his way home,
and he's gonna starve or worse.
Give me a check, Mom.
Ryan!
Ryan, did you get Cooper?
I'm trying!
Just find him and put him in
the back of the fucking car!
Cooper!
I don't know where
the hell he is!
Ryan, well, hurry up!
Cooper!
What the fuck is the
matter with you, Mom?
-Give me the fucking dog.
-No! No!
Give me the fucking dog, Mom.
-No!
-Give me the...
Do you want me to pull all your
fucking disgusting hair out?
Hey!
-Let's go.
-Get the fuck off of me, Ryan!
Get the fuck off of me!
You got no friends,
Dad fucking hates you,
do you know everybody fucking
hates you except for me?
Fuck.
Claire, let's go.
Come on. We gotta go.
Les?
Well,
hello.
Hey.
There you are.
You look great.
You're a sight for sore eyes.
-It's been too long.
-Hi.
So what brings you
down here anyway?
I had to drop a trailer off at
Nelly Godschalk's at Derby Ranch.
How is Nelly these days?
Oh, God, she's still
an awful old cunt.
Every time I leave, I just wanna
punch her straight in the face.
I haven't seen her in so long.
I mean,
haven't seen anybody really.
Well, you're not
missing much. Trust me.
So who's helping you
take care of the place?
No one.
No one?
God, Kate, are you
out of your mind?
It was always just me
and Patty, you know.
How you holding up?
I mean...
Thank God I have the
horses to take care of,
otherwise I wouldn't get
out of bed in the morning.
It's only been nine months...
and it was so sudden.
Yeah, it was. Yeah.
It was just...
I can't really talk about
her with anybody, you know?
-You can always call me, you know that.
-I don't wanna bother you.
-I don't wanna...
-You are never a bother.
Thanks.
Why don't I just stay and help out on the
farm today, and then I can stay the night?
You've got your own
stuff to take care of.
Oh, shut up.
Joan's mother's staying.
God knows I could use
a vacation from her.
We can make dinner,
I don't know, get
drunk as skunks
and laugh our tits off
just like old times.
Okay.
All right.
So you're teaching
riding lessons again?
Trying to.
I've been calling
my old clients.
Yes, as good as new.
I broke up our family.
I'm the one who fell in love
with the "lesbo ranch hand,"
as Richard liked to tell people.
-Yeah.
-All right, I'll order some takeout soon.
Order me anything,
except vegan turkey.
Oh, my God.
Do you remember the time Patty
served it on a silver platter?
She was so proud of that.
Christ. I mean, it tasted
like a thousand assholes.
Yeah.
And what about Claire?
The last time we talked,
she was back in rehab.
Yeah, she skipped out again.
Jesus.
I always thought I was too boring
for my life to be this messed up.
Your life is not a mess.
You're grieving, you lost Patty.
I mean, there's no
road map for that shit.
Fuck me.
That's the Hallmark card.
"Grief.
There is no road
map for that shit."
Fuck. Yeah.
Now... Okay, let's get
a little rest here.
-Okay, I wanna rest.
-Now, okay...
One foot in front of the other.
Easy.
You see? We can still dance.
Dance floor is closed.
Fuck.
My God.
-That's my sock.
-Yeah, yeah.
-I gotta go to bed.
-Here you go.
I gotta go.
Okay. Thank you.
There you are.
Les?
Hey, sweetheart. I found
Claire and calmed her down.
She feels terrible
about what happened.
We're gonna grab a quick
bite, and I'll bring her home.
This snowstorm is crazy.
There is so much snow on the road,
so it's going to take us a while.
Get some rest.
A little more
outside connection.
-Good.
-Straighten up, Mal.
For fuck's sake, you look
like Quasimodo out there.
Emma, do you mind?
Mom, she literally just
said I was doing good.
Use any of the bone
structure you have...
-God, can you stop for one minute?
-...to keep yourself upright.
Nice and easy.
What are you doing here?
I need help.
Okay.
Okay. Okay. Let's
get this off of you.
Are you bleeding?
I'm not. I'm sorry, Mom.
It's Ryan's.
Okay.
Okay, calm down. Breathe.
We went camping, and we
started arguing again.
And I promise I didn't know
what was in the bag, Mom.
-I didn't know what was inside.
-I know. I believe you.
I pushed him.
I didn't mean to
do it so hard, Mom.
And then he fell over the slope,
and he hit his head and it just...
Just opened up.
What opened up, honey? What...
His head, it just...
There was just blood
everywhere, Mom.
Just...
Is he okay?
Did you call the police?
-No.
-Why?
It was an accident. It was...
He... You were arguing and
he fell, and he hit his head.
That's not a crime.
-There's no reason to not call the...
-No. He didn't fall, Mom. No.
I hit him with a rock.
He was getting so
angry, and I got scared
and he was coming at me
and I just... I... Mom.
Mom, what do we
do? What do we...
What do we...
Where is Ryan now?
I'm gonna ask you
some questions,
and you need to be completely
honest with me, okay?
Where did you go?
Valley Forge.
We just...
We just parked
and picked a spot.
Did you check in?
I mean, was there
a check-in station?
No, it wasn't
anything like that.
We just parked on the side
of the street and then we...
We just walked deep
into the woods.
Did anyone see you?
No.
No one saw you park, and no
one saw you in the woods?
Yeah, we just...
-We just parked and...
-Claire, it's important.
No, Mom. I mean...
God, I don't think
they did, Mom.
We got there so late the first
night and then the next day,
we went for a walk, so maybe
people could have seen us
-down by the water, I guess.
-Yeah. Okay.
Yeah.
Do you have Ryan's cell phone?
Does anyone know where
the two of you were?
No.
Okay, go upstairs, take off all
your clothes, and put them in a bag
and don't leave your
bedroom till I come back.
Come back from where?
Just do what I say.
Let's go.
What'd you do?
I took care of it.
All of it.
Will you stay with
me for a little bit?
We need to go
through a few things
so that we're on the same
page, in case anyone asks.
So, the two of you came
back here after camping,
you got into an argument, I
witnessed it, and then Ryan left.
Wait. Why would we say Ryan
was here? Would we not...
Because you brought his
cell phone back here,
and if the police check phone records,
they'll know that he was here.
So that's our story.
The two of you came back here after
camping, you got into an argument,
I witnessed it, and then Ryan left, and
then you stayed here with me all night.
Where is he?
Marsh Creek Lake.
The lake? Why the lake?
Because it was late,
Claire, and I didn't think
-that I would have time to bury him...
-Oh, my God.
-Oh, my God. Mom.
-It's...
Claire, you have to
be strong for me.
-Can you do that?
-Oh, my God.
-Stop. Stop saying that, Mom.
-You have to. You...
I didn't ask you to do anything.
I didn't tell you to go...
You didn't have to tell me.
I did it because I love you.
I love you, Claire, and I won't
let anything happen to you.
What's wrong?
Jackie.
Jackie who?
The guy who was here before.
The one Ryan owes money to.
He followed me to the store, and he
said he was gonna fucking kill me.
What did he say?
He came up to me and he jammed
a gun right under my chin.
-He said he's going to fucking kill me.
-Okay. Calm down.
I'm freaking out right now
because he's asking about Ryan,
and the more people
he asks about Ryan,
they're gonna start
questioning where he is and...
How much money does Ryan owe?
Ten thousand.
-Bodies float.
-What?
I read that bodies float,
especially when it's...
When it's hot out
like it is right now.
This bacteria grows in the gut
and the chest fills with gas
and then they float
to the surface.
Finally came to your senses.
This is what my daughter
owes, so it's the end of it.
You're making the rules now?
Huh, Mom?
Nice.
You give lessons out here?
Horse lessons?
I always wanted to ride a horse, and I
just recently came into some money, so...
I never wanna see you on
this property ever again.
You understand me?
It must be fucking awful.
What?
Having a kid like that.
Always having to
clean up their shit.
It's over.
He won't bother us anymore.
Let's get up. Time
for breakfast.
Hey. This is Claire's phone.
Just text me instead.
Hey. It's me.
I'm just checking to
see where you are.
Call me.
Change your diagonal.
Good job.
Excellent.
Keep breathing.
Can I have your iPad so I can
log in and check my messages?
Hey, I don't understand
how you can sit there
and fucking watch TV all day.
I wanna fucking
watch TV all day.
Your fucking mom is outside.
What?
Claire.
Claire, open the door.
Let's go. Get off the
fucking couch. Let's go.
-Claire. Open the door.
-She fucking knows.
-What's going on?
-Let's fucking go.
-Get your fucking shit.
-Come on.
-Ryan!
-Out the back. Come on.
Open it!
-Claire.
-Let's go.
Fuck!
Come on.
Claire, get out of the car.
Get out of the car
and talk to me.
Whose body was that?
-Close the door!
-I can't!
Tell me what you did to me.
Claire. Come on. Get out.
-Ryan! No!
-Fuck off!
For fuck's sake.
Claire, please open the door.
Please.
Just so you know, if you end
up going over the two hours,
we're gonna have to charge
you for the whole day.
-Yeah. Two hours will be fine.
-Okay.
-Is this one good?
-Yeah. Thank you.
-Afternoon.
-Hey. Hi.
-What are you doing out here?
-I'm not doing much of anything.
Just swimming. Why?
Girl on the beach there said
you'd gone over your time.
-She was worried about you.
-Oh, no.
I mean, I...
I lost my wedding ring,
and I thought I
would try to find it.
It seems pretty stupid.
Thought I could find
it in this big lake.
You wanna hear something funny?
Okay.
I lost my ring on our honeymoon.
Down in the Keys.
My wife was ready
to strangle me.
Look, here's the
good, or bad news.
You're still married, right?
Yeah.
Maybe call it a day, huh?
Everything I thought about
love was just an imitation.
But now that I've stood in its
light, I never wanna be without it.
Okay, Patty. Your turn.
Here goes nothing.
Kate, my love.
I've spent my whole
life searching for home.
Home is a place of
comfort, refuge.
You are my home.
And the best part of today is that
it's just the beginning for us.
And now you can kiss the bride.
Jesus Christ. It's two
o'clock in the morning.
Is everything all right?
Not really.
What's wrong?
Everything.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
Is everything you told
me last night true?
Yeah.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, you're coming
with me to Wildvale.
I can't leave the horses, so...
I've taken care of everything.
Two friends from Denise
Denman's ranch are driving down.
They're gonna be
here in 30 minutes.
You need to rest for a few days
and then we'll figure this out.
Kate, get packed.
Anything interesting...
We're here.
Hi.
Aw, sweetie.
Les told me that you're
going through it.
Yeah, a little bit. Yeah.
I made you some tea.
Thank you.
Here.
-You know the way.
-Okay.
No, I got it. I got it. Yeah.
All right.
She called your mother?
-Oh, God. What did she say?
-Damn right.
"We found Les and another
female in the barn.
They were doing
things to each other."
"What kind of things?"
my mother said.
"Well, we heard moaning
of a sexual nature."
"Oh," it's my mother.
"Wonderful. Sounds like they were
doing the right kind of things."
I love that.
Cheers to Mrs. Granderson and
her long-suffering husband.
How is old Mr. Granderson?
Does he still have
that beautiful farm?
The old man burned
the place down.
He burned it down? Why?
He got diagnosed
with Alzheimer's.
He didn't want his kids to be
on the hook for long-term care,
so he set fire to the hayloft one night,
trying to make it look like an accident
so he'd collect the
insurance payout.
But the police caught him.
-Who's for a top-up? Kate?
-Yep. Yeah, I'll have a little.
No. No, no. Not you.
Looks like I'll be doing the
chores myself tomorrow morning.
Thank you.
-Ready?
-Yeah, God.
-Cheers.
Hello.
What are you doing at my house?
Come on out.
I'm not home right now.
I'm hours away.
Well, you should get home.
We need to talk.
About what?
About the body you dumped
at Marsh Creek Lake.
You still there?
Yeah.
You think it's important
that we talk now, right?
I'll be home tomorrow.
Noon.
Come in.
Hey.
Who was it?
Someone's cousin.
Someone's brother.
Someone's child.
-Stop fucking around. I want a name.
-Someone's kid.
-I wanna know who it was.
-Forget who it was.
What's important right now
is that you understand just
how utterly fucked you are.
Good.
All right.
So, Ryan owed me ten grand for
the drugs your daughter tossed,
and he starts dealing,
trying to earn it back.
But he gets impatient and he cuts the
drugs with fentanyl to stretch it,
and that's fine but he pushes
it too far 'cause he's dumb.
And this kid OD's on the
drugs that Ryan sold him.
And Ryan and Claire come to me
and they're freaking the fuck out,
and so I calm them both down,
and I come up with a plan.
And I gotta be honest.
I did not think
that you were gonna
fucking actually do it,
but Claire said that you would on
account of your unconditional love.
And she was right.
You dumped the body, you got
my money, and here we are.
Does Claire know
you're doing this?
She does.
No. She doesn't.
I'm seizing an opportunity.
You've gone this far. I figure
you'll go a little farther, right?
So what do you want?
Some things have come up, and I need to
leave town for a while, and I would like
-to get paid out before I go.
-I already paid you.
You paid me ten fucking grand.
I want more. Do you not
see what's going on here?
I'm light-years
ahead of you, lady.
Right now, no one's searching for
some fucking missing dope addict
and no one ever will, but
I make one anonymous call,
and all of a sudden, they're
dragging the bottom of that lake,
and then there's
an investigation
and all roads lead back to
Ryan and Claire and to you.
You're fucked.
I don't have any money.
-I am having a hard time...
-Don't fucking say that to me. Don't say
-you don't have any fucking money.
-...I'm having trouble just making...
-Fucking shut up. Shut up.
-...the bills.
You have acres and acres of
land in Chester fucking County.
You have horses and barns
and a fucking house,
so don't fucking sit there and
tell me that you have nothing
'cause you have a
lot, and I want it.
I can't do this.
Come here. Come here.
No. Get off!
-Get off me!
-No!
Get off!
-Get off! Get off!
-Stop.
Stop, stop, stop.
No, no.
No.
-No, no. No.
-Look at me. Look at me.
Okay.
There we go.
You're okay.
You're all right.
Wakey-wakey. Jesus
Christ. Get up.
Fuck. I gave you 200 milligrams, and
you're acting like Sleeping Beauty.
Let's go.
Come on.
All right, so I took your phone,
computer, car keys, house keys.
You don't leave this property without
my permission. You understand?
You got two days to pay me.
Where am I sleeping?
Someone live here?
My wife did before
we got together.
What happened to her?
She died.
Tractor backfired, her horse
threw her, and she broke her neck.
That sucks.
Hey. I don't want anyone hanging
around here except me and you.
Make a list of your clients.
I'll send out a text saying
you're not available for lessons.
You're not gonna eat?
I don't have much
of an appetite.
Hey.
Please don't feed him that.
He likes it.
Look at him.
You'll make him sick.
Shit.
Oh, God.
Jesus Christ. I must have
called you 50 fucking times.
Are you trying to give
me a heart attack?
Hey. Old Granderson's barn
fire, how did he get caught?
-What?
-He was arrested. Why?
I don't like where your
head's at right now.
Les, come on. Just
tell me, please.
He used a flare.
He'd researched it, and
I guess he found out
that starting a fire with a flare
would be virtually undetectable.
But he was arrested.
Because he left something
behind. A part of the flare.
I don't remember exactly what,
but when the fire marshal found it,
he knew it was set intentionally.
Why do you wanna
know all this anyway?
Kate, are you sure you're okay?
I'll call you back soon, okay?
That's $100,000 of
insurance on the barn.
If you burn it.
Right.
How exactly do you do that without
these guys knowing you did it?
Hay spontaneously
combusts at 130 degrees.
It happens all the time, but if you
use a flare, then it's undetectable.
How long after you burn it will
it take for me to get my money?
I don't know. I mean, a
couple weeks or a month.
No. No.
Figure out a different plan.
This is what I have.
I've thought about this.
I've thought about it really
carefully, and I promise you
-that you can get your money this way.
-How?
I will be clear across the country
by the time that payout arrives.
I could make you an employee of the
farm, and then send it in installments,
and then I don't think
it'll get flagged that way.
What about the horses?
What about them?
Are they insured too?
Yeah, but this is a
boarding facility,
so not all of the
horses belong to me.
How many do?
Two.
How much are those
two insured for?
25,000 each.
So we burn them too.
And that brings the
payout to 150,000.
-But if we...
-That's good.
-But if we just burn my horses...
-What, are you fucking stupid?
We're not just gonna burn your
horses. We burn all the horses.
Use your head.
-Who's that?
-That's Emma.
She's a client.
What's she doing here? I
thought we canceled her lesson.
We did. I'll get it.
No, no. You stay here.
Afternoon.
It's Emma, right?
Where's Kate?
She woke up with a fever.
Don't worry. I'm taking
real good care of her.
I'm sorry. Who are you exactly?
I'm the new fucking farmhand.
Just started a few days ago.
Okay. I'm just gonna grab some of these
saddle pads for the New Haven show.
-Let me help.
-No. I'm fine. I don't need any help.
I got it.
I said I don't need your help.
All right.
That means you can go.
Can you get out of my space?
Emma's a fucking bitch.
Okay. We'll burn it.
But it's on you.
All of it.
'Cause if shit goes sideways,
I'm nowhere near any of this.
Hey, Dale. Appreciate you fitting
me in on such short notice.
Yeah, you got it.
Is it ready?
Yeah. We'll do it between
2:00 and 3:00 a.m.
Let it burn for a while.
By the time anybody notices and calls
the fire department, it'll be too late.
Cool.
Hey, handsome.
I know.
Everything's gonna be okay.
You should probably go now.
You know, I think I'm
gonna stick around.
Make sure you go
through with it.
-How you doing? You doing okay?
-Not really. No.
The fire marshal
just informed me
that the blaze was set
intentionally, Ms. Garretson.
It's a wire stand. They're
commonly used in road flares.
He found that at the
point of ignition.
What are you saying?
You think that I did...
You mentioned there was someone living
in the apartment above the barn.
An employee. Jackie Lawson.
Was Jackie home last night?
Was he in the apartment?
His car was there
-when I went to bed.
-What time was that?
-When you went to bed.
-Like 10 p.m. probably.
So when you noticed
the fire outside,
do you remember if Jackie's
car was still there?
It wasn't. And I called him this morning
to let him know what was going on,
but I haven't heard
anything from him.
Ms. Garretson, we found a dead
body inside the apartment.
Do you think it was Jackie?
We don't know.
As you could imagine, it
was very badly burned.
I need you to come down
to the station with me.
Okay. Sorry for the wait.
Good news is we were
able to locate Jackie.
Oh, thank God.
How'd you two meet,
Ms. Garretson?
Jackie and I? Through my daughter,
Claire. He's a friend of hers.
He was looking for a job, and I needed
somebody to help me out in the stables.
It's odd 'cause Jackie claims
he never worked for you.
Never lived in the apartment. In fact,
he says he doesn't even know who you are.
He doesn't know who I am?
But he's...
He's been living on the
farm and working there.
Why would he say that he
doesn't know who I am?
What about clients?
I'd imagine they'd have seen
him hanging around the place.
I canceled all my lessons.
My wife passed away recently.
I've had a really hard time
getting back on my feet.
I'm sorry.
-Emma Hanway.
-What's that?
Emma Hanway is a client.
I texted her to pick
up a saddle pad.
I mean, you... I could
give her your contact
-if you think that would be helpful.
-Please.
Was there anyone with
Jackie that you noticed?
Anyone hanging around?
Going inside the apartment?
I mean, I didn't keep a
really... a close watch on him.
There was one person though.
He introduced
himself to me once.
-Greg.
-G...
Kamiski. Kaminski.
Something like that.
You recognize him?
Nope.
His name is Greg Kaminski.
Medical examiner just confirmed
it through dental records.
Okay.
His body was found out at
Echo Valley this morning.
Inside that apartment
above the barn.
All right. Well, I already told
you I wasn't staying at that farm.
-I don't know this fucking...
-Jackie, I know you been working
on the farm. I got the
bank statement to prove it.
Bank statement?
$2,500 wired to your bank
account from Ms. Garretson's.
In addition, a client
of Ms. Garretson's
confirmed that she saw
you at the property.
All right. Let's just
fucking rewind, okay?
Let's rewind and
just go from the top.
I'm gonna tell you exactly
what happened, all right?
I'm going to tell you
what actually happened.
Jesus Christ.
I must have called you 50 fucking times.
Are you trying to give me a heart attack?
Hey. Old Granderson's barn
fire, how did he get caught?
'Cause he left something
behind. A part of the flare.
Why do you want to
know all this anyway?
I'll call you back soon, okay?
Okay.
There it is. Stop.
He's gone.
We gotta leave.
It's okay.
Come on.
Good boy. Go, go!
You guys are being played.
We're all being fucking
played right now by her.
You know, just so I'm clear...
Your story is that
Kate's daughter,
and her daughter's boyfriend
killed Greg Kaminski
and had Kate dump the
body at Marsh Creek Lake.
-I know how it sounds.
-I wasn't finished.
Then she set the fire using
flares that you purchased
from the Quick Star gas
station one mile from her farm.
Do you wanna know what I think?
I think Greg Kaminski's
a known drug abuser.
I think you were his dealer.
I think something happened
inside the apartment.
-No! Fucking no.
-I think something happened inside...
-Don't fucking pin this shit on me!
-Relax, Jackie.
-Don't fucking...
-Put your arm down. Sit down.
You don't understand.
Don't fucking touch me.
-Get back there.
-Don't you fucking...
-Sit down!
-Don't fucking touch me.
Don't...
It's all right.
It's all over now.
Yeah, yeah. I hear
you, jerk off.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
-Hey, Randy.
-Hey, Kate.
-How's it going?
-So far so good.
I'll have this cleanup done
by the end of the week.
Then with a little bit of luck, we'll
be under roof before winter hits.
-That's great. Thanks.
-Yeah.
Hey, Randy.
Generator's backed in.
I gotta go play "Mom."
Okay, go to your working trot.
Stay in two-point
and ask him to walk.
Little slower.
There you go.
Hey, it's me.
We're on our way home now.
I let Claire know
that as a punishment,
she'll be mucking horse shit
for the next two months.
-Stop, Patty.
-She wants to tell you something.
Hi, Mom. I'm sorry for being
such a constant fuckup.
-Hey. We're past that now.
-And...
And I just love you, you know.
Did you hear that? She loves
you like crazy and I do too.
The snow's eased up
and we'll be home soon.