♪
[ Water lapping gently ]
[ Metal creaking ]
Looks pretty dead.
Should we just go?
Didn't book, eh?
Thought we'd just try our luck.
Wouldn't recommend it.
Especially not you.
Okay, yeah, why's that?
Last group he took out,
there was a young fella...
Looked like you. College kid.
He was taking a piss
off the side of the boat
and a bull shark jumped up.
Bit his dick off.
[ Laughing ] God!
Well, I don't like your chances.
Tuck only started
his holidays today,
and he doesn't interrupt
his hols for no one.
[ Dog barking ] [
Vehicle approaching ]
Speak of the devil, here he is.
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ Barking ]
Milo, shut up!
Mate, you won't need that.
We got some live
chum for you here.
Ah! Who do we have here, then?
Greg.
Tucker. American?
-Canadian.
-Ah, lucky escape.
[ Both chuckle ]
And this friendly
face belongs to?
-Heather.
-Ah!
Let her answer
for herself, Greg.
-I'm Heather.
-Heather, lovely.
Let me guess... Pom?
Oh, not bloody s'posed to
say that anymore, are we?
[ Chuckles ] No, it's
fine. Um, English, yes.
Mate, I told them you
were on hols, Tuck.
Ah, so where are you two
lovebirds staying, then?
Oh, we're not together. Um...
[ Laughs ] Just... Just
staying at the hostel.
-Okay.
-Sorry we didn't book.
We were supposed to go to
SeaWorld with a bunch of others,
but we slept in.
It was a big
night. [ Giggles ]
Yeah, I bet. [ Chuckles ]
[ Laughing ] Sorry.
So, ah...
I guess no one even knows
you guys are here, then.
Why?
Well, I just want to make sure
your last will and
testament's in order.
We will be swimming
with sharks, after all.
-Oh. [ Laughs ]
-Sweet.
[ Chuckles nervously ]
[ Waves crashing ]
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
♪
[ Music fades ]
[ Seabirds crying ]
So, I'm seven years old.
I'm out there on
my boogie board,
splashing around in
the shallows, you know.
Scrawny little arms and
legs kind of flapping away
and swimming out there
and, I don't know,
I guess from underneath I
must have looked like a seal.
Fuckin' boom!
-[ Gasps ]
This bloody white gets me.
[ Laughs ]
-And it just let you go?
-Yeah.
You are looking at a genuine
walking, talking miracle.
Did it hurt?
Well, it didn't tickle.
Yeah, it didn't tickle.
Woke me up, though, you know?
I've been wide awake ever since.
And this was just random?
I mean, apparently
there was a sign
about a shark sighting
or something, but...
oopsie!
Wasn't there someone
watching you?
Well...
Let's just say I used to
spend a lot of time on my own.
♪
I just can't believe you
do this for a living.
I'd never go near
water again after that.
It's not the shark's fault.
♪
[ Metal creaking and clanging ]
-You okay?
-Yep.
-It'll be alright.
-It's fine, yeah.
It's gonna be a
great experience.
Yeah.
♪
Alright, crew!
Enough foreplay. Let's,
uh, get you two wet!
[ Laughs ]
-Okay...
-Don't worry, I got you.
[ Chuckles weakly ]
Oh, my God, I can't believe
I let you talk me into this.
[ Shouting ] Oh! Oh!
Oh, it's a mako.
Cheetahs of the sea.
I can't do it.
I-I can't...
Well, not yet, you can't.
'Cause there's still one
thing we need to take care of.
Now, listen. This
is a very special
ancient relaxation practice
that, uh, was taught to me
and then it took many
years at sea to master.
If you'll just go with me
here, I promise you it'll help.
Now close your eyes.
Take a big, deep inhale.
And out.
And in.
♪ Baaaaaaaaa...
♪ ...by shark, doo
doo doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ Baby shark, doo
♪ Baby shark, doo doo doo
doo doo doo doo ♪ -Wha...?
- ♪ Baby shark -
[ Chuckling ] No.
- ♪ Baby shark - ♪ Doo
doo doo doo doo doo
It only works if you sing along.
-I can't!
-♪ Baby shark
♪ Doo doo doo doo doo doo
♪ Baby shark...
-Come on, Heather!
♪ Baby shark
♪ Here comes Mommy Shark
♪ Doo doo doo doo doo doo
♪ Mommy shark, doo
doo doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ Mommy Shark and Daddy...
[ Gate creaks, slams ]
♪
[ Breathing heavily
through respirator ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Muffled groan ]
[ Muffled whimpers ]
[ Muffled cries ]
♪
[ Breathing heavily ]
Mm-hmm. Mm.
[ Placid music plays ]
♪
[ Music builds ]
[ Gate bangs ] [ Laughs ]
Oh, my God, that was amazing!
Shits all over Sea World, eh?
You can say that again.
Yeah, something to tell
the grand-kiddies one day.
Dude. So awesome.
Yeah.
Oh, man, thanks so much
for fitting us in...
[ Groans ]
[ Muffled gasp ]
[ Spluttering ]
Welcome aboard.
[ Screams ]
♪
[ Upbeat music plays ]
♪ On the floors of Tokyo
♪ Or down in London
town to go, go ♪
♪ With a record selection
and a mirror's reflection ♪
♪ I'm dancing with myself
♪ When there's no
one else in sight ♪
♪ In the crowded lonely night
♪ Well, I wait so long
for my love vibration ♪
♪ And I'm dancing with myself
♪ Oh, oh, oh,
dancing with myself ♪
♪ When there's nothing to lose
and there's nothing to prove ♪
♪ Then I'm dancing
with myself ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh
♪ If I looked all
over the world ♪
♪ And there's every
type of girl ♪
♪ But your empty eyes
seem to pass me by ♪
♪ Leave me dancing
with myself ♪
♪ So let's sink another drink
♪ 'Cause it'll give
me time to think ♪
♪ If I had the chance, I'd
ask the world to dance ♪
♪ And I'd be dancing
with myself ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh,
dancing with myself ♪
♪ When there's nothing to lose
and there's nothing to prove ♪
♪ Then I'm dancing with myself
[ Music continues quietly ]
-[ Slurping ]
Should be there. Did
you look where I said?
Yeah, I looked. I can't
find the jumper cables.
Oh. Must be out, then. Sorry.
Thanks. [ Sighs ]
Don't s'pose you have any?
Nah.
What's up?
Hey, how's it going?
Cracker day out there, eh?
♪
♪ Well, if I looked
all over the world ♪
♪ And there's every
type of girl ♪
♪ But your empty eyes
seem to pass me by ♪
♪ Leave me dancing with myself
♪ So let's sink another drink
Hey.
Me again.
Yeah, dude, I said
I can't help you.
Ah, you really don't
have jumper cables?
For this?
-What can I say?
I live life on the edge.
I think the cashier might want
to see that security footage.
Are you serious?
Is this really
what you're doing?
You're blackmailing me.
Well, I just need
to get to my car.
I've walked like ten blocks
and I can't find any.
Look, I'm not a
serial killer, okay?
Promise.
[ Upbeat punk music
playing on stereo ]
♪
Aisle or window?
[ Music continues ]
I have... I have this theory
that, um, aisle people are
more... open and friendly
whereas, uh, window
people are more, um...
private and thoughtful.
Getting major window
vibes. [ Chuckles ]
Is this a Mormon thing?
'Cause I'm not joining,
so you can save it.
Why... Why would you
think I'm a Mormon?
Dude, you look like you stepped
out of The Book of Mormon.
Okay, yeah. No, I'm, uh...
I'm in real estate.
Great.
Selling apartments,
not eternal salvation.
Can you just shut the fuck up?
Ah, yep. [ Clears throat ]
Yep.
[ Music continues ]
♪
-Nice wheels.
-That was my mum's.
You know, she gave
me a good deal.
Is that your mom's, too?
So, where you been surfing?
Oh, ah, Snapper,
mostly. It's been good.
The peak's a little
shifty, though.
Yeah.
Do you want to know
a local secret?
Okay.
You can't tell a soul, though.
Window person, remember?
Yeah. Right.
Okay, well, next
time you paddle out,
you want to look to
shore for the blue bench.
Right, you wanna sit right
in the middle of that bench.
You'll double your wave count.
Thanks.
And look, for the record, I...
I never would have
narked about the Slurpee.
No, yeah, I probably
shouldn't have
judged a book by its
cover, so... we're good.
Moses Markley.
-Zephyr.
-Nice to meet you, Zephyr.
Now go start your car.
Yes, ma'am.
[ Engine starts ]
Yes! You're a lifesaver.
-You bet.
-Thank you.
[ Creedence Clearwater Revival's
"Ooby Dooby" plays on stereo ]
You a Creedence fan, huh?
Hell yeah. Are you into 'em?
Yeah, sure, just not this song.
What's... What's wrong
with "Ooby Dooby"?
Dude, you have "Fortunate Son,"
about poor kids fighting
rich people's wars.
And then you have "Long
As I Can See the Light,"
about, like, an outsider
searching to feel understood.
And...
And then you have
"Ooby-fuckin'-Dooby,"
you know, about some
goofy-ass dance.
I just, I don't know.
Yeah, it's a bad song.
Objectively.
-Okay.
The dance is a metaphor.
The song's about love.
-Wow.
It's about that "ooby dooby"
feeling you get in your heart...
-Okay.
-...when you find the one,
and you just gotta go for it.
So what's the alternative?
♪
♪ Your lips, my lips
♪ Apocalypse
[ Moaning ]
♪ Your lips, my lips
♪ Apocalypse
♪ Go and sneak us
through the rivers ♪
-Ow, ow!
-What, what, what, what?
[ Laughing ] What?
It's a fin key.
♪ Come out and haunt me
♪ I know you want me
♪ Sharing all your secrets with
each other since you were kids ♪
[ Slow music plays ]
-Give me a number.
-No way.
Oh, come on, I won't
judge. Promise.
Okay.
Nine.
Nine! [ Coughs ] Fuck.
Oh, fuck off. You
just said no judgment.
Yeah, but...
nine bread rolls in one day?
What can I say?
The waves were all-time,
and bread rolls are cheap.
Not that you have
to worry about that.
[ Exhales ] You have deep
psychological issues.
Mm!
-[ Laughing ] Sorry.
[ Coughs ]
I'm honored you'd
waste one on me.
It's not wasted.
Do you know how many
preservatives are in these things?
-I don't care.
-Mm.
You know I've got real
food inside, right?
Even have running water.
It's kind of a miracle.
I'm good.
[ Moses clears throat ]
♪
So, what got you into surfing?
Because...
it's us against the system.
The system that kills
the human spirit.
We stand for something.
To all those dead souls
inching along the freeway
in their metal
coffins, we show them
that the human spirit
is still alive.
You did not just quote
"Point Break" at me.
-Maybe.
-Mm.
[ Laughs ]
Mm, but really.
Uh, what got you into surfing?
Because there was
nothing for me on land.
♪
[ Music fades ]
[ Creedence Clearwater
Revival's "Ooby Dooby" plays ]
♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby
♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby,
ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby
♪
[ Crickets chirping ]
[ Melancholy music plays ]
♪
Shit.
Hello?
Anyone here?
Hey, if you can hear me, I'm
just looking for a fin key.
Promise I'll bring it back.
-G'day!
-[ Gasps ] Jesus!
[ Chuckles ] Yeah,
not quite. Tucker.
Sorry man, I was
just looking for a...
Fin key. Yeah, I
got you covered.
Let's see what we can do here.
Hey, you're pretty brave,
surfing up here all alone.
That rip can get pretty hectic.
You're alone, aren't you?
Touché.
Here ya are.
Thanks. I'll bring
it right back.
-I got heaps.
-Cool. Appreciate ya.
[ Cellphone chimes ]
[ Camera shutter clicks ]
[ Gentle music plays ]
♪
[ Dramatic music plays
] [ Muffled scream ]
[ Gasping, grunting ]
♪
[ Grunting stops ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Music fades ]
[ Mid-tempo music plays ]
♪ Come and see the real thing
♪ Come and see
the real thing ♪
♪ I am the real thing
[ Vocalizing ]
♪
♪ Trying hard to
understand that ♪
♪ Really not, you're seeing me
♪ Trying hard to
understand that... ♪
[ Seabirds crying ]
[ Dog growling ]
[ Barks, growls ]
[ Loud bang ]
[ Grunting ]
♪
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Music fades ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Ominous music plays ]
♪
[ Groans ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Gasping ]
-Hi.
-What is this?
W-W-Where are we?
We're on his boat.
Whose fucking boat?!
Uh...
[ Grunting ]
Sorry about the smell.
♪
Help!
-No one can hear...
-Help!
Somebody help!
-I've already tried that.
Help!
♪
[ Woman screaming
indistinctly on recording]
[ Screaming continues]
[ Chuckles lightly ]
[ Screaming continues distantly]
♪
Shit.
What are you looking for?
Something to get these
fucking cuffs off.
You know how to pick a
lock? What do we need?
Something long and
thin, like a hairpin.
♪
What is it?
[ Exhales shakily ]
Nothing.
♪
♪ She came all the
way from America ♪
♪ She had a blind
date with destiny ♪
♪ And the sound
of Te Awamutu... ♪
Mm!
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
♪
[ Banging ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Sighs ]
Hey, is there anyone that'll
come looking for you?
Boyfriend or anything?
There was this guy.
We did the shark dive together.
But...
What?
I don't think you wanna know.
♪
Is anyone looking for you?
No.
♪
♪ Summer's been and gone
♪ Only winter's from now on
[ Ominous music plays ]
♪
Look, her van was towed.
She wouldn't let
that happen, okay?
It's her home. Where...
Where's she gonna sleep?
Look, mate, these transient
types living in their cars...
She's not like that.
How long you known this girl?
I mean... I mean,
it was just...
It was just one night.
Or a day and a night. Uh...
A-A solid 10, 11 hours in total.
But it's not about the quantity,
it's about the quality.
-What was her name?
-Um, Zephyr.
Last name?
Um...
You don't know her last name.
No, I don't.
♪
[ Loud banging ]
I should have listened.
[ Bang ]
-[ Breathing heavily ]
My mum didn't want
me taking a gap year.
We had the worst fight
about it before I left.
[ Voice breaking ] Now I'm
never going to see her again.
[ Sobbing ] I'm never
gonna see anyone again.
♪
Why didn't she want
you to take it?
Because of this.
She was worried it wasn't safe.
You see all these stories on
the news about travelers and...
She also didn't want me
drifting from the plan.
The plan?
Law school.
House on the same street.
[ Scoffs ] That
sounds like her plan.
It's your life.
You should tell her that
when you see her again.
♪
[ Sighs ]
[ Bed bangs ]
Why are you here?
In... In Australia, I mean.
To surf.
[ Bed bangs ]
Get as far away from
home as possible.
Is your family back in America?
Which one?
I got a lot of fucking
foster parents to pick from.
Is that why you know
how to pick a lock?
What do you mean?
Like, from juvie or something?
Sorry, I... I didn't
mean to presume.
No, the only thing
I learned in juvie
is sleep with one eye open,
and a shit ton of bad jokes.
Can you tell me one?
Not really in a
joke-telling mood right now.
Just to think about something
else for one second.
Please?
What do you call the useless
piece of skin on a dick?
What?
The man.
[ Laughing ]
That is so true.
[ Both chuckle ]
[ Gasps ]
Is that an under wire?
Yeah, it's cutting
the shit out of...
-Give it to me!
-Wait, is this for...
-Yes, yes, the fucking lock!
-Oh!
Quick!
Sorry, I'm trying.
♪
[ Door scrapes open ]
Good evening, ladies.
Trust you've had a
chance to get acquainted.
Now, you must be starving.
Oh, not a Vegemite fan?
Well, I s'pose you wouldn't
be the first foreigner
to feel that way,
eh? [ Chuckles ]
There you go, just in case.
Water?
Really?
It's a thousand bloody
degrees in here.
Well, please yourself...
-Wait, wait.
♪
Hang on, what's
happened to your...
Hey, asshole. I'm ready
for my dinner now.
Oh, if looks could kill.
♪
Have you ever heard of
the scarlet king snake?
She's a harmless creature,
but quite cleverly mimics
the colorful stripes
of the deadly coral snake.
Now, you're trying hard to
be the coral snake, but...
...we both know that's me.
And you...
Well, you just have a
very pretty pattern.
♪
Mmm.
Tastes like fear.
♪
Hooroo!
[ Door slams ]
Are you alright?
♪
-Fuck!
-What's going on?
Hold on, I have to concentrate.
♪
-Have you got it?
-[ Groans lightly ]
Almost there.
Zephyr?
I-I don't feel good.
No! [ Wire clatters ]
No, no!
[ Grunting ] [ Door creaks ]
[ Chuckling ]
[ Gear clatters ]
♪
Oh, you're a fighter.
I love fighters.
Makes for a better show.
♪
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Dramatic music
plays ] [ Clattering ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪
[ Can tab pops ]
What is this?
[ Camera beeps ]
Why is there a camera?
[ Under breath ]
That's perfect.
Stunning, isn't it?
What is this?! What
are you doing?!
You know, most people think
that God is... up here.
Nah.
God's down there.
Where it all started.
Where it all ends.
So, I fish at your beach and
a couple of others, and...
I was really hoping it'd be you.
You know, I see you, like,
come alive on that board.
It's...
...spiritual.
Now, I don't surf, but
I feel the same about...
you know, what I do.
It's...
It's my true calling.
Don't you fucking touch her!
Hey!
[ Blade slicing ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
Heather.
-Huh?
-Hey.
There you are.
[ Breathing shakily ]
[ Keys jingling ]
[ Sobbing ]
You know why sharks are
more scary than mosquitos,
even though mosquitos kill
a million people each year?
I don't fucking care!
It's because people don't
think with their brains.
They think with their guts.
Now, your guts can't understand
mass-murdering insects
and microscopic diseases.
No, what your guts understand...
-[ Sobbing ]
...is 300 razor-sharp teeth
and 2,500 pounds of muscle
tearing flesh from bone.
What your guts understand
is the hierarchy of
animals in this world.
[ Dramatic music plays
] [ Machinery whirring ]
[ Shouting ]
No! No!
-[ Screaming ]
-[ Sobbing ]
♪
Please stop! Stop!
Please stop, please
stop! Please stop!
-[ Screaming ]
-Please stop!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
See, the thing about sharks is
they don't actually
enjoy eating people, no.
-I want my Mum!
-She's just a kid...
When they do attack,
it's unquestionably
a case of mistaken identity.
-[ Sobbing ]
You know, you throw chum
overboard day after day
so tourists can get their kicks,
and pretty soon, sharks start
to associate boats with food.
Now, some might argue that this
is a recipe for more accidents,
and, mm, I'm inclined
to agree with him.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Screaming ]
♪
[ Both screaming ]
Pull her up! Stop!
Fucking stop!
[ Button clicks ]
[ Whirring stops ]
[ Sobbing, screaming ]
♪
[ Screaming ]
No! Pull her up! Pull her up!
Just pull her up!
Pull her up, please!
[ Gasping ]
[ Under breath ] Fuck yeah.
[ Sobbing lightly ]
Tell me that ain't the
greatest show on Earth.
[ Muffled sobs ]
Oh, come on, don't be like that.
I know you ladies don't like
playing second fiddle, but...
it'll be your time to
shine tomorrow night.
♪
[ Distant thudding ]
[ Rock music plays ]
♪ I got some money
in my pocket ♪
♪ I got the car
keys in my hand ♪
♪ I got myself a
couple of tickets ♪
♪ To see a rock
'n' rollin' band ♪
♪ Come on, girl, just
get on your shoes ♪
♪ We're gonna hear some sounds
♪ Come on, babe, you know there
ain't no time to mess around ♪
♪ Evie
[ Music continues distantly ]
♪ Evie, Evie, Evie, let
your hair hang down ♪
♪ Evie, Evie
♪ Let your hair hang down
♪ You got the body of a woman
♪ The way you move
it like a queen ♪
[ Music continues distantly ]
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
♪
♪ Come on, babe, you know there
ain't no time to mess around ♪
♪ Evie, Evie, Evie, let
your hair hang down ♪
♪ Evie, Evie
♪ Evie, let your
hair hang down ♪
♪ Evie, Evie, Evie, let
your hair hang down ♪
♪ Evie, Evie
♪ Let your hair hang down
[ Scraping ]
♪
[ Spits ]
♪ So, won't you try it, baby
♪ I'll take you by the hand
[ Ominous music plays ]
♪
[ Banging ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Exhales deeply ]
[ Screaming ] Fuck!
[ Grunts ] Fuck!
[ Screaming continues ]
♪
[ Seabirds crying ]
[ Melancholy music plays ]
♪
[ Door creaks ]
May I?
Ah, come on, I know what
you're thinking, but...
a joke's only funny once.
Hey, listen, you've
lost a lot of fluid
and you know, you're gonna
need your strength later.
Where's that fight
I saw in you, huh?
Get away from me,
you twisted fuck.
Do you understand what
happens to the ecosystem
if you remove the shark?
Ah, their... their prey
operates without constraint.
But the shark...
The shark brings order.
And without this...
chaos reigns and...
...well, weaker
creatures just...
think they can do
whatever they want.
Jesus. [ Scoffs ]
Give me a fucking break.
I've never met anyone
who likes the sound of
their voice so much.
Don't compare
yourself to the shark.
They're highly evolved.
You're just a pathetic
coward who kills women
because Mommy never
loved you, or whatever.
You are the lowest of the low.
A worm.
Even lower than a worm.
You are the toxic fucking
trash that floats in the ocean.
♪
Hm.
I notice you haven't
used the facilities yet.
You might want to consider that.
You know, things can
tend to get a little...
undignified.
♪
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunts ] [ Handle snaps ]
♪
[ Heather screaming
on recording]
No! Pull her up, pull her up!
-Please, please, pull her up!
-[ Screaming]
♪
[ Dramatic music plays ]
-[ Groans ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Come on...
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
♪
-[ Shouts ]
-[ Groans ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Both grunting ]
♪
[ Gasps ]
[ Groans ]
[ Thud ]
♪
[ Grunting ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Hello? Hello?
[ Radio static, feedback ]
Help! I need help!
[ Static, radio noise ]
[ Groans ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Groaning ]
Help! Help!
[ Screaming ] Help! Help!
[ Gasping ]
Well, at least someone's
having a good time, eh?
♪
Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah.
Hey, be careful with that.
Hey, you fuckin' put that down.
-[ Grunts ]
You put that down or
you won't even make it
to the fucking hook.
Ah!
-[ Grunts ]
-[ Gasps ]
♪
Aah!
[ Gentle music plays ]
♪
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
We're looking for a
blonde female Caucasian...
[ Indistinct conversations ]
♪
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
Hey! [ Horn blows ]
♪
[ Muffled screams
] [ Banging ]
♪
[ Dog barking ]
Hey, Milo, shut
up! Hey, Tucky!
Mate, I thought you
were gone all week.
I gotta get some supplies.
That's not like you to run out.
First time for everything.
Mate, I got something for ya.
Mate, will you stop? I
got something good for us.
Yesterday, some
rich wanker, right,
pulls up with his
rich wanker kid
on a rich wanker boat.
But it was nice, mate.
They want to go diving.
I tell them the
Tuck's on hols, mate.
But now since you're back,
maybe we can catch them
before they go, mate.
I got their number
just in case, if...
It's on one of these.
Alright, I reckon there's gonna
be a nice tip in this for you
and maybe there's just
a little finder's fee
for the old Daveroo, mate.
[ Car door slams,
engine starts ]
[ Tires squealing ]
Ahoy there!
Tucker's Shark Experience
is currently closed
while your captain takes
a well-earned holiday.
Please call back after the
13th and I'll introduce you
to the most misunderstood
creatures on Earth.
[ Beep]
Uh, hi. Um...
I'm not exactly sure
what I'm asking for,
but, uh, just give me
a call back, please.
Thanks.
♪
Can you fucking move?
[ Breathing heavily ]
What?
♪
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Horn honking ]
♪
[ Horns honking ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪
[ Banging ]
[ Faint muffled cries ]
♪
[ Muffled cries, banging ]
[ Glass shatters ]
♪
[ Muffled screams ]
[ Dog barking ]
♪
[ Muffled screams continue ]
[ Splutters ]
Fuck. Fuck.
Hey, hey, hey.
Thank you.
You gotta go... go find
a paperclip or a skewer
or fucking something
to pick the locks with.
I'll talk you through it.
Quick, before he comes back.
Go! And call the cops!
Police, fire, or ambulance?
[ Grunts ]
[ Both grunting ]
Hello? Police,
fire, or ambulance?
-Poli...
-[ Grunting ]
♪
Sorry, I can't hear you.
Could you repeat that?
Help!
Aah! [ Groans ]
[ Shouting ]
♪
Sir, if you need assistance
but you're unable to speak,
please press...
-[ Beep ]
[ Cellphone clatters ]
Where the fuck
did you come from?
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Both grunting ]
[ Choking, gasping ]
[ Groaning ]
♪
[ Gasps ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Dog barking ]
[ Wheezing, coughing ]
Tuck, are you...
Are you alright, mate?
-Hello?!
[ Dog barking ]
[ Wheezing ]
Moses?
-Please!
-Hello?
Jesus, what...
-Help!
Mate, have you got a sheila
down there I don't know about?
[ Weapon squelches ]
Fuck, Tuck!
[ Barking ]
[ Snarling ]
[ Dog whimpers ]
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
Oh, God. What did
you do to him?
[ Door slams ] Moses! Moses!
♪
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Music fades ]
♪
Zeph.
I'm right here.
I have fucked up the rescue.
You almost stuck it.
Hm.
Some hero I turned out to be.
Coming to find me
is hero enough.
Don't suppose you got
through to the cops?
I didn't get to
say where we were.
[ Boat engines powering down ]
Why are we stopping?
[ Breathing heavily ]
That bad, huh?
Why'd you do a
runner that morning?
I told you. Early
bird gets the barrel.
Bullshit.
Tell me you didn't feel it.
I'm just better off alone.
No one's better off alone.
That's just
something people say.
No. It's not.
You don't know
me. You don't...
I know you.
I know you dig Creedence.
I know you're...
in the Guinness Book of Records
for the most bread rolls
consumed in one day.
[ Chuckles ]
I know you're tough.
And I know you're really warm.
And funny.
I know...
No, I sense...
...that you haven't
had as much kindness
in your life as you deserve.
Stop.
That's why you ran.
Because...
...it's hard to trust when...
...all you know is
why you shouldn't.
M-Moses, I really don't have
the strength for this right now.
[ Door creaks ]
No, you can't!
I've decided to add a matinee.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Music fades ]
[ Metal creaking ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Gasping ]
Holy fuck. Who
the fuck is that?!
[ Groaning ]
-No!
-Aah! Ah!
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
No, he's not a tourist.
He drives his Mom's
Volvo, for fuck's sake.
He has money. Think about it.
They're never gonna
stop looking for him.
Don't be fucking stupid.
[ Machinery whirring ]
-No!
-[ Grunting ]
No!
Moses!
Help!
Aah!
Fucking help!
No!
[ Both screaming ]
Fuck! [ Groans ]
Wait!
[ Whirring stops ]
-[ Whimpering ]
Put me up instead.
-Zeph, no!
-Please!
H-He doesn't deserve this!
Aw, how romantic.
It's too bad I'm
more of a horror fan.
[ Whirring continues ]
Fuck! Fuck! Wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Stop! Fuck! [ Groaning ]
Fuck!
[ Whirring stops ]
Don't you fucking move!
Be as still as you possibly can.
[ Shouts ]
That's a bull shark.
Most culled shark in the ocean.
Serious anger issues.
[ Grunting ]
[ Groaning ]
♪
[ Exhales deeply ]
[ Machinery whirring ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Whirring stops ]
-No!
-[ Groaning ]
Fuck you!
Well, that oughta
ring the dinner bell.
[ Machinery whirring ]
Fuck!
[ Coughing, gasping ]
♪
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Sobbing ] Please,
don't do this.
[ Machinery whirring ]
[ Groaning ]
♪
Fuck yeah.
[ Groaning ]
♪
[ Whirring stops ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Helicopter blades
whirring distantly ]
[ Sighs ]
Brief intermission,
ladies and gentlemen.
♪
[ Whimpering ]
Moses?
♪
Where's that fuckin' chopper?
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
♪
Keep going.
Keep going. Keep going.
♪
[ Muffled groans ]
[ Groaning, panting ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
Fuck!
[ Breathing heavily ]
♪
Ugh...
[ Bone cracks ] [ Groans ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Door creaks ]
♪
Guessing he's not hungry.
[ Chuckles ]
Look, if it's any
consolation, you...
You weren't right
for each other.
You know, he's
soft and... gooey.
And you're hard.
You're hard as nails.
Like me.
I'm nothing like you.
Yeah, you are.
Yeah, you and me...
...we're sharks.
Solitary creatures.
♪
We fend for ourselves.
Yeah, I've got a feeling that
tonight's show is gonna be
fuckin' one for the ages.
[ Door slams ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Groaning ]
♪
[ Joints squelch ] [ Groans ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
♪
[ Groaning ]
[ Inhales sharply ]
[ Exhales ] Fuck.
[ Gentle music plays ]
♪
It's probably a good
thing you can't see this.
♪
[ Gags ] [ Bones crunch ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪
♪ Mommy Shark
[ Door creaks ]
♪
[ Grunts ]
[ Panting ]
[ Engines power up
] Oh, yes, yes, yes!
♪
[ Gasping ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Electricity zaps ]
[ Panting ]
[ Sobbing ] Oh, fuck,
fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
No. Fuck!
[ Gasping ]
♪
Oh!
[ Ominous music plays ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Flare fires ]
-[ Groans ]
♪
[ Glass shatters ]
[ Grunts ] [ Glass shatters ]
[ Banging ]
[ Grunting ]
♪
[ Banging ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Screams ]
♪
[ Both grunting ]
[ Panting ]
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
♪
[ Music intensifies ]
[ Music fades ]
♪
[ Gasps ]
[ Engines revving ]
♪
Help!
[ Gasping, groaning ]
[ Music playing softly ]
[ Muffled shouts ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
♪
[ Indistinct chatter, laughter ]
[ Muffled screams ]
♪
♪ For you are mine at last ♪
♪ For you are mine
♪ At last
♪
[ Music fades ]
[ Spits ]
[ Gasps ]
Zeph.
[ Ominous music plays ]
Oh, mate, you think you
don't want to watch...
But deep down... you do.
That's the thing
about us men, man.
We don't really know what's
inside until it pops out.
And once that happens, there's
really no stuffing it back in.
[ Gasps ]
Now, can either of you tell me
why the marlin is the sports
fisherman's fish of choice?
Anyone? I'll give you a hint.
It's not because of her size
and it's not because
of her beauty.
It's because of her... fight!
See, every fisherman
loves a good fight.
And you'll get a marlin
and you'll fuckin'
bring her right in there
and you'll get her
right up to the boat
and you'll think you've got her
and then fuckin'... zzzz!
She makes another run for it
and it's fucking
exhilarating, man.
You know?
But the thing the
fish doesn't realize
is that once that hook sets,
no matter how hard she runs,
doesn't matter how many times...
she's already in the boat.
And the game's rigged, you know?
'Cause it's life and
death for the fish.
But for the fishermen,
it's just an afternoon of
good old-fashioned fun.
♪
Fun can't last forever,
though, can it?
No, no.
No, sooner or later, the
marlin must meet her fate.
[ Water splashes ]
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
♪
Oh! [ Gasping ]
[ Shouting ]
Oh, I'd hoped this would
be one for the ages.
I was right.
♪
Fuck, she's gonna turn
those little arms and legs
into toothpicks.
Right! Places, please!
And...
action!
[ Machinery whirring ]
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, be calm.
Be calm.
-Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Stop!
[ Dramatic music plays ]
-[ Sobbing ]
♪
[ Camera beeps ]
[ Music builds ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪
Oi! Get!
Go on, get! It's
not your night.
♪
[ Music builds ]
[ Music fades ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Quiet ominous music plays ]
♪
Where are ya?
I know you're there, babe, or
the bull wouldn't have left.
♪
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Camera beeps ]
♪
You just won't quit,
will you, marlin?
Behind you!
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪
[ Breathing heavily ]
-Boo!
-[ Gasps ] Aah!
[ Gasps ]
♪
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Music softens ]
♪
Where are you, marlin?
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪
Ooby dooby, motherfucker.
[ Harpoon fires ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Water splashes ]
[ Gasping, coughing ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Gasping ]
♪
[ Breath echoing ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪
[ Music fades ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Wheezing ]
[ Music softens ]
♪
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Line snaps ] Aah!
Zeph!
[ Melancholy music plays ]
♪
[ Dance music
playing distantly ]
♪
[ Gasping ]
Moses? Hey.
Moses! [ Grunts ]
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Moses, wake up. Wake up.
Moses, please wake up.
Hey.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪
[ Flare pops ]
Help!
Help! Help!
[ Ship horn blows ]
[ Horn blows ]
Moses! Hey, hey, Mo, wake up.
Moses, wake up.
Help is on the way.
Hey. Please wake up.
Please. Hey.
Hey, hey. Moses.
Hey, I want to
tell you something.
When I said there's
nothing for me on land?
There's you. Okay?
Please wake up.
Oh, my God.
I knew it.
[ Laughs ]
♪ Hey, baby, when
you jump over here ♪
♪ When you do the ooby-dooby
I want to be near ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby
♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby,
ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby
♪ Well, you wiggle to the
left, wiggle to the right ♪
♪ Do the ooby-dooby
with all of your might ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby
♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby,
ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Do-wah-do-wah-do-wah
♪ Well, you wiggle and you
shake like a big rattle snake ♪
♪ You do the ooby-dooby till
you think your heart'll break ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby
♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby,
ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Do-wah-do-wah-do-wah
♪
♪ Do-wah-do-wah-ah
♪ Do-wah-do-wah-do-wah-ah
♪ Ooby-dooby
♪
♪ Well, you'll be struttin'
'cause now you know ♪
♪ How to do the ooby-dooby,
now baby let's go! ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby
♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby,
ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Do-wah-do-wah-do-wah
♪ Hey, baby, jump over here
♪ When you do the
ooby-dooby I gotta be near ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby
♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby,
ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Do-wah-do-wah-do-wah
♪
♪ Don't walk up
close behind her ♪
♪ Don't whisper in her ear
♪ Don't think you
can outsmart her ♪
♪ For soon you'll disappear
♪ Be careful what you wish for
♪ Little fishies that you took
♪ There's blood
all in the water ♪
♪ And you just got the hook
♪ No man will ever own her
♪ She's dangerous
♪ The queen below the water
♪ Don't ever swim above her
♪ She's dangerous
♪ Don't say I didn't warn ya
♪
♪ Don't tread where
you not oughta ♪
♪ Don't curse away the sun
♪ Don't play the game
that brought ya ♪
♪ The sickness on the rain
♪ Don't sleep without
the darkness ♪
♪ Don't dream
without the light ♪
♪ The twisted mind inside ya
♪ Is bound to feel the bite
♪ No man will ever own her
♪ She's dangerous
♪ The queen below the water
♪ Don't ever swim above her
♪ She's dangerous
♪ Don't say I didn't warn ya
♪ No man will ever own her
♪ She's dangerous
♪ The queen below the water
♪ Don't ever swim above her
♪ She's dangerous
♪ Don't say I didn't warn ya
♪