Come away with me.
Where?
Home.
America?
You know I can't.
Your family will understand.
They can't expect you
to stay here forever.
We'll be fine on our own.
Promise.
I'll think about it.
You've got this.
♪ If that mockingbird
don't sing ♪
♪ Mama's gonna buy
you a diamond ring ♪
Sorry about that... hello?
Is anybody there?
Sorry.
No, it's fine.
I just didn't expect
anyone else to show up.
Is this the open house?
Yes, yes, it is.
I'm Natalie.
Am I too late?
Well, we're losing the
sun, but I think we
can squeeze in a quick look.
How'd you hear about us?
I saw a sign at the
end of the turnpike.
I always wonder if
people notice those.
So the house is two stories.
It's just under 14,000
square feet, including
the basement and attic.
It was built in 1890
and is registered
with the Historic
Preservation Society.
The original owners had this
added during Prohibition.
All of the original
features are still intact
and as you can see,
in pristine condition.
There have been
small renovations
in this room over the
years, but nothing major.
Have you been looking long?
There's still some
work to do down there,
but it has a lot of potential.
This is the master bedroom.
All of the furniture
is included.
What's the deal with the owners?
They died actually,
here on the property.
I don't know all the details,
but I was told they...
they were murdered.
It's almost like
they're still here.
Unable to leave.
I don't believe in
that kind of stuff.
Maybe you should.
No.
Maybe that's why no
one showed up today.
How... how did you know
no one showed up today?
It's getting pretty dark.
We should wrap this up.
Um, I have to get back.
I have a... a long drive.
Thank you for coming.
Freak.
What?
You gotta be kidding me.
Hello?
Is anyone there?
You know, I tried
calling earlier.
Nobody picked up.
That was you?
It's a cool place.
Yours?
No.
Trying to sell it.
My boss says it's unsellable.
Been in the market for years.
Yeah, why is that?
Just weird stuff.
Previous owners died.
Few other freak accidents
over the years after that.
I guess now people
think it's cursed.
Hey, were you messing around
with this before I got here?
No.
Why?
You got a stripped bolt here.
Could you excuse
me for a moment?
We're having a rough day, huh?
Make a deal with you.
You help me get
through the night,
I'll sing your favorite song.
See?
We'll be just fine on our own.
What's happening?
What the fuck?
To hell with this.
Sorry, I've been
really sensitive.
Guy?
There's a bathroom
right at the entrance.
Guy, are you in there?
Oh, my God.
Guy.
Guy?
Oh, my God.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on.
You.
What the fuck?
Come on.
What?
Motherfucker!
I know this place
better than you.
I know every corner
of this house,
every room, every hallway,
the creak of every floorboard.
I know every fucking
lie that's ever
been told inside these walls.
I also know something else.
I'm going to cut that baby
out of your fucking belly.
So let me in this fucking house!
Goddamn doors!
No.
Hello?
Someone's trying to kill me.
Yes.
1428 Craven Road.
Craven.
Yeah, yeah.
I think the baby...
it's coming.
Yeah, yeah.
1428.
Yeah.
Okay, okay, yes.
2-44, I have an adult female
in need of medical attention.
Roll EMS.
Hey, hey.
It's okay, it's okay.
Everything is okay.
Just try to breathe.
Subject appears to be in labor.
Requesting backup.
He's out back.
I'm on it.
Hey, hey, hey, okay.
Hey, listen.
What's your name?
Natalie.
Natalie, I'm Paul.
We've got to get
you to my car, okay?
Can you do that for me?
Okay, come on.
Okay, here we go.
Nice and easy.
I got you.
Come on.
2-44, I have no
visual on the suspect.
I'm going in.
You know who did this to you?
Stevens, come in.
Stevens, do you copy?
Look, just stay put.
I've got to go see what's
going on inside, all right?
Stevens!
Adam 244.
Officer down.
9-9-9!
I repeat, officer down.
Suspect is still at large.
Shh.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Hey, asshole.
What did you say you were
going to do to me and my baby?
Miss Flores?
Where am I?
County hospital.
You have a mild
concussion, and you
lost a fair amount of blood.
You should get some rest.
There's a man
upstairs an officer
would like you to
identify once you've
had some time to recover.
He's alive?
Is there anybody
you'd like us to call?
Any friends? Family?
No.
Where's my son?
Your son was found unresponsive.
What does that mean?
He didn't make it.
Miss Flores?
What?
Miss Flores, did you hear me?
Your son, he's in ICU,
under observation.
We're doing everything we can.
I want to see him, now.
Sorry, didn't see you.
Miss Flores, can you
confirm that this
is the man that attacked you?
Yeah, that's him.
He escaped a high security
psych ward 72 hours ago.
He burned them off.
Doctors say he
shouldn't be alive.
They can't make sense of it.
Who is he?
Officially, he's an
unidentified John Doe.
But if you ask him, his
name is Gabriel Marquez,
and he was born in
that house in 1929.
That's impossible.
That would mean he's...
He'd be 62 years old.
Yeah, I wouldn't place
him a day over 40 myself.
He's been obsessed with
that place forever.
They caught him squatting
there in the '80s.
So they had him arrested, tried
a few DNA tests over the years,
but nothing came up.
The orderly said
he was acting manic
a few days before the escape,
saying that the house was
calling to him or something.
Apparently, he thinks
that as long as the house
is still standing, so is he.
My guess, he was
on his way there.
He found you.
Could have been anyone.
Let's take you
back to your room.
It's remarkable being in labor
under those circumstances.
I don't know.
It was strange.
Something inside
me just took over.
I just found a way to push.
What is happening?
Hey, everything's okay, ma'am.
-I need to get my baby.
-Ma'am...
I need to get my baby.
Your baby is going to be fine.
-I need to get him...
-Just sit right here, okay?
Someone will come out
and take you outside.
No!