Hey, come on, I thought
we were gonna get high.
Yeah, we can get high later.
Jessica...
Jessica, what...
It's not funny.
Jesus Christ, Jessica,
what fucking size
shoe do you have?
Hey, come on.
Jess?
Oh, no, did you
get high already?
Run...
Aah!
What the fu...
♪ I ain't no joke I used
to let the mic smoke ♪
♪ Now I slam it when I'm done
♪ Make sure it's broke When
I'm gone no one gets on ♪
♪ 'Cause I won't let
♪ Nobody press up and
mess up the scene I set ♪
♪ I like to stand in a crowd
♪ And watch the
people, wonder "Damn" ♪
♪ But think about it
Then ya understand ♪
♪ I'm just an addict
addicted to music ♪
♪ Maybe it's a habit
I gotta use it ♪
♪ Even if it's jazz
or the quiet storm ♪
♪ I hook a beat up Convert
it into hip-hop form ♪
♪ Write a rhyme in graffiti
♪ And every show you see me in
♪ Deep concentration
♪ 'Cause I'm no comedian
Oh, please God, Dad,
no more '80s rap.
-It's dope.
-You do realize
that the '80s are
as far away from me
as the '40s were to you, right?
What? That is not true.
Do the math.
Shit.
Oh, well, uh, we're here.
Wow.
It's, uh...
It's big.
The town's previous
doctor used to live here
before he moved away.
You sure he didn't die in here?
Yeah, it doesn't...
smell great.
I think we'll just crack
a window, it'll be fine.
There's... no cell service.
What?
No, no, no, that's not...
I told them.
Come on.
Did you even look at this place
before you bought it, Dad?
I...
Okay, Quinn, look,
I wasn't in town for
a very long, they...
Careful.
Fuck!
Good to go, Doc.
Just get that chimney capped.
Okay, yeah, great. Thank you.
♪ Hey!
♪ There's something
in the way ♪
♪ Oh!
♪ It's just me and my brain
♪ Look!
♪ There's an elephant
in the room ♪
♪ And I'll write
the perfect song ♪
♪ For the perfect day
M... morning, Dad.
Uh, hey, morning, Quinn.
Are you good?
Hmm?
Yeah. I'm-I'm great.
How are you?
Oh, uh, yeah.
Good.
We're gonna be okay.
Are you sure?
Yeah, are you kidding
me? Look at this place.
It looks like a home
makeover dream come true.
Hey, it's your first day,
let me drive you to school.
Dad, I am 17 years old.
I don't need a
ride, I need a car.
I hear you, absolutely,
but in the meantime...
I'm just going to walk.
Okay.
Uh, sorry about breakfast.
I'll, um, I'll get
groceries after work.
Okay, do you think Wi-Fi
might be more important?
Yes, I hear you.
I will get on that.
Have a great day at school.
Make new friends.
-Not a chance.
Oh, hi.
Sorry, didn't mean to scare ya.
I saw you were new to the
neighborhood, and I...
Ow! Uh, sorry.
Hey, uh, is
everything all right?
Oh, yeah.
Sorry, it's just a neighbor.
Ruston Vance,
but everyone around here
just calls me "Rust."
Oh, I'm Dr. Maybrook.
This is my daughter, Quinn.
Uh, she's about to
head off to school.
Do you want to walk her?
That's exactly
why I'm here, sir.
Okay, cool. Let's do it.
So, what do you guys
do around here for fun?
Oh, um,
I might not be the
best person to ask.
I mean, the hunting
and fishing's good,
if you like that sort of thing.
Ducks are in season.
Shit.
What?
The look on your face.
I...
I guess I'm not doing
any good for stereotypes.
Oh, no.
Not everyone's a redneck here.
I just don't really care
what other people think...
Unlike some people.
So I guess I'll see you around.
It was nice meeting you, Quinn.
Yeah, thanks, dude.
Oh, and, uh,
be careful who
you hang out with.
There's some real
weirdos at this school.
Okey-dokey, Rust.
Thank you.
I will keep an eye out for 'em.
Just because it's
Founder's Day tomorrow
doesn't mean that there
won't be a test on Monday.
Listen, you kids
are spoiled rotten.
Back when I was in school,
we had it a lot
tougher than you do.
Hi.
Sorry, I'm...
Late.
Take a seat.
Okay.
As I was saying,
you kids are graduating
this year, and...
I'm graduating?
Sick, man.
Assuming you manage
to land a job,
which for some of you,
might be a long shot,
what do you think happens on
Monday morning every week?
You go to work,
and work is neither
easy nor fun.
In fact, sometimes it can
be downright miserable.
Okay, this is not funny.
Who did this?
Nobody.
All right.
Well, clear your desks.
We'll do the test now.
Brought this on yourselves.
It's time your generation
learned some consequences.
Uh, Mr. Vern, that's not
fair to the new girl.
Well, that's the
price of being late.
Oh, they put the wrong room
number on my schedule, so...
You know what?
Detention for you.
What?
Anyone else?
Come on, chill, she didn't
actually do anything.
Oh, well, then you
can console her
this afternoon, Mr. Hill.
In detention.
-Really?
-Mm.
Wow, you're on fire
today, Mr. Vern.
Try me. Anyone else?
What is so funny?
This isn't the test, Mr. Vern.
Of course it's the test.
Actually, I think it's
your dating profile.
If one of these
leaves this room,
you will all be suspended.
I will end you!
Okay, he is actually
losing his mind.
...participation
trophy generation...
Already 3,000 views.
Wow, his meltdown is a hit.
Man, I'm still trying to
figure out what I did.
Ugh, he's just a bitter old man.
He hates us,
and so we hate him
back, only more.
It's fun.
I'm Janet, by the way,
and that's Ronnie,
Tucker, Matt, and...
I'm Cole.
I'm Quinn.
Where are you from?
Philly, actually.
-Philly.
-Yeah.
My dad got put in Witness
Protection Program,
so we're just laying
low for a little while.
I'm kidding, obviously.
So, is Kettle Springs
everything you
expected it to be?
Man, it looks like
it's stuck in the '90s.
It still is the '90s
for everyone over 30.
Yeah, they're really big
on tradition around here.
Yeah, Founder's Day, right?
I keep seeing
that, what is that?
That is a stupid holiday
my family invented
to celebrate corn.
His dad is the local oligarch.
My great-grandfather
invented Baypen corn syrup,
like, a hundred years ago.
Whoa.
Every year, there's this parade
where everyone gathers
around a Frendo float
and worships him.
Frendo?
He's the clown on all
the Baypen labels.
He's practically a local legend.
Which is why we turned him
into a serial killer...
On our YouTube channel.
65,000 subscribers.
No shit?
Do you wanna see
some of our work?
Hell, yeah.
I work the night shift
here at the Baypen factory.
The power just went out,
and I swear I just
heard someone laughing.
There shouldn't be anyone here.
Okay, hang on.
Did you just hear that?
No, no, no, I gotta
get the power back on.
Okay.
Aah, shit, it's Frendo!
God, look at these prices.
It's $10 for a Salisbury steak
and a free side.
Think you can get off
your phone, Quinn?
Hmm? Yeah.
You missing your friends?
Mm-hmm.
That why you were
acting out today?
School called.
Detention on your first
day is not really like you.
Dad, the teacher
was a total dick.
Okay.
You all ready to order?
Yeah, no, actually, um,
I would love just one more
second with this menu.
It's my first time here.
Aw, take all the
time you need, Doc.
Thank you.
Can you please try and be a
little bit more respectful?
This is like the
only place in town.
What?
Tell me there's at least
a grocery store, right?
Mm-hmm, yeah, yeah, I just,
I didn't get a chance to go yet
because the cable guy was late.
Does that mean we have Wi-Fi?
You're welcome.
Oh, ho, ho, ho,
who is this person?
Have you seen my daughter?
She's like... she's
like about your height.
I think she's a little
taller than that.
Hi, George. Usual?
Hey, would you mind
putting some extra cheese
on that potato tonight, Trudy?
Oh, you got it, darlin'.
Thank you, doll.
Hey!
You must be the new doc.
Dr. Maybrook.
Yes, sir. Call me Glenn.
Hey, Sheriff Dunne.
Hi. This is my daughter, Quinn.
Nice to meet you, sweetheart.
I saw that new sign
on your practice.
When are you all fittin'
to take new patients?
Oh, uh, yeah, I'm gonna
start tomorrow morning.
Oh, okay.
Well, I might be first in line.
Got a plantar's wart
the size of Texas.
I tell you what,
folks around here
have been hurting
ever since that
factory burned down.
It's been a real mess, yeah.
Sheriff...
Sorry about that, Doc.
Been having some problems with
our local teenagers lately.
I recommend you stay away
from that crowd, sweetheart.
Yeah.
Thank you, that's
some good advice.
Uh, do you want to
join us, Sheriff?
Oh, that's mighty kind of
you. Don't mind if I do.
All right.
What are you doing?
Come on, okay?
Um, I actually just realized
I'm not that hungry.
You don't have to...
You sure about that?
I tell you what,
Kettle Burger's the
best you'll ever have.
I guarantee it.
I bet.
I don't really eat anything
with a face right now, though.
Yeah, she's...
she's a vegetarian.
Oh, yeah.
Well, her generation's
gotta save the world
one cow at a time, right?
Okay,
you guys have a
really good time.
I'm gonna...
Okay, but Quinn...
I'll see you at home, Dad.
You don't have to...
Hey, gotta let 'em
go someday, Doc.
Oh, look who's coming.
That was quick.
Yeah, I was about to
assault an officer.
Oh, Minnie Mouse is so tough.
I bet Sheriff Dunne
was trembling.
I mean, you should try
and avoid Sheriff Dunne.
That guy's got it out for us.
Hey, you don't have a
fake ID, do you, New Girl?
Oh, yeah, actually, I do.
Uh, it's just in some
boxes back at my house.
Bullshit.
Guys, we don't need fake IDs.
I got my guns.
These guns.
Oh, my God, you
are such a loser.
I'm pretty sure your guns
aren't going to get us drunk.
Speak for yourself.
My god, guys, chill.
Matty and I got this.
Watch and learn, boys and girls.
Watch and learn.
That's no way to treat money!
-Where are you from?
-Hmm?
Oh, I'm from the East Coast.
East Coast?
Damn, that's very far.
My grandmother?
Really? My grandmother?
How could you?
Look, sorry, I've got
a thing for old ladies.
Oh, really?
Can't blame a brother.
Hey, hey, stop that!
Dude plowed my grandma Gladys.
It's not like that, Matty.
It was magical. I'm in love.
-Oh yeah?
-Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
You gotta take this
and your grandma-loving
asses outside!
And... it's a miracle,
but she's pregnant.
What?
And I'm going to marry her.
You think you can
fuck my grandma?!
I'm going to be your
granddaddy, buddy!
No!
Come on, man, let's go!
Come on!
To Otis!
The best damn store clerk
Kettle Springs could
ever ask for...
and to Matt's sexy
grandmother Gladys.
Yes!
-To Grandma Gladys!
-Oh, my god.
-Oh, man. Ew!
Ronnie,
you couldn't have stole
anything better than this?
It was the first
thing I grabbed.
For the record,
I paid for at least
twice of what we stole.
Oh, Cole, you're so amazing.
Man, he thought
that the East Coast
was somewhere real far away.
Did you hear him say that?
I mean, it kind of is.
Both coasts are.
They call us "flyover country."
Oh, fuck that.
Yeah, man, people don't
know what they're missing.
This place is like paradise.
Ow, ow, ow!
-Hey, baby?
-Yeah.
I gotta go piss.
-Classy as always, Matt.
-Thanks, man.
Hey, uh, don't roofie
my drink when I'm gone.
No guarantees.
So, uh,
the sheriff was saying
that the factory
burnt down recently?
Uh... yeah.
We, um,
we filmed one of
our videos in there.
We snuck in.
We shouldn't have, I know,
but we didn't actually
start the fire.
Who did?
Nobody.
Faulty wiring.
Official conclusion.
But it's too big a coincidence,
so nobody believes that.
Including us.
What, you think
someone set you up?
Okay, what in the fuck was that?
Quinn! Quinn!
It's-it's not... It's...
Smile, Philly girl.
You're about to become
a YouTube sensation.
We got you good.
I can't believe
she fell for that.
You guys are fucking
idiots, you know that?
You guys are all idiots.
Welcome to the club.
You must be counting the days
till you can get out of here.
-No.
-No?
-No...
-Bullshit.
Yes, I literally have
a calendar in my room,
and I'm, like,
X-ing off the days.
I'm not even kidding.
It's not a joke.
It's so sad, just
this, like, red marker.
So, what comes next, then?
Just... just off to college?
Uh, yeah.
What about you?
No.
I got big plans for this town.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Like what?
Burning it all to
the fucking ground.
I guess you're halfway there.
So, what, it's just
you and your dad here?
Yeah.
My mom died of an
overdose over the summer.
So yeah, it's just us.
Fuck.
-It's okay...
-I'm so sorry.
It's okay, no, no, no.
I... my dad had,
like, a breakdown
and couldn't go back to the ER.
Um, so...
I guess Kettle Springs
just had an opening
for a family doctor, and, um...
here we are.
My younger sister
died last summer, too.
We used to hang out at this
reservoir all the time,
and...
she wanted to jump off
the cliff into the water.
She just didn't jump far enough.
Uh, I'm sorry, am I
interrupting something?
Because we have a
fucking video to finish.
Okay.
♪ If I look fine
♪ That's how you know I'm not
♪ Slips through my fingers
Everything I've got ♪
Well, tonight was
totally unexpected.
Yeah.
Total surprise.
In like a good
way, though, right?
Yeah, in a good way.
Okay, cool.
Thanks for listening
to all my shit.
Yeah, same.
♪ If I look fine
♪ That's how you
know I'm not ♪
-Shit! Fuck...
-Hey, Quinn,
What the hell? You
know what time it is?
Sorry. Sorry,
sorry, sorry, sorry.
We were out, and I
lost track of time.
What? Oh, and you've
been drinking.
Who are you?
Uh, Cole Hill, sir.
Uh, don't worry, I'm
totally okay to drive.
I had two drinks in four hours.
Yeah, that's two too many
for somebody your age.
Okay, but realistically,
everyone drinks in high school.
That being said, it
will never happen again.
Yeah, it won't,
because you won't be seeing
my daughter ever again.
Dad, stop.
Go home now.
Go home!
Dad, can you stop?
Oh, my god...
Fuck.
It's not my fault the
cell reception sucks here.
You cannot run away
without telling me
where you're going.
What, like how you just ran off
and moved us to the
middle of nowhere
without asking me about it?
I asked you.
Yeah, and I said I
didn't want to go.
Quinn, that's not fair.
I asked you, and you said
that you'd be willing to go
if it's what I needed, right?
Exactly, exactly. If
it's what you needed.
It never actually
mattered what I wanted.
That's... how
can you say that?
Of course it matters.
That's why I asked you
in the first place...
-No, it isn't.
No, it never mattered
what I wanted,
because you fucking ran away.
We ran away,
because I guess
that's what we do now.
We just run away
when things get hard,
or scary,
or fucked up,
and I don't want to run anymore.
I just want to be okay!
Huh.
What in the fuck was that?
What the fuck?
No way...
Cole.
It's payback time already, huh?
Never prank the prankster.
All right, game on.
Motherfuck.
Okay, guys, not cool.
Matt...
Shit.
Cole?
Come on, man, I can hear you.
Gotcha!
Matt, I swear to God.
Okay.
Okay, nice touch with
the plastic sheeting.
I like it.
Fuck.
What the hell?
Okay, y'all stepping
it up with this one.
Try this on and pray it fits,
because it's the last one.
What is going on with this?
It fit perfect last year.
This was my favorite
damn jacket.
You must have washed
it or something.
Don't blame the dry cleaners.
You need to lay
off that junk food.
Junk... What?
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
To the parade?
Not after detention, you're not.
Dad, the whole
class got detention.
I didn't even do anything wrong.
Mr. Vern just hates us.
Well, did you know
that Mr. Vern's brother
committed suicide last month
when he lost his
job at the factory?
I'm sorry, I didn't know that.
Oh, okay.
That's not my fault.
It's not your...
It's not his fault.
You know, you've got to start
taking some responsibility.
It's nobody's fault, baby.
Sometimes things just happen.
What are you doing?
Go on, now.
Happy Founder's Day.
I would like to welcome you all
to the 100th annual
Kettle Springs
Founder's Day Parade!
A hundred!
Today we celebrate
things that bring us together,
things that keep us together,
like tradition.
Yeah.
Like hard work...
Like good old small-town values!
Frendo!
-Hey!
-Hey.
You guys figure out who
that mystery Frendo is yet?
No, but we were thinking
it might be Rust.
He and Cole used to be friends.
Yeah, that guy.
He's, um...
a little off.
Uh, he's very off.
Yo, you guys seen
Tucker anywhere?
No, he's being a text bitch.
Okay, screw Tucker.
We're doing another video.
Really? Here?
Shut up, it's
gonna be hilarious,
isn't it, Ronnie?
Totally hilarious.
Okay, you guys
get the wide shot.
We're going to get
cutaways over there.
Yeah?
Okay, let's go.
-We'll get cutaways.
Okay.
-Hey.
Oh...
hop on my shoulders.
You want me to do it?
Come on, let's go.
Okay.
So...
I kind of throw this
party every year
after the parade.
Yeah?
Any chance your dad will
let me take you with me?
Oh, less than zero percent.
Awesome.
I'll pick you up at 10:00.
Yo, yo, yo!
Ha ha!
No fucking way.
-Hey!
-Shit!
Bozo, what do you
think you're doing?
No, no, no!
No! Shit!
Sorry, man!
Fuck.
What's going on?
Cole?
Who the hell is
responsible for this?
I think we should
get out of here.
Oh, yeah.
Guys, what the fuck?
Did you guys see that?
What the hell was that?
That was insane, right?
-You did this!
No, no, sir, I-I
didn't do anything.
Oh, the hell you didn't.
You probably already
put it on the Internet.
What...
We literally didn't do anything.
You sabotaged Founder's Day.
Now sit in here and stew on it.
Uh, Cole will call his dad.
Good luck with that.
I can't believe this
is actually happening.
17 years old,
and I've already
hit rock bottom.
He can't actually hold us here
without charging us, right?
This feels illegal.
You think he gives a
shit about what's legal?
This is how it works
in Kettle Springs.
I am so dead.
Yeah,
you are dead.
Never fuck with Frendo.
All right, you're free to go.
Not you, Daryl.
Aw...
Dad...
-What the hell, Quinn?
-I know.
I told you to stay
away from the Hill boy.
He didn't do anything.
The fucking sheriff
has it out to get him.
Yeah, maybe because he
burned down the factory
that employed half the town...
-No. No, no,
that was not his fault.
That was an electrical issue.
It was a wire that...
-Oh, he tell you that?
No, they did a
full investigation.
He's not a liar, Dad.
He's not even a bad guy.
He's actually a really good guy.
Wait, you've known
him for two days,
you end up in
detention and now jail.
Because the teacher
is a f... asshole.
-Oh, okay.
-But...
And so is the sheriff, Dad.
-Sure.
There is something fucked up
about the old
people in this town.
So it's everybody else's fault.
You know what?
You need to face consequences
for your actions.
You're grounded
until further notice.
No, no, no, no, I...
I am telling you, it was not...
Whose car is this, by the way?
-Yeah...
It was going to be a
surprise, but fat chance now.
Seriously?
Fuck.
I don't even know
how to drive stick.
Yeah, I know you don't.
It was supposed to be
like a bonding thing.
So you could experience
all the joy and trauma
of my generation.
Yeah, maybe some
other time, Dad.
Yeah.
I'm trying, Quinn.
One...
Two...
Three.
Yeah, six.
♪ Lean in, I do what
I want and I won't ♪
♪ Backbeat, I'm free Drop
a knee for your soldier ♪
♪ Breathe in, I do what I want
♪ And I'm gonna do you
Seriously, guys?
Tucks?
Check this out, Tucker,
wherever you went.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five!
Tucker, you asshole, man.
Take it.
Take it, I'm spent.
Okay, yeah, very
funny, motherfucker.
You fucking psycho!
God!
♪ Creepers left and
right Buzz like crazy ♪
♪ Everybody's trying
to steal my lady ♪
♪ Spot us in the mirror and
think this can't be right ♪
♪ Back to the scene
of a Friday night ♪
♪ To a blessed collision
still froze in time ♪
I can't believe we're
doing this right now.
My dad is actually
going to kill me.
No.
He's actually going to kill me.
He's not going to find out,
and even if he does,
I've already got a
sober ride home planned,
so at least he'll know
you were disobeying
him responsibly.
Responsibly, okay.
-Responsibly. Yes.
-That's very reassuring.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What? What is that?
That is what I
wanted to show you.
Isn't it cool?
Some Baypen schwag for ya.
Yeah, it is really cool.
Where did you get it from?
Oh, they have that kind
of stuff all over town.
Yeah?
Like your psycho Frendo costume?
Where'd you get that?
I'm OG Kettle Springs, baby.
I got all kinds of stuff.
Does it work?
Try it.
Look out!
Fuck...
Ruston?
What the hell, man?
It's Saturday night.
I fell asleep in the tree stand.
When I woke up, there he was.
You know, that's
barely a four-pointer.
It's a month of free dinner
while my pop's out of work.
Rust...
Quinn.
Uh, yeah, we met, actually.
Hi again. Quinn.
Uh, Rust and I used to,
uh, go hunting together.
Well, we're heading
to the hoedown.
I'd tell you to come join us,
but it looks like you
gotta go beat your meat.
Hey, did you tell Quinn
you used to practice
your boy-band dance moves
in the mirror?
Later, Rust.
Be careful, Quinn.
Come on.
So what do I got to do
to see some of
these dance moves?
Look, all I'm saying
is don't challenge
me to a dance-off.
Challenge accepted.
You're a big talker. I like it.
Are you sure the owners are
okay with us being here?
Oh, no, we're fully trespassing.
-So if we get arrested again...
-We won't.
Don't worry, we do
this every year.
Do you promise?
Absolutely.
You are totally safe here, okay?
Trust me.
Hell, yeah.
♪ Ooh yeah, like me
♪ Like me, ooh yeah, like me
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
♪ Say that then unless
you wanna move along ♪
Oh, hey, you guys made it!
Shots?
All right.
♪ Ayy, ayy, ayy, ayy,
ayy Shawty get loose ♪
♪ Tired of talkin'
Oh, my god, what is in that?
That's moonshine, I think.
Oh, look, it's Cole and
his shiny new plaything.
Shut up.
Where the hell are
Matt and Tucker?
Well, Matt was
supposed to pick us up,
but he just never showed.
He still hasn't texted me back.
I'm so fucking mad at him.
Same with Tucker.
It's weird, right?
They're planning something
again, aren't they?
I was just thinking
the exact same thing.
Be on guard, peeps.
Yo, yo, yo, y'all
having a good time?
Welcome to the Founder's
Day Barn Rave, baby!
Now, let me take a second
to thank my main man,
the one who paid
for all this shit,
the junior founder himself,
and the future of
Kettle Springs...
Cole Hill!
Give me a sec.
Look, I'm only going to
say a couple things here
before we get to the
real festivities.
Hell, yeah!
I know my great-grandfather
founded this town,
but let's be honest,
we're the future here, right?
-Whoo!
-Yeah!
So let's not subscribe to
some backwards-ass belief
of what this town used to be,
and instead think ahead
and dream up what comes next,
and let's have a
good fucking time!
♪ Driving with a
yellow dog I95 ♪
♪ He's got a smile on his
face and big shiny eyes ♪
♪ Up at a decent
hour never ate yet ♪
♪ Got a little Johnny Cash
in the ol' tape deck ♪
♪ Nothing in the trunk
but some baseball gloves ♪
♪ A pair of jumper cables
and a set of golf clubs ♪
♪ Blanket on the back seat
we're in rough shape ♪
Yes! Yes! Yes!
♪ Lookin' for a gas station
better make a list ♪
♪ Fill 'er up with regular
I need to take a piss ♪
♪ Sexy girl air freshener
Snacks and that pinwheel ♪
♪ Top up the fluids, clean
the bugs off the windshield ♪
♪ Not a care in the world
Not a how, when, and why ♪
♪ No destination Not
a cloud in the sky ♪
♪ Back on the road not
a moment too soon ♪
♪ Dish ran away with
some other spoon ♪
♪ Wicked and weird
♪ I'm a road hog
with an old dog ♪
♪ Singing slow songs
tryin' to hold on ♪
♪ Wicked and weird
♪ I'm a rat fish
Tryin' to practice ♪
♪ Doin' back flips
on your mattress ♪
♪ Wicked and weird
♪ I'm a road hog
with an old dog ♪
♪ Singing slow songs,
tryin' to hold on ♪
Like, you're just
not good at dancing.
Hey.
♪ Agitated, exasperated
♪ Why you look so mad
when the woman's elated? ♪
♪ Yeah, wipe that
look off your face ♪
♪ When you see a girl come
through in first place ♪
♪ Know that she bad 'cause
she worked through the hate ♪
♪ Too bad I'm the boss I'm
the one you can't play ♪
♪ Won't let you win and
you can't complain ♪
♪ No, sir, no, sir
We're not the same ♪
♪ I'm a real leader
Maybe we should slow down a bit.
Oh, you like slow kisses?
♪ Transistor sister
I play on the radio ♪
♪ Watching me 'cause
I do it with ease ♪
♪ If you can't catch up
you will feel my breeze ♪
♪ In our house we
increased them fees ♪
♪ 'Cause with my squad
it's guaranteed ♪
Slower.
Do you mean slow like this?
♪ Try all you want
You can't imitate ♪
♪ I'm a heavyweight
I mean, like, slow we...
we get another beer slow.
Oh, my god.
I'm so sorry.
Uh, no, I... Quinn, I'm sorry.
I feel so fucking stupid.
No, Quinn, Quinn, stop.
Quinn!
I have so much shit going
on inside of me right now,
and-and sometimes I...
I just don't know what
to do with all of it.
Yeah...
I can see that.
You figure that out
and get back to me.
Hey, new girl!
You get rejected yet?
Cole rejects everybody.
You could have told
me that, Janet.
You're a sucker, Quinn.
He sucked you into
his little web
so he could feed on
your naive little mind.
Oh!
Oh, you bitch!
You guys! You guys, stop!
Hey, Ginger,
you okay?
Stop!
Matt and Tucker, remember?
This time, you
don't fall for it.
Oh, my god.
Aw, Ginger,
did you die?
That is so sad.
Sucks to die so young.
Aw...
This is pretty pathetic.
I know, right?
Oh, my god, guys!
They made a plaster
cast of Matt's head.
Ronnie, think fast.
You bitch!
You got corn syrup
all over my new top.
Aw, baby, you look so sad.
Did you get a little
owie on your neck?
You guys...
Guys...
I can't find her pulse.
She's fucking dead.
Hey, check it out! It's Frendo!
Run!
Janet!
-Thanks.
-Yeah.
Run! Run!
Sorry!
Open the door!
Around the back!
Please don't.
Duck!
Holy shit.
Thank you.
Where's Cole?
I don't know. I
was just with him.
I don't know.
Did anybody call 911?
You can't.
It's a total dead zone.
Somebody drive
back to town, then!
He slashed everyone's tires
and pulled the batteries.
Take his mask off.
Holy fucking shit.
That's a lot of Frendos!
Get up!
You gotta get up!
Where were you?
I was looking for you. Come on!
Fuck!
Come on! We gotta get inside!
Come on, come on! Move!
Quinn?
You asleep already?
Um, listen, I just wanted to say
that I know how hard
this must be for you,
and I can't imagine what
you're going through...
Damn it.
Fucking teenagers!
I'm not getting any signal.
They're surrounding us.
We got you surrounded!
There's fucking
clowns everywhere.
There's no way out!
Rust, not that I'm
complaining or anything,
but do you bring
a loaded shotgun
to every party?
It's always in my truck,
locked.
That's why they didn't get it.
Those clowns hate us.
Ronnie, we're safe for
now. It's a steel door.
It's over.
We're all gonna be
headless teenagers
without heads!
Ronnie, Ronnie, you
need to calm down, okay?
Look at me. Breathe.
We're gonna kill you!
Who the fuck are they?
Why are they doing this?
And why is it only us?
Never fuck with Frendo.
We gotta go. We gotta
get out of here.
She's right. We
can't stay here.
What about the
Tillersons' house?
We can use their landline
to call for help.
That's like a mile
through a cornfield
in the fucking dark.
How many shells you got left?
Three.
You know, I never
thought I'd say this,
but I'm glad you're such
a fucking redneck, Rust.
Aw, thanks, man.
I love you, too.
What the hell, man?
What are you doing?
What? I got him!
Yeah, and you wasted
two shells doing it!
Now we only have one
left to get out of here!
Oh, my God,
can you stop being
so fucking stupid?
No, you know what?
You're stupid,
because you threw away
everything we had,
for what?
No, no, we never had anything.
Oh, bullshit.
Oh...
Why can't you just
admit who you are
for once in your fucking life?
Because I don't fucking know!
Fuck!
You guys?
There's a hole in
the ground over here.
Yes...
It's a drainage ditch.
Drainage for what?
You don't want to know.
Hey, I am not crawling
through a shit pipe.
I'm gonna kill you!
Never mind! Let's go.
Guys, they have us surrounded.
If we try and crawl out of here,
they'll just
Whac-A-Mole us to death.
Not if we distract them.
Driving around
looking for you now.
It's not a big town.
It's only a matter of time.
I'm not mad, Quinn.
Just please call me back.
Hello?
I don't have any drugs here,
if that's what you want.
Move.
Don't look. Keep going.
Okay, okay, okay.
What is happening?
Save him, or your daughter dies.
Where-where is she?
You'll find out.
First, you've got work to do.
Okay, okay.
Let's hope this works.
I can't do it! I can't!
Shut up, Ronnie! Go!
You owe me a new
outfit after this.
Not the time, Janet.
-Don't be long.
-Try and hold your breath.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah, man. You know I
love blowing shit up.
Here, take this. There's
on one shot left.
Rust, like...
I'm really sorry about...
-Tell me about it later!
I'll be right behind you.
Go. Go!
Fuck!
Oh, I hate my life,
I hate my life, I hate my life.
Oh, my god...
Move your butt, Ronnie.
Oh, geez.
Rust...
W-we have to go get him.
We can't. We have
to go for help.
We have one bullet.
One bullet.
Save it.
We have to go to the
Tillersons' house.
What, through the cornfield?
What choice do we have?
Cole!
Aw, hell!
Go, go, go!
He's having trouble breathing.
Let me just...
-I said leave it on.
Who are you people?
Did I say you could talk?
K4, you there?
We got more incoming.
Roger that. Send 'em
down. Doc's here.
Copy!
I need more saline.
What?
He's in shock.
He's going to die if he
doesn't get more fluids.
I need more saline.
Well, why don't you get some?
'Cause I'm in the
middle of an operation.
Fine. Where is it?
In the cabinet behind you.
Where?
Um, it's in the bottom drawer.
Come on, come on, come on...
Here.
Sorry about tonight, Quinn.
Oh, it's okay.
Don't worry about it.
You know, except for the clowns
trying to kill us and all.
That kind of sucks.
Ow!
This corn hurts.
Shut up, Ronnie.
I can't shut up.
Fuck, it's like we're in
some awful '80s slasher
horror movie in the corn.
Which means what, exactly?
It means I'm next.
Okay, stop it!
Guys, there's the road.
There's a car coming.
Come on.
-Let's go.
Hey, hey!
-Hey, wait!
-Hey!
Oh, shit.
Please tell me that isn't
the fucking sheriff.
Put the gun down.
Sir? Sir, I... I
know this looks bad,
but this isn't mine.
Put the gun down now,
and back away.
Okay.
Sheriff, you don't understand.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we
were attacked by clowns!
All right,
I've had about enough
of you, thanks.
It-it-it... This
wasn't me, okay?
Whoa, whoa, what?
No, no, no.
Quinn, no.
-Wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no.
Sheriff, you don't understand.
There's a massacre going on.
There's a bunch of
dead people back there.
Anything you say
can and will be used against you
in a court of law.
What is happening?
Why is everyone so fucking mean?
Hey!
Watch your language, girlie.
This is not a joke.
There's a bunch of psychos
dressed up like Frendo
who are trying to kill us!
Oh, my god.
Oh, that's my bad.
All right, okay,
y'all are making
one of your little
goofy Internet videos?
Is that what's happening?
Your little dirtbag
friends out there
filming me from the cornfield?
Is that right?
There's no camera, you idiot!
We're in a bunch of
danger right now!
Shut up, you're the one
who's in a bunch
of danger, homeboy.
-Wait, wait, wait!
-It's real, Sheriff.
I swear to God.
They have chainsaws
and-and axes...
Yeah, and-and pitchforks,
and my boyfriend's head!
Y'all had a shotgun,
so what's your problem?
This is insane. This is...
What? This is insane. Why
won't you listen to us?
Wait, wait, wait, arrest me too!
Please just get me out of here.
Next time, toots.
Y'all have a pleasant
rest of your night.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, don't!
We need help! We need help!
How do we have the worst
sheriff in America?
What the hell?
Why did he only arrest Cole?
Okay, let's get to
the Tillersons' house.
We can call for help there.
How far is it?
Not far. Come on.
What? Wait, wait, wait, no.
I'm not going back in there!
I'm drawing the line, okay?
I'm drawing the line right here!
Oh, shit.
Wait!
What?
Run!
Wrong way!
Change of plans!
Shh. Shh.
We're gonna die.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my god!
Did you seriously just
ring the doorbell?
Well, do we just go in?
I think we're past the point
of pleasantries, Janet, yeah.
Do you see a phone?
Shh...
Is he dead?
Well, I don't think
he's meditating.
I think he's dead.
It's a phone!
Oh, my god.
Upstairs.
Let's go.
There it is!
Hello?
What?
Look... I think the ph...
I think the line is dead.
Okay, call 911.
Well, where's the button, Janet?
Uh, what is this?
What is this?
What the fuck kind
of phone is this?
Quinn...
Holy shit.
What is this?
This was a trap.
We gotta get out of here.
Oh, shit!
He was meditating!
Oh, shit, Janet!
Oh, god, is it bad?
Is it bad? I can't look.
Oh, my god, it's bad.
Oh, it's so bad, girl.
Fuck, stay still, stay still,
stay still, stay still...
I know, I know, I know!
Don't let me die,
don't let me die.
-No, no, no, no, no!
-I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry!
I hate you, Quinn.
Me too.
Oh, fuck.
Jeez...
Come on, hurry it up.
This is taking too long!
What happened?
He's flatlining.
Um, look, I need your help.
Me?
Yeah, yeah, you!
Come on, take it, take it!
What are you looking at me for?
Take 'em, take 'em, take
'em, take 'em, take 'em!
Come on, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Ready? One, two...
Fuck the Hippocratic oath!
You shouldn't have done that.
Sorry.
Um, you're going to want
to leave that in there.
I'm going to get some help.
No, no. What are you doing?
No, no. No, no, no, I just...
Ah...
Okay, that's...
Now you're gonna bleed out.
Yeah. See?
That's...
This is exactly
what I was saying.
Aah!
Don't say I didn't warn you.
It's all going wrong!
Goddamn it! We shouldn't
have done it like this!
This is not my fault!
The damn girl's tougher
than we thought!
Just get her
and bring her back to
the Baypen factory!
Oh, my God.
-We'll deal with her there.
-Roger that.
Damn it!
Goddamn it!
No, don't do this
to me right now.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, please don't do
this to me right now.
Aah!
Damn it!
When your dad wants to
teach you to drive stick,
you fucking say yes!
Who the hell are you people?
Aw.
Welcome to the main
event, sweetie pie.
My fucking face hurts.
Don't complain.
I gotta work in the morning.
Work? This is work.
This is the best damn
job I've ever had.
Better than my day job.
Yeah, you're a lot
fucking better at it, too.
Language, sweetheart.
Why are you doing this?
Because...
it's a Founder's Day tradition!
I mean, only when
necessary, of course.
You're Cole's dad.
No.
No, Cole's no son of mine.
I disowned him.
Oh, come on, please
just let me go.
No, no, no, no.
It's way too late
for that, toots.
I didn't do anything.
Shh.
You know, Kettle
Springs is a good town,
filled with good people, right?
Uh-huh.
That's right, it is.
Best of America...
what's left of it.
And keeping it that
way all these years
hasn't been easy.
It takes vigilance,
because every couple
of generations,
well, we get
ourselves a bad crop.
I'm not even from here.
Go ahead.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Now, listen.
In the '30s, Baypen
became the national brand.
It kept this town afloat, right?
Uh-huh. You can say that.
And then this big old
train full of hobos
just rolled on into town,
and they just didn't
want to leave.
No, and then we had some
hippies in the '60s.
They came in and
started a commune,
sold dope to kids,
and then, oh, in the '90s,
we all know what
kind of burnouts
those guys were, man.
But your generation,
with your...
your fucking preening and
your goddamn cat videos,
well, you guys might be
the worst of them all.
Cancer.
A scourge!
A blighted crop is what you are,
that needs to be culled!
Oh, Cole!
Cole!
Surprise!
What are you doing?
He's your son!
No, I told you, he isn't my son,
not since he killed
his own sister.
He didn't kill her.
-It was on his watch!
-She drowned!
He took everything from me,
everything that I cared about,
and then you burned down
the goddamn factory.
That was the last straw, Cole.
I just came to the realization
that my boy is just a bad seed,
and Daddy has to start all over.
Oh, my god, you're insane.
You're an insane person!
I'm just doing what my
daddy did before me,
and his daddy did before him.
Tradition.
You really think
you're going to be able
to get away with this?
Look.
Would you like to see
Cole's suicide note? Hmm?
It's going live on his
socials tomorrow morning.
Yup!
Another spoiled rich kid
that shoots up a party,
and then he kills the
girl that spurned him
right before he kills himself.
Affluenza's a bitch.
Yeah.
Yeah, I would say so.
So let's go.
Let's get this show on the road.
You're fucking
sick, you know that?
You just pretend to care.
You're so worried about
what's wrong with the kids,
when you guys are the ones
that fucked everything up!
You don't care about the Earth.
You don't care about
the next generation.
Well, guess what,
the world's going to change
whether you like it or not,
and I know that scares
the shit out of you...
because if you can't have things
the way that you want 'em,
you'd rather burn it all
to the fucking ground!
You'd rather kill
us than just listen.
Let's hear it for Cole.
That was beautiful.
That was beautiful!
You know what?
I'm gonna put that
into the suicide note.
I mean, I'm not going to put in
all the gory details and stuff,
but, um, you know,
I'll put a lot of it.
Jesus fucking Christ,
this is endless.
Can we get on with it, please?
Well, yes, sir.
Thank you.
Listen, sweetheart,
I'm really sorry.
I mean, I... I
tried to warn you,
but you didn't listen.
Dumb fuck!
Just like the rest of
your goddamn generation.
No! No!
Sheriff?
I'm okay, right?
Uh...
Dad!
Cole! Get Cole!
Run, Quinn.
Run!
Shit!
Dunne...
You go get her, I got Cole.
Hey, Doc...
Come on, come on, come on...
It's over, sweetheart.
Come on out, now. There
ain't nowhere to run.
Don't worry, I'll make it quick.
See, that's the problem
with your generation.
You all think
that you're smarter than us.
You got that right.
And I'm not your
fucking sweetheart.
You're going down,
no matter what.
The truth is going to
come out eventually.
Oh, you are too
dumb to be my son.
You tell people what
they want to believe,
and you can get
away with murder.
You started the
fire, didn't you?
For the fucking insurance money.
Business was bad.
You were losing money,
weren't you, Dad?
You burnt down the factory!
Now I take it back.
You're not as dumb as I thought.
Oh, fuck you.
I'll see you in hell, son.
Cole! Cole!
Oh, my God!
Stay there! Stay there!
Cole! Help!
Rust.
Cole!
You're alive, man.
See?
You always second-guess, man.
No, it's because you
smell like burnt flesh.
You don't smell so good either.
Oh, fuck it.
Such a confusing fucking night.
Quinn!
-Dad!
-Oh, Quinn.
Quinn, oh, my God.
-Dad.
Oh, thank god you're okay.
Are you... are you okay?
No, yeah, it's fine.
He just shot me once,
but it was on the
spleen side, so...
Oh, my god, that looks
really fucking bad.
No, it's okay. Hey, hey...
Promise me we'll learn
to talk things
through a bit better.
Yeah, I would like
that very much.
Okay, let's get out of here.
Okay, you don't have to...
Okay, okay, I'll be fine.
Come on. Come on...
So, what do you guys think
of Kettle Springs so far?
Uh... well, I haven't
really been here very long,
but I hear it's fucking
lovely in the spring.
-Quinn.
-Oh, sorry, Dad.
Language.
Guys?
Oh, shit.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
Yes.
There are keys.
Quick, get in!
Here we go. All right.
Shit.
Shit! It's another
stick shift, Dad.
I can't do it!
I can't do it.
Please take over...
Quinn, Quinn,
you got this.
Just here, just
push in the clutch.
It's that guy over there.
Slide it into first,
and give it a little bit of gas.
Oh, yup, there we go.
Okay, good, good. Now
let it out a little bit.
There you go. You're doing it.
Yeah, nice job, Quinn.
Guys, we got a problem!
We gotta go the other way.
No, we're done running.
Quinn...
fucking punch it!
Die, you motherfucking clown!
♪ I'm invincible
Just off principle ♪
♪ Irresistible
♪ Ever since the bull
♪ Showed his face round here
♪ I've been head down grinding
♪ The only time I look up
♪ Never lose horizons
♪ See it by force
♪ Open up your eyes
♪ While the others disguise
♪ Imma make 'em realize
You sure you don't
need me to drive you?
Nah.
You gotta stay back and
work on your campaign.
Plus, this way, I can
listen to my own music.
I can't believe how
grownup you are.
I hate it.
I love you so much.
I love you too, Dad.
You're tough as nails, Quinn.
Uh, excuse me.
I'm sorry, were you
really going to leave
without saying goodbye?
No.
I was going to
stop by your house
on the way out.
Right, yeah, well,
we couldn't wait.
Brought you something.
A gift.
Wow.
It's a 16-inch collapsible
self-defense baton.
Just like I always wanted.
Yeah.
Sorry, Dr. Maybrook, but, uh,
there's some crazies out there.
Completely understand.
This is really sweet, you guys.
I hope I don't have to use it
against a bunch
of killer clowns.
Us too,
but just in case.
I love you guys.
You be safe, okay?
Stay away from old people.
Uh, hey.
I mean old clowns
that want to kill you.
Right. That's good advice.
Love you. Bye!
♪ Ay! Tried to blame it
on the city that I love ♪
♪ I point the finger at
the people up above ♪
♪ But, oh, babe
You'll be okay ♪
♪ When you get lost in
your head some days ♪
♪ When life ain't
goin' your way ♪
♪ Keep it up, it up, it up
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah
♪ I ain't a fighter
♪ But you're never
takin' me alive ♪
♪ So if you're comin'
♪ Then you ought to
know it's suicide ♪
♪ You won't make me crawl
♪ When my back's to the wall
♪ Ain't taking me alive
♪ Won't bleed me out to dry
♪ I'll tell you
like I said before ♪
♪ I never asked to start a war
♪ But now you know
that I'd rather die ♪
♪ You won't take me alive
♪ Don't complicate it You
created your own misery ♪
♪ Won't be a victim
♪ I won't listen to
your mind's disease ♪
♪ No
♪ You want me to bleed
♪ I got an ace up my sleeve
♪ Ain't taking me alive
♪ Won't bleed me out to dry
♪ I'll tell you
like I said before ♪
♪ I never asked
to start a war ♪
♪ But now you know
that I'd rather die ♪
♪ You won't take me alive
♪ Won't take me alive
♪ Ain't takin' me alive
♪ Won't bleed me out to dry
♪ I'll tell you
like I said before ♪
♪ I never asked
to start a war ♪
♪ But now you know
that I'd rather die ♪
♪ You won't take me alive
♪ Won't bleed me out to dry
♪ I'll tell you
like I said before ♪
♪ I never asked to start a war
♪ But now you know
that I'd rather die ♪
♪ You won't take me alive