♪ ♪
(glass tinkling)
(blade ringing)
(watch ticking)
(liquid sloshing)
(paper rustling)
(clocks ticking)
(glass tinkling)
♪ ♪
(breath echoing)
(pained grunting)
(coughs)
♪ ♪
(labored panting)
(Violet whimpering)
(grunts)
(coughs)
(whimpering)
(Violet sobs)
(breath trembling)
(whimpering)
You did this to yourself.
You need to listen to me.
You just need to listen.
T... To listen.
(Violet whimpering)
Yeah, you want to do it?
You want to do it?
Come on. You...
You do it. You do it. Go on.
That's it. That's it.
Show me how you do it.
Go on. That's it.
Okay, go ahead.
(breath trembling)
-Come on, shoot me.
-(panting)
Shoot me! Come on, come on!
You show me!
Show me how you do it!
Come on!
-(grunts)
-Come on, shoot me!
(screaming)
(screaming stops abruptly)
VIOLET: Okay, let's go back
a few seconds.
When you say
that you're worthless,
who does that sound like to you?
(on screen):
I know.
-We practiced this last week.
-(sighs)
I know. I feel stupid
talking to myself out loud.
We need to hear your voice.
Not his.
Okay.
Let's...
try something different.
Go to the top right corner
of your screen
and press the "show self" view.
Okay.
Don't say anything.
Just focus on truly seeing
the woman who's staring back
at you.
Everything she's been through.
How far she's come.
Who she was before the abuse.
♪ ♪
Now try and tell me
that she's worthless.
(breathes deeply)
(chuckles)
There you are.
♪ ♪
(phone chimes)
-(knock on glass)
-(gasps, sighs)
Oh. Sorry to scare you.
I just need to read your meter.
Oh.
It's in the back.
You can use the side gate.
Thanks.
-(toy whirring) -("Day from
Night" playing over speakers)
♪ I see more on Going Street ♪
♪ They don't walk for fun ♪
♪ They just got somewhere
they'd rather be ♪
♪ And I don't know
my left from right ♪
♪ I don't know
which way to fight ♪
♪ But I know
it's bound to catch me ♪
♪ If I never try ♪
(singsongy):
Uh-oh.
♪ Silver turn to twilight... ♪
Where could Toby be hiding?
Is he in here?
(song continues faintly
in distance)
How about here?
I don't see Sir Toby anywhere.
Nowhere to be seen.
-(roars playfully)
-(exclaims)
-Take that!
-(imitating swords whooshing)
(grunts) Critical hit!
(groans)
(singsongy):
Oh, Toby.
-Auntie Fun Times!
-Toby Tornado!
-Hi, buddy.
-Hi.
-What?
-No, it's, uh...
-I didn't do my makeup yet.
It's not the makeup.
It's that.
-This?
-No, don't worry.
We're gonna fix it.
"Fix it"?
JEN: God, this magazine
is stressful.
Pretty sure I have
half these disorders,
starting with abulia?
VIOLET:
A-what-ia?
"The pathological inability
to make decisions."
You know, I was at the store
the other day,
and I'm in the deodorant aisle
and I'm just staring
for like 20 minutes;
I can't pick one.
VIOLET: When'd you start
wearing deodorant?
(scoffs) You're hilarious.
Okay, better?
Oh, wow.
Oh, much worse.
Did you mean to dress
like a candy cane?
You're... the meanest person
in the world.
Yeah, well, I'm your sister.
That's kind of my job.
-(Violet sighs)
-Tell me you're at least
wearing something sexy
under this.
Okay, that's a no.
Uh, I'm sorry. You know what?
No, you look great.
No, I don't. I look like
I'm going to play bingo
in a rest home.
(chuckles):
Stop. No, you don't.
VIOLET: I haven't been
shopping in forever.
All I have are work clothes.
(sighs)
I don't think I should go.
I mean, Toby's not feeling well,
-and I just feel like
I should... -Vi, no.
-...stay here in case
he needs me tonight. -No, Vi.
-It's just really bad timing.
It's not... -Vi, no, no, no.
Hey. Hey.
Look at me.
They're not all Blake.
Yeah.
-It's just a date.
-Mm-hmm.
You know? You're just gonna go,
and you'll have a nice dinner
and enjoy the company
of the very handsome
and extraordinarily patient man
-who's been talking to you
for three months. -(laughs)
And if you're not feeling it,
you just cut it short.
-There's no harm, no foul.
-Okay.
But if it's going well...
Oh, yeah. Mm-hmm. Come here.
-Uh... (chuckles)
-Come on.
If it's going well,
you're gonna be glad
you're wearing this.
'Cause you deserve to be happy.
And you need to get laid.
(both laughing)
It's getting kind of weird.
TOBY (in distance): Mommy, the
boogers are stuck in my nose!
Kid still doesn't know
how to blow his own nose.
-(sighs): Yep.
-(clicks tongue)
All right, you put this on.
I'm gonna go
deal with the boogers.
Thank you.
Yeah, of course.
-Come on, come on,
come on, come on. -Yeah.
Salt it, salt it, salt it.
Toby, look.
Okay, ready to go.
Wow, Mommy.
You look beautiful.
(chuckles) Thanks, little man.
You gonna be good
for Auntie Jen?
Does he know about my dad?
Yeah, he does.
Okay.
But hey,
how much do you love me?
This much!
(chuckles) I love you more.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
Um, okay, don't forget
humidifier, um,
-sound machine...
-Yes.
...and teeth brushed
with actual toothpaste.
Of course, yes.
We're gonna be fine, right?
We're gonna be fine.
-(sighs): Okay.
-Have fun.
Oh, and bedtime is 8:00 sharp.
Big Sister is watching.
Okay, yes, ma'am. Have fun!
-I love you both.
-Bye.
♪ ♪
(siren wailing faintly)
(sighs) It's just a date.
♪ ♪
(elevator bell dings)
(couple chattering quietly)
(elevator bell dings,
doors close)
(elevator whirring)
(phone chimes)
(elevator bell dings)
(Violet sighs)
Welcome to Palate.
Do you have a reservation
with us tonight?
Uh, yeah.
I think it's under Campbell.
-Henry Campbell?
-Mm-hmm.
Here you are. For two?
He's running a little late.
Is it okay if I wait for him
in the bar?
Of course.
Just head through the corridor.
You'll see the bar
straight ahead.
I'll come find you when
the rest of the party arrives.
-Okay, thanks.
-May I take your coat?
Oh, uh, yeah, that'd be great.
Thanks. Thank you.
Hi. Welcome to Palate.
-Hi.
-Do you have a reservation?
♪ ♪
(phone chimes)
-Oh, my God! I'm so sorry.
-(phone drops on floor)
-All good.
-Thank you.
-I should really watch where
I'm going. -(chuckles): Yeah.
-(gentle piano music playing)
-(lively chatter)
Can I get you something?
Um, oh, uh...
How's the house red?
-Mm, Malbec's better.
-Malbec then. Thanks.
Oh, thank you.
Love... love that outfit,
by the way.
Oh.
My sister made me wear it.
Oh. First date?
That obvious?
(laughs)
Sure I can't get you
something stronger?
I probably should
stick with this
in case I have to make
a run for it.
Right. (laughs)
Diane? Richard.
Oh.
I'm not Diane. Sorry.
-Oh, no. Sorry.
-No, it's-it's okay.
-Of course you're not her.
Sorry. -No worries.
(sighs)
I'm doing a blind date, so...
-Oh, wow, they still do those?
-Apparently they do.
If you, uh, get set up with
the only woman in Chicago
-who's not on social media.
-Wow.
I know. Crazy, right?
-(laughs): Yeah.
-Not even on, uh, Friendster.
(chuckles)
I just dated myself.
(stammers) Facebook.
Wow.
-It's kind of cool, though.
-Yeah.
I mean, mystery, it's kind of
hard to come by these days.
That's a good way
of looking at it.
I'm just kind of rusty
at all this stuff.
I feel like I'm sweating.
Am I sweating?
No.
-You look great.
-Thank you.
-(chuckles)
-You're very kind.
Um, hey. Well, to us.
-Oh, yeah.
-To getting back out there.
-Cheers. To getting back
out there. -Cheers.
So, are you early
or are they late?
-Um...
-BARTENDER: The same?
Oh, yeah. Keep 'em coming.
(sighs)
-Got any requests?
-(inhales sharply) No.
Oh, come on.
What's your favorite song?
Phil, she is literally
waiting on her date.
And I'm just asking
what song she likes.
You know any Pinkfong?
"Baby Shark"?
Banger.
I guess we'll see
what we can do.
Don't forget to tip.
(clicks tongue)
-I am so sorry.
-(laughs): It's okay.
It's the new piano guy, and
apparently being a corny sleaze
is actually part of
the job description.
(laughs)
How old's your kid?
Five.
-Oh.
-Going on 13.
Right. Nine.
-Oh.
-Already hates me.
(laughs)
So enjoy those "Baby Shark"
days while you can.
DIANE:
Excuse me. Are you Richard?
I am.
Uh, I'm gonna assume
you're Diane.
That's right. (chuckles)
-Oh.
-Come here. Should we hug?
It's great to finally meet you.
You, too.
Yeah. (sighs)
Oh. All right.
Guess we're ready to go.
(mouthing)
(phone tapping)
(phone chimes, vibrates)
(phone vibrates)
♪ ♪
-Hey.
-Hi.
Wow, you look, uh,
very beautiful.
Oh, thank you so much.
-I'm sorry I'm late.
I had to... -Oh, it's not fine.
I mean, it-it is fine.
It's not a problem.
Sorry, I got a drink
because I was nervous.
It clearly hasn't helped.
Yeah, I had a couple
in the car on the way over.
-(laughing)
-Also didn't help.
What do you say
we, uh, get our table?
-Yeah, okay.
-(laughs) Great.
(laughing)
HENRY: Did you hit traffic
coming here?
VIOLET: No. Luckily, I'm only
a few minutes from downtown.
(lively chatter continues)
-(piano playing "Moon River")
-Just here.
Thanks.
Sorry about the bag.
I can't leave my camera
in the car.
Otherwise, someone will take it.
Oh, of course.
And then I would be
out of a job, so...
HOSTESS: Your server will be
with you shortly.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
(sighs) What a view, huh?
VIOLET:
Ooh, that is high.
Wow.
-(exhales sharply)
-(both laugh)
I can't believe
we're actually doing this.
-Yeah. -Just-- I-I didn't know
if you'd ever agree to meet.
I just-- I can't imagine
all these creeps you must
come across on these apps.
I mean, you are the first guy
who didn't ask for feet pics,
so I just figured...
-That's usually, like,
an in-person request. -(laughs)
No paper trail, you know.
So have you, um...
have you been here before?
Uh, no, no.
I've always wanted to.
Just haven't had a reason to.
Uh, I'm really sorry.
I know this is rude,
but do you mind if I leave
my phone on the table?
It's just, my sister's
babysitting Toby,
and it's the first time he's
been without me in a while.
-It's totally fine.
-Thanks.
Uh, Jen, right?
Yeah. Wow, very impressive.
I actually studied all of our
DMs before coming on the date.
Did you?
I make really bad jokes
when I'm nervous.
-I thought it was a pretty
good joke. -Oh, I, um...
I got this for Toby
because I thought
he should know who to root for
now that he's a true Chicagoan.
I hope that's not weird
that I did that.
No, it's actually really sweet.
He's gonna love it.
He's gonna break
one of my windows with it,
but he's gonna love it.
-Feel free to send me a bill.
-(laughs)
WAITER:
Hello.
I am Matt.
I'll be taking care of
you two lovebirds this evening.
(laughs)
What are we celebrating?
Yeah, it's actually, uh,
it's our first date.
Wh-- Are you serious?
Yeah.
(chuckles)
This is my first shift.
(laughs) Can you believe that?
Okay, well, I will do my best
to make sure
it is special for all of us.
-(laughs)
-Thanks.
I'm actually, um...
I'm actually
in the improv scene.
-This is just sort of
a side hustle. -Mm.
You guys ever heard
of Second City?
-Yeah, sure. -Yes.
-(chuckles)
-Do you have a show coming up?
-Mm-mm. No, no.
Just classes, for now.
I'm actually working
on this sketch
where I play, like, a hat on
top of Allison Janney's head.
And, you know, she's tall,
and the catch is
the hat is afraid of heights.
(laughing):
So, he's just--
he is really going through it,
and his friend...
(stammers, clears throat)
I-I see that the lady is
taken care of.
Um, could I get you anything
to... to wet your whistle, sir?
Um, yeah. What-what is that?
-Um, it's a Malbec.
-Glass of Malbec.
All right.
One Malbec coming right up.
-I'm just gonna, uh, grab
these. -Oh, yeah. Of course.
(Matt chuckles)
All right. Be right back.
Malbec.
-HENRY: Whoa.
-Oh, my God.
-That was a lot.
-Yeah.
-(exhales sharply)
-(phone vibrates)
That should be Auntie Fun Times.
♪ ♪
Everything okay?
Somebody keeps sending me these.
Oh, digiDROP.
I'm more of
an AirDrop guy myself,
but that's, uh, sign guy--
vintage classic.
Yeah, I got a couple
at the bar before, too.
-It's weird.
-Uh-oh.
You've been chosen.
Happens to me all the time
on the L train.
-Oh. (laughs)
-Just a bunch of dumb kids
probably trying
to mess with you.
I feel like it makes sense
on a train,
but here it just seems...
I don't know, weird.
I mean...
-Who do you think it is?
-Oh, I don't know.
(woman laughs)
Okay, it's definitely not them.
The only thing they are seeing
is each other.
Um...
I mean... (laughs)
it's definitely not them.
They're still trying to figure
out how to work a VCR.
(Violet laughs)
Oh, what about them over there?
(coughs)
Oh, okay, so they're actually
here on a blind date,
and I was at the bar
when they met,
and it was really sad
because she was, like,
visibly disappointed
when she saw him.
-Poor guy.
-Right, but who is it?
Oh.
It's the prom kids.
Ah. Should I be flattered?
-I would be.
-Okay.
I mean, at least
it's not a dick pic.
-Oh, my God. -Actually happens
to me a lot on the train.
-(laughs)
-And the worst part is,
is that the lighting
is always atrocious.
Oh, yeah.
That would be the worst part.
It's like, if you're gonna
do it, at least, like,
-put some effort into it.
You know what I mean? -Yeah.
Photographer's nightmare,
for sure.
-(both laughing)
-(phone vibrates)
Um, I'm not even gonna
look at this one.
Yeah, let me check
just in case it's a--
you know, it's a-- Oh, God.
I'm just kidding.
It's not a dick pic.
-Oh, my God. (chuckles)
-Yeah.
HENRY: Someone really wants
your attention.
Well, then we probably
shouldn't give it to them.
(phone vibrates)
I'm not gonna look at that.
But it might be my sister.
Oh, yeah, there she is.
Just stuffing him
full of ice cream.
-Aw, that's cute.
-Mm-hmm.
(phone vibrates)
♪ ♪
What is it?
They know my name.
Oh, well, that's-that's
totally fine. Here.
I'll show you.
So, this...
-that's you.
-Yeah.
Violet Gates.
With your name and your photo
for everybody to see.
Here's your friend.
And then this is everybody else
that's in the restaurant.
So, just got to match up
the faces with the names.
-Oh.
-What?
It's really strange.
Everybody's on here.
So whoever your friend is,
it's somebody else.
I know you got to be
within 50 feet, I think,
-to send or receive a digiDROP.
-Oh, that's a fun fact.
We can figure this out.
-(sighs)
-What are you doing?
Solving a mystery.
♪ ♪
(chuckles softly)
-That was very impressive.
-Thanks.
You should see me with a level.
(both laugh)
Okay, so?
So, uh, the lobby's out of range
and most of the kitchen, too.
-Everything else is fair game.
-(phone vibrates)
VIOLET:
Hmm.
Um, yeah, he's just taunting us.
Hello. Here you go, Mr. Malbec.
(chuckles)
-So, who wants to hear
about our specials? -Sure.
Specials away.
All right, great.
Well, I will start
with the biggie.
The South African lobster.
(Matt laughs)
I'm not gonna lie, she's pricey,
especially for a first date.
I'm kidding. (chuckles)
Well, actually, no, I'm not,
because the lobster, it's...
it is... (sputters)
it's expensive.
Um, but let's see.
What else do we have?
-(phone vibrates)
-We have the tuna tartare,
which is delicious.
Also, the lemon oyster soup,
which sounds weird.
And it is. (laughs)
But it's-it's good, it's good.
I mean, I wouldn't order it,
but-but, uh,
some of these people did.
Um, so can I get you started
with any appetizers?
What are you thinking?
For appetizers?
Yeah. Um, you can order.
-You sure?
-Mm-hmm.
Big responsibility. All right.
Um, you like calamari?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Uh, how's the coconut calamari?
Be honest.
MATT:
I'm told it is
our most popular special
on the menu.
HENRY:
Great. We'll do that.
MATT: Well, I will
get that started for you,
and I will BRB.
(breath trembling)
(Henry's voice distorted
and echoing)
Violet?
Violet, everything okay?
(clearly):
(phone vibrates)
♪ ♪
What-what's going on?
Uh, yeah, I just--
I have to, um...
I have to call home.
I-I'll be right back.
(phone vibrates)
♪ ♪
-Oh.
-(gasps)
This keeps happening,
I'm gonna have to start
-taking it personally.
-Sorry.
Hey. Are you okay?
Fine.
Sorry again.
(panting)
(breath trembling)
(static crackling)
(girls chattering)
-We're going back to his,
and then... -Yeah. Uh, yeah.
-(chatter continues)
-Sorry.
-I really need your help.
I need... -(phone vibrates)
-You need help?
-Um...
Uh, I need your eyeliner.
-I left mine at home.
-My eyeliner?
-Yeah, I'll give it right back.
-Uh, okay.
-"Cal"? Cal who?
-No. (shushes)
We should really
get out of here.
(phone vibrates)
Uh, can I have my eyeliner back?
Uh, yes. Sorry.
-It's fine. -GIRL: Yeah,
let's get out of here.
-(girls murmuring)
-Oh, my God.
Yeah, go, go.
(door opens)
(door closes)
♪ ♪
(panting)
(gasps)
(door opens, closes)
Everything okay?
Yeah, just, uh...
a little bedtime emergency.
Are you sure?
-You just seem a little upset,
that's all. -(chuckles)
Sorry. This is so embarrassing.
Um...
I just-- I haven't been
out like this, really,
since he was born, and, um,
we just have a little routine.
You know, he likes things
a certain way, so I guess
-we're both just feeling
a little emotional. -Ah.
Yeah. I'm-I'm...
You know what?
I think this is my fault.
-No. -I feel like
I rushed you into this.
-No, definitely not.
-Are you sure?
Just know that I get it,
and if anything comes up,
I completely understand.
Having a kid is-is
the most important thing.
That comes first.
Um, I-I appreciate that.
Yeah.
Actually, um,
they-they lost his stuffy,
but I-I think I know
where it is.
It's just, he can't go to sleep
without his Lamby.
Well, I hope they find it.
Yeah, I mean, technically, I'm
on, I'm on call all the time,
but it's nothing
compared to being a parent.
Yeah, uh,
we're pretty inseparable,
you know, especially
since his dad passed.
Yeah. I-I can't imagine.
(phone vibrates)
♪ ♪
Are you getting more drops?
No.
Well, you just keep looking
around the room.
I'm so sorry.
I'm, like, the worst date ever.
Oh, no, no, no. You're great.
You're-you're great.
You're amazing. I just, uh...
If something's wrong,
I just... I want to help.
That's all.
Um...
I got a thing with heights,
so I just--
I think I'm trying
to center myself a little.
(Henry chuckles)
What are we doing sitting here?
(laughs)
Uh, we can fix that.
That's easy.
Um, Matt.
Hey, yeah, the, um, the
appetizers will be right out.
Uh, it's not that. It's, uh...
Actually, you know, Matt?
You think maybe
we can change tables?
It's just, the-the view's
a little disorienting, I think.
Sure. Uh, let me check.
Oh, thank you.
Easy.
It's really not, um, necessary.
Well, look, this is
probably Matt's first
table change request,
and the guy is just nailing it.
-(laughing)
-Killing it.
Don't worry about it.
Thanks.
Yes, yes, yes, yes! I did it!
I made some calls,
I dropped some names,
pulled some strings.
I got y'all a new table, so,
um, get your things, follow me.
Amazing. Thank you.
-Come on.
-Great.
(phone vibrates)
MATT: Here we go.
Just right this way.
And... new table, vertigo-free.
(chuckles)
(phone vibrates)
Wait.
Uh, I'm sorry.
Can we go back
to our other table?
Uh, uh, I could, I could ask
if there's another one
if this one doesn't work.
No, no, I'd really like to go
back to our original table.
We came for the view.
So I'm just gonna get over it.
I'm good. Let's go back.
Back we go. (laughing)
(whispers):
Jesus Christ.
♪ ♪
All right.
-We happy?
-Yes. -Yeah.
Well, you guys let me know if
you need anything else, okay?
-Thank you.
-All right.
(Henry grunts)
Sorry about that.
That was crazy.
That's okay. I need to get
my steps in for the day anyway.
(chuckles) Well, I'm working
on overcoming my fear,
so this is good.
(camera whirs, clicks)
It's good for me.
-You afraid of heights?
-Among other things.
(phone vibrates)
They find Lamby?
Yes.
-Finally.
-Good.
Crisis averted. Hmm.
HOSTESS:
Good evening.
I just want to make sure there's
no problem with the table.
-No, everything's great.
-No? -Yeah, it's great.
Okay, good, 'cause this is the
one you reserved, Mr. Campbell.
No, it's not.
I just, uh, asked
for one with a view.
Oh. Well, it's in my notes
that you had called
and reserved this table
specifically.
That's funny.
I don't remember doing that.
But, uh, we're-- I think we're
good with this table, yeah?
-Yeah. Mm-hmm.
-Yeah.
-Enjoy.
-HENRY: Thanks.
Uh, must have gotten us
mixed up with another res.
You know what?
I bet you
that explains the drops.
We took someone's table.
We took their reservation,
and they're pissed.
(phone vibrates)
-Um...
-Got to be what it is.
-Should we order? (chuckles)
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-Let's order.
Um...
Are we ready to order?
-Yeah, I think so.
-All right.
Milady, you first.
Um, ooh.
Decisions, decisions.
-Um...
-(phone vibrates)
Um, how's the duck salad?
Oh, it's, like,
my favorite thing on the menu.
Like, I love it.
It's got this, like, candied
ginger and these, um, cashews.
It gives it, like, a real
crunch-runchy kind of vibe.
-(phone vibrates)
-It's really good.
So, the duck salad?
Uh, yes, perfect.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
(singsongy):
And for the gentleman?
HENRY: Uh, I'm gonna do
the Kobe filet.
Mmm, good choice.
Uh, do you want the eight ounce
-or the big boy twelver?
-Better stick with the eight.
(chuckles):
Okay.
Uh, medium rare?
-HENRY: Medium.
-Okay.
And any sides?
Would you share the truffle
mashed potatoes if I got them?
-Love it.
-Great. Let's do that.
MATT:
Got it. Truffle mashed...
All right, I'm gonna
get those, uh, turned in,
and I will be right back.
(chuckles)
-Oh, no.
-What is it?
My watch, I... (sighs)
I've been meaning
to get the clasp fixed.
It must have
fallen off somewhere.
Well, uh, where was the last
place you remember having it?
Um, I don't remember.
Oh.
I had it when I walked in,
because I remember the hostess
complimented me on it.
Um... (smacks lips)
Well, it's got to be
around here.
Would you mind?
I-I'm gonna look around here,
but w-would you mind
just asking the hostess
if anyone turned it in?
Yeah. Yeah. Sure. Sit tight.
I'll be right back.
♪ ♪
(camera beeping quietly)
(sighs) No luck.
-(sighs)
-I'm sorry.
My mom got me that watch.
-Oh, really? That's a bummer.
-Yeah.
Well, look, it's got to be
around here somewhere.
I'm sure it'll turn up.
(phone vibrates)
Oh. You know what?
I bet it came off
in the ladies' room.
I'm just gonna quickly run
and grab it. Sorry.
♪ ♪
Okay, I'm here.
(phone vibrates)
(door opens)
(toilet flushing)
Okay. It's done. I did it.
Get your guy
out of my house now.
(phone vibrates)
Please.
Please. I did what you asked.
(phone vibrates)
(panting)
♪ ♪
(gasps softly)
(phone vibrates)
No.
No, I can't...
I can't do that.
(phone vibrates)
(whimpers)
♪ ♪
HOSTESS (muffled, distorted):
Did you find your watch?
Ma'am?
(clearly):
Your watch, did you find it?
Uh...
No. I didn't.
Well, if anyone turns it in,
I'll come find you.
Thanks.
♪ ♪
(phone rings, beeps)
HOSTESS:
Thanks for holding.
I'm sorry.
W-We're just fully booked.
Another time.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you for calling.
Excuse me. Sorry. Just curious.
Did anyone else specifically
request a table tonight,
maybe the same time
we're dining?
I just want to make sure
that we didn't accidentally
take someone else's.
You're at the right table.
Excuse me.
-Ready?
-Sorry.
♪ ♪
DISPATCHER (over phone):
911. What's your emergency?
-Hi. My son is being held--
-(line beeping)
Hello?
-Hello--
They cut the line.
♪ ♪
Mmm. Coconut calamari.
Here we go.
Oh, you don't have plates.
(chuckles)
Is she coming back or...
-Sure hope so.
-(chuckles): Um, right.
Well, I will, uh,
I'll be right back
with those plates.
(phone vibrates)
(sighs)
♪ ♪
(footsteps approaching)
(gasps)
-(gentle piano music playing)
-(lively chatter)
-Hi.
You again.
Yeah.
You've been waiting here
for a long time.
Uh, I'm meeting my sister.
She's stuck on the tarmac
at O'Hare.
I'm sorry.
-You are?
-Violet.
Violet, aren't you
on a date right now?
Why do you ask?
Well, I think
he's looking over here.
You might want to get back
to your table.
Right.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to bother you.
It's no bother.
(phone vibrates)
Are you sure you don't
want that boxed up?
Uh, yeah. That's okay.
Thank you so much.
You're not leaving, are you?
Uh, yeah.
Look, it's clear to me
that Toby really needs
his mom right now,
and I think you're just
too polite to say it.
So I'll-I'll let you
off the hook.
Please don't go. (chuckles)
I'm... I'm so sorry.
I know I've been... I've been
so distracted all night,
but I-I really, I really
don't want you to leave.
-Please stay.
-You don't have to apologize.
We can, uh, maybe, you know,
pick it up some other time.
♪ ♪
(audio fades)
(gentle piano music playing)
Sit with me.
Please?
Okay.
(table bangs)
DIANE:
You're a real jerk.
Loser.
(others chuckling, murmuring)
(sighs)
Well, you folks have
a lovely evening.
Actually, you know what, Matt?
I think we're gonna stay.
-(phone vibrates)
-Really?
Aw. Plot twist. Okay.
-Keeping me on my toes. Cool.
-Trial by fire, am I right?
-(Henry laughing)
-MATT (laughing): Yes.
I'm here for it. Really, I am.
-Um, should I get you
another glass of wine? -Yeah.
-(phone vibrates) -Yeah,
how-how do you feel about wine?
(playing dramatic chord)
(playing gentle piano version
of "Baby Shark")
-Uh, what do you think?
-Oh.
Sorry. I requested this song.
MATT:
Oh, you requested "Baby Shark"?
Yeah.
My son loves it.
Wine.
-Yeah.
-Sounds good.
This was a little heavy for me.
I might switch to something
else. Is there a wine list?
There certainly is. Right here.
Would you mind?
I'm terrible at that.
-Oh, yeah. Yeah. Love to.
-Thanks.
Um, let's see here.
What do we got?
♪ ♪
Wow. You got a pretty big list.
MATT (laughs):
It's really big.
Heavy to carry. (chuckles)
HENRY:
Um, got a bunch of pinots here.
What do you recommend?
MATT:
I mean, like, I'm no somm--
sommel-- sommel-- somm--
uh, wine guy, but I, uh,
I've tried, like, all the reds,
and the one from, uh,
Paso Robles is just as good
as the Napa Valley stuff,
-and it's, like, half the
price, so... -Let's do that.
Great. All right.
So, two of those?
All right, great, and
the entrées will be right out.
Can you just give this to the
piano player, say it's from me?
Aw. Yes, I will.
-Thank you.
-Mm-hmm.
Here's a little something
from the lady over there.
-That was really nice.
-(chuckles softly)
Well, he... he did play my song.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
-(gentle piano music playing)
-Um...
How long have you been
working for the mayor?
Uh, five years.
-Mm, a while.
-Yeah.
So you must know him
pretty well.
I mean, I'm-I'm just
the guy's press photographer.
It's not like
I'm his best friend.
Is he a good guy?
(sighs)
(sighs) Yeah.
Yeah. He's, um, he's okay.
I, uh, I just take pictures
of people for a living.
You get their whole life.
I mean, that's got to be...
that's got to be pretty crazy.
Honestly, it can be
intense, yeah.
-Yeah.
-I recently switched my focus
to, uh, survivors of abuse.
What made you,
what made you do that?
Experience.
My ex-husband, Toby's dad.
(softly):
Oh.
I'm sorry.
It rears its head now and again.
See tonight for details.
But I'm still here for Toby,
and that's what really matters.
Of course.
Well, thanks for telling me.
I appreciate it.
Back in five.
(phone chimes)
♪ ♪
HENRY:
Hey, uh, I'm sorry to do this,
but I got a work call
I got to take.
-Is that okay?
-I owe you. Of course.
-Take your time.
-Okay. I'll be right back.
Okay.
♪ ♪
(gentle piano music playing)
(sighs)
Everything okay?
Yeah. (chuckles)
Yeah, it's gonna be good.
Yeah, just some
scheduling stuff.
Okay.
And now for the main event.
(chuckles) All right.
So, we have the duck salad
for the lady.
Thank you.
And the Kobe filet
for the gentleman.
And the truffle mashed potatoes.
And do you need anything else?
-HENRY: Thank you so much.
-Yeah, we're good.
Okay, great. I'll be
right back with that wine.
Enjoy.
Man, this looks great.
♪ ♪
How's your salad?
(phone vibrates)
-Sorry, Jen texted.
-Oh, that's all right.
(phone vibrates)
(piano playing discordant notes)
(panting sharply)
(bangs piano keys)
(people gasping, murmuring)
-Hey, buddy.
-(Phil groaning)
You all right?
(phone vibrates)
(static buzzing)
♪ ♪
(gasps)
(sniffles)
(whispers):
No.
(sobs)
Please.
Please, I'm begging you.
Please. Don't do this.
(Phil groaning)
PHIL:
I got it. I got it.
(panting)
(Phil groans)
Sorry, folks.
Guess that was
one too many vodka martinis.
Back in a few.
(both exhale)
That was so insane.
-Yeah, scary.
-I hope he's okay.
Me, too.
♪ ♪
(woman grunts)
(phone vibrates)
(siren wailing in distance)
You think that's for him?
Well, I don't know. Maybe.
(sighs) Can we start over?
Tonight's been so weird.
Start over how?
Uh...
What if we took a shot?
Oh.
(chuckles):
Okay.
That's not where I thought
you were going with this.
Yeah. I just feel like
we could use the reset.
Um, yeah, I-I'd love to.
I just-- I have to,
I have to curate
a bunch of photos
when I get home,
-and I'm already
a little buzzed. -Oh.
-Yeah. No, that was dumb.
-So...
Actually, forget it. I, um...
I realize that I made
this night pretty heavy,
so I just wanted
to lighten the mood.
Ah, you know what?
Screw it. Yeah.
-Let's do it.
-Yeah?
Yeah, a shot never
killed anybody, right?
(laughs)
Uh, what's your poison?
Hmm. Uh...
-Tequila.
-Ooh.
-I love tequila.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-Let's get a couple shots.
-All right.
Um, I'm gonna get it
from the bar.
No, I got it.
Please sit down. I got it.
Matt's around here somewhere.
I can get a...
MATT: Who is gonna be
covering this? Okay.
Looks like he's having
a really rough first day.
Um, I'll go get it.
It's no biggie.
No, don't be silly. It's fine.
I can-- I-I got it.
No, please. Honestly,
it is the least I can do.
I'm gonna go,
and I'll be right back.
Two minutes.
-Okay.
-Come right back.
-All right.
-Okay?
♪ ♪
Hey, you're back.
-Hi.
-What can I get you?
Uh, two shots
of tequila, please.
So, how's the date going?
It's good.
Sure about that?
-You seem kind of on edge.
-I'm fine.
Just... first-date jitters.
Okay.
♪ ♪
(phone vibrates)
(whispers):
He needs to see me do it.
Oh, um, just remembered
I left my purse at the table.
Don't worry about it.
I'll just add it to the tab.
-Okay, thank you.
-Want some limes?
(sighs) No, thanks.
Good luck.
♪ ♪
Oh, where did you find it?
Oh, your, uh, your purse.
When you got up,
your purse fell on the ground.
It spilled out.
-Henry, I, uh...
-You're lying to me.
You're looking around
the restaurant.
You're distracted.
You're on your phone.
Something's happening.
No, it's not.
Is it, is it...
someone in the restaurant?
Is it the drops?
I just want to help.
Violet.
BLAKE:
Come on, come on! You show me!
Show me how you do it! Come on!
-(screaming, wailing)
-(gun clicking)
-You can't!
-(baby crying)
(panting) Oh, baby.
(baby continues crying)
I am going to take
everything from you.
(whimpering)
-(crying echoes)
-Please, no. Please.
HENRY:
Violet?
Why did you message me?
What do you mean?
On the app.
Why did you message me?
I mean, you know that
I'm a widow with a kid.
That's a lot of baggage.
Well...
I, uh...
I really hate these apps.
And, uh...
I was really close
to deleting my profile.
I feel like
everybody's trying to present
this version of themselves
that they're not.
A version that they think
other people want to see.
And then I saw you.
And I didn't see any of that.
You just seemed kind.
Genuine.
No pretense. Just a good mom.
I'm not.
I stayed in
an abusive relationship
even after Toby was born.
And he was really little...
...but he saw things that, um...
I mean, no child
should ever see that.
Well, you know what?
You got out.
That's all that matters.
I didn't.
(sniffles)
I never got out.
I'm still stuck in that room.
The night that I watched Blake
almost kill my s-son.
(crying):
And I just...
(sobbing)
I just sat there.
I did nothing.
And that's the kind
of mother I am.
(breathes deeply)
You know, I, um...
(sighs)
I found myself in a,
in a pretty messed-up situation
not long ago, and somebody...
somebody I really trusted
ended up being
somebody totally different.
And for a long time...
...people were getting hurt.
Really good people were
getting hurt, and I...
I stayed silent
and I didn't say anything,
and then I finally did.
And I tried to do
the right thing,
whatever I thought
the right thing was,
whatever that is, and, uh...
...I still found myself feeling
guilty about it, you know?
And I know I didn't do
anything wrong.
You know, I think
that's what abusive people do.
They make us feel...
(sighs softly)
They turn everything around
and they make us feel crazy.
You know, they take it away.
Even if they're dead.
Take what?
Hope.
And I think that's what...
I think that's what
brought me here today
on this date. (laughs)
Hope that I can, uh...
that I can be happy.
That things can be different.
I think maybe that's
what brought you here.
(sniffles)
You are good, Henry.
I try. I try.
-Nobody's perfect, right?
-(chuckles softly)
(sniffles) Yeah.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
Yeah.
(phone vibrates)
Well, I guess
I killed the mood for these.
(both laugh)
No, no.
It's never a bad time
for some tequila, right?
Well, I forgot the limes.
I can get some limes.
Can you tell I haven't
taken a shot since college?
(laughs)
I think you're really great.
Thank you.
I'm gonna go see a guy
about some limes.
-(laughing)
-All right?
(sighs)
I'll be right back. Okay.
♪ ♪
MATT:
Hello.
Pinot delivery.
Just checking in over here.
See how things are going.
Yeah, everything's great.
-BARTENDER: You good?
-Uh, yeah.
Can I get a couple
lime wedges, please?
What, she changed her mind?
Um, yeah.
MATT: And you don't need
anything else?
No, thank you.
Okay. Oh.
Oh, we got some shots.
That's fun. (chuckles)
Shot, shot, shot, shot,
shot, shot, shots. (laughs)
All right, well, I'll just, um,
I'll leave you to it, so enjoy.
♪ ♪
(phone vibrates)
(sniffles)
(clears throat)
(sighs):
Here you go.
-Some limes.
-Oh, thank you.
So what should we toast to?
(breath trembles)
That's a,
that's a good question.
I don't, I don't know.
How about hope?
Okay, yeah.
To hope.
(glasses clink)
♪ ♪
VIOLET:
Oh, my God.
-Henry, I'm so sorry.
-Um...
Oh, wow. I really could win
the award for worst date ever.
-(laughing) It's okay.
-I'm so sorry.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
I was gonna, I was gonna
get rid of these pants anyway.
Uh, I'm just gonna go,
I'm gonna go, uh, clean up.
Yeah, of course. Take your time.
Okay, uh, I'll be right back.
(sighs)
(panting softly)
(phone vibrates)
Hi. (chuckles)
-CONNOR: There she is.
-Hey.
(chuckles)
-How are you?
-Hi.
♪ ♪
Wow, that was quite the spill.
(sighs):
Oh.
Yeah, sorry.
I'm... a real klutz.
Come on.
I know what's going on here.
I've been a bartender
my whole life,
and not just
in fancy places like this.
You've been acting nervous
all night.
I've seen it a million times.
If you feel unsafe with your
date or you're afraid of him,
I'll get you out of here.
Uh, look, I know
I've been acting
a little on edge all night,
but it's not him.
Really? 'Cause your waiter
noticed it, too.
No.
He's, uh, he's been great.
Thank you, though.
Hey, um...
do you know who that is?
She looks familiar.
Oh, her? Yeah.
She's in here all the time.
Although, weird.
She usually requests
that table over there.
By the way, I do not blame
his date for ditching him.
That man's been
staring at you all night.
Well, enjoy the rest
of your date.
I'll just get you another.
♪ ♪
(startled grunt)
(chuckles):
Hello again.
I'd ask how it's going,
but I imagine
you're having an infinitely
better night than me.
(chuckles softly)
I thought you could use this.
No way.
To getting back out there.
Violet, wow.
That's-that's incredibly sweet,
but, um...
I think one drink's
my limit for tonight.
(sighs)
I don't remember telling you
my name before.
You're right. (chuckles)
No, you're right.
You did not. That's a good one.
Please sit.
Sit.
♪ ♪
I admire your tenacity.
I do. No, I really do.
I mean, you had a shit hand,
and you played the heck
out of it. I mean...
It-It's not gonna do you
any good, but, um...
Pick one.
Pick a goddamn shot.
Drink it.
Oh, there you go.
That wasn't so hard.
So this was the best table
to watch me from?
It's an okay table.
I mean, yeah, it's fine,
but it's the only one in
the blind spot of the cameras.
Killing Henry won't stop
whatever this is.
I mean, I'm sure
he backed up the photos.
Yeah, of course. I mean, all
official photos go straight to
the mayor's private server,
which, you know,
we already scrubbed.
But the SD card,
that was a loose end.
But you crushed it.
I mean, literally crushed it.
Hey, fun fact.
Henry just got a call about
a meeting tonight with the FBI
to hand it over.
He's an informant.
That's a bit of a grand word.
No, he's a rat.
Which makes you a rattrap.
(laughs)
-I've seen your face.
-Okay, great.
I'm just, you know...
a guy enjoying a nice meal.
I'm gonna tell the police
about the drops.
Oh, shit.
You mean the, um,
the little notes and the memes
that are in the camera roll
on your phone?
Drops are untraceable.
There's no way to prove
they came from anyone.
I mean, you could've
put them there yourself,
for all anyone knows.
Well, what about Diane?
I'm sure she'll be able
to tell them
that you were on your phone
the whole night.
Is that a crime or is it
just, you know, a bad date?
You didn't have to
bring me into this.
I kind of did.
Suspicious death
of a future star witness
is not really a great headline
for my employer.
But if you become the headline:
"Widow assassin strikes again."
(laughs):
I mean, come on.
Nobody's gonna be
looking anywhere else,
and the FBI's case
just goes poof.
I didn't kill my husband.
Okay. Sure. I mean, yeah. Sure.
Not that Blake's family could
prove in court, but, I mean,
you were the only one
there, right?
The night he died.
I mean, your fingerprints
were all over the gun.
♪ ♪
(baby crying)
No. No, no.
(sirens approaching)
(crying softly)
(wailing)
(yelling)
-(gunshot echoes)
-RICHARD: I'll tell you what.
I am gonna take your word
for it on Blake.
But what about poor Phil?
Did he have to die, too?
-You did that?
-No, you did that,
when you pulled
that stupid stunt.
It's a good thing for Toby
I got to him
before he got to the cops.
Otherwise, your son's brains
would be splattered
all over the wall.
Fuck you.
I'm flattered,
but I'm at work right now.
Panna cotta?
(chuckles):
Oh, wow.
That looks gorgeous.
-Thank you.
-Can I get you anything else?
RICHARD: No. I mean, it's gonna
be a hard act to follow, right?
-Right. Enjoy.
-Look at this.
Oh, my God.
It's like, I don't know
if I should photograph it
or eat it. (laughs)
You have to help me with this.
Oh, and, um,
the cameras over your table,
I mean, they recorded you
spiking that shot.
Sertraline.
Laced with a little fentanyl.
You-you prescribe sertraline
a lot, right?
Of course you do.
That's why I chose it.
You don't get it, do you?
I'm, like--
I'm playing chess here.
I'm, like, at least
two moves ahead at all times.
What are you doing? You're
playing-- What are you playing?
You're playing Yahtzee. (laughs)
You can't win.
In fact, you lost
the second you walked in here,
so you need to accept that.
You want to save little Toby?
You get Henry
to drink that shot.
It's your last chance.
Oh, no way.
We were just talking about you.
Sorry, I'm Richard.
-Henry.
-Pleasure.
Um, Violet and I are old pals.
We go all the way back
to the, uh, bar earlier.
Yeah.
Comrades in
the first-date trenches.
RICHARD:
I like that, yeah.
I don't know if you noticed,
but I'm, uh--
haven't had
the best night tonight,
and Violet is such a sweetheart
she brought over those shots.
But now you're not
drinking them.
You're leaving me hanging.
Well, I'm a little tipsier
than I thought.
And, um...
well, this was yours anyway.
-I think I'm good.
-Oh, please.
Please.
Don't make me drink alone.
Yeah, come on.
After tonight, you earned it.
(glass taps on table)
(Richard laughs)
Masterfully done. (chuckles)
Hey.
Can you just give us
one more minute?
-I'll explain everything.
-Yeah, of course.
-Nice to meet you.
-My pleasure.
It's done.
Call it off right now.
All right. Fair enough.
(line ringing)
-(line clicks)
-MAN (over phone): Yes?
He drank it.
I'm just gonna finish up here.
(over phone): Okay.
I'll wait for confirmation.
Right.
Happy?
-Is he leaving?
-Your son's safe.
-Don't worry about it.
-(sighs)
What happens now?
I eat this delicious dessert.
(laughs)
And wait for Henry to...
keel over,
which unfortunately,
I mean, you're gonna be
on the hook for,
but, you know, hey,
at least you saved
your son, right?
No way.
Oh, man.
You can't leave.
I will eat this all myself.
(chuckles softly)
The last time Blake took me out
to dinner, he had panna cotta.
-Okay.
-It was an Italian restaurant.
The same one he always
took me to after he...
(sighs heavily)
The apology dinner.
Mm-hmm.
And I'd sit across
from him and...
just pretend
that everything was fine.
I got really good at it.
Pretending I believed him
when he said
it wouldn't happen again.
And pretending
I was gonna leave.
But...
I knew I wouldn't.
And like tonight, when I
pretended to poison that shot.
♪ ♪
Yahtzee.
-Goddamn bitch!
-(people gasping)
(people screaming)
-MAN: He's got a gun!
-(panicked clamoring)
-Where are you going?
-(yelps)
Where are you going?
You better hide from me!
-(gasps)
-(shouts)
(screaming)
-(blade stabs)
-(screams, whimpers)
(yells)
(gasps)
(both panting)
(phone ringing)
RICHARD (weakly):
My guy.
(wheezes)
He's still in your house.
Kill them.
(shouts)
-You missed.
-(glass crackling)
-(wind rushing)
-(screaming)
(Richard screaming)
(screaming)
Help me!
(gasping)
(grunts)
-(fabric ripping)
-(screams)
(both grunting)
(panting)
(whimpering)
Oh. Oh, God.
Oh, God. Okay.
-Okay.
-(Henry grunts)
Okay. Put pressure on it.
You're gonna be okay.
Look at me.
-I knew there was
something going on. -Shh.
Don't say anything.
Okay, stay right here.
I'll be right back.
(siren wailing in distance)
You're gonna be okay, all right?
-Help's coming.
-Okay.
(grunts)
♪ ♪
Shit!
I need your keys.
They're in my bag.
Get my phone.
Here's your phone.
Where's your car?
Uh, P3, row J.
-Okay.
-I'll call the cops. Just go.
-27 Allen Street.
-Go.
(panting)
(Matt yells)
My horoscope was right.
♪ ♪
Shit!
Come on, where is it?
-Where is it?
-(car alarm chirps)
-(line ringing)
-(engine starts)
(tires squealing)
(phone ringing)
(phone beeps)
(clattering in distance)
(panting)
Toby.
-Toby!
-(phone ringing)
-(tires squealing)
-(line ringing)
Pick up, pick up, pick up!
(grunts)
(phone ringing)
VIOLET (over phone): He's
right behind you! Get down!
(tires squealing)
(sirens wailing)
(panting softly)
(footstep creaks)
Toby, no!
Run!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
(man yelling)
(screaming)
-(blade stabs)
-(man screaming)
Go! Go! Run!
Run, run, run!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Go!
Go.
-(horn honks)
-Come on!
-Move!
-(horn honks)
-(tires squealing)
-(screams)
-(horn blaring)
Get in the corner.
(grunting)
(straining)
(panting)
-Shit!
-(tires squealing)
(silenced gunshots)
Get under the bed! (grunts)
(man grunting)
No, no!
-(worker shouting)
-Move, move, move!
(horn blaring)
(yelling)
(man screaming)
(panting)
(tires squealing in distance)
(car door closes)
♪ ♪
(silenced gunshot)
-(Violet yells)
-(man screams)
(Violet coughing)
(pained gasping)
-(grunts, screams)
-(man shouts)
(whimpering)
(Violet coughing)
(strained grunt)
(pained grunting)
(panting)
(groans)
(toy whirring)
(silenced gunshots)
-(whimpering)
-(gun clatters on floor)
Toby!
(groans)
Mommy!
(crying): You're okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
I know. You're okay.
So how was your date?
(laughing)
(sniffles)
Oh.
♪ ♪
TV NEWSMAN:
What authorities claim
was a plot to murder
a key witness has now led
to explosive new evidence
linking the mayor's office
to a widespread
embezzlement scheme
and implicating many
of the city's top leaders.
-Got you, dickhead.
-(knock on door)
-(door opens)
-(P.A. chimes)
(indistinct announcement
over P.A.)
Palate was closed
for renovations.
Oh. I wonder why.
-It's not Kobe.
-I'll take anything over
the stuff
they're giving me here.
Right.
(Henry sighs)
-(phone vibrates)
-Uh-oh.
I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
Everything okay?
(door opens)
(laughs) Too soon?
-Bitch, yes.
-(Jen laughs)
Unbelievable.
Hey, Henry.
I'm the sister down the hall.
Nice to meet you,
sister down the hall.
You got him some food?
-But you know I got shot, too.
-Do you want to get shot twice?
Okay. (chuckles)
-I'll go.
-See you later.
-Have fun.
-Thanks for stopping by, Jen.
JEN:
Save me some fries.
You know, she's really nice.
I think she's in
the wrong kind of hospital.
(both chuckle)
So, that was a...
-pretty hardcore first date.
-(laughing)
Oh, my God, there were
so many moments where
I was just thinking, "What is
this guy still doing here?"
You must have thought
that I was a crazy person.
You saved my life.
I don't even know
what to say to you.
Say you'll brave
a second date with me.
I would love to go
on a second date with you.
-(chuckles)
-What'd you have in mind?
(sighs):
I don't know.
Well, I was thinking
something really...
really...
boring.
-Oh. Yeah.
-(laughing)
(laughing):
That sounds great.
-How do milkshakes sound?
-Oh, pretty damn good to me.
-Yeah?
-What are we working with?
Okay, I got one of each.
So, are you a chocolate girl
or a strawberry girl?
Oh, I'm a strawberry girl.
-That's this one.
-Oh, great.
("Healing" by FLETCHER playing)
♪ I'm finally breathing ♪
♪ The smoke ain't gone,
but it's clearing ♪
♪ I ain't there yet,
but I'm healing ♪
♪ I ain't there yet ♪
♪ Inhale, exhale
on repeat, yeah ♪
♪ Lately, it's so hard
to breathe, yeah ♪
♪ Falling 'bout
a million times ♪
♪ It's a miracle
I'm still alive ♪
♪ No one said that it was easy ♪
♪ Trying to piece
the broken pieces ♪
♪ But that's the shit
I'm working on ♪
♪ The journey is a work of art ♪
♪ I can't erase all the things
that I've done ♪
♪ But all the mistakes made me ♪
♪ Who I've become ♪
♪ I've been feeling ♪
♪ Inside out in my feelings ♪
♪ Upside down on the ceiling ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I'm finally breathing ♪
♪ The smoke ain't gone,
but it's clearing ♪
♪ I ain't there yet,
but I'm healing ♪
♪ I ain't there yet ♪
♪ But I'm healing ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I ain't there yet,
but I'm healing ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I ain't there yet,
but I'm healing ♪
♪ Breaking down
don't mean I'm broken ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm broken ♪
♪ Losing hope
don't mean I'm hopeless ♪
♪ And maybe all I need is time ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ It never happens overnight ♪
♪ I can't erase all the things
that I've done ♪
♪ I've done ♪
♪ But all the mistakes made me ♪
♪ Who I've become ♪
♪ But I still take 'em back ♪
♪ I've been feeling ♪
♪ Inside out in my feelings ♪
♪ My feelings ♪
♪ Upside down on the ceiling ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah, yeah ♪
-♪ I'm finally ♪
-♪ Finally ♪
♪ Breathing ♪
♪ The smoke ain't gone,
but it's clearing ♪
♪ I ain't there yet,
but I'm healing ♪
♪ I ain't there yet ♪
♪ But I'm healing ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I ain't there yet,
but I'm healing ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I ain't there yet,
but I'm healing ♪
♪ I'm finally breathing ♪
♪ The smoke ain't gone,
but it's clearing ♪
♪ I ain't there yet,
but I'm healing ♪
♪ I ain't there yet ♪
♪ But I'm healing ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I ain't there yet,
but I'm healing ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I ain't there yet. ♪
(song ends)
♪ ♪
(music ends)