Bonjour, Madame.How Much ForA Reading?
Fortuneteller 3 Francs, Dear,
And lt's Written On The Door.
l'm sorry
l cannot see.
We've Got To Go.
We're Late.We'll Miss The Bus.
ThankYou, Madame.
What Do You see?
l see Your 34th Year.
shut Up.
That's The Porter.
He spotted Me
As l Was Making My Getaway.
These Are First-Year Rooms,
Aren't They?
They're very Luxurious.
The Ones AtYale
Are Like Monk's cells.
"Aristotle And virtue."
Oh, God, l'm sorry.
lt Doesn't Matter.
Of course lt Does.
l Ruined Them.
Wait.
lt's Getting Heavier
Out There, Huh?
Do You Mind lf l stay Here
Till lt Eases Off? No. Of course You can.
l Go Out
With One OfThe Dons.
l Know. Julian Ellsworth.
We Just Had
An Awful Row. l can't Go Back To His Rooms.
l Have To Get Out
OfThese Togs.
Excuse Me.
Help.
lt's completely
stuck To Me.
l Don't Mind lf lt Tears.
Thanks.
Bless You.
l can't LetYou Go Out
ln This. You can sleep ln My Bed.
ButWe Haven't
Been lntroduced.
l'll sleep On The chair
And Keep Watch.
That's very Noble But l Wouldn't
Dream Of Kidnapping Your Bed.
You're Taking A Terrible Risk
Having Me Here AtAll.
sorry. No. Don'tApologize.
l'm Flattered.
lt Doesn't Normally...
l should Hope lt Does.
l'm Gilda Besse.
l Know Who You Are.
That sounds Ominous.
You're Famous Around Here.
Where Are You From? Dublin Originally.
We Moved Up North
AfterThe Treaty.
WhyWas That?
My FatherWas A Policeman.
And He Was Killed
During The Troubles.
so Are You British Or lrish?
On Paper, l'm British.
But l Don't Believe
ln countries Much.
Nor Do l.
How Did You
End Up Here?
l GotA scholarship.
Beauty, Bravery, And Brains.
WhatA catch.
You Also Have A Nice Willy,
And l Hope To Dream About lt.
Good Night, Guy.
Good Night.
We Made lt.
l Owe You My Life.
You Don't Owe Me Anything.
ltWas Fun.
Everyone Knew Gilda Besse.
Her Father Owned One OfThe
Big French champagne Houses.
Her MotherWas A Rich American socialite.
The Marriage Hadn't Lasted,
And Gilda Had Lived Most Of
Her Life ln The United states.
she Was Quite Notorious
At cambridge,
And Last Night,she Had
Actually slept ln My Bed.
lfAnyone Knew,
l'd Be A celebrity Overnight.
Are You Guy Malyon?
Yeah.
Julian Ellsworth.
Look, l'm lncredibly Grateful
About The Other Night.Gilda said You Were A Brick.
l Really can't
ThankYou Enough.
You saved My Bacon.
l'd Have Been Dismissed And Most Likely Disinherited
lfThey'd Found Her Here.
Glad To Have Been Of Help.
Listen, We're Having
A Bit OfA Beano At The Weekend.
Uh, Gilda Wanted Me To lnvite You.
Don't Know lfYou're Much OfA Jitterbugger,
But The Old Man's Away,
You see, And l'll Have The Run OfThe Place.
You Need A Girl,
Of course.
l can Line One Up.
When l Was A Freshman,
l Didn't Know What Girls Were.
l'm Afraid Mr. Ellsworth
Won'tAllow You ln Unless You First Drink
One OfThese.
The Password ls "Martini.
Thanks
Oh, God,
lt Tastes Like Paraffin!
One Doesn't Taste lt, Darling,
One simply swallows.
Ah, New Blood.
Hello, Old Boy.
Julian!
You Girls should Want
To Dance With Me This Evening
Because Gilda Has Got Herself
stranded ln calais.
Poor Gilda. Do come Through.
Please
calais ls such
A Dreadful Place.
Hello, Guy.
Hi.
Glad You could Make lt.
You're The Troubled Boy Whose Girlfriend
Julian ls Planning To Monster.
Are You sad?
Nah, l'm Thrilled For Her.
You Don't Mind
lf she Gets Debauched?
so Long As The Debaucher's
From A Fucking Good Family, l couldn't care Less.
Do You lmagine You're Being
lncredibly Daring Using Words Like That?
Ah, You should
Try 'Em sometime.lt's Good For constipation.
l'm Going To Feel
so Wicked ln The Morning.
WhatAre You Writing?
An Ode
To YourTummy Button.
Gilda.
sir Knight.
Don't Go Up There.
Why shouldn't l Go Upstairs?
There's An Orgy Goin' On.
sounds Promising.
My Partner ForThe Evening's
The Main course.
Your Partner lsn't Molly
Twelvetrees,ByAny chance ls she
Yeah. she's ln
Danger Of catchin' A cold.
Julian's Writin' A Poem
On Her stomach.
Oh, WhatA cad.
Don'tYou Mind?
l Feel sorry For Molly.
He's A Terrible Poet.
You're very Modern,
Aren'tYou?
l Don't Feel
very comfortable Here.
l Feel Guilty
Being Around All This Wealth.
lt's JustA Game.
Don't Take lt seriously.
lt's Not Much OfA Game.lfYou're Out OfWork
And Trying To Feed A Family.
Fortunately, l'm Not.
And NeitherAre You.
l Only came Here Tonight
To see You.
There, l've said lt.
Good.
You Look Lovely.
You Don't.
our Eyes Are All Red. You Look Like A Bloodhound.
You Have Excellent
Recuperative Powers.
What lf someone comes?
We Were Here First.
Oh, God!
Think sunday school. What?
Think sunday school.Why?
Because This ls A Team sport.
Mmm, ThankYou, Unwin.
l Thought
lt Might Be Prudent To
Good ldea.
Good Morning, Unwin.
l ThoughtWe Might Uh Have Breakfast
On The Terrace This Morning.
Gilda!
What On Earth
Are You Doing Down Here?
appy Birthday, Darling.
Who's That?
Oh, My Friend, Guy.
You Really Had
Your Hands Full When l Got ln.
Gilda,
He's Avirtual Primitive.
l Know.He's The Piltdown Man.
l'm Planning To Exhibit Him.
Julian, Nothin' Happened.
l Don't ForA Moment
ThinkAnything Did.
Apart From Us Writing sonnets
All Over Each Other.
All Right. Do You Mind Getting Up,
Please, Before Anyone Else sees You?
Be A Darling And Lend Me
Your Dressing Gown,Would You?
Gilda, What Have You
Got On UnderThere?
Well, seeing lt's Your Big Day,
l'm Wearing My Birthday suit ln Your Honor.
Thought For certain l Would HearThat Gilda And Julian
Had Broken Up,
But Nothing seemed
To Have changed Between Them.
A Few Weeks Passed,
And JustWhen l'd Resigned
MyselfTo Never Being With HerAgain,
something Unexpected Happened.
The Divorce Was At Least 12 Years Ago.
Yeah, she Must Be Devastated.
can l Join?
That's 5 shillings
Annual Membership Fee.
l Read AboutYour Mother.
lt Must Have Been Awful.
she Was A strangerTo Me,
Really.
But How Have You Been?
Practicing My Billiards.
l Wanted To see You,
To Tell You That l'm Leaving England.
Why?
The Wanderlust Has Got Me.
l Want To Travel.
Where Will You Go?
l Loved The Arabian Nights When l Was Younger.
Maybe l'll start There.
Would You Like
A Traveling companion?
You Have To Finish
Your Degree.
Does Julian Know?
l'll Leave Him A Nice Letter.
You're The One Friend From This chapter
l'd Like To Keep.
3 Weeks Later, Gilda Left England
And so Began
Our One-sided correspondence.
For she Was Never ln One Place Long Enough For My Letters
To catch Up With Her.
AfterAYear,
she stopped Writing.
By The Time l Graduated, And Began Teaching
ln The East End Of London,
l'd Managed To Finally
Put Her Behind Me.
Aid For spain
civil War Had Broken Out ln spain,
And l Was campaigning
ForThe Republican side
ln lts lncreasingly
Desperate FightAgainst The Fascists.
Tiberius ls ln A Bad Mood!
Where Are Those slaves?
We'll see How Brave You Are
ln The coliseum.
Take Away
Their Drinking Water.
l Hadn't Had A Letter
From Her ForAlmostAYear.
But Gilda Always Had
An Uncanny sense OfTiming.
she Was Back ln Paris,
Telling Me AWhole
New chapter Of Her Life Was Beginning,And Demanding l visit Her.
Once More, Nothing Else
ln The World Existed For Me.
Bonjour.
Guy! You came! And so soon!
Well, You Finally
sent Me An Address.
LookAtYou.
suddenlyYou're A Man.
l Even shave Now.
How Long can You stay?
Only Till Tomorrow.
l Have To Work.
That's Ridiculous.
You Have To stay ForAt LeastA Month.
You'll Be Able
To see My show.
What sort Of show?
You'll see Tonight.
l saw You ln A Film
As A slave ln Ancient Rome.
Wasn't lt Ludicrous?
How Did You Get The Part?
l MetAn American cameraman And Went Back To, Uh,
Hollywood With Him.
At First l Wanted
To Be An Actress,
But Then l--l Got More
lnterested ln cameras.
l'd Pick His Brains
ln Bed Every Night.
Are You Married Yet?
Not Quite. Good.
l'm sure You Have
A Menagerie OfAdmirers.
so What Do You Do
AfterWork?
l Raise Money
For Republican spain.
l Forgot
You Had A conscience.
Max! This ls Guy.
He JustArrived From London.
Welcome To Paris.
Are You Here
ForThe Opening?
He Doesn't Know Anything About lt, so He'll Be
completely Objective.
Right.
Where Are You staying?
There's A Hotel One Of My Friends Like,
JustAround The corner.
He's staying Here.
He And Mia can sing
Each OtherTo sleep.
Good.
This ls Going To Be
lncredibly Glamorous, lsn't lt?
And l'm Going To Be
lncredibly Dowdy.
You're British.
People Expect lt.
Do You Mind?
so Max ls A Lover?
He Owns The Gallery.
Actually,
He's Good company,
But He's Become Extremely
Proprietorial Lately.
He's On very Thin lce.
Then l Hope
lt Melts
Don't sulk.l Didn't Know
You Were coming so soon.
And Anyway,
l'm sure You're Not sleeping Alone
ln London Every Night.
Moments OfYearning.
Lust, Vanity, And Joy.
Loves Won And Lost.
lt's An HonorTo Be The First To Host The Work
OfThis Gifted New Photographer.
Finally, As A Bonus, May l Present
A Living sculpture
created Especially
ForTonight?
The Pictures Were Good OfTheir Kind.
But The sculptures Were something Else.
The Trouble ls Now
We're Never Going To see Them Again.
You should Film Them, Gilda.
Record Them For Posterity.
They Need To Be Live,so People can Lean Over,
And smell The skin OfThe Models.
Mmm, Does ThatWorryYou, Mia?
Having People sniffing
Around You Like Dogs?
l'm A sculpture,
so l lgnore Them.
WhatAboutYou, Guy?
Have You seen Anything
Like That ln England?
No, l Haven't.
Guy Thinks
Art should Be Political.
ln London, He spends Most Of His Time campaigning
For Republican spain.
German Artists spent The Last 15 Years Lampooning The Nazis,
And Had No EffectAtAll.
At Least They Tried.
Rather Pointless lfAll TheyAchieve ls A Ticket
To One OfThose camps.
And The satisfaction
Of Knowing They Had The courage OfTheir convictions.
Well, Here's
To Judicious cowardice.
No, No, No, No, No. Here's To Mia,
Whose Beauty lnspired Us All.
You should Model
For coco chanel.l could lntroduce You.
Mia's Training
To Be A Nurse.
she Only Models
ln Her spare Time
And l Have
An Exclusive contract.
But l Do Feel
l've seen You Before.
l Never ForgetA Face.
Perhaps You saw Me
At Le Grand Jeu.
so How Do You carry On
Your crusade For spain?
Do You sit On A committee And Hand Out Pamphlets
ln The street?
And lfYou Really Feel so strongly,
Why Don'tYou Enlist ln The lnternational Brigades?
l Plan To
At The End Of school Term.
Are You serious?
-Yeah, l Am.
Well, The Line Must Be Drawn.
Fascism Must Be stopped
Before lt Engulfs Us All.
Good Night.
You've Become so serious.
The World Has Become serious.
We'll All Die
Of Gravity.
l'm sorry
l can't Be With You Tonight.
Do You Even Like Him?
Occasionally.
But l Admit, He's Trying A Little
Too Hard At The Moment.
Mia, Get Out
OfThe Bath! You'll Turn lnto A Prune!
l Take lt Le Grand Jeu
ls A cabaret?
Burlesque. striptease.
she came Here
With Nothing. she's My Protege.
l Want The 3 Of Us
To Be Friends.
Gilda, Are You coming?
l'll see You
ln The Morning.
This One's comfortable.
l Used To sleep Here
When l First came.
How Long
Have You Been Here?
HalfAYear.
Whereabouts ln spain
Are You From?
Asturias.
ln The North.
Don't Be Jealous.
He's Not special To Her.
None OfThem Are.
He Wants You To Hear.
He's Afraid
Of Her Feelings ForYou.
Yeah, Well,
l'm Afraid Of Mine For Her.
Who ls lt?
lt's Me.
so Pathetically Melodramatic Walking Out On Me Like That?
How Dare You Be
What's There To Drink?
l'm Bone Dry.
Hello.
Uh, This ls Linda.
Hello
l'm sorry l Woke You.
l Got seasick On The Boat,
And Then l Tried To Eat something To settle My stomach,
But The Food
ln This country ls Awful.
ls This A Bad Time?
What Do You Think?
Does Max Know You're Here?
Max Was Being very Boring AboutYou,
so l Expelled Him.
l'm Not Going To LetYou Go
And GetYourself Killed.
You'd Probably come BackWith Your Brain shot Out.
conversations Would Be lncredibly One-sided.
Now, Get Me A Blanket
And You can Go Back To Bed.
WhatAre You Doin'?
l'm Going.
Well, she's sleepin' ln There. l'm Just Getting Her
some Bedclothes.
Guy, l Was With You
At The cinema.
AfterYou saw Her,
You Hardly spoke The Rest OfThe Evening.
And When You Got Her Letter,
You couldn't Get On A Train Fast Enough.
l'm Off.
There's No Need.
l've GotAn Early start
ln The Morning.
And Besides, l Think
l'm A Bit ln The Way.
You Didn'tAsk Her
To Leave, Did You?
No.
seeing As she Has,
l suppose l Don't Have To sleep Rough.
You've no idea how iadored you at cambridge.
And when iarrived here,nothing had changed
ltwas miraculous
so How Did You And Mia Meet?
l saw Her On The street.
Followed HerTo A cafe.
You choose People,
Don'tYou?
"come lnto My Life."
sometimes You see complete strangers
But There's something special About Them,
And You Think,"l should Really TryAnd Talk To Them
Because l'll Never see Them Again," ButYou Don't,
Because lt's Not Done.
But lt's All Fated, Anyway.
lt Had To Be Your Room
l came lnto That Night ln cambridge.
What Do You Mean?
The Whole Room Was Familiar.
l'd seen lt Before ln Dreams.
lt Probably Reminded You
Of some Place You've Been Before.
We Just Think
We've Dreamt Things.
You're so complacent!
Maybe lt can Jump
Forward ln Dreams.
Maybe lt Doesn't Have
To Obey Physical Laws.
But lf My Room Was Already There,
Then ThatWould Mean Everything Was Fixed ln Advance.
You Think
l Was Being spontaneous,
But l Was Always
Going To Do That.
JustAs l Was Always
Going To Win This Argument.
That's What l Learned At school.
l've Got To Work OutWhat l'm Going To Do.
Resign From YourTeaching
ForA start.
And What Do l Live On?
l'll Give You A Job
As MyAssistant.
How's The Pay?
Good Bonuses.
l Listen To Them Every Night.
Do We Keep You Awake?
she can sleep
Through Anything.
she Has Amazing conversations
ln Her sleep.3 Or4 People.
sometimes speaking
Different Languages.
so, Do You Accept?
You Odious Little Boy.
How's That?
Now The, Uh,
Horrible Little Girl Has Turned Around.
Hello. We're Just Off
To The Pictures
so, Guy,
You Have Forsaken London
ForThe city Of Light?
lt seems so.
Mmm-Hmm.
Mia!
change ln Here.
Why?
He came To The Exhibition.He Won't Be seeing Anything
He Hasn't seen Before.
You Were Part
Of My sculpture. You're Flesh And Blood Now.
WhatAre You Doing
Going OutWith Him, Anyway?
l'm curious.
You Know What They sayAbout Him.
You should Hear
What They sayAboutYou.
Oh, Your Dresser
Has Excelled Herself.
so You're Having Dinner
Afterwards?
We Haven't Decided. What Time
should l Bring Her Back?
Oh, shut Up
see You Both Later.
Bonsoir.
You're Avery Lucky Man,
Living With 2 Beautiful Women.
But Gilda still
Doesn'tApprove Of Me.
sometimes l Think
she's Jealous.
You seem To Have A calming
lnfluence On Her.
she Used To Move ln Wild circles,
But l'm sure You Know That.
And You Don't care.
No, l Don't.
very commendable.
he PastAnd The Future Are lrrelevant.
The Moment ls Everything.
You Know, At First l ThoughtYou Were An ldealist, A Bore.
ButYou're One Of Us,
AfterAll.
Tell Me,
As One Man To Another,
What Does Gilda
Like ln Bed?
As One Man To Another?
That's None OfYour Business.
come On, Mia.
Dance For Us.
Please?
lt's christmas.
Yes, come On
All Right.
Why Not?
WhatAre You Two
Talkin' About? Huh?
You.
And WhatAre You sayin'?
WhatAre You saying?
WhatAre You saying? WhatAre You saying?
lt's Past 4:00. We've Almost Lost
christmas Day.
come On.
l'm starving.
An American Turkey Made An lll-starred Bid
For Freedom AtWhipsnade Zoo Today,
Only To Touch Down ln The Arctic
Fox Enclosure With Mixed Results.
A Happy Ending ForThe Fox,
Less so ForThe Turkey.
The Weather ln...
l'm sorry.
l Don't Understand AWord.
You Don't Need To.
lfAn Animal Made Hose sounds,
You'd Know ltWas Evil.
All He's saying ls ThatWhen Greater Germany ls Restored,
He'll Have No OtherTerritorial claims.
And You Believe Him?
l Used To Paint Pictures
OfAll These Places When l Was Home From Boarding school.
can l see Them?
l Threw Them All Away.
l Had No Talent Of My Own. l JustWanted To Be Van Gogh.
Bonjour, Francoise.
Bonjour, Mademoiselle.
WhatAre You Doing, Father?
l Am, Uh, saving
The Lives Of lnsects.
l've Never seen You
so compassionate.
l Don't Like
The Popping sounds They Make.
WhyAre You
Wearing Your Uniform?
There Was A Rally ln Rheims,
The croix-De-Feu.
Our Popular Front ls Not
Quite so Popular Here ln The country.
The World ls veering
Towards Moscow,
Which ls A Little Worrying
For Us Minor Landowners.
But, Uh, Politics Has Never
Been One Of My Daughter's stronger Points.
Take Your Feet OffThe couch,
Darling.
charles Besse.
Guy Malyon.
Uh, You'll Be Joining Us
For Dinner?
Guy Recently Moved Here
From England.
so, Um, How's The,
Uh, Acting?
l Only Did That One Film. ltWas Never
Going To Be A career.
Oh. Whatever Next?
l can't Keep Up With Her.
First ltWas Dance,
And Her Room Was Full Of Ballet.
Then she Discovers stendhal,And, Of course, she Wants To
Be The World's Greatest Novelist.
And Then There Was, Uh,
What, Painting?
One Thing l Learned
From You, Father, Was NeverTo Dwell On One's Mistakes.
Where's My stepmother?
she's Probably Out
Walking The Dogs.
Uh, What Happened To That,
Um, That Max Fellow?
A Light Of Other Days.
l sired A Dilettante,
ln EveryAspect Of Her Life.
That's Why l ResentYou, Father,
For Bequeathing Me such superficial Genes.
They sayAWinemaker's Taste ls The Last Of His senses
To Desert Him.
But Gilda Tells Me ThatYou're Not
Much lnterested ln Wine, Mr. Malyon.
l Was Brought Up On Guinness.
We Drink Guinness ln France.very Good
ForAn Upset stomach.
The Old Hair OfThe Dog.
lndeed.
Why, Gilda, You're Looking
very Fetching Tonight.
she Likes To startle Me
ByWearing Her Mother's Things.
l Think she lntends To Make Me Feel Guilty.
You see, she Blames Me For Her Mother's Death.
l Don't Blame You, Father.
Fate Deals some People
A Rotten Hand, That's All.
Fate ls An Excuse
For People Who sufferA Failure Of Nerve.
so ltWas Her Fault, Was lt?
Oh, No, No, NotAtAll.
lt's Absolutely
And completely My Fault. l Am An lnsensitive Brute.
You see, Darling?
You Married A Beast.
l Married A Beast
Because l'm A Huntress.
And lf l can't Tame You,
l'll shootYou.
Ooh. Then l Must
Mend MyWays.
lsn't, Uh, Your Birthday
coming Up soon, Dear?
Now, We Must Do something
To celebrate This Year.
You Know l Never
celebrate My Birthdays.
lfYou're Afraid Of Birthdays Already,
You'll Be AWreckWhen You're MyAge.
l can't lmagine
Ever Being That Old.
ThankYou, Gilda.
There's something About That House That
Turns Me lnto A Monster.
l Didn't Like His Politics,
But l Enjoyed The Repartee.
He Ends Up Humiliating
All His Women.
You saw Her,
How Hard she Was Trying.
All He Wants Her For ls To show Her Off
To His shooting Friends.
Mia?
Mia, We're Back.
That Bastard.
You Don't Have To
Go To Work Today.
l'm All Right.
Mia...
should We
Tell The Police?
she Was
A striptease Dancer.
They'd say
she Asked For lt.
Then l'll Go Round
And see Him Myself.
And End Up ln A cell?
He Has Powerful Friends.
Lucien?
Gilda Besse.
Mia Doesn't Know
l'm calling.
Oh, she GotA Little
carried Away The Other Night.
Yes. Yes, That's Right.
Look, l Like lt The WayYou Do.
And l'm--l'm stronger
Than she ls.
l ThoughtWe should Meet. l see.
Guy?
-Yeah?
Max Wants To Have Lunch Today.
He Wants To TalkAboutAnother Exhibition.
Do You Mind?
No, Of course Not.
You should Take Mia
To A Film Or something.
she Needs To Get Out.
hat's A Good ldea.
Maybe A comedy.
l ThoughtYou Might
change Your Mind.
My English Friend Tells Me
l'm very stubborn.
l Assume He Doesn't Know
Where You Are?
No One Does.
Perhaps l should
Lock The Door.
Why Did You Decide
To Become A Nurse?
l Wanted To Be A Dancer.
My FatherWas A coal Miner.
An Anarchist.
Our House Was Full Of Politics
All The Time,
But l Would Always Be
Running Away To Dance.
2 Years Ago, They Declared
A socialist Republic ln Asturias.
A House ln Our street
Became A Hospital.
l Tried To Help,
But l Didn't Know Anything.
And People Were Dying ln MyArms.
And Then The soldiers came.
l Tried To stop Them From Taking My Brother,
And That's When They Hurt My Leg.
AfterThat, l Knew
l couldn't Be A Dancer.
And l Wanted To Help People.
so That's Why
l Am Becoming A Nurse,
And Why l Need
To Go Back To My country.
Hello.
How Did lt Go?
ltWas Fine.
so You're Doing
Another Exhibition?
We Played Around
With A Few Different ldeas.
l Did Most OfThe Talking.
WhyAre You Two
Looking so Miserable?
Trois
cognacs.
We saw A Newsreel
On spain.
You Were supposed To Be
cheering Her Up.
ltWas My ldea.
We Wanted To see What Else
Was Going On ln The World.
There Will Always Be Wars
While There Are People Dying To Be Martyrs.
Go On. say How Guilty
You Feel.
Afterwards, We sat Out
ln The Gardens.
l'm serious. You Need To Get lt
Out OfYour system.
Because You Feel Guilty
That Life ls Good Here,
While Terrible Things
Are Happening There.
And AfterYou've Talked About lt,
You'll Feel Better,Because You've shown You care.
To You,For Getting Rid
OfYour Guilt.
And You,For Getting Rid
To Us.
You Live ln A cocoon.You Don't Think
About The World Outside.
l Give MyAllegiance
To Those Around Me.
We share The World,
WhetherWe Like lt Or Not.
And You can share My Bed As Long
As You Don't Bring Your Newsreels Or Newspapers lnto lt.
Marry Me.
What?
l'm serious.
lf l Woke One Morning And You'd Turned
lnto A Husband, l'd Flee.
How Would lt Be
Any Different?
Once People Get Married,
They stop Trying.
Anyway, You Would
Want To Have children.
One Day.
You should Have One
With Mia. He'd Be Beautiful.
sometimes You say The First Thing
That comes lnto Your Head.
should l censor
What l say?
lf l Had A child,
l'd Have ltWith You.
My MotherWas Mad.
You've Met My Father.l Have Doomed Genes.
You Talk such Nonsense.
Guy.
What's Wrong?
Things Are Getting
Worse And Worse ln spain. here Are Friends Of Mine There Now.
And You Want To Go
And GetYourself Killed, Too, ln someone Else's War?
lt's Not someone Else's War.
lt's As Much Ours
As lf ltWas Happening Here.
We All share The same World.
Any Trained Nurses
They'll Take At Once.
l've GotAn Address
ForYou To Go To.
Who'll Take Any Trained Nurses
At Once?
l'm Going To spain.
l Didn'tWant To sayAnything
Until ltWas Definite.
And lt's Time For Me
To Go Back, Too
They Need Nurses There.
We've Been Living Together
ForAYear
Am l such An Ogre ThatYou
can't Even Discuss Your Plans With Me?
l Didn't see Much Point.
You Didn't see Much Point
ln Talking About Throwing AwayYour Life?
And Taking Mia With You?
Gilda.
l Was Always Going To Go Back
Once l Became A Nurse.
You Would Just Never Listen.
Of course. l should Have
seen lt coming.
You Feed Each Other's Guilt.
lt's Like A Disease.
Thank God
lt Hasn't lnfected Me.
Gilda's FatherWas
Traveling ln America,
And As A Kind Of Farewell,
We spent The LastWeekAt The chateau.
The sense Of Our Departure Hung Over Every Moment,
Though ltWas Never Mentioned
Again Until The Last Day.
l can't DrinkAny More.
Yes, You can.
We're Drinking ForAll Those Times
We Won't Be Able To Drink TogetherAgain
There'll Be Periods
Of Leave When l can come Back To Paris.
l Wouldn'tWant To see You lfYou came Back
With some Hideous lnjury.
come On, We're still Drinking.
You're Not Going To sleep.
Wake Up
l'm Tired.
Gilda, You're Drunk.
Why Do You Have To Go
As Well?
Traitor.
Wait. Wait.
Fire!
Forward
Poor Bastards.
They Didn't stand A chance.
My Dear Gilda,
Yesterday, ln An Ambush Behind The Enemy Lines,
l Killed AYoung Nationalist soldier.
How lnadequate
Those Words seem.
He Was clutching A Locket
When He Died,
With A Photograph
OfAYoung Woman.
l suppose, As l Write This,she's Waiting For News Of Him,
Hoping Against Hope He ls safe.
Dearest Gilda,still No Word From You,
Which Breaks My Heart.
l Know That To You
All Wars Are Useless,
And For Us To Risk Our Lives ls A Betrayal
Of Ourselves And OfYou.
But My country's A Part Of Me.
And lf l Was Not Here,
l Would Be Betraying Myself,And Even More, My Brother.
Believe Me,My Being Here Does Not Mean
l Love You Any Less.
Forgive Me lfYou can,
And Know That l Think OfYou
All The Time.
l Wonder lfYou Are Writing
To Either Of Us.
But l Do Beg You,
At Least, To Write To Guy.
His Unit ls At Teruel
Where The Fighting ls Especially Bitter
And Made Worse
By The lntense cold.
l can't stay.
We're Operating
ln A Few Moments.
l Know.
We Treated Men
From Your UnitA Few Days Ago.
That's How l Knew
You Were Here.
l Asked AboutYou.
They said
You Have No Nerves.
You're Always The Quiet One
ln The center OfThe storm.
lf l Am, lt's Because
l'm Too Tired To Be Frightened.
When Do You
Finish Your shift?
We Never Know.
Where Are You Tonight?
Not Far From Here.
lt's An Old Tannery.
l Know lt.
lf l can, l'll come.
Mia You Must Be Dead
On Your Feet.
No. l--l Have
A secretWeapon.
lt's strong Enough To Help You Forget
WhatYou've seen During The Day.
Have You Heard From Her?
l've Had Other Letters,
But None From Her.
And You?
No.
WhyWon't she Write?
Guy,she Loves You More Than
she'll EverAdmit.
And One DayYou'll Be
TogetherAgain, l Know lt.
These Last Few Days,
l've Been Asking Myself lfAny OfThis ls Worth lt.
Perhaps she Was Right. The World should Be Left
To LookAfter ltself
You Know
You Don't Believe That.
ButWhatAre We Achieving?
With The Germans And The ltalians
On Their side,lt's OnlyA Matter OfTime.
But ln That Time,Maybe The Rest OfThe World
Will Begin To Realize What's Happening.
You Were Always
The sensible One.
Was l?
Not ln My choice Of Men,
Remember?
We should Try To sleep.
You Know, Gilda Once said
We Two should Have A child.
You Know she And l
Were Lovers?
l Knew Underneath.
l Wanted To Tell You,
But she Always said You Were Too British.
she Was Probably Right.
Those Were The Happiest Times Of My Life,
The 3 Of Us Together.
And You And l came Here.
We Had No choice.
How can l Be so Tired
And still Feel Jealous?
l Was Jealous OfYou
All The Time.
she'd Be Pleased.
Everything Needs
Her Blessing.
Here's Your Lift.
My Doctor Friend.
He's convinced
l'm some Kind Of saint Because l Never Go With Anyone.
He Was so Relieved
When l said l Wanted To come And see You
He lnsisted On
Giving Me A Lift Himself.
l Finally Got Rid Of My Halo.
There ls No 2nd sight.
We Grope Towards
Our Future Blind.lt's KinderThatWay.
On The Morning Of Her Final Day,
she came To Her Death clear-Eyed,Brave, Unknowing.
And When The snow Melts,
spring Has come. There ls An End To War.
One small Flower,Blessed, Unique,
Will Flower No More.
Gilda,
l Have To Tell You
That Our Dear Friend ls Dead.
l saw Her
Just Before lt Happened.
she Was so Beautiful And Had Become so Wise.
Far strongerThan Me
A Few Months Later, As The Forces OfThe Republic
Began To Disintegrate,
l crossed Back lnto France
With The Remnants Of My Unit.
All Our Efforts
Had come To Nothing.
The War ln spain Was Lost.
l Am speaking To You From The cabinet Room
At 10 Downing street.
This Morning, The British
Ambassador ln Berlin
Handed The German Government
A Final Note
stating That Unless We Heard
From Them By 11:00,
That TheyWere Prepared
At Once To Withdraw TheirTroops From Poland,
A state OfWar
Would Exist Between Us.
l Have To Tell You Now
That No such Undertaking Has Been Received
And That consequently
This country ls AtWarWith Germany.
The WarAgainst The Fascists
ln spain Was OnlyA Rehearsal.
The Greater struggle
Was About To Begin.
Less Than AYear Later, Poland, Norway, Holland,
Belgium, And France Were Overrun,
And The Germans
Entered Paris.
l Doubted l Would Ever
see HerAgain.
MyWarWas
ln The Field Of lntelligence.
And Early ln 1944,l Was sent To Establish Links
With Resistance Fighters
Based ln The countryside
Near La Manche.
ln The Late spring,l Was Transferred To Paris.
6 Long Years Had Passed since l Was Last There.
My coverWas As An Official
Working ForA Firm Manufacturing Rolling stock
ForThe Hard-Pressed
French Railways.
And some Time After l Arrived, l Was Waiting
ForA Rendezvous.
Tankyou
How"your mother
she's back on herfeet
Thankyou A pastis
Pleased to meetyou
There's a delay
He'll come attwo
l'll stay since he knows me
so let's have lunch
Good idea
Red wine and a coffee
what's wrong
lt's alright
l'm starving
Did she see Me? l Wasn't sure.
ButAfterThe lnitial shock,
How could l Be surprised?
Gilda Didn't see The World
As Others Did.
she Was Looking After Herself,
Bravo
3 Mornings l sat
Across The Road Waiting ForYou.
You Mustn't come Again.He could come Here
AtAny Time, And Everyone Watches.
They'll Have seen You come lnto The Building,
The Patron And His Wife,From The cafe.
Yeah, Well,
They Don't Think Much OfYou There.
Of course Not.
And You Don't care?
Did l Ever care
What People Thought Of Me?
l'd Like To Believe That
Once You cared What l Thought.
Why, Gilda? Why This?
l Never Much Liked My Own company,
You Know That.
Yeah, ButWith One OfThem?
lt's JustA Game.
Not Now.
l'm Glad You're Alive.
You Know About Mia?
she Loved You, You Know?
As Much As l Did.
You should Go.
We could Leave Paris.
Make OurWay To The coast.l Have The Papers.
Don't Be Absurd.
Are You ln Love With Him?
This German?
Or ls lt JustA convenience?
A Business Arrangement,Like With Max?
ForThe Duration
OfThe Exhibition?The Duration OfThe War?
Go Out The BackWay.
When We Were Making Love Just Then,
You Felt ltAs stronglyAs l Did.
Yes.
Our Bodies Were
Always Good Together.
ForgetAbout Me, Guy,
As l Have You.
You're Out Of My Life Now.
Hello, sir.
When They Told Me You'd Been sitting
AtA cafe 3 Mornings ln A Row,l Didn't Believe Them.
Now l Find lt's Because
You Were Waiting To see An Old Girlfriend.
A Girlfriend Who Happens To Be Hobnobbing
With A German Officer.
Do You Realize The Risk
You're Taking?
The RiskYou're Taking
With All Of Us Here?
You're LuckyYou Didn't
Wake Up With YourThroat cut.
Did You Know she Was lnvolved
With A German?
Yes, sir.
And YetYou still
Went To see Her?
l've Known HerA Long Time.
l've A Good Mind To Have London Pull You Out.
heyWon't Have lt,
Because There's No One With Your credentials
can come ln At This short Notice.
l Won't Be seeing HerAgain.
lfYou Do,
l'll Kill You Myself.
You're so Beautiful.
ltWas The Right size, Yes?
l Feel very special.
One Day, l
Will GetYou stockings.
When The War ls Over.
(speaking German)
l Want To speakYour Language.You Promised
You'd Teach Me.
ButWe Have Our Own Private Language,
You And l.
And When The Allies
Win The War,
We'll All Be speaking
English ln Our sleep.
To Think, lf l Had Been
At cambridge One Year Later,
We Might Have Met Then.
Here We Go Again.
You seem A Little
FarAway Tonight.
l'm Here.
l Wonder
Who's Gettin' lt Tonight.
You Were Good At The Meeting.
You Got lt Just Right.
l'm sorry
l Followed You That Day.
No, You Had Every Reason.
l Know What lt's Like
To Love someone.
ThankYou.
(speaking French)
Why Do You
Let Them lnsultYou?
lf Our Roles Were Reversed And This Was Berlin,
You'd Find Yourself Doing The same.
And Expect To Be Punished.
l'm Angry Because--
l Don'tWantAnything
To spoil Tonight OfAll Nights.
Why Tonight? Because...
Because
Because lt's Your Birthday.
You've Always Refused
To Tell Me, My Darling.
And l Know lt's AWoman's Prerogative,
But l Wanted To Know so We could celebrate.
Forgive Me,
l--l checked Your Papers.
My Puppet, You're Upset?
ButWhy? 33.
l Thought 28 At Most
Open lt. Please?
so we're on standby
Go Down To The Lavatories
And Put On The clothes There,
My Love.
They Picked Up The Man
You Were Meeting, Bisquet.
How Did You-
There's A Bicycle Outside.
You Have About 2 Minutes.
Remember cambridge?
The Next Morning?
How l Dressed Like A Boy?
Gilda
l Had No ldea
ltWould Be You.
Give Me 30 seconds.
What Happened?
BisquetWas Picked Up
Last Night.
We Just Found Out. Who Tipped You Off?
The Woman l Went To see.
(speaking French)
This ls A surprise. l ThoughtYou Were On Alert.
We've Been stood Down.There's A storm
ln The channel.
No lnvasion
ln This Weather.
How Was Your Day?
Puzzling. Frustrating.
But NotAnymore.
l Was Elated. ln some Way,
somehow, she Was On Our side.
Before l could Even Think Of Finding AWay To see Her,
D-Day.
(Lisette speaking French)
(speaking French)
ForA Few Days l Was Looked After By The Priest.
And Then l Was Flown Back To Hospital ln England
l still Had No clear ldea
Of Gilda's lnvolvement ln The Resistance.
All l Knew Was That ln spite Of Everything,
When The WarWas Over, We Would Be TogetherAgain,
As Mia Had Foretold.
The MajorWill
see You Now, sir.
JustWait Here
ForA Moment, Please.
Long Time, Guy. -lt ls, sir.
lt ls, sir.
The First contact Didn't
come From Our side. she Approached Us.
ln Fact, ltWas More Than AYear Before l Discovered
Who she Was.
When l Realized ltWas Gilda,
l Was As surprised As l'm sure You Were.
Although l suppose
You Knew Her BetterThan l Ever Did.
Her First LoverWorked
ln stulpnagel's Offices.
she copied Documents From His Briefcase
With A Miniature camera. she's Good With cameras.
Then Passed Them On Through Her contact
ln A Beauty salon.
The lntelligence Officer she's With Now ls Much More circumspect.
But One Tip-Off she Gave Us
And When You Went To see Her,
You Were Putting All ThatAt Risk.
Why Didn't she Tell Me?
You Know Why. lfYou Were caught
And Tortured... ltWasn't Just ForYour Own Good
Paris ls ln chaos.The Resistance ls Trying To Liberate
The city Themselves,
And There's No Possible Justification
For sending You Back There.
But she ls very Resourceful,As We Both Know.
l Wouldn'tWorryAbout HerToo Much.
lt's Not The Germans
l'm Worried About.
Of course, lfYou Were To Go OfYour Own Accord,
l Wouldn't Do Anything To stop You.
You Got My Message? l'm Not coming With You
Gilda, Have You seen The People Out There?
l'll Be All Right lf l stay Here. When The Allies come
WhyWill You Not
come With Me?l can Take You To Germany.
l Know ltWon't Be Easy,
ButAt LeastYou'll Be safe.
l Don't Love You, Frans.
Oh, God!
No!
Well, My Love, l'm Trying To Make sense OfThings
Of How l Was, And How l Am Now.
l Have Always Believed
Our First Duty ls To Ourselves, To Live Life To The Full.
But l Have Also Been Haunted
ByAnother conviction,
That Everything
ls Preordained, Lying ln Wait,
And Time ls Running Out.
l seem To Have
charged Through My Life ln A Kind Of Panic.And Looking Back,
l Feel l Have Achieved
Little OfWorth Beyond Our Friendship
Yours And Mine, And Mia's.
Then One Day l Woke
And Found l Had Lost The 2 People
l cared For Most.
Only Then Did l Begin To Realize
ThatWe cannot Live Alone Aloof From The World,
And That To Believe We cannot Fight
Against Fate ls An Act Of surrender.
You Were RightWhen You said That Once l cared
ForYour Opinion Of Me,
ButWrong ln Thinking
l Ever stopped caring.
l Love You.