And so, heh...
Heh.
I chose jellyfish as my favorite...
You all fed? Yeah?
Yeah...
Marcy! Marcy May!
Where are you going?
Marcy, what are you doing here?
Worried about you.
Well, I'm fine.
Yeah? And Patrick is worried about you.
I just wanted to come into town.
Oh, I could have given you a ride.
I wanted to walk.
Through the woods?
Can I get you something?
No, thank you.
Are you done?
Yeah.
Uh...
You're not gonna finish that?
Okay, thanks.
Mm.
Ready to go?
Not right now.
No?
Hey, don't do that. Come here.
You're shaking.
Calm down.
All right. You take care of yourself.
Hello?
He Ho ?
Martha?
Yeah.
Where are you? Where have you been?
Uh, I'm not sure. I'm upstate, I think.
You're in New York?
Yeah, I think.
When did you get back?
How long have you been here?
Martha?
Martha, what's wrong?
I don't know. Um...
I should go back.
Go back where?
Martha, what happened? Are you okay?
Um, I have to go. Um...
I can't stay gone, so...
No, no, no, don't go.
What are you talking about?
Martha.
I'm sorry for calling.
Please don't hang up.
Don't hang up the phone.
Find out where you are
and! will come get you.
Martha?
I can't wait that long.
What do you mean? Tell me where you are
and I will come right now.
No, it's okay, you don't have to.
Martha, I wanna see you. Please.
Martha?
Martha.
I made you some tea.
Thanks.
You're dripping everywhere.
Ted should be up from the city soon,
make us some dinner.
I'm pretty tired.
Is it okay if I just go to bed?
Sure.
Get a good night's sleep tonight
and you'll be as good as new tomorrow.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Hey.)'...
Well?
She seems okay.
What did she say?
Not much.
She's really tired.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Where's she been?
She had some boyfriend.
They were living in the Catskills.
What?
It's okay.
Heh, it's not really, Lucy.
It's fine.
She's here now.
Hmm.
How long is she gonna be staying again?
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh, Martha.
Welcome.
Hi.
Great to finally meet you.
Yeah.
Did you sleep all right?
Mm-hm.
Good.
So how do you like our house?
It's nice.
It's just a rental.
Yeah, well, I love it.
Mm.
I didn't know there was a lake.
Mm. Yeah.
Do you still like to swim?
- You don't still live in the city?
- Heh, heh.
We do. We just like to come up here
on weekends and holidays.
You know. Ted is working
on this new building downtown...
and as soon as it's finished...
we're taking one of the apartments.
Do you wanna see pictures?
Do you think she's excited
to have you back?
This is just the view, and obviously
the interiors aren't finished...
- but it's nice, right?
Mm-hm.
We were supposed to move in
in the spring...
but, uh, construction was halted, so
it's gonna be just a little while longer.
Yes, just a little while longer.
Okay, sorry, no more work talk.
Aren't you hungry?
Not really, sorry.
Well, you have to eat something.
It's okay,
I can make you something later.
Where are we?
Connecticut.
Well, how far are we?
From what?
Yesterday.
You mean from where I picked you up?
About three hours. Why?
I was just wondering.
Put out your cigarette.
Why?
Just do it.
Is that him?
Yeah.
Hey.)'...
Is this Martha?
Hi.
How you doing?
Great.
Oh, you've got a really nice place here.
It's as much yours as it is mine.
I thought you quit.
I did.
I worry for you.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize to me. It's your body.
Zoe, look after this girl.
For once in her life,
she deserves some real care.
I will.
She's been great.
Everyone's been really great.
Good.
Martha.
You look like a Marcy May.
Marcy was my grandmother's name.
Wow, there you go.
Heh.
I'm going in. Do you wanna join'?
Sure.
You coming?
In a minute.
Martha!
That is an interesting choice
of swim wear.
Martha, get out of the water.
- What?
- Get out of the water.
Why aren't you wearing any clothes?
What is wrong with you?
- You can't do that around here, you know.
- Why?
Because there are kids around.
People come by.
So?
You just can't, okay? Get out of the water.
We don't do that kind of thing. Get out.
You could have asked me.
I have a bathing suit you could borrow.
What's wrong with you? Jesus.
Hey, hey, Marcy.
- Max.
- Hey.
Where do they go at night?
Uh...
Pfft! I don't know. Heh.
I never get invited.
You wanna have a drink with me?
They won't be back for a few hours.
I shouldn't. I'm not gonna drink for a while, actually.
I think it's a good idea for me.
All right.
Wake up, everybody.
Good morning.
We switch out jobs each day
so we all know how to do different things.
Do you knit?
No.
I can learn, though.
Oh, no, that's okay.
You'll find your role.
It takes time for people
to find their role in a new family.
Mostly, we sell blankets in town
because we still need some money.
But once the farm is up and running,
we'll be self-sufficient...
and we'll never have
to worry about it again.
Hey. I'm sorry, Patrick. Hey.
What are you sorry for'?
Ahem.
Um, here.
How are you, man?
Good, you?
Feels like...
- It's a really great consistency.
- Yeah, and it's sticky.
And it holds together like glue.
- And it can flow around. Like...
- You should talk to her.
That's why I need to
figure out how to do it.
Yeah.
Yeah, you'll figure it out. Don't look...
How's everything going so far,
Marcy May?
- Good.
- Do you like it here?
Yeah, it's... It's great.
I want you to feel at home.
- I do, thank you.
Mm-hm.
I know people have abandoned you
your whole life.
Your father.
What?
I don't blame you
for not trusting people.
But if you're ever going to have
a meaningful relationship...
you need to let your guard down.
It's not your fault, but it's there.
And if you feel safe here,
and I hope you do, let us in.
We wanna help you.
Yeah. We think you're fucking awesome.
But if you're gonna live here...
you need to be a part of things.
Play another song.
Do "A Patch of Land."
It's not a song.
Good morning.
How are you feeling today?
Good.
Yeah? Good.
So, uh, I stopped by the juice place
and I got you a kale with ginseng.
Do you mind just putting your feet
off the counter?
I got you a kale and ginseng
because it's just...
I don't know,
I thought it might make you feel better.
If that doesn't appeal to you,
I also got a pineapple orange.
Yeah, that might be better. Thank you.
Okay.
Oh, and I also got you protein bars,
just in case you want a snack.
Why is the house so big?
The house isn't so big.
It's big for two people.
Well, yeah, but we like to entertain.
And sometimes friends come up
for the weekend...
sometimes we have parties.
It's just nice to have space.
So no one else lives here?
Of course no one else lives here.
You're married?
Yeah.
When?
April.
I tried calling you, but, uh, apparently
you got rid of your cell phone.
I lost it.
You didn't think to get a new one?
I got used to not having one.
Cocktails, anyone?
No, thank you.
Martha?
Mm-mm.
Was it a big wedding?
About 40 people.
Mostly Ted's family.
Did Aunt Dora come?
Ha, yes.
Did she smoke like a chimney
and complain about everything?
She's not that bad.
You didn't have to live with her.
You lived with Dora?
She lived with me after Mom died.
- And where were you?
- College.
Huh.
- She'd love to know you're okay.
- She hates me.
She does not hate you.
- Look at me. Come on.
Mm-mm.
- No.
- I don't have any pictures of you.
God, you're gorgeous.
It's really rather irritating.
There you go.
You don't need to shake it.
That's a myth.
- Is it true married people don't fuck?
- What?
No, heh.
Excuse me.
Put this on.
You're kidding.
Your clothes are disgusting. Try it.
Why does it matter?
Because it feels good to put on
something nice and comfortable.
It looks really good on you,
you little shit.
Whatever makes you happy, mama bear.
You're making fun of me,
and I think it looks really good on you.
What, ifs not good?
No, no, it's fine.
Uh, it's a bit dry.
It's not dry.
It just needs a little bit more salt,
that's all.
She seems better today.
Yeah.
I wish I didn't have to go tomorrow.
Well, let me take you.
No.
I don't want her to be alone.
You'll be nice to her, right?
I'm always nice.
Oh.
I know you feel like something bad
just happened, Marcy May.
But you have to trust me,
that wasn't bad.
That was truly good.
We've all been in this situation.
We wouldn't all still be here
if what happened in that room was bad.
We all love each other very much.
We're all together on this.
You have to trust us.
Do you believe me?
Yeah.
You're so lucky.
I'd give anything
to have my first time again.
Really?
Yeah.
It's so special.
I can't remember anything.
I just woke up and felt this pain.
That's the cleansing.
It's good. It means it's working
if you can't remember things.
You're cleansing yourself of the past
and the toxins.
You need to share yourself.
Don't be selfish.
I'm not.
So smile, then.
Enjoy this amazing night.
It only happens once.
Thanks.
Is that a new one, Max?
There's one right there.
Yeah. Is that a new song?
Yeah, I wrote it yesterday.
That was the first half.
Great.
That was nice.
Thanks, man.
Yeah.
All right. This is called "Marcy's Song."
Well, she's
She's just a picture
Who lives
Lives on my wall
Well, she's
She's just a picture
The reason, reason,
reason it is so small
The smile's so inviting
Ana' her body so rah'
Well, she's
She's just a picture
Just a picture
That's all
Well, you stand there
Stand there with the nightshade
Her dripping
Dripping down your hands
You ask me
Ask me about the lightning
The lady, lady, lady,
she understands
So dream for the future
Water for the sand
And the strangeness is wandering
Through many calling lands
You've been saying
the same thing to me for two months...
and I still don't have them.
I'm going into the meeting
in 14 fucking days.
Great. No, that's all I wanted to hear.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Cleaning.
I thought I'd help out more.
All right.
Ahh. I'm gonna take the boat out.
Do you wanna come'?
Is Lucy coming?
Uh, no, she had to run to the city.
Oh.
Come on,
I'll teach you how to drive the boat.
It's okay.
Come on.
Sorry.
It's going, it's going, it's going.
Okay. Okay.
All right.
Okay. All right. Okay.
Want one?
Yeah.
How's it been with Lucy?
Fine.
Is it strange to spend time together?
No. Why?
It's been a long time.
I don't know. It's normal, I guess.
Where is she?
She's at the doctor.
Why?
Getting a checkup.
We are trying to have a baby.
What?
I just can'! imagine it.
Lucy holding a baby.
Why?
Well, she wouldn't know
what to do with it.
Do you want a baby?
Mm-hm.
If she's happy, I'm happy.
So you're unhappy?
What, now? Ha-ha-ha.
No, no, no, she's doing well.
She's doing well.
Do you want another?
Here.
She is, um, relieved to have you back.
You know, you worried her.
Why?
Because you disappeared.
You hadn't called in two years.
I just lost track, I guess.
Well, it's a good thing to let people know
where you are, Martha.
People worry.
I didn't think Lucy would worry about me.
Well, she did.
Can I go swimming?
Hey, you don't need to ask.
- Jesus Christ.
- What?
- Martha, what are you doing?
- Nothing.
Jesus.
You can't just come in here like that.
Sorry.
Goddamn it, what's wrong?
I'm just having a hard time
sleeping alone.
All you do is sleep. Christ.
Just stay. Stay.
Why would you think it was okay
to come in here like that?
I don't know. it's a big bed.
You guys were on the other side.
You can't come into our room
when we're having sex.
That's not normal. it's private.
Sorry.
You don't need to apologize. Just...
I need you to understand
why it's not okay.
Okay.
Do you?
Yeah.
Well?
Because it's private and not normal.
Oh, God.
Just lie down, Martha.
- Oh, this is just brilliant.
- Don't go.
Just go to sleep.
I'm sorry you slept out here.
Thank you for being patient.
I didn't have much choice, did I?
I'm just trying to make sure she's okay.
I have two weeks a year
to come up here...
and try to relax.
I know.
I'm under pressure...
I know you are.
To get this building up and running
or the bank takes it.
That has nothing to do with Martha.
No, I guess my point is,
I just don'! need the extra stress.
I'm her only family.
You know, she needs to know
that she can depend on me right now.
- It's complicated.
- As complicated as it might be...
we can't ignore the fact
that her behavior is fucking insane.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Do you ever hear things
hit the roof at night?
No.
Maybe it's pinecones?
Where did you pick up gardening?
There was a garden where I lived.
You're good.
I'm good at some things.
I know you are.
Was he ever physical with you?
Who?
Your boyfriend.
What do you mean?
Did he ever hit you?
No.
You had a bruised ear...
and when you called me,
you were hysterical.
I never noticed.
Are you sure he didn't hit you?
Yeah.
You can tell me.
He never hit me.
I wish you felt more comfortable
talking to me.
I do.
So talk.
There's nothing to talk about.
I had a boyfriend, he lied to me, I left.
That's it.
Not everything has to be a big deal.
- Hey, don't stare.
- No.
No.
You okay?
Yeah.
He's right. I don't know why I'm so weak.
You're not.
You'll quit.
Who's that?
Her name is Sarah, I think.
You should handle her.
You think?
Yeah, you're ready.
Zoe can help, but you'll be great.
Jesus.
Hey, guys.
Hi.
Katie, this is Sarah.
Hi, Sarah.
Zoe and Marcy May.
Hi.
We share all this.
So if it fits, you can wear it.
Cool.
And this is where we sleep.
You can take any bed that's open
or, uh, you can sleep downstairs.
I'm hungry. Can we eat?
We don't eat until the evening.
Really?
You'll get used to it.
Your body doesn't need that much food.
Hi. Hi.
He's beautiful.
Who's the mother?
Katie.
But we all help out.
Is Patrick the father?
Uh-huh.
Come here. Oh, yeah.
Looks just like him.
Oh, oh.
All the kids here are boys.
He only has boys.
You're good with him.
Do you wanna hold him?
No. I don't...
I don't have to take care of them, do I?
No, not if you don't want to.
There are plenty of jobs you can do.
You'll find your role.
It takes time to find your role
in a new family, huh?
Yeah.
I called my dad today
to ask for money.
Does Patrick know?
Yeah, he asked me to.
Sometimes if there's something
we need, I'll call.
Well, how was it?
Fine. They're not bad people.
Did he give you the money?
Yeah. He thinks I'm on drugs.
Did you tell him that you're not?
No, that's why he gives it to me.
I guess he'd rather pay for it
than think I'm sucking dick for it.
I've done drugs.
Not a lot,
but I tried pretty much everything.
Except heroin.
It's good to try everything at least once.
You find out who you are.
What about drinking? Do you drink?
No.
I have, but I don't.
Good. We don't drink.
It makes you angry and less focused.
Don't get the wrong idea, Sarah.
We don't really talk to our old families.
I wouldn't call my dad anyway-
Marcy.
Hey.)'...
Hey, have you met Sarah?
Sally, yeah.
That's enough.
Half. Half is fine.
Okay.
Excuse me.
I can finish this if you wanna go to bed.
I don't mind.
Why don't you get some sleep?
Okay.
Hi.
What...? What do I have to do?
Nothing you don't want to.
Drink this, it will help you relax.
Thanks.
It's herbal. It starts the cleansing.
We've all done it
so there's nothing to worry about.
Why do I have to wear this robe?
Heh.
I know it's a bit silly
but it's just part of it.
Oh, my God.
You look amazing.
Thanks.
You know,
this is your special night with him.
Enjoy it.
You'll be great.
Yeah.
I don't feel well.
It's okay, just lie down.
Shouldn't I start cooking?
Well, I just made a salad
and Ted is cooking the fish.
I thought we were going to cook.
We cooked last night.
Oh, yeah.
Do you ever have that feeling where
you can't tell if something is a memory...
or if it's something you dreamed?
Not really. No.
Do you blame me for anything?
No.
Like what?
I don't know.
I'm trying to figure out
why we stopped talking.
I don't really think about it.
Really?
Well, we were far apart.
Sometimes I wonder if maybe
I couldn't have taken better care of you.
The past doesn't matter.
It does matter.
Well, I took care of myself.
I know you did, but sometimes
I think I could've done more.
Stop.
You really never think about it?
No.
You're not angry with me?
God, I know you don't think much of me...
but I knew what I was doing then
and I still do.
No, Martha, I think the world of you.
Sometimes I just think
I should have come home...
and made sure you went to college.
You had so much potential.
I don't need your guidance now...
and I didn't then.
I am a teacher and a leader.
You just never let me be that.
But now, I am... I know who I am.
A teacher and a leader?
What are you talking about?
- I am always...
- Dinner's ready!
I was the one who encouraged you
to push yourself, always.
You were the one who shut me out.
Martha...
Just because we're sisters...
doesn't mean we need to talk about
everything that comes into your head.
Dinner's ready.
Come on, don't be rude.
So, what are your plans, Martha?
For what?
Um, life.
I don't know.
Are you thinking about
what you could do for a job?
No.
You're at an age when you need to start
thinking about a proper career.
Why?
It is a part of adult life.
There are other ways to live.
Really?
Sure.
Like what?
I don't know.
People don't need careers.
People should just exist.
He's just saying we should start talking
about what you are interested in.
We can come up with some ideas
that we can put together...
But there are moments in my life when I
would love to just go to France and exist.
- You can do that if you want to.
- It is not that simple.
You know, it's not your fault,
but you learned to measure success...
by money and possessions.
It's just not the right way to live.
It's not the right way to live?
What is the right way to live exactly?
Martha, what is the right way
to live? Hm?
Is it, um, vanishing off the face of the earth,
not calling your family for two years...
or until they're worried sick,
is that the right way to live?
Or is it living without possessions
until you need someone...
and then turning up on our doorstep...
where you know you can get some?
Is that the right way to live? No, no.
You sit there,
lecturing us about our lives.
And so far, I have not witnessed one sign
that you have any values of your own.
You should remember
that you are living under my roof.
You are eating my food
and you should watch your mouth...
because you are rude.
You don't know anything about it.
Hello?
Who's this?
Zoe?
Is she not there?
She's not.
Where is she?
Who is this?
Who's this?
Marlene Lewis.
Marcy?
Steal.
Have you seen my brother?
He's got really red hair
and a bunch of freckles.
Good job.
- Very nice.
- Hey.
Let's mind our own beeswax, huh?
Heh, okay.
I'm seriously the best one at this
and no one will out-fast my hands.
Yes. Oh, God.
Oh, God, you are so hot
when you shoot.
You know that?
This just makes my willy hard.
Get off me.
Thank you. I'm set.
All right, Marcy, let's have fun.
Make sure your knees
are smooth and loose...
and your heart is in the right place.
Max, is this just an excuse to grape Marcy?
I'm teaching her how to shoot, okay?
And then you just squeeze.
Hi, Patrick.
Nice shot.
Hey.)'...
Focus.
Take a deep breath.
Feel the tension leaving your stomach
and moving to your hands.
Think of someone who hurt you,
who lied to you. Feel it.
Feel how they made you feel.
Let it build.
Let it transfer to the gun.
Building in the gun.
Breathe out.
Release.
Feels good, right?
Yeah.
Now try that.
What do you mean?
Shoot it.
They're living animals.
So shoot Max then.
Yeah, go ahead. Let's get it up.
Breathe.
- Go on.
- All right, fuck this.
Don't walk away from me, Max.
The cat has terminal cancer.
- It's in excruciating pain.
- I can't.
You know, Max has no substance.
He's just here to freeload,
be around the girls.
But you're different.
You're a teacher and a leader.
You don't see it
because no one let you believe it.
You're a teacher and a leader, Marcy.
Now prove it.
That cat reminds you of some fluffy thing
you think you used to love.
You're clinging
to some misguided emotion.
So I could spend my life being selfish,
living alone and using this gift for me...
but I've sacrificed
in order to be what you need me to be.
Why don't you trust me?
I do.
Then you shouldn't need me
to explain everything.
Why...? Why did you do that?
You said it was sick.
One of them was sick.
Zoe knew which one it was.
Sorry.
Try again?
My sweetheart
Come here.
Ready.
Aim.
You shouldn't smoke.
What?
I don't smoke.
Especially if you're trying to have a kid.
Maybe you should
mind your own business.
I can't deal with talking to anybody
right now.
Press them together.
I think that's better.
You look really pretty.
Thanks.
I see you, see you now
Smoking, drinking
Never, never thinking
Of tomorrow
Nonchalant
This guy...
Diamonds shining
Dancing, dining
Hi.
Um, everybody, I want you
to meet my sister. This is Martha.
Is that all you really want?
No, no, no
Sophisticated lady
I know
You miss the love you lost long ago
And when nobody is nigh
You cry
That was very cool.
What's your name?
I'm sorry?
Uh...
I'm Mike.
Um, can I get you something to drink?
I used to drink this.
Okay. Straight?
I thought you're not
supposed to drink, Mike.
I'm not drinking.
You think you're so fucking smart.
And when nobody is nigh
Martha.
Martha, are you all right?
Hey. Hey, what is going on?
He's a fucking liar!
Who?
We have to leave.
Okay, hey. Listen to me. What's going on?
We all have to leave. I know him.
Go into our room.
What's this?
We have to leave.
You don't wanna live with this.
Martha, get into my room.
- Let's go into the bedroom.
- Please.
What is wrong with you?
You're not listening to me.
I am. I don't know who
you're talking about.
He's fucking here!
All right, take it...
Please don't touch me!
You're not listening to me!
- Come on.
- Take a deep breath.
Stop!
Take a deep breath.
- Take a deep breath.
- Let go of me.
Martha, take a deep breath.
No. No.
What is going on?
I have no idea.
Martha, take a deep breath.
Come on.
You're all right. You're all right.
Martha, please try to breathe.
Please try to breathe.
Can you tell me what you're talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Please try to breathe.
There you go.
Swallow.
There you go. Okay.
Okay. Okay, look at me.
- Hi. Hey.
- What the fuck?
Um...
We can go.
What do you want?
Nothing.
No, there's no need for that.
Um, we're leaving now.
So come on, guys.
Hmm?
Sorry.
- Jesus Christ.
- Calm down.
If you calm down, no one will get hurt.
What do you want?
We don't want anything.
Get out.
We were looking at the house. It's nice.
We wouldn't have come in
if we knew you were here.
Just leave.
I would, but I can't be sure
you won't call the police.
I won't.
You didn't take anything?
Mm-mm.
So just go.
I just want to make sure my family is safe.
Safe?
Why wouldn't anyone be safe?
Unless you call the police,
everything will be fine.
I won't.
I give you my word, so please go.
Get the fuck out of my house.
Marcy, go now.
I got it.
Go on.
All right.
Oh, fuck.
Hey.
Martha.
Hey, I made you some tea.
Thanks, Mom.
If it's too hot,
you can just blow on it, okay?
Sorry I ruined the party.
You didn't ruin the party. It's fine.
Is it over?
Mm-hm.
You slept through the night.
That's good.
Do you wanna try to sit up
and drink the tea?
No, I don't need it.
- You okay?
Mm-hm.
You know that death...
is the most beautiful
part of life, right?
Death is beautiful
because we all fear death.
And fear is the most amazing emotion of all
because it creates complete awareness.
It brings you to now...
and that makes you truly present.
And when you're truly' present,
that's nirvana.
That's pure love.
So death is pure love.
- Hello?
- Hi, is Watts there?
Who is this?
Jane. Is Watts there?
Can I help you?
Who is this?
Marlene Lewis.
What's your last name, Jane?
Heller. Sorry, do I
have the right number?
I don't know. Do you?
It's a Jane.
What?
Jane.
Hello?
Hey, how are you?
Uh, sure, let's do it.
I'll be around there on Friday.
No, that was my cousin Marlene.
Okay, sure.
All right, I'll see you then.
I'm glad you called.
All right. Bye.
Hey.)'...
Marcy.
We don't eat until they're finished.
You know better.
I know. Sorry, Katie.
- Who's Katie?
- What?
Why don't you go sit down
and I'll finish this?
What's going on?
Who the fuck knows?
She needs to see someone.
I know.
Okay. I'll start looking
into places tomorrow.
Places?
I don't think she should
stay with us any more.
We can't do anything for her
when she's like this.
I don't wanna talk about it any more, okay?
Zoe.
Yeah?
I can't stop thinking about that man.
I know.
It just happens, though.
We're never really dead or alive.
We just exist.
So he's still existing,
but it's in a parallel time.
Just don't think about it.
Patrick?
Yes?
Hey, I'm sorry to interrupt...
but I've heard some of the girls
talking outside.
It's Zoe. Can we talk?
Will you let me in?
Get over it.
You haven't learned anything.
I have.
I thought we had a connection.
We do.
Show me.
Maybe I asked too much from you
too soon.
I'll expect less of you
from now on, okay?
I'm sorry.
No, no, no. Shh.
You're my favorite...
and I won't lose you.
Martha.
Oh, fuck.
- Are you all right?
- Fuck. Yes.
Jesus. What happened?
She kicked me down the stairs.
She what?
She kicked me down the fucking stairs!
Christ! I mean,
what is it gonna fucking take, Lucy?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I was confused.
About what?
What are you confused about?
I thought he was someone else.
You thought he was someone else?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I'm not doing this any more.
Okay, I'm not gonna do this any more.
I have beat myself up over you for years
and I am sick of it.
I am sick of chasing you down
and worrying about you.
I'm sorry.
You need help, Martha.
I know.
What happened to you?
What happened?
I don't know!
We're gonna get you some proper help.
Are you gonna send me away?
I don't know how to help you
Please don't. Please.
I can't help you, Martha.
Please, I can't be alone. Please.
No.
We're trying to have a family
and I don't feel safe with you here.
Lucy.
What?
You're gonna be a terrible mother.
Do you have any money left?
No?
No, I didn't think you did.
We'll make sure everything
is taken care of.
Hey.
You're going swimming?
Yeah.
It's a bit chilly.
I don't mind.
I think we both said some things last night
that we didn't mean.
Yeah.
We scheduled an appointment for you
for tomorrow morning.
What's it like there?
It looks nice.
It's not that far from us.
We head back to the city
in about an hour.
You're gonna be ready, right?
Yeah.
What the hell is he doing?
Fucking lunatic.
- God. Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
He just came out of nowhere.
The ghost of her
Floats over there
And her smile, her smile, it seems
So lonely
She gave me her hand
As I struck up the band
And she seemed to say
She seemed to say
"You're the only
Then we danced like two snow?akes
In the falling wind, in the wind
And do me a favor, God
Won't you let Marlene come in?
The gymnasium ?oor
The brass bound door
The jungle bird, the jungle bird
That you showed me
Her love was so clean
To tell the truth, Marlene
The sound of your tambourine
Still haunts me
We were so young then
Now that I'm old I know
Oh, I know
I loved you right then
I would've made Marlene let go
My friends in the bars
Hell, they only see the scars
And they do not give a damn
They do not give a damn
That I loved you
I don'! know why
But once you've seen the sky
You think you know all
birds are lovely
But there's snow on the ground
In Woodstock tonight
It's 22 years dead
Since I saw the light
The world did explode
At such a high-powered load
To run, to run, to run
Was all I left me
Up here there's breeze
High in the clouds we're free
To fly, to fly away was the lesson
And though the fire
That burned her life out
Left me a little more
lam a crippled singer
And it evens up the score
The ghost of her
It floats over there
And her smile, her smile, it seems
Seems so lonely
She gave me her hand
As I struck up the band
And she seemed to say
She seemed to say
"You're the only
And then we danced
like two snow?akes
In the falling wind, in the wind
And do me a favor, God
Won't you let Marlene come in?