Ha!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
That's very close, by the way.
I'm just
saying.
Who's my little man? Are you my little man?
That's my sixth husband right there.
The best of 'em.
Tonya's my fifth child
from husband number four.
She was always a handful.
And I guess we spoiled her,
which is a goddamn hat trick
when you haven't got shit
your entire life.
Still, drove her to competitions,
practices, sewed her all her costumes.
But to her,
her mother's a monster.
Generally,
people either love Tonya
or... not big fans.
Just like people
either love America
or they're not big fans.
Tonya was...
totally American.
You know, originally,
Jeff and Tonya,
uh, wanted to take out
Nancy Kerrigan.
"Take her out."
And I was the one
who popped up and said,
"There are other ways
to disable people."
So...
you're welcome.
Well, I was a reporter
for Hard Copy,
a pretty crappy show that the
legitimate news outlets looked down on.
And then became.
Well, uh, I mean, at 27,
I was, uh, the most
hated man in America.
Maybe the world.
Um, with a mustache,
I still can't
apologize enough for.
Uh, my name was a verb.
Like, if you bash someone
in the kneecap,
you, uh...
you Gilloolied them.
That was...
That was cool though.
Most people's
impression of me?
Um...
That I'm a real person.
You know? I never apologized for
growing up poor or being a redneck.
Which is what I am.
Um, you know,
and it's... a sport
where the friggin' judges want
you to be this old-timey version
of what a woman's
supposed to be...
for being the first US woman
to land a triple axel.
So fuck 'em.
Diane!
LaVona Harding.
I spoke with you on the phone.
Yeah.
Give me a minute, okay?
Mrs. Harding.
LaVona. It's LaVona.
I am so sorry, but there's
no smoking on the ice.
Oh. Well, I'll smoke it
quietly then.
This here
is my daughter Tonya.
Mrs. Harding,
I told you on the phone...
I know what you told me.
Only you never seen her skate.
I don't train beginners.
All she does is talk about
skating, all day and night.
Can't shut her up about it.
So it's easier for me to put her
on ice, if you know what I mean.
And we figure with the right training
she could make the most of her gift.
Like Ice Capades
maybe one day or somethin'.
How old are you, honey?
Mmm.
She's a soft four.
Well, she's
a very pretty girl.
But I'm sorry, I don't take
on students this young.
Now, if you'll forgive me,
I have a class waiting.
How'd it feel?
Feel good?
Go on. Skate.
Stay away.
Look out.
I mean, six months later
I win my first competition.
I was four, okay?
I mean, those bitches
didn't know what hit 'em.
Wrong!
Ordinary.
Nothing special there.
Are you even trying?
'Cause there's other places
I'd rather fuckin' be.
Concentrate.
You call that a clean skate,
for Christ's sake?
Would you not swear in front of the kids.
Please, LaVona?
- I didn't swear.
- You cunt.
Hey, stop talking to her. Yeah.
That girl is your enemy. You're
not here to make friends.
Mmm. Where do you
think you're going?
- I have to go to the bathroom.
- Don't tell me what you have to do.
I paid for you to skate. You're
gonna stay on the ice and skate.
Get over here.
You gotta get off the ice some time.
You hear me?
I'll be right here,
waitin'.
Oh, shit.
Skate wet.
To hear her tell it, I would operate
on her daily without anesthesia.
Please.
One fuckin' time. I hit her
one time with a hairbrush.
You're a terrible,
scum-suckin' loser!
Please!
What?
A child sometimes
wants to be corrected.
Answer me when I talk to you.
When I felt this, I gave her criticism...
Stop that.
The thing about Tonya was,
she skated better
when she was enraged.
If there was no "you
can't do it" type thing,
she wouldn't do it.
On the ice, I was there to inspire her.
Off the ice...
she was a happy, well-adjusted girl.
Dang!
- Clean shot, Tonnie.
- I know it.
I was aiming for her eyes,
like you said.
Otherwise I could've
got her, probably.
No sense shooting a bunny if you
shoot half the meat off her.
When I'm older, I'm gonna work at
an office and have a deadline.
- Thought you wanted to do Ice Capades.
- I can do both.
Yesterday, Mom made me wear
my skating costume to school.
The red one
with the tassels.
Everyone made fun of me.
- Why'd she do that?
- 'Cause they were taking school pictures.
She said we could use the
samples for competition.
I told Mom that Margie Sussman
called us "white trash."
- Mom told me...
- Spit in her milk.
I hope you didn't do that.
Not yet.
Do you love her?
I guess.
Do you?
- Yeah.
- Like you love me?
Nope.
Good, Tonnie.
But check out sooner.
What does she need a fuckin' fur coat for?
I don't have a fuckin' fur coat.
Because it's not
just about skating.
- The judges want figure skaters to be...
- Yeah. Rich, prissy A-holes.
Well-rounded. It's a
question of fitting in.
She's 12 and she lands
fuckin' triples.
She doesn't fit in.
She stands out.
She stands out because she looks
like she chops wood every morning.
She does chop wood
every morning.
LaVona, you wanna
work with me a little?
Twenty-three students I train
so I can coach Tonya full-time.
And I waitress full-time
to pay for your coaching.
- Yes, but she's not my child.
- No, she's mine.
And I'm not throwing my money away so
she can fit in with these little shits.
You can dress up a pig however you want.
You know what I saying?
It's not just about fitting in.
It's about how she's growing up.
Lick my ass, Diane.
She can do
a fuckin' triple.
Beautiful.
I didn't have a
lot of fun growing up.
I mean, we never went
to, you know, Disneyland
or on trips.
If I wanted something, I had to
come up with a way to get it.
What kind
of coat is that?
Go on! Get out!
I thought
you'd never leave.
I'm sorry.
- It's not your fault, Tonnie.
- Then take me with you.
Gotta work 12-hour night shifts.
I can't look after you.
You could if you want to.
We'll talk on the phone.
Everything's gonna work out.
You gotta move now, honey.
Tonnie, please.
You're not gonna
leave me here.
Daddy.
Daddy?
Take me with you!
I need you.
You're in... my... way.
Who's that?
Yeah.
We met at an ice rink
where I was practicing.
I was 15.
I was there
eight hours a day, skating.
I don't know
what he was doing there.
Hey.
I was young,
and I had no game
whatsoever.
So... do you like food?
Back then, my stepbrother, Creepy Chris,
was living with us.
I remember
Jeff and my's first date
because I'd had
Creepy Chris...
arrested earlier that day.
Jeff did, uh, consult
me regarding Tonya
and asked me,
"What do you think?"
And I said, "Go for
it, man." But...
Not to be a bragger or anything,
but had I told Jeff "You
can do better, man,"
no one would be talking about
the two of them today.
I mean, I've never
been a girlie girl.
Jeff was
my first date ever.
And my mom came.
- Hi.
- I got it.
You a gardener
or a flower, John?
It's... Jeff.
In a relationship there's
a flower and a gardener.
Um...
- Don't answer.
- I don't know. I mean, I...
I just thought...
I'm a gardener
who wants to be a flower.
How fucked am I?
This one can't garden
to save her life.
You're gonna have to do
all the gardening.
- Mom!
- What?
You two fuck yet?
Hey.
My dad's only been laid off
for a couple months now.
So he stopped sending money.
We had plenty of money before. I have a...
You know, I have a fur coat and stuff.
- Yeah?
- You know, otherwise...
My family's poor.
You need me to, um,
tighten that
before you reconnect.
Okay.
There you go.
It's okay.
So, um...
what are you gonna do
now that school's done?
Uh, well, I...
I do this job
for the, um,
Association
for Retarded Persons.
I mean,
I'm not a retarded person.
I'm their driver,
which is cool.
My...
My dad was air force and
he died when I was young,
so my college
is paid for, just...
I don't know.
My parents
had me quit school
so I could concentrate
on skating.
It's like your super power.
Fucking awesome,
what you can do.
So, um...
What, do you,
like, like me?
You're
so fuckin' pretty.
No, I'm not.
You are.
He was really
sweet in the beginning.
He was a good kisser.
He told me he loved me.
And I believed him.
You're not having
a conversation.
- You're just fucking yelling at me.
- Hey.
- Hey!
- Fuck.
- But then...
- He started hitting me a few months in.
I'm sorry... Ow!
Then he would say
it would never happen again.
- But I figured...
- My mom hits me. She loves me.
And I thought
it was my fault.
That's just what I knew.
- Hey. Watch it.
- Don't touch me!
He'd say he was sorry. Then things
would be normal for a while.
- I'm sorry.
- Mmm.
He was the first boy I ever loved.
The only catch was...
He beat the living hell
out of me.
And I thought
it was my fault.
Nancy gets hit one time...
Why? Why?
and the whole world shits.
For me, it's
an all-the-time occurrence.
I never hit her.
That's... not me.
I'm, uh...
I'm actually
a pretty meek guy, um...
She hit me.
Packed a wallop.
Fired a gun at me too.
This is bullshit.
I never did this.
Then comes later.
We're still happy now.
I can see that shiner
through your makeup, you know.
- Yeah, I fell on the ice yesterday.
- I don't know, Tonnie.
I would never be with
someone who fuckin' hit me.
- You hit Dad.
- That's different.
Anyway, he said
he was sorry.
Seriously though,
you're a dumb piece of shit
who thinks
she deserves to get hit.
How did I get that idea?
Maybe he should hit you.
Yeah. Maybe you'd learn to keep your
big mouth shut. Sure helps me out.
I'm supportive of this relationship.
You hear me?
Gotta go to practice.
Hey.
Kiss your mother
good-bye.
Up next is Tonya Harding,
skating to ZZ Top's
"Sleeping Bag."
4.8, 4.9...
They hate me. Emily Ann
fell and scored higher.
- Honey, you're different.
- I'm not dressing like a retarded tooth fairy.
The judges expect
a conventional program.
- I don't wanna be conventional.
- Your scores reflect that.
If I did the triple axel, they'd
have to give me my fucking score.
- You can't just do the triple.
- Sometimes I can!
- It wasn't my fault...
- Nothing's ever your fault.
I out-skated the other...
You skated like
a graceless bull dyke.
I was embarrassed
for you.
Sorry.
Your father's not paying
alimony, you know.
Every penny I make... Every
penny goes to your skating.
And you weren't even
fucking trying.
I said I was sorr...
Don't talk back to me.
- Saying "I'm sorry" is not talking back.
- That's supposed to be smart?
Stop it. I just said...
Rolling your fucking alien eyes
at me when I'm talking to you!
- I didn't roll my eyes!
- You think I like working for you?
- You're bat-shit crazy!
- You selfish bitch!
Are you fucking crazy?
You fucking that mustache,
you're gonna start paying rent.
- I'm not paying for you to act like a whore!
- Fucking psycho!
- I don't wanna fucking live with you anyway!
- Ugly fuckin' whore!
Oh, please. Show me a family
that doesn't have ups and downs.
Tonya needed to
get away from her mom.
So we got
a place together.
There was no more talk
of college or air force.
And I didn't care.
I wanted
to take care of her,
to protect her.
Come here.
Okay.
Does it need
more tulle?
I want it
to look pretty.
Tulle's classy,
you know.
You think any more about
getting your high school GED?
I don't give a red-hot shit
about that anymore.
Well, I think
you should look into it.
What about a bow
at the back?
What if
I'm not smart enough?
I ever tell you what I was
most afraid of growing up?
No.
"Oh, my's."
- "Oh, my's"?
- Yeah.
You know, like in The
Wizard of Oz when they say,
- "Lions and tigers and bears, oh, my!"
- "Oh, my."
My brother convinced me that "Oh, my's"
were gonna come in the middle of the night
and eat me alive.
You're so fuckin' dumb.
And I got
a high school diploma.
Well...
you're gonna get a medal
for your sewing alone.
Oh, my! Oh, my!
No!
Looking back,
that was probably
our happiest time.
I'd make peanut butter
and jelly sandwiches,
and she'd go off
to competitions.
We had exactly the same interests.
I mean...
We both liked trucks
- and fixing cars up.
- Whoo!
So I just thought it would last forever.
This is fucking wrong, Diane.
Tonya!
Hey, how do I get
a fair shot here?
'Cause I'm up at 5:00 every
morning working my ass off.
Does someone wanna just tell me to my face
you're never gonna give me the scores I deserve?
Uh, this is how it's done. Some of
these girls have paid their dues.
I don't give a shit.
I out-skated 'em today.
We also judge
on presentation.
Well, you know what?
If you can come up with $5,000 for a
costume for me, I won't have to make one.
Till then,
just stay out of my face.
Maybe you're just not
as good as you think.
Maybe you should
pick another sport.
Suck my dick!
This is fuckin' rigged!
Do you really think your scores will
improve now that you've told them to...
If you dressed appropriately, maybe
they'd score you appropriately.
I dressed pretty!
God, you don't like the way I
dress or talk or any of my music.
It's like you want me to be
an entirely different person.
I want you to be
a better competitor.
Otherwise,
I'm wasting my time.
Well, then you're
wasting your time.
'Cause you know what? Dodie Teachman
wants to be my coach anyways.
You're fucking fired,
Diane!
That wasn't my fault.
Unless puberty
is my fault.
To be fair,
Jeff did love her.
He really loved her.
Like...
I remember a time
when he took her
to a Richard Marx
concert.
That's when I knew
shit was serious.
You do dumb things
when you're young.
Like marrying Jeff.
The wedding was nice.
It made sense at the time.
Okay?
I mean, I could have insurance,
good benefits all around.
I mean, he had a car.
Plus, I was doing six hours a day
of practice and competitions
while I worked
at a hardware store.
And I ran a forklift and a drill
press, and I did welding.
But... But now...
now I could just skate,
like all the other girls.
I don't know
what to tell you.
Marrying the first idiot
who says you're pretty.
You fuck dumb.
You don't marry dumb.
Most people don't even understand
how insanely difficult it is
to attempt a triple axel.
There's a reason why
nobody was trying it.
You skate backward,
and then take off from a forward
position on your left leg,
and then somehow...
Fuckin' hurl yourself blindly three-and-a-half
rotations like you're light as shit,
which, I'm tellin' you,
Tonya never was.
Land on the opposite foot on the back,
outside edge of a razor-thin blade.
It's that extra
half rotation,
when you already
did three,
that made us call Tonya the Charles
Barkley of figure skating.
It was bad-ass.
I don't know
if I can do this, Dodie.
I missed it
in last training.
Of course you can.
You got this.
Hey, Tonya.
You suck.
What is this, Rednecks on Ice?
The Lice Capades?
- You know what...
- Hey! Come here.
Oh! Here she comes!
White Castle queen!
No woman in the history of figure
skating has landed a triple axel.
All of those women before you,
not one of them did it.
- Ignore him. Hey. Hey.
- You suck!
- The skating association doesn't think you can do it.
"Trashy Tonya
doesn't belong."
Your mother doesn't think so.
Now show 'em.
- Hey, Tonya. Where'd you park your double-wide?
- Don't listen to him.
- Get out there. Focus.
- You suck!
- Go.
You suck!
Tonya
Harding, 20 years old,
from Portland, Oregon.
Here now is Tonya Harding,
second after
the original program.
Just 20 years old,
from Portland, Oregon.
Great power, great speed,
great athletic ability.
And the question is
whether, three moves into the program,
she will do a triple axel.
First, a triple lutz.
Nicely done.
And now we will
find out whether she will be
the first American to attempt and
complete a triple axel jump.
We will know that here,
whether she tries it or not.
- Atta girl!
- Isn't that great?
Oh, my God, I mean, it was...
totally
the most awesomest thing.
'Cause leading up to it
you're like,
"I can't do it.
I can't. I can't."
And, then, bam! I can!
And all those people
who said I couldn't make it,
well, fuck you... I did.
I proved everyone wrong.
I was loved.
I can't describe how it felt.
There... I mean, there were
people standing up.
I mean, I was just...
For the first time I knew...
I knew I was the best
figure skater in the world.
At one point in time.
Sorry. No one ever really
asks me about this anymore.
Tonya! Tonya! Hey!
I was blindsided.
As soon as she got back from nationals,
she was an entirely
different person.
And that person
didn't want ol' Jeff no more.
Where the fuck
are my Dove bars?
We can't afford 'em. Eskimo
Pie is just as good.
I'm America's
best figure skater.
I don't want Eskimo Pie.
I wanted...
Oh, Jesus. When was the
last time you showered?
Just wanted
a fucking Dove bar.
After the triple...
- everything changed.
The Jeff I fell
in love with was gone.
If I got up in the morning,
I got hit.
If I took a shit,
I... H-He didn't need a reason
anymore, is what I'm saying.
And I'd just had enough.
You know?
My... My whole, entire life
I'd been told
I wouldn't amount to anything.
Well, you know what?
Maybe I would.
So suddenly Kristi and Nancy
are coming in second and third,
and Tonya is coming in second
at world championships
and winning Skate America.
Fuck 'em. I'm skating
better than ever.
So the skating community
is like, oh, my God.
What the fuck...
I mean, this is
our skating champion?
Tonya did the triple axel.
No one else could
or even had the balls to try.
Tonya Harding
was not the image...
Could I just interrupt with a quick word
about Nancy Kerrigan? It'll just take a sec.
Nancy and I were friends. Okay?
We were roommates, sometimes,
on the road.
But the press wanted Nancy
to be a princess
and me to be
the pile of crap.
To sell papers.
I mean,
what kind of friggin' person
bashes in
their friend's knee?
Who would do that
to a friend?
This is bullshit.
I mean, you gave her everything you
have, and this is how she treats you?
- Tell her that.
- Why are you being such a bitch?
You're acting
completely different, Tonya.
- I am different.
- Yes, but...
Everything's different, Jeff.
People actually smile at me now.
- What's she saying?
- People... People smile at her now.
Mmm. "People smile at..."
Oh...
And how could you file a
restraining order on me? Huh?
- They showed up at work in front of everybody, Tonya.
- Yeah.
I filed a restraining order so I wouldn't
have to look at your fucking face.
What?
- She hung up.
- No, she didn't.
- I'm calling her back.
- Call her back, Jeff.
Mrs. Eckhardt, uh, do you mind
dialing that number back?
- It's local, Ma.
- Okeydokey!
This shit
is unbelievable.
- Tonya.
- Fuck you!
What'd she say now?
Just one more time,
Mrs. Eckhardt!
Mom, just help us out!
I said fuck you!
Don't...
- Did she...
- We're going to Sun Valley. Let's go.
I like
when you're like this, Jeff.
- You're not gonna let her get the last word, man.
- No way.
None of my women
get the last word.
I'm going to Sun Valley. She'll
be there for a competition.
- I'll get the last word, 'cause I'm the man.
- We're the man!
I've been a co-op specialist
in Switzerland and Europe.
Hostage retrieval
is my area of expertise.
I'm telling you, man,
we're in, and we're out.
Mind control may be necessary, which
I've been practicing in Kenya, Korea...
When traveling internationally
I'm as resourceful as a lizard.
My skills have been honed by years of
infiltrating underground organizations.
So we blend
and we disappear.
And under
no circumstances
do we create
or cause a scene.
Tonya!
No!
Fuck you!
I liked being married.
Just not to him.
But he was calling
all the time,
saying "I've been to therapy"
and "I love you. Take me back."
I... I wanted to be loved.
I hoped it would work.
So I... I went back.
The second
we were back together,
everything went to shit.
The closer the Olympics got,
the worse my skating got.
It was like a nightmare,
or a frickin' curse.
I still believed.
I knew I was gonna do it.
Mesdames et messieurs...
Ladies and gentlemen...
from
the United States of America...
- Tonya Harding.
I would be the first
and only woman
to do the triple axel
in the Olympics.
My whole life was leading up
to this one moment.
Visualize the triple
when you're in the lay-back.
This is everything
you've been working for.
Yeah.
I fuckin' got it, Dodie.
She was first
in the United States in 1991.
She was second in the world
in 1991,
third in nationals
in Orlando.
She arrived late
for these games
and missed
the opening ceremony entirely.
Here is Tonya Harding.
Now, her opening move,
a lay-back spin, is unique,
because you're dizzy
from the spins.
And her next jump,
the triple axel,
is the most difficult jump being
performed in the ladies' event.
This is so exciting.
No woman has attempted and completed a
triple axel in Olympic competition.
Tonya Harding
could make history
right here.
So, I'd broken off
my skate blade
two days before,
in practice,
and they put it back on
a little off.
So all my landings
were off.
All of them.
I mean,
that wasn't my fault.
5.2, 5.2...
So I come in fourth
behind Nancy.
And... I mean,
I was really happy
with that.
It was awesome.
It just wasn't fuckin' fair.
Tonya Harding of the United
States wound up in fourth place,
followed by Surya Bonaly,
Chen Lu and Yuka Sato.
Very athletic skater.
Her weakness
is her artistry.
Tonya Harding's Olympic
competition is complete.
Um, this next part...
I mean...
Not true.
I never said that.
I never even said that!
You're full of shit!
Tonya.
Tonya,
get in the house.
I'm not going
inside with you.
Why would I go...
- Don't you fuckin' touch me!
- Hey!
I swear to God!
Fuck! Aah!
Damn it!
Things got out of hand.
I mean, we couldn't be
in the same house together.
I called the authorities on him
the whole summer.
I mean, I was filing
restraining orders, you name it.
Finally...
I divorced him.
Whoo! Missing something?
Jesus... Fuck.
Fuck.
- Got your bag, Tonya. Open the door.
- Jeff... Jeff...
- I have your bag!
- You can't be here.
- Listen. I have your bag.
- You can't be within a hundred feet of me.
- Can I not drop something off?
- If you don't fuck off, I'm calling the cops. Okay?
Baby...
I'm gonna break your fucking
legs, you fucking cunt!
Fuck!
Jeff, get the fuck
outta my... Get the...
Hey!
I'm gonna fuckin' kill you.
- You want me to do that?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- You want me to kill you?
- You're gonna put a fucking gun in my...
- Want me to kill myself?
- Stop it.
- Which is it?
- Stop it!
Jeff, I am fucking serious.
I am serious.
- Give me the fucking gun. This is not a joke.
- I will fucking kill you.
You don't need your purse! You
don't need anybody. You need me.
- Okay. Okay.
- All right? That's it.
- Okay. Just put down the fucking gun.
- Okay.
Jeff!
Fucking stop it.
Give me the gun.
Give me the fucking gun.
Jesus. Oh, fuck.
You're okay.
Hey, you okay?
Stand back! Stand back.
- Are you kidding me?
- Everything is fine.
A loaded gun? What the fuck?
Get in the car.
Yep. Everything's fine.
What? Oh, fuck.
Goddamn it!
Pull over!
Fuck.
Fuck. You fuckin' bitch.
Look what you made me do.
I'll fuckin' kill you
if you say anything.
Aah!
Fuck.
Good evening.
I'm gonna need you to get out of the car.
Okay.
Do you know how fast
you were going?
- Forty-five.
- Didn't say anything about the blood.
Can you open the trunk,
please?
Took two guns out of the
truck, and alcohol.
And then just leaves me there, with him.
Kind of like Kristi Yamaguchi
kind of guys. I don't know. Sympathetic.
Which is why
I don't trust the authorities.
Or anyone.
Jeff can talk his way
out of anything.
Never talk to him.
Well, my story line
is disappearing right now.
What... the... fuck.
When you come in
fourth at the Olympics,
you don't get
endorsement deals.
You get the 6:00 a.m. shift
at Spud City.
Where's my fuckin' smokes?
You look well.
I look like someone who had a way
out of this shit and fucked it up.
I was being polite.
I know.
Are you okay?
Well...
my skating career is over
and I have... no savings.
And I ended up a waitress,
just like my mom.
But on the plus side
I'm unskilled, so...
Mmm.
The Olympic Committee
announced today
that the next Olympics are going to
be in two years instead of four.
No heavy metal.
Lose the blue nail polish.
I'm too out of shape.
Pear is a shape.
The world is giving you
a second chance.
I know you don't believe
in them, but I do.
Thank you.
This is how Rocky trained when he had
to fight the Russian. It worked.
She actually did this.
And this.
It's okay, honey, you...
Hey. Excuse me.
Sir?
Excuse me.
Sir, can I...
Can I just talk...
Can I just... Can I talk
to you for a second?
I just...
About my score?
Happy to.
I know that you guys
don't... like me.
But... I'm landing
all my jumps out there.
Tonya.
It's never been entirely
about the skating.
I'll deny I ever said it,
honey, but you're just not...
the image
that we want to portray.
You're representing our country,
for fuck's sake.
We need to see
a wholesome American family,
and you...
you just refuse
to play along.
I don't have
a wholesome American family.
Why... Why can't it just be
about the skating?
They want a
wholesome American family?
Fuck you.
Give me that.
Well, it's not gonna be easy, but,
yeah, I could pull that out of my ass.
Shit.
I know you don't expect
me to wait on you.
Nope. I didn't
expect a thing, Mom.
Well, aren't you
a little hothouse flower.
I don't know if you heard,
but I'm training
for the Olympics.
So what do you want?
Money?
God, no. I just...
I just wanted
to see you.
You're a taker.
Every cent I made went to your
skating, and you took it.
- What do you want?
- Jesus.
Well, this was
a stupid fucking idea.
Um...
Was anything I did
ever good enough for you?
You were soft.
At three?
I made you a fighter.
- You never had a chance without me.
- You fucked with my head.
You made me think that I could
skate best when my life was shit.
And now my life is shit... You made
that fucking real... I don't want that.
You would have picked it in a heartbeat.
You should be thanking me, not blaming me.
Did you...
I mean,
when I was a kid,
did you ever love me
or... anything?
You think Sonja Henie's
mother loved her?
Poor fuckin' you.
I didn't stay home making apple brown
betties. No. I made you a champion.
Knowing
you'd hate me for it.
That's the sacrifice
a mother makes.
I wish I'd had a mother
like me instead of nice.
Nice gets you shit.
I didn't like my mother either! So what?
I fuckin' gave you a gift.
You cursed me.
You're a monster.
Spilled milk, baby.
Jeff, are you down here?
Oh, Jeff.
I was pretty surprised
when Tonya called me.
But she said...
I don't think I
can make it to the Olympics without you.
I admit it.
A part of me still thought that
the sun rose and set with her
and wanted her to look at me
the way that she used to.
I just wanted to hold on.
I figured it was
just for three weeks,
and the second I made the team
I was gonna dump his ass.
But...
before I could think
too much on that,
that... leads...
I mean, it's what you all came for,
folks... the fucking incident.
The incident.
Mmm.
The fucking incident.
Everyone remembers the incident
differently, and that's a fact, um...
Some people, honest to God,
remember Tonya
whacking Nancy herself.
Um... I never talked
about how it went down,
except to the FBI.
The press
got everything wrong.
Excuse me.
I'm with the Clackamas County Sheriff's
Office. I'm gonna need to talk with you.
Oh, goddamn it, Jeff.
What did you do?
I've received
a death threat.
- From Jeff?
- Against you.
What the fuck?
What did
they say, exactly?
Uh, i...
"If Harding skates today,
she'll get a...
a bullet in the back."
What the fuck?
- How seriously should we take this?
- Right?
Girl skaters
at this level,
they're always messing with each
other with the, um, costumes,
with each other's
skate blades.
- I never knew that.
- Yeah. It's a thing.
Well, the point is, this is a large
venue and we can't protect you.
In the end, she was
too freaked out to skate.
It screwed with her head
for a long, long time.
And it got me thinking.
Which...
isn't always my strength.
What if I do the same thing to Nancy
Kerrigan, only right before nationals?
Yeah. Sort of
even the playing field.
Right.
I wouldn't be the first guy
to cheat at figure skating.
A lot of the judges
are corrupt.
It's not exactly
prim and proper.
Someone did it to Tonya,
lest we forget.
It's... my way of...
saying "I love you."
Interested. Go on.
No, that's it.
I figure I'm gonna mail some
letters to screw with her head.
Whoa.
You f-in' greenhorn.
You cannot mail letters
from here.
- It'll be postmarked from Portland.
- No.
What we do, see, is...
we send somebody
out there.
We fly 'em out there, or maybe to
Massachusetts, where she's from.
Yeah.
Takes the suspicion
off of us, see?
Right.
I know a guy.
Shouldn't even be
saying his name.
Derrick.
All in, you're probably
looking at a thousand bucks,
but you really ought to
let me handle everything.
Us being great spies and all,
we call up a friend who leaves a
message where Kerrigan trains...
For fuck sake. Jeff,
just call her back.
Only our machine is so old we
can't completely understand it.
She just said Nancy
Kerrigan trains at...
- Kerrigan trains...
- At Tuna Can Arena.
Nancy Kerrigan trains at Tuna Can Arena.
She just said that.
Well, who's gonna name
an arena "Tuna Can"?
Fishermen. Everyone's
fishermen in Massachusetts.
Just fucking
call her back and ask.
Hi, Vera.
It's Tonya again.
Mm-hmm. Our machine's
a piece of crap.
Could you just tell me where
Nancy Kerrigan trains again?
- Oh, sure.
- Yeah, I had a stupid bet with Jeff.
Mm-hmm.
Spell that for me, hon.
Uh-huh.
- And what time?
- 5:45.
- Got it. Thanks, Vera.
- No problem.
Yeah. See you later.
It's that fuckin' easy.
Tony Kent.
Thank you. Tony Kent.
- Tony Kent Arena.
- Not Tuna Can.
Tony Kent Arena.
It's the same fucking thing.
Dinner's ready.
It's bullshit. I mean, the FBI
found this piece of paper
in some random Dumpster,
supposedly in my handwriting, with Nancy's
training schedule or something on it.
It was the arena Nancy skated at
and her training times.
What do you need
training times for
if all you're doing
is mailing letters, right?
Jeff Gillooly can change his story all
he wants to make himself feel better,
but he confessed to the FBI.
Guilty.
I told the FBI that Tonya
was in on planning it,
which she was.
But the plan was
to mail some letters.
Tonya didn't know
about the assault,
because there was never
supposed to be an assault.
Just letters.
I gave Shawn
a thousand bucks.
Nothing happens.
Gonna need to come up
with more money.
Do I have "stupid"
written across my head?
All they had to do was mail letters
someplace. I'm not giving them more money.
But these are two
of my top operatives.
Derrick needs
expense money...
You know what? Call Derrick and tell
him we're calling the whole thing off.
- No.
- Sweetie, the death threat's off.
Whatever.
You cannot
call this thing off.
This baby has moving parts. Balls
are already being played with.
That's too bad. All they had to do
was mail fucking letters, Shawn.
These are not the guys you
wanna double-cross. Trust me.
That's your problem. Get me my thousand
bucks back. They didn't do anything.
Your thousand bucks?
Jeff, come on.
Are... Tonya. You still
want this to happen, right?
- I can still make this happen.
- I really don't care, Shawn.
I clearly have
bigger shit to fry.
You eat shit?
- What?
- "Fish to fry," not "shit to fry."
"Shit to fry" is a meal
best served never.
Who cares, you big, fat fuck?
You can't make it happen anyway.
- I'm on your side, Tonya.
- You're not a secret agent.
You're not a hit man.
You're just
a fat, nobody gasbag,
who still lives with his parents
and drives a '76 Mercury,
gets laughed at behind his
back, and has never been laid.
Just stay away from me!
- January 6.
- I had a session later that night so...
- I was sleeping, yeah.
- I was asleep.
Remember, if your mind is blank,
no one can pick up your vibes.
Also, they can't identify you
if they don't see your eyes.
Go.
Mind's blank.
Don't let them see my eyes.
The john?
Hey. Hey.
Which one's Kerrigan?
What the fuck?
Go! Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go!
I mean, we had no idea that
something like this could be done
by two of the biggest boobs,
in a story
populated solely by boobs.
- Yeah?
- Jeff?
- Holy shit!
- Tonya.
They broke her knee.
They broke her fucking knee!
Whose knee? What?
- Are you fucking watching this?
- What?
Turn on the fucking TV!
It's everywhere.
- What are you talking about?
- Nancy Kerrigan!
Some guy just fucking broke
her fucking knee!
No, no, no, no, no! It was
supposed to be uh, just letters...
It's not a fucking letter, Jeff!
They broke her fucking knee!
It was supposed to be letters,
like a death threat!
Jeff, I'm telling you, forget the death
threat. Some guy broke her knee!
Trying to claim
one of two Olympic spots
- on Saturday night.
- Why? Why?
She was practicing for
that performance this afternoon.
She was just leaving the ice.
Reporter Daniel Scarborough
was waiting to interview her.
Aah!
Fucking mustache.
- Oh, Jeff.
- Jeff.
We did it, man.
We're everywhere.
It is so
friggin' awesome.
- What the hell, Shawn?
- What?
- What the fuck did you do?
- What did I...
Changed the course of history,
if you've been watching.
Are you insane? Nobody
was supposed to get hurt.
It was supposed to be
psychological warfare. Right?
What if the psychological
warfare didn't work?
What if it didn't scare her?
Then what?
You know, all of our hard work
would've been for nothing.
What hard work? It was
mailing fucking letters!
I had to handle it though, Jeff. I had to
handle this and make sure it happened.
Look, I'm Tonya's bodyguard,
and now all the other skaters, maybe more
athletes, are going to need a bodyguard.
So the money's
gonna be flowing in,
and we pocket that money,
and I change the course
of history.
...joins us with
the latest in sports...
Dad, make sure it's a
blank tape this time.
It was a simple plan, Shawn.
Why didn't you just stick to it?
- I did stick to the plan.
- This was not the plan.
This was always the plan.
Do you hear me?
A guy like me, you think
it's easy in my profession,
having to think four
steps ahead of everyone?
Or did you not realize
that I was the one who...
I was the one who called
the death threat on Tonya.
What?
Two to the back.
People don't take me
seriously, Jeff.
But I'm in control
of the situations.
I proved that today.
This was not the...
- You better think...
- This is out of control!
Relax.
Everything is great.
Yes, my parents did tape over my
favorite episode of Star Trek
to record the CNN coverage,
but I'm keeping it together.
You're a fucking idiot.
Oh, shit, shit.
We gotta get those guys
out of Detroit, okay?
Shane and Derrick, they're just stuck
there. They don't have any money.
Four steps ahead.
Jeff. Jeff.
- Jeff.
- Unbelievable.
She
told us today, she said,
"I know there's
a lot of people out there
who think I'm a has-been."
Well, with Lillehammer
just six weeks away,
now's her chance
to show the country
that she deserves a spot
on the Olympic team.
It'll be interesting to see
whether she plays this
conservatively or not.
She can be powerful,
intimidating, and vulnerable
all at the same time.
Make it to Derrick Smith
and Shane Stant.
The height
and the speed is so different
from all the other women.
This is a big improvement
from two years ago.
A huge jump she made.
Pretty great control.
This is her final combination.
Not paying you to stand around.
She may make it to the Olympics.
- Hey.
- I wanna see her face.
- LaVona, come on.
- I wanna see her fucking face at the end.
...Tonya's peak had past,
she's proved tonight
she is still a winner.
This is a great moment
for Tonya.
She's had everything go wrong.
She's let everything go wrong.
And now, all of a sudden,
to pull this off...
- LaVona.
- and become our national champion is terrific.
And it looks
like she has most definitely
earned herself a place
on the US Olympic team.
Shane Stant was clueless,
completely.
Before the attack, he waited outside
the arena in Massachusetts,
where he thought
Nancy Kerrigan was training.
Now, he moved his car
every 15 minutes
to avoid suspicion.
He did this for two days.
That's when he found out that
Nancy was actually in Detroit.
Dah dah dah dah.
Later we found
out they left a trail
as big as the Cumberland Gap.
Phone records, bank records.
How'd you find me?
Next time you pull off a hit,
son, don't put it on Visa.
Thanks very much.
- Thanks. That's enough.
- Thank you.
- We gotta go.
- Thanks.
- Tonya?
Okay. Thanks.
Before this blows up, we gotta
get our stories straight.
Yeah. You do the talking.
You're my manager.
Okay. 'Cause we have to be real
careful about what we say.
We can't afford to make any mistakes.
I've waited so long for this.
Tonya. I wanna be
a skater like you.
Really? Oh, hey.
Hope you mean it.
- What's your name?
- Annie.
Annie. There you go.
See you later.
Hey, we play it cool. After
all, we both have alibis.
What, for... Alibis?
For Wheaties?
Wheaties?
What are you talking about?
My endorsement.
The attack.
- Excuse us.
- We're with the FBI.
It's just a formality.
We're talking to everyone.
Well...
we don't know anything.
That must make life
difficult.
Maybe you heard something.
Saw something.
I mean, I was asleep,
and Jeff wasn't even here.
I wasn't even here.
Uh, I was asleep too.
In, um, Oregon at home,
which is in Portland,
where I live.
In Oregon.
So what do you
make of all this, Jeff?
Well, um...
It's a scary prospect, what
the world is coming to.
How long are you
in Detroit?
We're actually heading
to the airport right now.
Why don't we give you a ride?
Oh, yeah. Thanks very much.
Yeah.
But, first,
who's Derrick?
I don't know any Derricks.
I know lots of Derricks.
We're gonna miss
our plane.
Tonya, how do you feel
about going to the Olympics?
I'm really happy, but it
won't be a true crown
until I get my chance
with Nancy at the Olympics.
Let me tell ya,
I'm gonna whip her butt.
- Did the FBI speak to you?
- Um...
I mean, they talked
to everybody.
And, uh, they're doing
a thorough investigation
to try and find the man
who did it.
Thanks, guys. Thanks.
Holy shit. I'm going
to the Olympics again.
They were taking my picture.
I mean, fuck
the Skating Association.
- Fuck 'em.
- This is a clusterfuck.
- Shit.
- It's not funny!
- We gotta fix this.
- Fix what?
We talked to the FBI.
Everything's fine.
She's right, man.
We outsmarted them.
My guys are paid,
and deep in cover...
Fuck!
Jesus,
what is your problem?
You wanna tell me what happened, Shawn?
Who did you talk to?
Nobody.
Yeah?
Well, if you don't tell me now,
then... then we're all
gonna be fucked!
I didn't talk to anybody.
Somebody knows something when
they shouldn't know anything.
- I never said anything.
- Then how come they know the name Derrick, Shawn?
I don't know. How can
you even ask me that?
I could withstand torture
and I would still never talk.
They could never break me!
That whole Nancy Kerrigan thing,
that was my crew.
We were paid 65 grand
to take her out.
Then my team
obtains press credentials
by beating up a reporter.
That's what gets us
inside the ring.
Then, bam, my hit man
whacks Kerrigan three times
with a retractable baton.
And then he shouts at her,
he says...
Shawn Eckhardt.
No.
Who is it, Shawnie?
I brought you boys
some nice tea.
- Thank you.
M-Maybe some shortbread too,
Mom?
What can you tell us
about Tonya Harding?
Mmm.
I don't know
a Tony Harding.
Aren't you
her bodyguard?
Well...
you didn't let me finish.
Well, I-I don't...
I don't know her well.
How about
Nancy Kerrigan?
- Who?
- You haven't heard of Nancy Kerrigan?
Oh, yeah.
I thought
he said Nancy Herring.
- Shawn...
- Jeff did it.
Jeff Gillooly did it.
What the fuck
is going on?
Nothing.
Don't answer it.
Fuck!
Jeff Gillooly speaking.
- You gotta pay me my money, and I gotta get outta town.
- Who is it?
- They know something.
- Wait. What are you...
Meet me, or else
I'm gonna be forced...
Shawn, calm down.
Where do you wanna meet?
The Golden Buddha,
uh, at our regular table.
Meet me
at the stroke of midnight.
I'm not meeting you at the
fucking stroke of midnight.
Th-That's the plan, man.
And bring the fucking money.
Great, great.
Tell your mom I said hi.
What's going on, Shawn?
Nothin'. Just...
why don't you sit down?
You wanna go to that bar
on, uh...
No, no, no.
We're... We're fine here.
Sit down.
What's up, man?
You okay? You're, uh,
sweatin' an awful lot.
- Even for you.
- No, I am not.
Okay.
You know I'm not okay.
They know something.
- Who?
- They...
- You know.
- I don't.
The FBI.
Okay? The FBI,
they know something is up.
What's up?
Whoa. Uh...
- Oh. Oh.
- Jeff. Yeah, Jeff.
Shawn... are you
trying to tell me
you had something to do with
the Nancy Kerrigan thing, hmm?
What the fuck?
Jeff, of course
I had something...
- Jeff...
- Don't...
say another word,
or I'll be forced
to go to the authorities.
Oh, Jeff.
I hope you
hear me loud and clear,
you fat fuck.
But you made your bed.
Now die in it.
Diane's husband is a lawyer,
so in the morning,
we meet up at their house.
It was nice. I mean, they had
a living room and stuff.
- Hello there. Come on in.
- Hey.
So why don't we
just turn his ugly fat ass in?
- Because...
- Big, dumb, fucking tub of guts.
It's only his word against ours.
You and I gotta stick together.
Yeah, but, Jeff,
I'm gonna lose everything.
I worked my whole life for this, and I'm
gonna lose it because of fucking Shawn?
If it ever
came down to that,
I would tell them you didn't
have anything to do with it.
But right now we gotta
get our story straight.
And since they can't
pin anything on us,
we didn't know anything.
Yeah, but we didn't
know anything.
Right.
Look.
They've arrested Shawn.
And he's saying that
it was all your idea, Jeff.
We didn't know anything.
I mean, it was supposed
to be letters...
It's... It's gonna be a
real shit-show for us soon.
Um... we gotta go home.
- Don't grab me. Fuck.
- Just get in the fucking car.
What part of keeping your
mouth shut was unclear,
you stupid fucking cunt?
There's more to this than
you're telling me, isn't there?
Shut up, Tonya.
I'm telling ya.
Jeff.
Did you do it?
Goddamn it.
Shit. Fuck.
Jeff, fuck!
What the fuck?
I mean, this is my...
this is my fucking life.
This is... Skating is
my whole fucking life.
What did you do?
What did... What did you do?
What did you actually fuck...
Shut up!
And then, bam!
Nails me
right in the frickin' face.
That's when I knew.
I mean,
he's never admitted to me...
He wouldn't care anymore
anyways.
But he's never admitted to me
that he actually did it.
But I knew... In that moment,
I knew he planned it.
And he had it done.
Tonya Harding,
23 years old.
Damn it.
I can't believe it.
You gave me up!
No, I didn't.
Yeah, well, the FBI
showed me your transcript!
Well, that's just cheating.
I...
- Open the door.
- Fucking liars.
Tonya, I told you
they couldn't...
they couldn't prove anything.
All... All I ever wanted
was to protect you, Tonya.
Baby, you're...
you're all I ever wanted.
Honey.
I fucking lost you now,
didn't I?
Look, Jeff, I...
I mean, what did you
want me to say?
I told them that you did this
because you did fucking did this!
Tonya, what am I
supposed to do?
Tonya. Honey?
I don't know. I...
I really think that you
should just kill yourself.
Now, there's
this feeling out there
that the one
who was power mad,
the one who was
megalomaniacal was you.
Incorrect. Um, I am
a professional bodyguard
and an international
counterterrorism expert.
I-I work around the world
for espionage agencies.
But, Shawn,
you don't.
But I do.
But, Shawn, we checked
and you don't.
- But I do.
- But you don't.
But I do. I, uh,
have actually been quoted
as an expert, uh, in terrorism
trends and profiles.
Where?
Um, in...
I believe it was a travel
magazine a couple of years ago
during the Gulf War.
Here in Portland, Oregon, another day
of practice for skater Tonya Harding.
She's still working out every
day right here behind me,
fully expecting
she'll compete later this month
at the Olympics in Norway.
Police and the FBI
continue looking into
last week's attack
on skater Nancy Kerrigan.
Even as the US Figure Skating
Association convenes a hearing panel
to consider whether there are
grounds to remove Tonya Harding
from the American Olympic team.
Harding's former husband
said Tuesday
that she knew about the attack
on Nancy Kerrigan
from the beginning.
The papers all said I
pled guilty, which I did,
but not to planning the attack,
uh, which it turns out
didn't really matter because...
once I knew about it and didn't
report it and try to cover it all up,
I was guilty.
Tonya's mom put out a red
velvet rope in front of her house.
Get your fat ass
where it belongs.
Told us if we wanted to take her
picture, we all had to stand behind it.
And we did!
I made bail.
I was charged with racketeering
and fined $100,000.
Which I never paid.
And I never
talked to Shawn again.
I thought being famous
was gonna be fun.
I was loved...
for a minute.
Then I was hated.
Then I was
just a punch line.
It was like being abused
all over again.
Only this time,
it was by you.
All of you.
You're all my attackers too.
With just four
weeks to go to Lillehammer,
she returned to training
this week in Oregon
under intense media scrutiny and pressure
to withdraw from the Olympic team.
Kerrigan also was
back on the ice this week,
striving to make it
to Lillehammer.
But in interviews
with Hard Copy,
former Olympians
and skating insiders
have said
the events of recent weeks
could turn into major stumbling
blocks for both competitors
as they pursue the gold...
Go away.
Shit.
Could you please
just leave me alone?
For now?
Now...
So, what's new?
Like your hair
pulled back like that.
You look young.
I'm 23, Mom.
Yeah, well...
You seem to be
holding up good.
Fuck 'em, you know?
I know.
I never did
like that Jeff.
- Mom...
- I'm not here to tell you I told you so. I'm not.
Why are you here?
What do you want?
I want you to know...
I don't know.
I-I'm on your side.
That's a big crowd
out there.
A lot of people support you.
You done good.
I'm proud of you.
All right. I'm going.
Mom.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Hey, hon. Did you know
about the attack?
Well, you can tell me.
What?
What are you looking for?
What are you...?
Stop it!
Uh...
It's just a...
Oh, wow.
I still meant
everything I said.
- Get the fuck out of my house.
- You hear me?
- Get out!
- I still meant everything I said.
Go! Get out!
Fuck, that hurt.
No comment.
No fucking comment.
Hey! Out of my way!
- Wait!
- Tonya!
Okay. I used to
have her tires flattened
and her truck towed sometimes.
So we can get a picture,
you know?
This was the first time there was
a 24-hour news cycle to fill.
We all needed that story.
Bullshit.
I shouldn't have to apologize
for something I didn't do.
Tonya, there's talk about not letting
you skate at the Olympics at all.
You need to give them this.
We're hanging on by a thread.
I earned my place on the team
fair and square.
Taking out the competition
with a retractable baton
doesn't strike everyone
that way.
I didn't know about it!
And that's exactly
what you'll say.
I can't fucking focus
when I'm trying to skate.
I keep falling
in front of everyone
while Nancy gets
her own private rink
where someone catches her
before she falls.
Honey, you'll apologize,
and this will all be over.
Okay.
I'll do whatever it takes.
I apologized for ever knowing
or being associated with Jeff,
which looks like
I'll never stop doing, ever.
I had no prior knowledge of the
planned assault on Nancy Kerrigan.
I am responsible,
however,
for frailing to...
failing to...
And when the Olympic committee
threatened to take me
off the team,
I filed a $10 million lawsuit
against them.
I mean, it was getting ugly.
But do you think that CBS,
who is showing the games,
was gonna let this ginormous
ratings fucker not happen?
I mean the whole entire world
was waiting for this... showdown
between me and Nancy, so...
I made the team.
You know, and I was
ready to show you all.
And this is one of the nights
everybody's been talking about
around the world.
One of the most controversial and
talked-about sports events in memory,
the women's figure skating
competition.
World champion Oksana Baiul
in second place
going into
tonight's competition,
Nancy Kerrigan in first place
after the technical program,
and Katerina Witt,
a two-time gold medalist
who will be the last to skate.
Right here.
Have a seat.
I was asked to comment
on everything for Hard Copy.
And they paid a lot,
which was cool.
Representing the United
States of America, Tonya Harding.
And now the public address
is announcing
Tonya Harding's name.
It is her turn to be
on the ice right now.
Tonya Harding after the warm-up
had a problem with her laces.
If she's not out here, I
think they're gonna disqualify her.
I'm not sure. I've never
seen anything like this.
Is it gonna hold?
Pull it tight enough?
How does that feel?
It's okay, honey.
It's okay.
We're just gonna...
Okay, okay.
It's okay, honey.
It's okay.
Breathe, breathe.
- How long do we have?
- We have, uh, one minute.
A minute?
Oh, my God.
Do you wanna try?
It doesn't matter. Just...
Let's go.
It's not gonna hold me.
I'm gonna break my ankle.
You check out those
edges in the beginning.
You jump high, check out
hard, and go for it.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Please. They broke.
I really tried
to get out here on time.
Please.
In a situation like this,
the referee, the judging panel
will give her every opportunity
to put out her best performance.
I would think, though
no announcement has been made,
they've obviously given her
a set amount of time.
Things like
this just don't happen.
Again, it's so important
that the skate is tied properly.
It's important that it's
comfortable on your foot.
Well, I think they're allowing
Tonya to fix her skate.
Again, this is every skater's
recurring nightmare.
This is one that you wake up
screaming from every morning.
Can I just say one quick thing
about Nancy Kerrigan?
So, my lace breaks,
which I guess is my fault,
but really kinda isn't.
And I go out and do the same
stuff as everybody else.
I didn't get the marks because I didn't ever
have a shot with the judges to begin with.
I mean, it was a big story,
but I don't need a big story.
I'm a big story on my own
when I skate.
I did my best,
and I got eighth.
But Nancy...
she goes out and gives
a beautiful skate.
I never said different.
She wins
a friggin' silver medal.
And when they put that medal
around her neck,
she looked like
she stepped in poop.
She does.
I mean, come on!
How am I the poor sport
in all of this?
An Olympic silver.
She looks like
she stepped in poop.
Defendant, please rise.
They postponed my trial
till after the Olympics.
Tonya Harding, you are hereby
sentenced to three years' probation.
$100,000 fine, plus $10,000 to the
DA's office for special costs.
Another $50,000 to set up
a fund for the Special Olympics.
Five hundred hours
community service.
A psychological evaluation.
And your immediate
resignation
from the US
Figure Skating Association,
banning you for life
from all figure skating association
competitions and events.
So ordered.
No. I...
All I did was the hindering
of prosecution...
- What? That you're never...
- He already ruled.
Never gonna let me
skate again?
I can't ever... I mean,
I'd rather do the
jail time, please.
- The...
- Tonya.
They... They only got
18 months.
They... They got
I-I'll do that.
You can't...
Your Honor, I don't
have an education.
All I know is skating.
That's all I know.
And I... I am no one
if I can't...
- if I can't skate.
- It's okay.
I'm... I'm not...
- I mean, I'm not some monster...
- Miss Harding.
I'm just... I'm just trying to...
I'm trying to do the best
- with what I know how to... and you're giving me...
- Miss Harding.
It's like you're giving me a life sentence
if you do that. You can't do that.
Miss Harding, that's enough.
You can't...
Please, because...
Just send me to jail
and then I can still skate.
- I've given you...
- Just send me to jail and then I can skate.
I've given you my decision.
Thank you, Your Honor.
This is
the best we could get.
Top ten questions Connie Chung
asked Tonya Harding earlier.
Here we go. Number 10:
Would you walk through the metal
detector for me one more time, please?
Uh, number nine: Do you think
you could kick my ass?
Number eight: Can you help
me and Maury have a baby?
Well, I think
that's uncalled for.
Uh, number seven: How much do you
think your pals would charge
to whack
Dan Rather's knees?
Number five:
Do you know Amy Fisher?
Number four:
When you hit Nancy in the knee, did
it sort of sound like, "Chung!"
Got a two-year sentence
and did eight months to the day.
All that craziness,
you know, everything
I'll ever be known for
was only a few months,
from start to finish.
I got up one morning
before I went to jail,
and the press was leaving.
Like I dreamed it.
Simpson told
police he was in Chicago
at the time
of the killings.
He arrived at the home
12 hours after the bodies
were discovered.
Police escorted him
to the rear of the building.
And a short time later,
Simpson was seen in handcuffs.
After a conference
with Simpson's attorney...
I never see Tonya anymore,
and this is fine.
I could care less.
I lead a full life.
Very happy.
Tonya... would never have thought
of calling in a death threat.
And... I was too caught up
in all the terrible things
that she was saying
about me...
rather than the fact
that I...
completely
ruined her career.
Absolutely ruined it.
Once I was banned
from figure skating for life,
I didn't have a lot of options.
Did what I had to do
to just stay in the public eye
and pay the bills.
I was the second
most-known person
behind Bill Clinton
in the world.
That meant something.
And people
still wanted to see me.
So I became a lady boxer.
I mean, why not?
Violence was always
what I knew anyway.
America, you know...
They want someone to love.
But they want
someone to hate.
And they want it easy.
But what's easy?
And the haters always say,
"Tonya, tell the truth."
There's no such thing
as truth.
I mean it's bullshit.
Everyone has their own truth.
And life just does
whatever the fuck it wants.
That's the story
of my life.
And that's the fucking truth.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
'Cause there's no "You can't
do it" type of thing.
She won't do it.
That's incorrect.
Um, my training
and education,
um, has been in the areas of
counterespionage and counterterrorism.
- I can't talk about the specifics.
- Sure.
And we're just as anxious
to talk to you guys
as you are to us.
- There'll be more in a few days.
- Yeah, hopefully.
I'm really happy,
but, um, there won't be
a true crown
until I get my chance
with Nancy.
That is the Olympics, and let me
tell ya, I'm gonna whip her butt.