It's over, Rick, they're
gonna disqualify you.
One, two, three. Come on.
Get him out of the corner.
Do you wanna quit?
I'll break it!
I'll snap his neck!
One, two, three.
Ring the bell! It's
over. It's over.
Let's go.
Hey, now. Hey,
Kevin. Hey, David.
- You crushed that guy, Pop.
- I sure did.
Oh! The Iron Claw!
Kevin's got me in the Iron Claw!
You're getting strong.
Nice to have you
guys here for once.
Hi.
- Did you see anything, Dottie?
- Not a chance!
But it sure sounded like
everyone was angry at you.
That's the idea.
What is that thing
attached to our home?
You guys like it?
Oh, Dad. It's incredible.
Yeah, it's incredible.
Jack, where is our car?
I had the boys swap it
out during the show.
Surprise!
Wait. What are you thinking?
We can't afford this.
Well, hear me out.
I was talking to the promoter,
and he said if I wanna be a
star, I need to act like a star.
So, he told me to
rent a Cadillac.
I'm not even gonna
ask how much it costs.
How much does it cost?
It's gonna be fine,
Dottie. I'm almost there.
We need a real house. A safe
place to raise these guys.
How does blowing a bunch of money
on a fancy car get us a house?
The only way to
beat this thing...
There's no "thing."
The only way to beat it
is to be the toughest,
the strongest, the
most successful,
the absolute best.
To rely on no one but ourselves.
I will get us there.
I will be the NWA World
Heavyweight Champion
and nothing will
hurt us ever again.
Let the morning bring me
word of your unfailing love,
for I have put my trust in you.
Show me the way I should go,
for in you, I entrust my life.
We've been through hell,
and we're gonna leave all
that behind. I promise.
- What?
- Let's go for a run.
- Go for a run?
- Yeah.
- Come on. Let's go!
- No, no. I'm not doing that.
All right.
Ever since I was a child, people
said my family was cursed.
We never talked about it.
And I don't know if my brothers
and I believed it back then,
but bad things kept happening.
Mom tried to
protect us with God.
Pop tried to protect
us with wrestling.
He said if we were the toughest, the
strongest, the most successful...
nothing could ever hurt us.
I believed him. We all did.
We loved our father.
And we loved wrestling.
One, two, three, four!
One, two...
That's an eye gouge!
That's a trip!
And stay out, you
son of a bitch!
Or I'll come out of retirement!
One, two, three!
Yeah!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the winner and the new
Texas Heavyweight Champion,
Kevin Von Erich!
- Congratulations, Son. You did well.
- Thanks, Pop.
This is just the start. Tomorrow
you're back working harder than ever!
- Proud of you!
- Yes, sir!
Morning.
- Morning.
- Morning, Son.
Pants tomorrow please, David.
Sorry, Ma. I couldn't find them.
They are in the
wash. Heard of it?
Michael, breathe.
Eat like you're starving mutt.
Good morning.
That's why I eat quickly.
They take my food, Ma.
No!
Mike, you need to start
hitting the weights more, kid.
You're growing well,
but you need to bulk up,
get some strength in those arms.
I'll always have
your back, Michael.
You won't always be around.
Mike's fine, Pop.
Kid won't be able
to defend himself.
Well, may not be the strongest,
but I still can eat the most.
It's not a joke.
Kerry is about to become
the family's first Olympian.
Kevin is the NWA Texas Champion.
- David is about to make his ring debut.
- Pop, come on.
It's time for you to start thinking
about what you're gonna be.
Now we all know Kerry's my favourite,
then Kev, then David then Mike,
but the rankings
can always change.
Everyone can work
their way up or down.
Good.
Hold it up a little higher.
That's it. Now push forward.
Goddamn it, Mike!
Come on!
Come on, David, I
gotta take a dump.
- Hurry up in there, man!
- Mike, shut up! Give me a second.
David!
Come in.
- Hi, Ma.
- Hey, Kevin.
Hey, I've been thinking. Can
I talk to you about something?
Baby, that's what
your brothers are for.
I know, but...
I don't want to be late.
Dad's too tough on Mike, Ma.
You gotta say something.
- Please?
- Kevin, that's between them.
Now go, get ready.
We leave in 15 minutes.
All right.
Hey, how are you?
How you been?
Nice to see you.
Hi.
Come on in.
- How are you?
- Good.
Hi, how you doing?
- Hey, how you doing?
- Hey.
Howdy. How you doing?
All right, good.
- This is your biggest fan.
- Thank you.
Yeah. It's nice
to see you again.
Likewise. Likewise.
Thank you so much.
Thanks for coming out, yeah.
How are you?
Good to see you again.
You see this guy?
Yeah, that was good. That
was... That was good.
- All right, bye.
- See you later.
How was orchestra
practice, Michael?
It was great. Thanks, Ma.
I'm starving. Uh... Can
we get burgers on the way?
We got food in the cooler.
I miss Kerry.
He would get burgers
for me right now.
I'll eat a burger with
you, little brother.
- Come on.
- Come on, Kev.
All right.
♪ Love doesn't last that long
♪ I got this feelin'
inside night and day ♪
♪ And now I can't
take it no more ♪
♪ Listen honey can you see
♪ Baby you would bury me
♪ If you were in
the public eye ♪
♪ Givin' someone else a try
♪ And you know you
better watch your step ♪
♪ Or you're gonna
get hurt yourself ♪
♪ Someone's gonna
tell you lies ♪
♪ Cut you down to size
♪ Don't do me like that
Don't do me like that ♪
♪ What if I love you baby ♪
Hi, Kevin!
Welcome back, ladies
and gentlemen.
We have the newly crowned Texas
Heavyweight Champion, Kevin Von Erich here,
and he is scheduled to fight in
a tag-team match later on tonight
against Gino Hernandez
and Bruiser Brody.
But his partner is
still a mystery.
That's right, Bill.
First off, I just
wanna say to Gino,
you've been running that mouth
of yours way, way too long,
and I'm here to take care of it.
Boy, oh, boy.
Do I have somethin' special
for you tonight, buddy.
- Can we just do that again from the top, yeah?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Thank you.
- Take it from the top, okay?
Okay.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Ready.
Welcome back, ladies
and gentlemen.
We have the newly crowned
Texas Heavyweight Champion,
Kevin Von Erich here tonight,
and he's scheduled to
fight in a tag-team match
against Gino Hernandez
and Bruiser Brody.
But his partner is
still a mystery.
That's right, Bill.
First off, I just
wanna say that, Gino,
you've been shooting your mouth off way,
way too long about me and my family.
I got something special
for you, boy, oh, boy.
It ain't gonna be
all roses... Fuck.
It's okay. We'll go again.
- David, I hear you. Stop.
- I didn't say anything.
Welcome back, ladies
and gentlemen.
We have the newly crowned
Texas Heavyweight Champion,
Kevin Von Erich here
and he is scheduled to fight in
a tag-team match later on tonight
against Gino Hernandez
and Bruiser Brody.
But his partner still
remains a mystery.
That's right, Bill.
I got something special for... that the
hometown crowd fans are really gonna love
tonight.
You know, first off, I
just wanna say, Gino,
you've been shooting your
mouth... shooting your
shoot... shooting your mouth...
- Shoobadoobadoo.
- Shit, sorry.
David.
If it's so easy, you get
up here and do it then.
Yeah, I mean I... I'd love to,
but it'll kind of ruin
the surprise, you know?
Yeah, I know.
- You're not helping.
- All right.
Just get out of here.
- Wanna try again?
- Yeah, yes. Okay.
♪ All our times have come
♪ Here but now they're gone
♪ Seasons don't
fear the reaper ♪
♪ Nor do the wind
the sun or the rain ♪
♪ We can be like they are
♪ Come on baby Don't
fear the reaper ♪
♪ Baby take my hand
Don't fear the reaper ♪
♪ We'll be able to fly
♪ Baby I'm your man ♪
I'll give you a big boot, so
I want you to really sell it.
I tag Gino in, fight him back.
Give him a body
slam, an elbow drop.
He's gonna drive you to
the corner, stay there
'cause I'm gonna be coming
in and take the post.
And I'm a go straight up top, so
don't leave me there too long.
- Okay? Cross body.
- I'll still be sellin', my feet up.
- And then double drop kick?
- Yeah.
- Then the Claw?
- Right, yeah.
You been working on
that with your dad?
A little, yeah.
All right, just don't fuck
with my hair too much, okay?
All right, David.
Welcome to the show.
One, two...
And a kick out from Gino...
Let's go, David!
David picks up Gino, but he
pushes him in the corner.
And here comes Brody
charging across the ring.
He misses him. He misses him. And comes
all the way back over to the side.
Kevin getting up
on the top rope.
Brody dazed now.
And a huge flying cross body
knocks down Brody.
The brothers line up
a double drop kick.
An incredible double drop kick!
Blowing the roof off of this place!
Can you hear these people?
And here comes the Iron Claw,
his father's notorious
signature move.
Oh, and he slaps it
on Gino. Look at him.
The pain is too much. Gino taps
out, and the Von Erichs win!
Look out, NWA!
David and Kevin
Von Erich are here!
David and Kevin Von Erich!
- No problem.
- Excuse me. Can you make it out to Emily?
- Emily. That's for you.
- Thank you, thank you.
Thank you. Thanks
for coming, guys.
- Thank you so much.
Yeah, thanks for coming.
Come next week, all right?
I'm gonna go.
- Okay, bye!
- Bye, bye.
All right.
Hi, Kevin. Hey, um...
Can I get your autograph?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thanks.
Oh, don't you wanna ask
me who to make it out to?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
It's Pam.
- Pam.
- Mmm-hmm.
You're supposed to say,
"Nice to meet you, Pam."
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Uh, it is nice to meet you, Pam.
It's nice to meet
you too, Kevin.
Did you, uh, want
my brother to sign?
No, just you.
Okay, then.
Your folks not teach you
how to ask questions?
Like what?
Well, like, you know,
"Who shall I make this
out to?" Or, um, or...
"Would you like to have a
drink with me sometime, Pam?"
Are you asking me out?
Make me feel a little
worse while you're at it.
No, no, no. Sorry, no, I, uh...
I would love to go
out with you, Pam.
Wasn't that... Yeah, I just...
I've just never been asked before.
Oh.
Well, hopefully, it will go well
and then no one else will have
the chance to ask you again.
Yeah.
Morning.
David's good.
Got the Saturday ratings back.
Highest numbers ever.
And somebody called
me from over at ESPN.
They wanna offer us a national
slot for Saturday nights.
That's great news.
Break it down for me.
Well, it's good financial base.
Uh, we'll have ad revenue.
Bigger and bigger
names coming through.
But if we perform and we have a World
Heavyweight Champion in our roster,
we could be the biggest
promotion in wrestling.
Oh, we'll have a World
Heavyweight Champion.
I can promise you that.
- Let's move forward.
- Okay.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
Yeah, have a good one.
Are you this famous everywhere?
No, not everywhere.
- They're not such big fans up in Missouri.
- Oh.
That's for sure.
You travel a lot?
Uh, yeah. Yeah. We
go out on the road.
But we don't have
to as much anymore,
because our show
is doing so well.
So, what do you want in
life, Kevin Von Erich?
More ribs.
I wanna be World
Heavyweight Champion.
Hmm. Well, can you
just explain that to me
'cause ain't it all just fake?
Fake?
There's nothing fake
about what we do.
Okay. All right.
All right. Not fake.
Um...
Prearranged? Written?
Look, you move up
in any industry
based on your
performances, right?
Mmm-hmm.
So a belt, like my Texas title,
is really just a job promotion.
The promoters keep you
moving up if you do well.
And if you reach the top,
you become World
Champ as a reward,
because you're the best
based on your ability
and on how the crowd
responds to you.
Is that all you want?
No. Of course not.
I wanna be with my family.
You know, be with my brothers.
Mmm, that's sweet.
What do you like to
do with your brothers?
Anything. I don't know.
Just being together,
we can do anything.
Hmm.
What about you?
Well, I wanna be a vet.
I want kids. I want
my own practice.
I want a man who's
okay with that.
Cool.
So, would you be okay with that?
Oh, damn right, I would.
We could be one of those
modern super couples.
We can have our own ranch.
Everyone could come live with us.
All my brothers, their families.
Okay.
You know, you have
oldest brother syndrome.
- Yeah, you wanna take care of everyone.
- Maybe.
I'm not the oldest, though.
When I was five, my big
brother, Jack Jr., he died.
Oh. Oh, my God. Kevin, I'm
so sorry. I had no idea.
Oh, it's all right. I don't
really think about it.
Not anymore.
What was that like?
I don't know. It was strange.
As a kid, he just, uh...
He just wasn't there
to play with one day.
So, I'm not the oldest.
I must have the, uh
the second-oldest
brother syndrome.
I'm so sorry.
It's a part of the
family curse, I guess.
What's that?
Oh, I'm just joking.
What, you never heard of
the curse of the Von Erichs?
No.
- Really?
- No.
Oh, it's uh...
it's a silly story.
Hmm?
My dad changed his
last name to Von Erich,
which was my
grandma's last name.
And I don't know, I guess her
family had all sorts of tragedy.
So, when my brother died,
people started saying
that it was this curse.
But I don't believe
in any of that.
I know it was all just bad luck.
Well, I don't believe in curses,
and I don't believe in luck.
I think we make our own luck.
You're lucky then.
- Kev.
- Hey, Pop.
Get in here. Come
in, Son. Sit down.
Big news for you.
I booked Harley Race to
come to the Sportatorium.
You are gonna fight the
World Heavyweight Champion.
No way.
You kidding me, Pop?
Your first match will
be a non-title fight,
but if you put a whooping on him and show
the world who you are and what you can do,
you will become the
number one contender
for the World
Heavyweight Championship
and get your title shot.
Pop, thank you.
Thank you. I... I will
make you so proud.
I've dreamed of having that belt
in this house my whole career
but the NWA never gave
me the chance I deserved.
I got close many times,
but they always robbed
me at the last minute.
So you have to take
this opportunity.
You can be the one to
bring it home for us.
Yes, sir.
I am the four-time World
Heavyweight Champion.
Me, Harley Race, the real
World Heavyweight Champion.
Not any of this plastic nonsense
that you all parade
around with, out there.
You have all these
guys walking around
talking loud about
how they are the man.
Ric Flair, Dusty
Rhodes, Tommy Rich,
or one of your snot-nosed
Von Erich kids.
Well,
this belt is the only
measure of who is the man.
And that man is me.
The World's Heavyweight
Champion, Harley Race.
Good evening, ladies
and gentlemen,
and welcome to an exciting night
of World Class Championship
Wrestling on ESPN.
Tonight, we have a
momentous main event,
NWA World Heavyweight Champ
Harley Race is in town
to take on Texas
Champion, Kevin Von Erich.
And here we go, folks.
You can feel the excitement here
at the world-famous Sportatorium
in downtown Dallas, Texas.
As that man right there,
local hero Kevin Von Erich
faces his biggest
challenge to date.
Four-time World Champion,
the indomitable Harley Race.
What an occasion this
is for Von Erich family.
The 3,500 fans in the building
and everyone watching at home
as we are broadcasting in 62
countries around the world.
All eyes are on this contest.
Now this is a non-title fight.
The belt cannot change
hands here, tonight.
But it is a tremendous
opportunity for Kevin.
If he can win, he would become
the number one contender.
And they lock up,
Harley Race overpowering
Kevin into the corner.
And he delivers a big
blow to the midsection,
knocks the wind
right out of him.
Not a great start
for the young man
looking to make an
impression here tonight.
And a devastating shot to the
lower back puts Kevin on the mat.
He's lining up a big shot,
and Kevin blocks it
and returns a punch.
Connects once. Twice.
And three times.
Hits Harley Race again
pretty hard on that one.
Kevin coming off the
ropes with a clothesline.
The champ doesn't budge.
Kevin again off the ropes.
Oh, and he knocks him down!
He knocks down the old
oak tree, Harley Race,
with a spectacular
flying clothesline.
But the champ is right
back up. Shaking it off.
Kevin goes straight
into a bear hug.
Looking for that
belly-to-back suplex.
Hey, break it
off. Break it off!
Oh, and a low blow.
Oh, I don't think
the ref saw that.
Kevin's struggling now.
A vicious tactic from Race who looks
to get back on top in this contest.
Let's go for a ride, kid.
Oh, and he... he tosses
Kevin over the top rope.
My goodness! Kevin crashes
down on that concrete floor.
Race, absolutely ruthless,
gets Kevin in a suplex.
Oh, no. I hope he doesn't
do it. And he does!
Harley Race puts
a standing suplex
on Kevin Von Erich, directly
onto the concrete floor.
Kevin is down. This
crowd is stunned!
Kevin is not moving, folks.
Kevin Von Erich is not moving.
Harley Race gets
back up to the ring.
Kevin! Kevin! Kevin!
One!
Two!
Three!
Come on! Get up!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Kevin! Kevin! Kevin!
Seven!
Eight!
He's starting to step up!
Nine!
Unbelievable what this
man has been through.
He's seen it all. He's...
Well, he's self-sacrificed.
He's worked very, very hard,
and here he is, back in
the ring with Harley Race.
Kick to the ribs! That
has to do some damage.
And this is why Harley Race
is the most dominant
champion of our time.
Kevin's gasping for air
as Race gets him into
yet another suplex.
But Kevin spins out and
a knee right in the jaw,
knocking the champ
flat on his back.
He's back in this match.
And here he comes off the
ropes. And a big splash!
This could be it!
- One, two...
- One, two!
And Race gouges Kevin's eyes!
The ref cautioning, but
he doesn't wanna hear.
Oh, and he throws the ref out!
And that's it. Surely,
he will be disqualified.
Yes, and there's
the bell, folks.
The boos ring out.
The fans did not want
to see it end like this.
And the winner by
disqualification,
Kevin Von Erich.
Oh, oh, here comes
David Von Erich!
Get out of here!
I dare you to come back in!
Harley Race, I dare you!
Go on! Get out of here! You
ain't got no place here!
Harley Race.
You coward.
You afraid I was gonna beat you
so...
Harley Race, tonight,
we showed you what
we're made of.
All right?
You came into our
building with our fans...
And my brother here
put a good old-fashioned
Texas whooping on you.
You are the past, my friend.
We are the future of this sport.
So, you keep on running,
but everyone sees you.
Oh, yeah. Everyone sees you.
And we'll catch you
whether you're man enough
to stop back through Dallas
or if we have to chase
you down in Missouri.
My brother here
deserves his rematch
and he will fight you anywhere,
anytime for a fair shot
at that NWA World
Heavyweight title.
You were long getting up.
Yeah. I've just never hit
the floor that hard before.
You gotta take it and get up.
Yeah, I know.
He wasn't supposed to
throw me out of the ring.
Caught me off guard.
There was nothing I could do.
I physically... I
just couldn't move.
This is how they test you.
- Did I do enough to get my rematch?
- Of course, you did.
We'll see.
Those rat bastards will use any
excuse they can to screw us over.
But I'll chase 'em.
David.
Great on the mic,
Son. Really great.
We'll get you out on the road,
get you some more exposure.
Okay.
Hey, listen. Dad's
downplaying it
'cause he doesn't wanna
get your hopes up.
But you were
incredible out there.
Why didn't you let me talk?
Well, you didn't.
You should've let me talk.
Yeah, I'm sorry, Kev, I
thought I was helping.
Hey, smile, man.
You just beat the World
Heavyweight Champion out there.
All right, Kerry, let's
make this a big one.
Ready?
You all set?
In my judgment,
what we are doing
is preserving the principles
and the quality of the Olympics,
not destroying it.
It is absolutely imperative
that we and other nations
who believe in freedom and
who believe in human rights,
let our voices be heard
in an absolutely clear way
and not add the
imprimatur of approval
to the Soviet Union
and its government
while they have 105,000 heavily armed
invading forces in the freedom-loving,
and innocent, and deeply
religious country of Afghanistan.
And I hope recognition
of a grateful nation
will at least partially make up
for the sacrifice that you'll
have to make this summer
in not going to Moscow
for the Summer Olympics.
I can't say at this moment
what other nations will not go.
Ours will not go.
Hi!
- Hey!
- Kerry.
Welcome home, Kerry.
I'm sorry it didn't
work out, Pop.
Me too, Son.
- Hey.
- Hey, Ma.
- Hey, boys. Hi.
Come here, man.
Oh, Mikey. Look at you!
Ready, set!
Hike!
You're the fastest
in the family, Kev!
No one could ever catch you.
You still got it, Son.
Gotta put him on his ass before
he breaks past you, Kerry.
Blue 82. Hut, hike!
That's how you make
a hit on someone.
- What?
- What? Come on!
Hut, hike!
You gotta dive for them, Mike.
You gotta lay out for that.
Come on, Son.
Hike!
Oh, my God, look at that!
That's why you're the best
linebacker in the state, Kerry!
Coach Royal called me from UT.
He said, "Why is the best
linebacker in the state"
"watching from the stands?"
Good job, Son.
- Hey, Pam.
- Hmm?
I can pour you some more...
more lemonade or something.
Sure, thanks, Mike.
You keep a hold on her,
Son. She's a good one.
You put that down, someone
else will pick it up.
Yes, sir.
Hey, I, uh... I saw
the new show, Pop.
It's great.
And I was real proud watching
you fight Harley, Kev.
Thanks, Kerry.
Now, when's the rematch?
Uh, I'm not sure yet.
We just haven't got the call.
- Oh.
- I'm working on it.
Hey, Ker, you see all
the new camera angles?
- They're cool, right?
- Yep.
We're talking about
wrestling, not camera angles.
Your brother fought the World
Champion on national TV.
Who gives a damn
about camera angles?
Hey, how's the
music coming, Mike?
Hmm? Hey, what do you play?
Lots of things. Um...
Viola, violin, piano,
some other instruments.
Musical like his father.
What?
Dad's musical?
When I first met your father,
he was classically
trained on the clarinet
and had a Music scholarship
to University of Texas.
Wow.
But he gave it up to play
football at Southern Methodist.
Wow.
Decided there was
no future in music.
I chose sport and I was right.
He used to play the most
beautiful pieces for me
when we first dated.
Aww.
Such a well-rounded man.
Not like anyone I ever met.
Dottie, please.
I've been meaning
to tell everyone, I
well, I got this...
I got this quartet that
I'm a part of from school
and um, well, we... we
actually have a gig.
- Yeah?
- Michael, that's great. When?
That's the thing. It's
well, it's tonight
at UT, Dallas.
Oh. No.
You're too young to set
foot on a university campus
- on a Saturday night.
- Ma... Kev...
Kev went on national
tour at 17. Excuse me.
That was for work.
Your mom said no and
that's the end of it.
This is work. We're...
We're getting paid.
- I mean, we could take him.
- Yeah. Yeah, we could.
He could play the gig, and
we'll leave right after.
- Sure.
- No.
The answer is no.
Shh!
Get down, get down.
Okay, come on.
Watch out.
Oh, yeah.
- Cheers!
♪ Come on open the gates
♪ I'm hanging onto this feeling
till they drag me away ♪
♪ I wanna live
that way forever ♪
♪ So hold your head up high
♪ I'm not ready to run
♪ So Mama now don't you cry
♪ I'm gonna light up the sky
♪ Roman candle just waiting
for the 4th of July ♪
♪ I wanna live
that way forever ♪
He knows what he's doing.
♪ I wanna live
that way forever ♪
Five, six, seven,
eight, nine, 10!
Yeah!
Look at my beautiful brothers!
He's got an appetite.
Yeah, Kerry can put
'em back for sure.
That's good. He's
letting off steam.
So, what do you think?
Like, we're a lot.
I love your family, Kevin.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You know, you're beautiful.
♪ Wanna live that way forever ♪
Yeah, come on.
- Oh, my God!
- I got it.
- This okay?
- Oh, yeah.
Ow.
- Hey, uh...
- Yeah?
Have you ever?
What? Why?
Why, would that be a problem?
What? No. No, no,
no. Not at all, no.
What is it then?
I just, uh... I just...
Honey, never?
Not never, never.
Oh, Kevin, you sweet thing.
Okay.
One, two, three!
He did it! He did it!
Ric Flair has just defeated
the NWA World Heavyweight
Champion, Harley Race!
There you see, he's up
on the screen, you folks.
Ric Flair, the new...
- Kerry.
- Yes, sir.
I don't know if you've been
thinking about your future,
but you should think
about wrestling.
Now, I wouldn't wish
wrestling on any of you.
I only wrestled to
provide for you all.
And I always hoped you boys
would choose another profession.
But the Olympics has
been taken from you
the way professional
football was taken from me.
The world keeps taking from
us, and I'm sick of it.
I wanna fight back.
And the more of us in
it together, the better.
So, Kerry, I want you to join
your brothers in the ring.
Yes, sir, I'd love that.
Glad to hear it, Son.
Thank you.
Get you training,
little brother.
Whoo!
Okay!
One, two...
Come on!
Whoo!
We get Kerry front-row St. Louis
and the crowd was electrified.
He's gonna be World
Heavyweight Champion one day.
You aren't pressing.
This is pressing.
You feel that? You feel that?
Now push.
Damn it! Well, you
gotta get this!
Freebirds, ever since
you've arrived in the WCCW,
you've done nothing but lie, bully and cheat
your way to victory. And we're sick of it.
There you go!
Now, you've made this about
Georgia versus Texas and it isn't.
It's about filth versus
decency. And you know it.
And we're here today to
restore justice and order
to the wrestling federation
that our father built
with his own two hands.
The hands that were
passed down to us.
The hands that will deliver
the Iron Claw to you.
Whoo!
Welcome to WCCW.
The only promotion being
broadcast worldwide!
To my left at a combined
weight of 740 pounds
from Bad Street,
Atlanta, Georgia.
The reigning NWA six-man
tag team champions,
The Fabulous Freebirds!
And the challengers
from Denton, Texas,
weighing in at a combined
weight of 690 pounds,
Kevin, Kerry, and
David Von Erich!
It's total mayhem.
Gordy kicks out and
Hayes elbows his own man.
Kerry moving out of
the way just in time.
All hell has broken loose.
Kevin tossing Michael
Hayes through the ropes,
the ref trying to
restore some order here.
He forces Kevin
back to his corner.
Buddy Roberts comes in.
Two-on-one on Kerry.
Oh, no. But Kerry flips
Buddy over the top rope.
Kerry off the ropes
with a cross body.
Terry Gordy catches him. What
he's going to do with him?
Here comes David
with a drop kick!
Kerry falls on
Gordy. And that's it!
That's it!
The Von Erichs win!
What a special moment today!
The winners and new NWA World's
six-man tag team champions,
Kevin, Kerry, and
David Von Erich!
You did it! I'm
real proud of you!
- So?
- Freebirds,
tonight, you saw the strength
and resilience of my family.
We're sending a
message to Sam Muchnick
and every other territory
out there in the NWA.
WCCW is the best
in the business!
The Von Erichs are the
best in the business!
And we're coming for y'all.
Well, Fritz, calling out the man
who runs the NWA on air by name.
That's a bold and
unprecedented move.
It's necessary, Bill,
because I will make it my
life's work to see to it
that David Von Erich
will be the next.
NWA World Heavyweight Champion!
And then each and
every one of my sons
starting with Kevin,
then Kerry, then Mike.
All one day will lift that
World Heavyweight title belt,
because the Von Erichs
are and will forever be
the greatest family in
the history of wrestling!
Congratulations, boys.
I'm sure he doesn't
mean me first.
Pop doesn't make
mistakes like that.
Is there a problem?
No, sir.
Boys, I've got good news.
We are finally getting a
World Heavyweight title shot
with Ric Flair.
And they want it
to be you, David.
Don't look to your brother.
This is your time,
your opportunity.
You've been chosen.
You earned it.
You'll go on the road
and feud with Flair
in every territory in America
over the next six months.
Then you'll go to Japan.
You can't be World Champion
unless you win over Japan.
Then you'll fight with Flair
at Parade of Champions in May
at Texas Stadium.
Are you up for it?
Of course I am.
I love you, Pop.
I love you too, Son.
I've waited my whole
life to have that belt.
We've had a couple of
setbacks, but I can feel it.
If you perform, the
title will be ours.
Now, this wouldn't be happening
without the two of you.
You've made your brother better,
and your collective effort
has pushed him to the top.
Keep it up out there.
You never know when your
opportunity will come.
- Yes, sir.
Fuck yeah, David! Fuck yeah!
♪ Put your lovin' hand out
♪ Baby
♪ I'm beggin'
♪ Beggin' Beggin' you ♪
♪ Put your loving
hand out baby ♪
♪ Beggin' Beggin' you ♪
♪ Put your loving
hand out baby ♪
♪ Ridin' high when I was king ♪
♪ I played it hard and fast
'cause I had everything ♪
♪ Walked away Wondering then ♪
♪ But easy come and easy
go and it would end ♪
♪ Beggin'
♪ I'm beggin' you
♪ Won't you give
your hand out baby ♪
♪ Beggin' Beggin' you ♪
♪ Put your loving
hand out baby ♪
♪ I need you to understand
♪ That I tried so
hard to be a man ♪
♪ The kind of man... ♪
Too much already? It's early.
Who is it?
Shit, Brother.
- You all right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah... just some
stomach cramps.
Jesus, man.
- You need to see a doctor.
- No, I'm fine.
You're not fine.
No, it's just a bug I
picked up on the road.
Don't worry about it.
Maybe you're pushing too hard.
You need to rest.
I'm almost there.
You think it's gonna slow down
when you become world champion?
I'm fine, Kev. Seriously,
I'm just sick. I'll be good.
I don't think you should
go to Japan next week.
Okay. All right, yeah.
- Shit.
- For sure.
- Hey, Dave.
- Hmm?
I just wanna say,
I didn't take it so well,
you jumping me and all.
I understand.
I got pretty angry.
Not at you. Just at
the whole situation.
Thing is, I didn't even
really want it that bad.
I just love being out
there with you guys.
It's the only thing
that matters to me.
Look at you, man.
Married two hours
and already losing
your competitive edge.
Maybe.
I'll be pretty happy to
focus on my family, though.
Family?
Turns out this is
a shotgun wedding.
- You rat bastard.
- Don't tell anyone.
Goddamn it, Kev!
Oh, man, that makes me so happy.
Shit.
- I'm gonna be an uncle?
- Yes, sir.
Gonna be an uncle, all right.
I'm happy for you guys. Now we
got some dancing to do. Come on.
Hold on. Let me look
at you real quick.
No, I'm good. Let's go.
Let's get out there.
♪ Well, life on the farm
is kinda laid back ♪
♪ Ain't much an old country
boy like me can't hack ♪
♪ It's early to rise
early in the sack ♪
♪ Thank God I'm a country boy
♪ Well, a simple kinda
life never did me no harm ♪
♪ A raisin' me a family
and workin' on the farm ♪
♪ My days are all filled
with an easy country charm ♪
♪ Thank God I'm a country boy
♪ Well, I got me a fine wife
I got me an ol' fiddle ♪
Look how lovely she looks
when she puts a little
effort into her appearance.
They're a great couple.
Reminds me of a
couple I knew once.
How about we get
out of here, Dottie?
Well, I could use some air.
We could take advantage
of the situation.
No boys in the house.
And I don't have to worry about
you getting me pregnant anymore.
Big stud.
Whoo!
♪ Well I wouldn't trade my
life for diamonds or jewels ♪
♪ I never was one of
them money hungry fools ♪
♪ I'd rather have my fiddle
and my farmin' tools ♪
♪ Thank God I'm a country boy
♪ Yeah city folk drivin'
in a black limousine ♪
♪ A lotta sad people thinkin'
that's a mighty keen ♪
♪ Well son let me tell ya
now exactly what I mean ♪
♪ I thank God I'm
a country boy ♪
♪ Well, I got me a fine wife
I got me an ol' fiddle ♪
♪ When the sun's comin' up I
got cakes on the griddle... ♪
Pop?
Pop, what is it?
David.
What happened?
He died in his
hotel room in Japan.
A ruptured intestine.
How does that happen?
Take those sunglasses off.
All of you.
No hiding.
And I don't wanna see any tears.
The Lord decided it was
time for David to move on.
We have to accept that.
In his 25 years, he lived
75 years' worth of life.
Kev, sorry I sent
this to the house.
I couldn't remember
your new address.
I miss you, Brother.
You gotta come
with me next time.
It's wild over here.
Someone asked me for
an autograph today
because they thought I was you.
It made me very happy.
I'll probably be home by
the time you get this,
so this is stupid.
But just wanted to send.
See you soon.
Come on, hon.
I am here if you wanna talk.
No. I'm good.
It's hard to see clearly
in this dark moment,
but we cannot let this
tragedy define us.
Our greatness will be measured
by our response to adversity.
Now, David's title
match against Ric Flair
at Parade of Champions is
a moment of a lifetime.
We still have a chance to bring the
World Heavyweight Championship home
if one of you will step up
and wrestle in his place.
Everything we have ever
worked for in the ring
is riding on this moment.
I'll do it.
I can do it, Dad.
I can do it, too.
Kerry, I'll do it.
I'm ready, Dad.
I want it.
You don't have to. It's my mess.
No! I deserve it, too!
Boys, boys.
It's a tough decision.
You are the oldest, Kev,
but Kerry's been getting
the most heat lately.
We're gonna flip a coin.
That's the only
fair way to decide.
Heads for Kerry.
Tails for Kevin.
Texas Stadium, please welcome
the modern-day warrior,
Kerry Von Erich!
35,000 people
here to celebrate
the life of David Von Erich.
Make sure you're on for his
brother, Kerry Von Erich.
Ric Flair here,
can't find a handle.
The champion is always the
favourite in a match like this.
Here on the biggest stage.
Step over to the hold from Flair,
and Kerry puts a stop to that.
He knocks it away.
Here's Flair, to the ropes.
Wants to toss Kerry, but...
Kerry's... Kerry's got him.
He's got him in a backslide.
There's the pin. Two, three!
Kerry Von Erich, the NWA
World Heavyweight Champion!
He wins it for his brother
David, for his father Fritz,
and for the whole
Von Erich family!
The winner and new World
Heavyweight Champion,
Kerry Von Erich!
Hey, I didn't know
you were still here.
Yeah, just helping Pop.
I'm about to head home.
How you doing?
I'm having trouble coming down.
Yeah.
Yeah, I bet.
I can't believe it's
finally in our family.
Yeah.
You know what? I think I'm gonna
go for a ride or something.
- All right. Yeah, be careful.
- Hmm.
- Hey, Ker.
- Yeah.
You were great today.
Thank you.
Is everything correct?
Actually, his last
name will be Adkisson.
That's my birth name.
- Do you have your birth certificate?
- Yes, I do.
- Thank you.
- Let me update it
and I'll be right back.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Thanks.
Are you sure you
want to do that?
No.
I just... I'll feel
safer for him, I think.
Kev, you know it's got
nothing to do with the name.
Yeah, I know.
Don't cross your
damn feet. Shuffle.
Yup. Stand tall.
Use your height!
Hey! That doesn't mean
anything, all right?
Twist it again, make
it mean something.
Headlock.
Keep that S grip tight. I
don't wanna see any windows.
There's no air in there.
Switch your hips.
Switch your feet.
Come on, Goddamn it!
Switch your feet!
- Like that?
- Yes.
There it is.
Let's do it again.
It's... it's still not...
It's fine, Mike. You're
doing fine. Just keep going.
Circle up.
Michael Von Erich,
moving around the ring.
He looks ready for this match.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Come on. Where does it hurt?
Come here! Come here.
- Ow!
- Where does it hurt?
- Hey, Doc.
- Kevin. Fritz.
How'd it go?
Um... we completed the
surgery as planned.
We repaired the shoulder, but it
was trickier than we anticipated.
Mike's temperature skyrocketed.
We worked really hard
to bring it down,
but it was close to 107 degrees
for almost two hours.
We believe he suffered
toxic shock syndrome.
What does that mean?
I'm sorry to say that
Mike is in a coma.
What? How?
It was a routine
shoulder surgery.
Well, it's rare,
but it happens.
All we can do now is wait
and pray he pulls through.
I'm very sorry.
Why is this happening to us?
Why does it just keep happening?
Okay, baby, stay
with me. Okay?
But it keeps happening.
It's taken over.
It was a terrible accident.
Nothing more.
He shouldn't have
even been in the ring.
This is not your fault.
If you want to blame someone,
you blame your father,
but it is not your fault.
- I should've stopped him.
- No. No.
What could you do, Kevin?
There is no getting
through to that man.
Hey. Hey, hon.
I'm late for work,
and I can't get him to settle.
Can you take him for me?
- I can't.
- What? Just...
Okay, just take him till your
mom gets here. I gotta go.
I can't.
Kevin?
Kevin! Come on.
- Yeah. Sorry.
- Here.
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
Hey.
It's okay.
Thank you all for coming,
and thank you all
the love and support.
Hey, Mike, are
you feeling okay?
Yeah.
We're all just so excited
that Mike pulled through.
Shows how much of
a fighter he is.
And uh
after losing David, it's just
it's too much to think that
we almost lost Mike, too.
I... I'm moved that, uh,
my whole family is here
with me through everything.
And uh
that y'all out
there sent flowers.
Uh,
and um, I'm thankful
to everyone.
So what's the time frame for
your return to the ring, Mike?
I know I'll be back,
uh... soon.
Yeah, soon.
Mike's a fighter more than
people even realize, I think.
And... he's gonna be back
in the ring in no time.
One, two, three!
Whoo!
Fuck!
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
That's the house I grew
up in. I painted that.
What... what? Why
didn't you tell anyone?
I had my reasons.
Just don't remember 'em anymore.
I'm scared, Ma.
God loves you, Michael.
There is nothing
to be scared of.
I'm not David.
What?
Everybody wants me to be David,
but I can't replace him.
♪ I've got a fever these days
♪ Revved up like a riot
at the end of a game ♪
♪ Got a feeling till
they take it away ♪
♪ I wanna live
that way forever ♪
Come on!
♪ I wanna live
that way forever ♪
Ow!
I see how much pain you're in.
We can't rush this. It's
gonna take time, Kerry.
I'm ready. I'm ready. Again!
Maybe this is God trying
to tell you to slow down.
Huh?
Maybe you should do something
else with your life.
Why?
So, you're the only
brother left in the ring?
You get all Daddy's
attention? Fuck you.
I want you in the ring! I
can't do this by myself!
Come on! Come on!
Can't just hide this, Kerry!
You want back in?
Then get up!
You want back in, then get up!
Get up!
I'm sorry if I hurt you,
but I'm going to a better place.
Mike!
Mikey!
No, Mike! Mike!
Doris, honey, we should go.
I can't put it on.
Everyone will recognize it. I...
I can't.
I can't. I... I need
a... a new dress.
Honey.
Honey, listen to me.
People here love you.
All right? They don't care.
Doris
we all love you.
All right, come on.
- All right.
- Come on.
Today we are here
to lay to rest our son,
Michael Brett Adkisson,
my sweet, beautiful boy.
Kind, funny,
and uh
truly good.
Are you coming home tonight?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Um, I know how
painful this is. I do.
And uh, I'm trying
to be patient.
But this... this
doesn't work for me.
- - Okay?
- I know.
So, just come home, all right?
Just be with us.
Hey.
I don't want him to get it.
I don't want you
guys to catch it.
- Kevin, you can't be serious.
- I'm sorry.
- Just...
Come home.
I can't, okay?
Okay.
Ever since I was a child,
people said my
family was cursed.
It never seemed to
worry my father.
He said if we were the
toughest, the strongest...
The toughest, the strongest.
- The most successful...
- The most successful,
- the absolute best...
- The absolute best,
nothing could ever hurt us.
Faster!
I believed him.
We all did.
This match is
scheduled for one fall
and it's for the NWA World
Heavyweight Championship.
Now, Ric, there's
been a lot of talk
that you've been resisting
coming down to the Sportatorium
to defend your title
against Kevin Von Erich.
It is so hard to be humble
when you're looking
like Ric Flair.
You see the
difference between me
and a lot of these
so-called big-time stars
is that I'm custom-made
from head to toe.
That's why I've got
the biggest house,
on the biggest hill on
the biggest side of town.
That's why this sports
coat costs $800.
And I don't know
what that costs!
I'd be ashamed to wear it!
That's why I've got on lizard
shoes and a Rolex watch,
and I've got a limousine
out there, a mile long
with 25 women in it
just dying for me to go,
"Whoo!"
Now, let's get to the
less pretty facts of life.
Kevin, your daddy got together
with the powers that be
and ordered me back
down here to Dallas
a nothing-happenin',
second-rate sports community.
I am the World's
Heavyweight Champion,
because I am the greatest
wrestler alive today,
the toughest
wrestler alive today.
I have bled and
sweat for this title
and no daddy's boy is
going to take that from me.
This is professional wrestling.
It is the most grueling of
all professional sports.
I've been stabbed,
hit by chairs,
beat up by everybody.
I don't cry.
I don't complain. I carry on.
But the bottom line is...
- You're denying...
- I am talking right now.
Hey, listen to me! Listen to me.
I'll tell you what, you like
talking to me on the show.
You'll listen to me
talk while I'm out here.
The bottom line is,
if you're a man,
you take the ups and downs.
If you're a real man,
you'll never go down.
You'll just stay up.
That's why I am the World's
Heavyweight Champion.
And I can go through
Kevin Von Erich,
or any Von Erich in the
worst day of my life.
Whoo!
Whoo! Whoo!
Walk the aisle, daddy's
boy! Walk the aisle!
And here comes Kevin.
A meteoric rise
these last two months
to become the
number one contender
for the NWA World
Heavyweight title,
the most prized belt
in all of wrestling,
the only title that
escaped his father,
living legend Fritz Von Erich.
Whoo!
Ric, come on.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Come on! Come on!
Kevin, come on, now.
Hey, Kevin, come on now!
What are you doing?
One, two, three...
Come on, Kev, break the hold!
- Come on, Kev, back up.
- Leave me alone!
- Come on, Kev!
Ring the bell!
Winner by disqualification
and still NWA World
Heavyweight Champion...
What are you doing? Come
on! Hey! Come on, Kev.
Come on!
Ric Flair!
Kevin Von Erich has
been disqualified.
What the fuck happened, Kev?
I don't know.
Whoo!
Ah, Kevin.
Oh, man. You were great.
You were crazy, you were
one crazy son of a bitch.
I mean, I always thought
you were a little soft,
but, baby, you got it.
I'll give you a rematch any day.
Christ, let's get a drink.
Where can we get
fucked up around here?
Oh, I'm... I'm good. Thanks.
All right, well, if you
change your mind, let me know.
I'll be down at the
Holiday Inn. Phew!
Oh.
Come on, Son.
Oh, God. Hang on.
I hear you. Hang on, I'm
just gonna have to...
Hey. ROSS: What's up?
- Hey, guys.
- Hi!
- How you doing? How was your day?
- Good.
- It was amazing, yeah.
- What'd you learn?
We have learnt...
Hey, boys, come
set up for dinner.
A couple more pieces of it.
- Hey, Mom.
- Hey, Mom!
Hi, Mom.
Oh, hello, hello.
I love you.
May I be excused?
Have one more piece of broccoli.
- All right.
- Make it two.
All right. Get out of here.
Hey, how was your day?
It was
- long.
- Yeah.
- You?
- Yeah, all right.
I think we need
to make a change.
We need a bigger boat.
So, what did you decide, boss?
I think we need to cut
down again to one show.
Two is still too many.
We can get the guys
touring during the week.
Bring 'em home for
a Saturday night.
That sounds
painful, but smart.
The numbers just
haven't been there
since Kerry went to the WWF.
Jerry called again this
morning. It's a good offer.
You should think about it.
Hey, Dad.
So, we have an offer
on the table from Jerry Jarrett.
He wants to buy us out.
Son, I didn't give
you the company
so you could turn
around and sell it.
I need to think
about my family, Dad.
I'm almost broke.
We need a house.
And we can't fit in
that apartment anymore.
If you sell,
you can forget about stepping
through these doors again.
Damn, you're almost
40 years old.
Still can't take
care of yourself.
I've been through the books.
It doesn't add up.
I didn't make nearly
what it says I did.
I did what was right all along.
You think living
here was a free ride?
Don't you dare question me.
One, two, three!
Yes!
Attaboy, Kerry.
That's how you do it.
Look at your uncle, boys.
Hey!
- Welcome home, champ.
- Hi.
We've been watching
every match on the TV.
Thanks. Thanks, Pop.
- Oh, Hands Man.
- What's going on?
Hey, Pam. Where's the
babies? Where's the babies?
- They're asleep.
- Yeah?
- Hey!
- Hi.
- You're late.
- Yeah, I know.
- Who's this?
- That's uh... that's Tania.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- How do you do?
- It's so nice to meet you.
Let me get a look at you.
You look strong, Son.
WWF Intercontinental Champion,
second-biggest
title in wrestling
since your brother
ruined our promotion.
Knew it was time to
retire when I did.
Kerry, Kerry. Can you
get me a drink, honey?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dad, I got you, um...
I got you something
for Christmas
and I... I don't wanna wait.
I wanna give it to you now.
- Is that all right?
- No! Kerry, no.
We wait for Christmas.
Oh, come on, Mom. It's
so good, it's so good.
And Tania and I,
we're going to, uh,
to Mexico for Christmas. Right?
I thought you were
home for Christmas.
I'm here now,
but we got this great deal
on a Christmas day
flight to Mexico.
And, you know, I need the
rest. Been hitting it hard.
That's, um...
That's for you.
Go ahead.
Now, that's a Smith &
Wesson 35725th anniversary.
What do you think?
Hmm. It's beautiful, Son.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Don't... don't do that. Don't
do that. What are you doing?
- You gotta shoot that.
- Oh, I don't wanna shoot it now.
Well, you always shoot
a gun when you get it.
- I don't wanna shoot it, Kerry.
- Why the fuck not?!
Kerry, what is wrong with you?
What, me? What's
wrong with him?!
Watch it, Son. You brought
company to the house.
Now, we don't wanna be rude.
Just settle down and
we'll have a nice dinner
that your mother
worked hard to prepare.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Now, come tell me.
When are you getting your
world title shot over there?
Hmm?
I see your old tag team
partner Hellwig's holding.
That guy's got nothing
on you. Never has.
Oh, soon. Soon, Pop. Soon.
Are these the boys?
They're so cute!
Yeah.
- Hi.
- Hey!
Hey, man! Oh, I'm so
excited to be home.
- Yeah, I can see.
- Good to see you.
Let me look at you. Hmm.
- You look good.
- Yeah, you too.
Hey, stop. Stop.
- Hey, you okay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Never been better.
Yeah, okay.
Hello.
Oh, hey.
Good. Good. You're still up.
Yeah, yeah, I'm up.
Where are you?
Oh, I'm in some
hotel in Dallas.
Why didn't you go
home? You okay?
Kerry?
No, I'm scared, man.
I'm scared. I'm out of control.
Well, you've got
to get some help.
I'm in pain.
I'm in pain all the time.
I'm fucking deformed!
It takes too much to hide it.
Well, it doesn't
show in the ring.
They're not giving
me a new contract.
And they got me in
house shows from now on.
They don't want me anymore.
Well, I got... I
got nowhere to go.
I've got no one.
Where's Tania?
- Who?
- Tania.
Ain't... That was nothing. I...
I need someone.
You know, I need a family.
Just come here.
Stay with us.
No, I can't. I can't let
your boys see me like this.
Well, then let's get
breakfast somewhere.
Or meet me at home. Mom
can make us pancakes.
You know, I want it all to end.
No, you don't.
No, you don't. You
don't mean that.
I do.
I'm fucking cursed. I wanna die.
How are you gonna
say that to me, huh?
After everything?
It's in me now.
It's got a hold of me.
Kerry, just tell
me where you are,
and I'll come and get you.
Kerry?
- Hello.
- Dad. Dad.
All right. Sorry
for the early call.
It's okay. I'm heading
out to do some work.
- Where's Mom?
- Sleeping.
Hey, I just talked to Kerry.
He's in a pretty bad state.
I'm worried about him.
I'm gonna come out there.
We need to figure out
how to help him, okay?
You boys need to work it
out between yourselves.
Just look out for
him, okay, Dad?
I'll be there as soon as I can.
No! No!
Kerry, Kerry! Kerry!
Come on! Hey, Kerry! Kerry.
I told you to look out for him!
You didn't take care of him!
You didn't take
care of any of 'em!
He called you, and
you didn't help him!
You...
I don't know what's
on the other side,
but I can't be here anymore.
Tonight, I walk
with my brothers.
Hey!
Brother.
Hey, brothers!
There he is.
Hey, Mikey.
Hi.
World champion of
the afterlife, huh?
Oh, finally.
Hey, where's Jack Jr.?
You must be my oldest
brother, Jackie.
So nice to meet you.
Come here.
I love you, Kerry.
Thanks, Kevin.
No, I'd love for you to stay
on wrestling if you want.
I appreciate it. I could
use the extra work.
Just so you know,
your dad called me
out to his ranch.
Tried to intimidate me out
of buying this from you.
Oh, he never stops.
- Well, glad it didn't work.
- Yeah.
Well...
I'll give you a minute.
Dottie?
In here.
What are you doing?
Painting.
What's for dinner?
I didn't make anything.
I'm not hungry.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
- Whoa, okay! Careful, careful.
- Hey.
We want pancakes!
Mmm-hmm. How about
a good morning?
Good morning!
Marshall!
Oh.
Marshall.
You okay, Dad?
Hey, I'm sorry. I...
I'm sorry, boys.
You shouldn't see me like this.
A man doesn't cry.
I'm sorry, boys.
It's okay, Dad. You can
cry. Everyone cries.
Yeah. What are
you talking about?
We cry all the time.
Do you think you
know why you're sad?
Well...
I guess it's because
I used to be a brother
and uh,
and now I'm not a
brother anymore.
Oh, well.
We'll be your brothers, Dad.
Yeah, Dad. We'll
be your brothers.
Oh. Thank you, boys.
Thank you.
All right.
Thank you, boys.
♪ I got a feeling these days
♪ Revved up like a riot
at the end of a game ♪
♪ Come on open the gates
♪ I'm hanging onto this feeling
till they drag me away ♪
♪ I wanna live
that way forever ♪
♪ I fell asleep at the wheel
♪ I ran myself off the road
and woke up in a field ♪
♪ It's getting harder to stay
♪ But I've got a vice
grip on my future ♪
♪ And I'm tougher than pain
♪ Hold your head up high
♪ I'm not ready to run
Mama don't you cry ♪
♪ I'm gonna light up the sky
♪ Roman candle just waiting
for the 4th of July ♪
♪ I wanna live
that way forever ♪
♪ Want you to know my name
♪ I want you to think of
my face when you run away ♪
♪ Don't wanna be replaced
♪ But you're waiting
for another today ♪
♪ I feel it slipping
♪ Oh I feel it slipping
♪ Oh, don't say it's slippin'
♪ Oh don't say it's
slipping away ♪
♪ I wanna live
that way forever ♪
♪ I wanna live that way
♪ I wanna live that way... ♪