VAIL: On my first day of law school,
my professor says two things.
First, "From this day forward,
when your mother says she loves you,
-"get a second opinion. "
- CONNERMAN: (CHUCKLES) And?
VAIL: "If you want justice,
go to a whorehouse.
"If you want to get fucked, go to court. "
Naomi!
CONNERMAN: Let's say you have
a client who you know is guilty...
VAIL: No, don 't even start with that.
Our justice system doesn't care
about that, and neither do I.
(TAP RUNNING)
Every defendant, no matter who he is,
regardless of what he's done,
has the right to the best defense
his attorney can provide. Period.
CONNERMAN: So where
were you with the truth?
Truth?
- How do you mean? Naomi!
- NAOMI: Coming.
(CLEARS THROAT) I'm not sure
how many ways there are to mean it.
VAIL: You think there's only one?
- I can't do this.
- NAOMI: You're late.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Okay.
Actually, you're right, you know.
- There is only one that matters.
- Marty, hold still, please.
My version of it,
the one I create in the minds of those
12 men and women sitting on a jury.
Now, if you want to,
you can call it something else.
The... The illusion of truth, if you want.
It's up to you.
NAOMI: Good. Yeah.
VAIL: Yeah?
Jack, is that it?
You need some more stuff?
- Yeah.
- Tomorrow afternoon?
- CONNERMAN: Yeah.
- All right, I'll have my secretary set it up.
Okay.
- This is a cover story, right?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bye.
(CHOIR SINGING GREGORIAN CHANT)
(INAUDIBLE)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING SOFTLY)
M. C. : Saint Michael's Boys Choir.
Thank you. Thank you.
- What a talented group.
- Tell you after.
- Sure.
- Right now, ladies and gentlemen,
we 're gonna have a brief photo session
while we have the boys here
with His Excellency.
I'll be back in a few minutes.
Please bear with us,
enjoy your dessert and thank you.
- Here we go. Okay.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
Good, good.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Thanks.
Marty. What an unexpected surprise.
VAIL: Well, I'm here to help
our friendly prosecutor off the hook.
JANET: Excuse me.
SHAUGHNESSY: What's it gonna cost?
- A lot less than the alternative.
- Tomorrow at my office, 9:30.
Is this on? Ooh. Yes, it is.
(FEEDBACK SCREECHING)
Your Excellency. Nice to see you again.
Ladies and gentlemen, we have come
to the heart of the matter,
the reason we've all
gathered together here tonight.
This is the fifth straight year
that it's been my privilege
to serve as your master of ceremonies
for The Chicago Bar Association
and Catholic Charities Ball.
I'm afraid
you're gonna have to put that out.
It's a bar, for Christ's sake.
Tonight, due to your generous efforts,
we 've broken last year's record
in terms of attendees and the amount
-of money raised for the Archbishop's...
- I thought you quit.
-...charity, and I think that deserves...
- I cut down.
...a big round of applause.
(APPLAUSE)
- You look beautiful. Cut your hair?
- Yeah. A few months ago.
M. C. : And now, as it has been
my pleasure for the last four years...
- Want to dance?
- There isn't any music.
Sure there is.
...longtime State 's Attorney,
God love him, Mr. John Shaughnessy.
(HUMMING)
(APPLAUSE)
Thank you very much,
ladies and gentlemen,
-and my personal thanks...
- Come on.
All you have to do is turn around.
I thought you liked it better like this.
That way you don't have to look
at the person.
Mean.
Considering the hour, 17! try to keep...
VAIL: Look at me.
First of all, I want to thank all of you
for coming out tonight
to support the Archbishop...
Come on, let's go find a bar
you can still smoke in.
Thanks for the invite,
but I don't like one-night stands
all that much.
- We saw each other for months.
- It was a one-night stand, Marty.
It just lasted six months.
(APPLAUSE)
Thank you, John.
(CLEARS THROAT) Well, I must say
I haven 't seen this many lawyers
and politicians
gathered together in one place
since confession this morning.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
(HEARTY APPLAUSE)
YANCY: There is no way
the People are gonna tolerate
a monetary award to a cockroach
who deserves 20 to life.
He may be your client,
but Joey Pinero is a hard-case felon.
Dealing, racketeering,
money-laundering, attempted murder.
- Did you say "alleged," Yancy?
I didn't hear you say...
Did you hear him say "alleged"?
Mr. Pinero has never been
convicted of anything.
Cops jumped him,
left him bleeding in the snow.
It's a miracle he survived.
Having said that,
I'm not opposed to a settlement.
1.5 million, and Pinero leaves the state.
You can't limit a citizen's right to live
wherever he wants to.
Legally, that's unenforceable.
Whether or not it's enforceable
or just a gentlemen's agreement,
Mr. Pinero will know what we want.
Get the answer you're looking for.
Don't sit around and chat.
It's been a pleasure.
You're worse than the fucking thugs
you represent.
SHAUGHNESSY:
That's enough, Bud. It's over.
- Obviously, I've got to run this by him.
- You're on 40% commission, Marty.
I have nothing but confidence
your recommendation will prevail.
Thank you, John.
(HUMMING)
(GASPS)
(THUMPING)
RUSHMAN: My hand!
Oh, shit.
- Hey.
- Mr. Vail.
How you doing?
(POOL BALLS CLACKING)
(SPANISH MUSIC PLAYING
ON STEREO)
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
Nice tune.
(ORDERS TEQUILA IN SPANISH)
So, what'd they say?
Take it or leave it all for 1.5 million.
From Shaughnessy himself.
What do you think?
I think we should take it,
unless you want to spend
the next two years of your life
tied up in appellate court.
- No, fuck that. Close it.
- Done.
(THAN KS IN SPANISH)
Okay.
(BOTH TOASTING IN SPANISH)
Your shot.
There's one more little thing.
They want you...
They want you to leave the state.
- They want you to disappear.
Disappear?
(SCOFFS)
- That's good. Same bullshit, right?
- What? What are you talking about?
(SINKS BALL)
Ah!
I keep getting these offers
from these guys, Marty.
What offers?
Well, a couple of months ago,
a cop walks in here.
He says,
"You testify against Alderman Martinez,
"and we'll owe you, Joey.
"Say he did you favors,
say he's on your payroll,"
shit like that, right?
So I tell him to go fuck himself.
Why? Because Martinez is a good man.
He's the only one holding out
while the others try to turn South River
into high-rent condos.
- Why didn't you tell me this before?
- Why?
'Cause this shit happens every day.
I didn't think it had anything
to do with this.
- You don't?
- Hey.
I've spent a lot of money in this place.
- They've spent a lot more, a lot more.
- I built a clinic here.
- These people depend on me.
- I don't give a shit.
Send them checks from California.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
I respect your advice, Marty,
but I can't take it.
I'll take the money,
but I ain't going anywhere.
- This is my home.
- I don't like it, Joey.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
- So what are they gonna do, kill me?
- They tried once.
How are they going to kill a man
who never sleeps?
(CHUCKLING)
- Get the money.
- You're too much.
- Hey.
- Yeah.
That song you like? Fourth cut.
- Very nice, thank you.
- Yeah.
(MEN CHATTERING)
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(HELICOPTER HOVERING)
(REPORTER CHATTERING)
Christ, we got enough
fucking cops here?
No doubt, the police are gonna have
their hands full with this one.
WOMAN: Captain Stenner,
can you tell us anything right now?
STENNER: I don't know anything.
I just got here.
AN DY: Captain Stenner,
can you tell us what's going on?
Andy, I haven't seen anything yet.
As soon as I go inside,
I'll come out and tell you, okay?
AN DY: All right.
(SNIFFLING)
(COUGHING)
You should be home in bed, Abel.
It's going around.
I'll consider that, Harvey.
- Christ.
- HARVEY: What a mess, huh?
(SNIFFS)
(PANTING)
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
Sam, you got all you need?
Okay, gently roll him over.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
Police! Stop!
MEDICAL EXAMINER:
Right thumb and forefinger severed.
Symbol "832.156"
is carved into the chest.
- Body temperature, still warm.
- Captain, we got a live one on the run.
(GRUNTING)
ANCHOR ON TV: You can see now,
a passing train has separated
the fleeing suspect...
VAIL: You want to know what I hate?
I'll tell you what I hate.
I hate when they go on and on
about what big fucking whores
the defense attorneys are.
...the suspect is headed into the train...
We're the bad guys. You know why?
'Cause we're always sitting
next to some creep,
we start to look creepy, you know?
Plus, they assume they're guilty.
You know, they assume they did it,
and, like, we know or something.
You don't know.
You don't ask. You don't care.
You do the goddamn job.
It's not like they're your friends,
for Christ's sake.
...there's no telling
where the suspect may have gone...
Well, some are your friends, but...
(BOTH LAUGH)
(MEN CHATTERING
ON POLICE RADIO)
(HELICOPTER HOVERING)
CONNERMAN: So, Why'd you leave
the State's Attorney's Office?
Dead-end job.
You either... You either run for office,
or you end up a judge.
Why become an umpire
when you can play ball?
ANCHOR ON TV: ...continue to pour into
the area around Saint Michael's
and the Archbishop's mansion.
(MAN SHOUTING)
(TRAIN HORN BLARING)
(TRAIN APPROACHING)
Over here! He's over here!
We will, of course,
stay with this shocking story
as it continues to unfold
throughout the day.
Now, what we do know right now
is that at approximately 11:08
this morning, this...
So, when did you know you had them?
Now, at this hour, the scene
at Saint Michael's is crowded...
- What? Sorry.
- Was there a moment
during the Pinero trial
when you said to yourself,
"I've got them"?
The day I took the case. Excuse me.
...the shocking murder this morning
of one of Chicago 's
most beloved figures,
Archbishop Richard Rushman,
has left the city just numb.
Okay, I understand we have Andy live.
Let's go to Andy.
AND Y: Diann, we have just learned
that Chicago police have arrested
a 19-year-old man
tentatively identified as Aaron Stamp/er.
Now, according
to Captain Abel Stenner...
We're gonna have to reschedule.
Call my office, okay? I'm sorry.
...underneath McCormick Place
just minutes after the murder...
(PHONE RINGING)
...through cold-blooded savagery, a
beacon of hope has been taken from us.
Law offices of Martin Vail.
VAIL: You got the news on,
by any chance?
Yeah, we're watching it.
All right, I want you to call Sullivan
in Judge Trotter's office.
Find out where they took him,
and call me right back.
I'm at The Alibi.
- A lot of guys are gonna want this one.
- Okay.
The police have taken the first steps,
acting with speed and determination
with the arrest.
(CAR LOCK CHIRPS)
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
AN DY: Are you taking
the Stampler case?
Andy, I'm sorry.
I can't talk to you about anything.
(ALL CLAMORING)
Thank you very much.
FEMALE REPORTER:
When are you gonna talk?
- VAIL: State's Attorney left yet?
- Yeah. Yancy, no less.
- Yeah? P.D.?
- Come and gone. Lockup!
- VAIL: Give my best to your brother.
- Yeah, sure.
I'd like to see him alone, if I could.
All right,
but I'm gonna have to look you in.
Understood.
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR SLIDES SHUT)
You know who I am?
Well, no. No, sir. No, I don't.
My name is Martin Vail.
I'm what you call a big-shot attorney.
I don't... I don't have no money.
No, I didn't think you did.
I'm willing to take your case pro bono,
which means you get all of my expertise
and hard work for free.
Or, if you want to,
you could get the $40,000-a-year,
court-appointed public defender,
who will almost certainly
escort you personally to death row.
Your choice.
No. No, sir. I...
I'd surely be grateful
for anything you could do for me.
You're welcome.
Now, your full name is?
(STAMMERING) My...
Aaron Luke Stampler.
Stampler.
- You from Kentucky, Aaron?
- Yes, sir. I'm from Creekside.
Does it say that there?
How long you been here in Chicago?
Well, two years next month, I think.
- Have you ever been arrested?
- No. No, sir.
So how do you know the Archbishop?
I was begging on the street
up on Wacker Drive,
(CLEARS THROAT)
Bishop Rushman came by
in his Cadillac.
(STAMMERING) He saw me,
and he stopped.
He took me into Savior House.
I work as an altar boy.
I sing in his choir.
How long were you there
at Savior House?
Year, year and a half.
You're supposed to leave
when you're 18,
but Bishop Rushman let me stay on
way past my 19th birthday.
That was nice of him.
Yes. Yes, it was.
Aaron, did you have any reason
to dislike the Archbishop?
Dislike? No. No, sir.
He was like a father to me.
Yeah, but you...
How do I say this? Were...
Were you in the room
when he was murdered?
How can you explain that?
There was someone else
in that room, Mr. Vail.
- There was a third person?
- Yes, sir.
Did you tell the police this?
Yes. Yes, I did,
but they didn't believe me.
All right. Well, you tell me now.
I was returning a book
to Bishop Rushman's library.
I heard noise, so I went back into his...
In his bedroom.
Bishop Rushman was laying
on the floor.
There was blood all over everything.
And then I seen a shadow. I seen
a person leaning over Bishop Rushman.
He looked up and then he came at me,
and that's when I lost time.
What does that mean, "lost time"?
(STAMMERING) I blacked out.
It just... It happens to me sometimes.
I just... I have spells.
I have spells. I lose time. I can't...
I can't remember nothing.
Why did you run from the police, Aaron,
if you didn't do anything wrong?
Well, when...
When I woke up, I was covered in blood.
I didn't know what to do.
I got scared. I heard sirens, so I ran.
Look, I know how it looks, Mr. Vail,
but I swear...
Yeah, I don't need you
to try to convince me, Aaron.
I just want you to answer my questions.
But I didn't do this.
You've got to believe me.
No, I don't have to believe you.
I don't care.
I'm your attorney,
which means I am your mother,
your father, best friend and your priest.
In other words, I don't want you talking
to anyone but me from now on.
Not the cops, not the press,
not the other guys in the cells here,
nobody without my permission,
you understand? Yeah?
- Yes. Yes, I do.
- All right.
Now the important stuff.
What's your suit size?
- My what?
- Suit size. What, you're about a 38?
Oh.
(CHUCKLES) I don't know.
- About a 38 long.
- Okay.
ANCHOR ON TV:
Stamp/er was flushed by the police
from his hiding place in the bushes
behind the cathedral.
The police chased him through the train
yard, just north of McCormick Place,
almost losing him
as he scrambled over tracks
before an oncoming train,
separating him from the police.
In a later development,
prominent local
criminal defense attorney Martin Vail
is believed to have visited Stamp/er
at the Maxwell Street Precinct...
After a brief chase across the rail yard
behind Saint Michael's Cathedral,
Stamp/er was apprehended in a hole
beneath train tracks.
- AND Y: Are you gonna defend this man?
- Andy, I'm sorry. I can't.--
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
Thank you very much. Thank you.
We 've taken the first step
in the process.
I can now take your questions.
REPORTER 1: Can you tell us anything
about the altar-boy group
-that Aaron Stamp/er was part of?
- SHAUGHNESSY: Not much at this time.
REPORTER 2: Have you
ruled out the involvement
of any of the other altar boys?
SHAUGHNESSY: We have no reason
to suspect anyone other than Stamp/er.
He had access
to the Archbishop's quarters.
He was caught fleeing the area
of Saint Michael's.
The blood-soaked Aaron Stamp/er
was chased
down under McCormick Place,
but not before he was almost killed
by a passing train.
(PHONE RINGING)
SECRETARY: Law office of Martin Vail.
He's gonna call you
as soon as he gets in.
I know. I promise you.
Okay, thank you very much.
- VAIL: Naomi!
- Yeah.
- Talk to you law. Bye.
- Hey.
Sorry I'm late. We have a new client.
NAOMI: I was afraid
you were gonna say that.
Who?
You know what
they're calling him already?
- The Butcher Boy of Saint Mike's.
-(CHUCKLING) I like that.
Well, that's good.
You're gonna be hearing it a lot.
This kid who chopped up
the Archbishop, he's our new client?
Tommy, you're gonna have to try harder
to get the word "allegedly"
into your vocabulary,
-especially if you want to be a lawyer.
- Here you go.
- Tommy, you want coffee?
- No. No, thanks.
All right. He admits he was in the room
when the killing occurred,
but he didn't actually see it happen.
- TOMMY: Can I stop you right there?
- No.
He was returning a book
to the Archbishop.
He heard loud noises in the bedroom.
He went in. He sees a figure,
someone in the shadows
kneeling over the body. He blacks out.
Next thing he knows,
sirens are screaming,
he's covered in blood.
The cops find him in a train tunnel.
He's got the Archbishop's ring
in his pocket.
TOMMY: He stole the Archbishop's ring?
I didn't say that.
I said it was in his pocket.
Is that it?
Yep.
That's... That's bullshit, Marty.
That's the worst bullshit story
I've ever heard in my entire life.
Now it's our bullshit story.
Okay, let's get to work.
Now, the name of the game here
is motive,
as in, the prosecution doesn't have one.
So what we have to do here
is prove that someone else
could have committed the crime.
Then we can establish
reasonable doubt.
So I want to know everything I can
about this guy, everything he was into.
We go to database,
go to Hall of Records, IRS files.
- Even his so-called charities.
- So-called?
The guy was a priest, for Christ's sake.
Naomi, write this down.
(LAUGHS)
8-32.156.
That was carved
into the Archbishop's chest.
- Allegedly.
- No.
That was a fact,
but I appreciate the effort, Tommy.
Thanks.
I also need case histories
on murder by stabbing,
murder by mutilation,
murder by religion.
- Also, I'm gonna need a psychiatrist.
- You're telling me.
And not the kind
that lives in a witness box, either.
I need a real one this time,
and someone who knows
about amnesia.
- What does he look like in person?
- The Butcher Boy?
Like a Boy Scout.
A Boy Scout
with a merit badge in carving.
YANCY: The Archbishop was a close
personal friend of Mr. Shaughnessy.
He came to me earlier this morning
and asked me who was my best man,
- I said you.
- Thank you.
I trust, Mr. Shaughnessy,
if I am to prosecute this case,
I'll be given the authority
which comes with the assignment.
You're the one trying the case, but
let's establish one thing at the outset.
I want the death penalty.
I'd like an opportunity
to go over the case
before we make a determination
on whether or not
to seek the death penalty.
I'm open to anything
you have to say, Janet,
but in my mind there's no debate.
Did he say anything,
the boy they picked up?
Yeah. He didn't do it.
It's a slam dunk, Janet.
Excuse me.
I appreciate your faith in me,
and I don't mean to be argumentative...
Hey, that's what we pay you for.
...but if it's as open and shut
as you say it is, then you don't need me.
The P.D. will plead no contest,
throw the kid on the mercy of the court.
- There's not a public defender.
- He's got a lawyer already? Who?
Hey, I'm Martin Vail.
I'm defending Aaron Stampler.
- I need to inspect the murder site.
- The Butcher Boy, huh?
Thank you. Yes. I forgot his real name.
(DOOR OPENS)
What's the matter, Marty,
lost your faith?
Looking for a little religion?
Now tell me, Counselor,
which one of us
is the true headline-chaser here?
- Unlike you, I was assigned to this case.
- Yeah? Think you're up to it?
Sell the book rights yet,
or are you gonna wait a while?
Want to see some pictures?
Come on. They're kind of cute.
I think you'll agree they clearly show
the heinous nature of the crime.
(JANET CLEARS THROAT)
A small piece of advice,
don't use the word "heinous"
in a courtroom.
Half the jury won't know
what you're talking about.
One small piece of advice,
I'm not sitting second chair
to you anymore.
In case you hadn't noticed, I graduated.
- I had no reason to leave.
- You had every reason to leave.
How can you still work for them?
What? You really expect me
to trot out after you, Marty?
Quit, just because you did?
I don't need a Mercedes.
I don't need to see my face
on the evening news.
You knew I was coming here,
didn't you?
You knew I would defend him.
That's why you took the case.
You asked Shaughnessy for this,
didn't you?
Oh, please.
What's the matter, Marty, you nervous?
Been a while since you rubbed up
against a woman with a brain?
What is the matter? You tired?
You haven't been sleeping well?
You're the one
with the score to settle, Marty.
I sleep great at night.
(DOOR SHUTS)
- Hi.
- Hey.
(DOOR BUZZING)
Thanks.
- Hey. Where is he?
- Over here.
VAIL: All right,
we 7! be sitting at a table together:
along with two of my associates.
Now, once the charges are read,
the judge is gonna ask you
how you plead.
-(STAMMERING) Not guilty.
- No.
- But I'm not guilty, Mr. Vail.
- I don't care. It doesn't matter.
You can keep your mouth shut.
You don't say anything.
Well, you're going to say I'm not guilty.
(EXCLAIMS IN EXASPERATION)
I'll say whatever I say.
You don't have to worry about it.
- But, Mr. Vail...
- This is exactly what I'm talking about.
This can't go on in the courtroom,
so you might as well get used to it now.
I speak. You do not speak.
Your job is just to sit there
and look innocent.
Well, I am innocent.
That's it!
That's exactly how I want you to look.
That's exactly it.
Now, can you remember that?
Look in the mirror if you have to.
That's the look.
I don't have to.
This is how I always look.
Well, then you're way ahead
of the game already, aren't you?
Don't smile.
Don't.
(PEOPLE PROTESTING)
Mr. Vail, can we have a statement?
No. We're gonna find out
what happened here.
How can you defend Aaron Stampler
in the face of all this public pressure?
VAIL: The only pressure
is to find the truth.
...with the Archbishop's blood on him.
You've been talking to the police again,
haven't you? I told you not to.
As usual, they get everything wrong.
Come on. How're you gonna explain
the fact that
he had blood-soaked clothing on him?
- We all saw that.
- At this juncture,
I'm not going to explain it at all.
I've only recently been retained
in this case.
Significant facts are in dispute here
and continue to be in dispute.
Marty, you're a master at putting
the victim on trial
to help your own client.
That's going to be very difficult
in this case-
A victim in this case is my client.
We have two victims here, no suspects.
Thank you very much.
Are you worried about his safety, Marty?
No. Thank you.
(INAUDIBLE)
SHAUGHNESSY: It's not a case.
I don't think there'll be any question
about the verdict.
All rise.
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
- Bailiff?
- BAILIFF: State v. Aaron Stamp/er.
Is everyone here? Sit down.
Is everyone here?
BAILIFF: Yes, Your Honor.
JUDGE: Madam Prosecutor?
The State charges the prisoner,
Aaron Stampler,
with the crime
of murder in the first degree.
How does your client plead, Counselor?
Your Honor, if it pleases the court,
I need time to make
a complete psychiatric evaluation
before any charges
are brought against us.
JANET: State has
more than enough evidence
to warrant the allegations, Your Honor.
I agree. Motion denied.
Mr. Stampler,
Do you understand the charges
brought against you?
- Yes. Yes, I...
- Your Honor, I direct my client
not to answer that question
on the grounds that his response
may tend to incriminate him.
The defendant is taking the Fifth
on whether or not
he understands the charges?
Yes, Your Honor. Until we have
a complete psychological evaluation,
he will be taking the Fifth
on any and all questions posed to him.
State v. Appleby for your review
of precedent.
Thank you.
(MAN CHATTERING ON TV)
No, no, I can't do that. No.
What do you want?
I'm looking for the room
a kid named Aaron Stampler stayed in.
- You the police?
- I'm his uncle.
(TRAIN APPROACHING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(DOOR RATTLING)
(FOOTSTEPS FADING)
- VAIL: Thanks.
- Well, hey.
- This is Alex's.
- Who's Alex?
(STAMMERING) He's one
of the other altar boys.
An altar boy?
An altar boy was wearing this?
Well, not at the mass.
Well, this altar boy attacked
a colleague of mine.
He hurt him pretty bad.
What do you think he was doing there
in your room?
- My room?
- Yeah.
(STAMMERING) I can't... I don't know.
- I mean, I don't have nothing.
- You know where I could find him?
Who? Alex?
Uh-huh.
- No, I don't... I don't know where he is.
- You don't?
- Who's Linda?
- Linda?
She your girlfriend?
- Where is she? I'd like to talk to her.
- I don't know where she is.
Why is it that I get this feeling
you're not telling me something, Aaron?
- I'm telling you the truth.
- I don't think so.
Are you surprised that Alex
attacked my friend?
No. No, I mean, he has a temper.
(LAUGHS SARCASTICALLY)
Yeah. Yeah, I'd say so.
Let me ask you this.
Do you think it could be Alex
who was that figure you saw
at the Archbishop's room?
- I... Alex? I couldn't be sure.
- But it could be him?
(STAMMERING) I don't know.
Aaron, you're not understanding this.
The State wants you dead.
If you don't help me,
that's exactly what they're gonna get.
I...
I'm trying. I can't remember.
I don't understand. Why would Alex
want to do such a thing?
For his own reasons. He...
Maybe someone hired him.
- Hired by who?
- I don't know. Forget it.
(SIGHS)
What I need to know is,
do you think he's capable of doing it?
(STAMMERING) I don't know. He...
I don't know
who's capable of such a thing, Mr. Vail.
VAIL: Thanks.
SECRETARY: Sure.
So he claims there was someone else
in the room
and that he can't remember.
And you want me
to look into this amnesia question
- And see what he actually knows.
- Yeah.
What if he knows he did it?
The major causes of amnesia
are substance abuse, seizures,
head injuries and malingering.
(SIGHS)
I think the kid's telling the truth.
Okay.
Then let's get something straight.
I'm more than happy to go in
and analyze him.
In fact, I'm looking forward to it.
But I won't go in there
to validate his story, understood?
- You do your job, I do mine. Yada, yada.
- That's right.
Listen, if I think it's necessary,
I'd want to get an MRI, EEG,
and neuropsych testing, agreed?
- Yes, Doctor. Good night, Doctor.
- Good night.
MOLLY: I'll be recording our meetings
for Mr. Vail,
so what we talk about
isn't as confidential the way it might be
if you were to be consulting
with a doctor for help.
He may even call me as a witness,
so if you have any questions
about what I've just said,
you should raise them now,
while he's still here.
(STAMMERING) No, ma'am.
I understand.
Good.
- So, okay. I think we'll be fine.
- VAIL: All right.
- I'll see you later. All right.
- Okay.
Bye.
(DOOR SHUTS)
Mr. Vail told me
that there was a period of time
surrounding the Archbishop's death
that you don't remember.
- Is that right?
-(STAMMERING) Yeah. Yes.
I lost the time.
I mean, I blacked out.
- Have you had these blackouts before?
- Yes. Yes, I have.
When's the first time
you remember them happening?
They started
when I was about 12, maybe.
Were your parents aware
of what was happening to you?
No. My mother was dead.
And your father?
No. No. No. He was not a nice man.
- Did you seek treatment?
- Did I what?
Did you see a doctor for them?
Oh.
(CHUCKLES)
No. No.
You don't go see a doctor in Creekside
unless your leg's broke.
(MOLLY CHUCKLES)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
- Hey. Can I talk to you?
- Talk.
- Excuse us. I'll bring her right back.
- How dare you. What am I?
I'm some kind of chess piece
you can just move around?
- I was in the middle of my lunch.
- When are we getting all the discovery?
What do you want, Marty?
I want to know
when we're getting all the discovery.
- I've got motions to file.
- No, you don't.
You're looking to make a deal.
I have no authority to deal.
I haven't discussed this with my client.
What's your excuse?
(LAUGHS) Well, if I thought we needed
to make a deal,
I have all the authority I want.
Bullshit! Shaughnessy wants
the whole shot on this,
and he's using you to get it.
Anybody in your position
would deal this down
to murder with no death penalty.
My position?
We have a fucking great case.
Great case?
Lack of prior record, no eyewitness,
no confession, no motive.
Hard evidence.
I assume this conversation means
you're not going with insanity,
which is a shame.
My shrinks would have torn him apart.
By the way, your pleading the Fifth
on the charges was brilliant.
- It was good, wasn't it?
- Yeah.
I liked it.
You lose this case, you take the fall,
not Shaughnessy.
- Talk to me.
- We're going to trial, Marty.
All right, all it takes is one,
just one juror
that doesn't believe he did it.
One juror, with a kid his age,
looks into that face...
I've got to admit, that face is great.
Are you prepping him to take the stand?
(IMITATING AARON'S STUTTER)
That stutter, it's priceless.
Oh, Marty, don't tell me
you think he didn't do it.
What, has little Aaron Stampler
gotten to you?
We're not just talking about jail here.
It's about ending someone's life.
If you're wrong
and Shaughnessy's made you do this,
-you gonna be able to live with it?
- I'll live.
See you in court.
VAIL: Your Honor, we stipulate
that murder was done here.
Therefore, these photographs
have no remaining probative value.
This is not just murder.
This is a case of mutilation and torture.
(SCOFFS) The only reason
the prosecution wants to show
these gory pictures to the jury
-is shock appeal.
- That is not true, Your Honor.
- They should be excluded, absolutely.
- They clearly identify
the heinous nature of the crime,
and they connect the defendant,
who was found covered in blood,
to the crime scene.
- Prejudicial.
- JAN ET: I beg to differ.
- VAIL: Beg all you want. I don't...
- Counsel, please.
The photographs are in, Mr. Vail.
Now, would you two like a recess
so you can carry on this discussion
in private?
I'm sorry, Your Honor,
but this is too much.
Next thing you know, he'll be objecting
if we want to bring in
the murder weapon.
Well, now that she brings it up...
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
This is a public building.
Excuse me, Mr. Vail.
Would you sign this for me?
Tell me about Linda.
Mr. Vail said she was your girlfriend.
Yes. Yes, she was.
How'd you meet?
Well, we was both at the Savior House.
I was an altar boy,
and she was doing work
for Bishop Rushman.
- What was the relationship like?
- Me and Linda?
Mmm-hmm.
She's real cultural.
Real cultural and very smart.
We had a nice time together.
We might get married.
Were you sleeping together?
- Well, that's private.
- I know. I have to ask the question.
Were you having
a sexual relationship, Aaron?
Yeah, yes, yes, we were.
Were you sleeping
with anyone else at the time?
- No.
- Was she?
Has she been to see you, Aaron?
- Well, well, no, but...
- And that upsets you.
No. No. Thing is, she went away.
She went away for a while.
She left before this happened.
I don't even think...
Don't even think she knows about it.
(CAR LOCK CHIRPS)
(PHONE RINGING)
- Yo, boss.
- Hey.
- VAIL: You got something for me?
- Yeah.
There's nothing cataloged
at the downtown branch
under the numbers 832156.
But I don't think the "B" is a "."B
I think it's an eight.
I think the knife slipped. 832156.
"Thomas Jefferson"?
I don't think he did it.
All right. Well, you're not gonna be
much happier with this.
A list of the Archbishop's charities
and his foundation's investments.
Nothing startling here,
except for how many there are.
Wait a minute here. What's this?
What was he doing
with the South River deal? Pull that up.
(TAPPING KEYBOARD)
Who are the investors?
Shaughnessy?
That's Joey Pinero's neighborhood.
PINERO: See this lot here?
This all used to be houses.
In fact, there was a house
over there on the corner
where I kissed my first girlfriend.
Got her pregnant, too.
- Hell of a kiss, Joey.
- Oh, yeah.
Anyway, this whole neighborhood's
gonna end up high-rent condos
if those guys get their way.
That's why I'm gonna buy back the lot
with the settlement you got me.
- You heard about that, right?
- Yeah.
- The money?
- Who hasn't?
- Marty's the best, man.
- Just doing my job.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah. A million fucking five,
he's just doing his job.
Alderman, Joey tells me
a cop came around,
wanted him to set you up.
(LAUGHING)
It's typical.
Can't buy me,
so they try and buy a brother.
See, most people assume
that this land we're walking on
belongs to the railroad, but it doesn't.
It belongs to the church.
- VAIL: The church?
- Mmm-hmm.
- So that's the Rushman Foundation?
- That's right.
Along with a bunch of rich developers.
- Including John Shaughnessy?
- Yeah.
Then they got greedy,
started buying up all the land
and old buildings
around the church property,
then tearing it down.
Our old neighborhood
was gonna disappear.
So I went to the Archbishop and I said,
"What are you doing to these people?
They're poor.
"They're getting kicked
out of their homes,
"and they're Catholic."
Fucking A.
He listened. I couldn't believe it.
He told them to stop developing
around the church property.
So the partners are left
holding these empty buildings
they can't knock down
-and land they can't build on.
- That's right.
Shaughnessy loses millions.
Mmm-hmm.
Look, if I need you to, will you testify?
Who, me? Yeah. Easy.
Just change out of this suit,
put on a Brooks Brothers
-with loafers and tassels, you bet.
- Joey, thank you.
Thank you. Not you.
Sure.
I'll testify.
SHAUGHNESSY:
Well, you know what people think.
Think this great city runs itself.
They think it gets up, goes to work and
climbs into bed at night just like we do.
They're unaware of what it takes
to make sure the whole damn thing
doesn't break down.
Crime, fires, riots,
the goddamn water pipes
bursting under the city.
Christ, what a fucking mess that was.
And who does
the water commissioner call?
The contractor who built it? No.
He calls me. They all call me.
God damn, this is terrific.
They call me,
because I keep the peace.
That's my job.
This city doesn't burn
because I won't permit it.
I'm the great negotiator.
You think people get that?
Truth is, they don't care.
Dumb bastards don't even vote.
All they want to do is eat,
sleep, watch TV
and occasionally fuck their wives.
Guess we should all thank you.
(LAUGHS)
You're welcome.
John, you need some new material.
I've heard this "great city" speech
10 times already.
Your boy Pinero's not honoring
his side of the deal.
Is that what this dinner was about?
Pinero?
In part.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I told him what the deal is.
He's a grownup. What's the other part?
I understand your assistant's
been digging around
in the Archbishop's financial affairs.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah. Well...
How much did you lose
when he pulled the plug
from South River, John?
Let me tell you something.
It's a mistake to stick your thumb
in the eyes of the most powerful people
in the city.
It's not their eyes I'm aiming for.
Do not fuck with me, Marty.
Pipes are bursting again, John.
In the most anticipated murder trial
in recent Chicago history,
former State 's Attorney prosecutor
Martin Vail will lead
with his opening statement
on behalf of Aaron Stamp/er...
The prosecution 's case is headed
by Assistant State 's Attorney
Janet Venable. Venable was...
JANET: Richard Rushman
was a man of God.
He spent his life giving
to the people of Chicago.
He was a beacon of inspiration,
not only as a spiritual leader,
but as a citizen.
...will deliver his opening statement
tomorrow on behalf of defendant...
VAIL: My name is Martin Vail,
and the reason I'm here,
and the reason you're here,
is to make sure
that the whole truth is known.
Now, we can begin to learn the truth
by talking about What the prosecution
does not want you to hear.
JANET: Do not be fooled
by the defendant's innocent
appearance and demeanor:
Aaron Stamp/er sat in judgment
of Archbishop Rushman
and determined that
not only should he die,
but he should die
the most brutal way possible.
VAIL: Aaron was arrested Within minutes
of the Archbishop's death.
We all know that.
We all saw it on television.
But why? Because he was convenient.
Because there was enormous pressure
on the police to solve this crime.
JANET: The evidence will show
that Aaron Stamp/er stalked, ambushed
and savagely murdered this great man.
VAIL: The prosecution does not want
you to hear
about the other altar boys
in the church choir
who have mysteriously disappeared.
JANET: At the close of evidence,
ladies and gentlemen,
you will learn that Aaron Stamp/er
had everything he needed
for the perfect assassination.
Using this knife,
Aaron Stampler repeatedly stabbed
at the Archbishop's chest,
his genitals, his eyes.
They don't want you to hear
that the Archbishop made investments
on behalf of the Roman Catholic Church
and that those investments
resulted in huge losses
for some very, very powerful people.
They don't want you to hear about
the 20 death threats this year alone
that the Archbishop received
prior to his death.
And they really don't want you to hear
about their theory of motive.
And why is that? Very simple.
They don't have one.
JAN ET: Inspector Woodside,
can you explain to the court
where these sneakers came from?
They were taken off the defendant
when he was apprehended.
And what was the result of
the bloodstain analysis done on them?
The result of the analysis
proved to be human blood
matching the blood type
and DNA characteristics
of Archbishop Rushman.
JAN ET: What do the bloody footprints
surrounding the body tell you?
The killer left a pattern
of bloody footprints
around the area of the struggle,
as indicated by the spread of blood
through the room.
VAIL: All right, yes or no, Inspector?
Could there have been a third person in
the Archbishop's quarters that morning?
WOODSIDE: There is no evidence
to suggest that.
But there's no evidence
to prove there wasn't.
No.
And after the struggle,
what happened then?
Well, analysis suggests that the killer
was startled during the mutilation
and ran from the bedroom
down the stairs.
Is it possible, Inspector,
that the real killer, a third person,
who maybe was smart enough
not to tramp a whole freeway of blood
through the whole place here,
couldn't this third person have placed
the defendant's prints
on the knife while he was passed out?
Mr. Vail, anything is possible.
JANET: So, clearly, the victim suffered
a great number of stab wounds?
WEIL: Yes, he did, 78.
He tried to defend himself.
And that explains the cuts
on the hands and the forearms.
Doctor, isn't it a fact
that you can't be sure
whether more than one person inflicted
these 78 stab and incise wounds?
That's true, Counselor. It could've been
more than one person, but I doubt it.
From your analysis
of the knife wounds, Dr. Weil,
do you have an opinion whether the
killer was left-handed or right-handed?
Well, the incise wound to the throat
and most of the chest wounds
were made from an angle that strongly
suggests that a left-handed person
was using the knife.
To your knowledge,
is the defendant left-handed?
Yes, he is.
Well, then it's possible
that a right-handed person
could've deliberately used his left hand
to inflict some of these wounds.
Yes, I suppose that is possible.
Then it would be reasonable to assume
that there was, in fact,
a third person there at the crime scene?
Reasonable, no. But it is possible.
Then following opening statements,
it was a day of strong
and detailed testimony
from the prosecution 's first witnesses,
Cook County Forensics Chief
Harvey Woodside
and Cook County Medical Examiner
Emile Weil.
It was also a day of
tough cross-examination
of Woodside and Wei!
By Stamp/er defense attorney
Martin Vail.
By most accounts, though,
the prosecution...
JAN ET: Captain Stenner,
I would like to thank you
for all the time you've given us today,
but, finally,
I would like to turn your attention
to the symbol carved
into the Archbishop's chest.
Now would you please tell the jury
about that, Captain?
Yes. The letter
and the numbers 832.156
were carved into
the Archbishop's chest.
What you just described,
have you been able
to find an identical reference anywhere?
I believe so, yes.
The symbol B32.156
is actually catalog code for a book
discovered in a private reading room
located in the church basement.
That particular number, the B32 part,
refers to a book,
The Scarlet Letter
by Nathaniel Hawthorne.
When we opened the book to Page 156,
we discovered an underlined passage.
Would you please read
this underlined passage to the court?
"No man, for any considerable period,
"can wear one face to himself
and another to the multitude
"without finally getting bewildered
as to which may be the true."
Thank you.
What does that passage
mean to you, Captain?
Objection. He's a policeman,
not an English professor.
His interpretation would be speculative
and irrelevant.
I didn't hear her ask
for an expert opinion.
The witness can answer.
Well, to me, it's simple.
The killer thought
that his victim was two-faced,
dishonest in some way.
In your experience, Captain,
do killers ever intentionally
leave clues to their motive?
STENNER: Not often, but it happens.
Thanks.
- Thanks, man.
- Yeah, sure.
Did you underline that book?
- Did I what?
- Did you underline that book?
- No. No, Mr. Vail.
- No?
(STAMMERING) No. Mr. Vail.
I never even opened The Scarlet Letter.
I don't like Hawthorne.
I tried to read that one about the house
with the seven somethings
in high school.
I couldn't even get past Page 10.
I mean, I weren't the only one using
Bishop Rushman's library.
You know what? Everybody borrowed
books from Bishop Rushman.
He encouraged it.
His altar boys and staff,
everyone was in there.
Guard?
Thanks.
(DOOR CLANGS SHUT)
You don't give up, do you?
(CHUCKLES)
(THUDDING)
So you didn't know anything about that?
VAIL: No.
CONNERMAN:
What about the impact of...
VAIL: Look, I can't talk to you right now.
My office will call you, all right?
- Yeah. Thanks.
- Okay, bye. Yeah, I'll see you.
- Bye.
What the fuck happened in there?
I guess that eight was a "B" after all.
(CHUCKLING)
You think this is funny?
We're losing this case.
What the hell happened, Tommy?
How could you have missed that?
Marty, there are 50 of them,
plus the entire
Chicago Police Department.
How was I to know he had a private
reading room in the church basement?
- It's your job to know.
- Fuck, Marty, you want my job?
No. I want you to do your fucking job!
Marty, come on.
I'm working
on a third-man defense here.
Do you know that?
Have you figured that out yet?
I don't have a third man.
You know why I don't have a third man?
'Cause you can't fucking find him!
That's why.
Is it that hard to find one indigent kid?
Look, maybe we already got
the kid who did this.
We have to at least consider
the possibility that he did it.
All the hard evidence
is pointing towards him,
and you keep refusing to even look at it.
I'm not refusing to look at anything!
I don't think he did it!
Look, you two,
we're up there in a couple of days,
and we got dick!
So I wish the two of you'd do
your fucking goddamn jobs, all right?
Fuck!
(SIGHS)
It must have been hard for you
to come here to Chicago.
You didn't know anybody.
No. Nobody.
Didn't have any money?
(AARON CHUCKLES)
No, nothing.
I want to talk more about your girlfriend,
Linda, now. Can we, Aaron?
- No.
- Why not?
(CAMERA BEEPING)
Aaron.
(STAMMERING) I'm sorry.
Do you think we can do this later?
- No, I want to stay with this for a minute.
- I'm just feeling a little tired.
I know. Why does talking
about Linda Forbes upset you?
(STAMMERING)
(CAMERA BEEPS)
It doesn't.
I just don't want to talk
about it right now.
- Why not? Are you all right?
- No, my head hurts.
(RAPID BEEPING)
Okay, okay, I'm sorry.
Let me just fix this.
Hey, you know what I can do
with this thing?
(MALEVOLENTLY)
No, how the fuck should I know?
Jesus Christ.
Aaron?
What?
(STAMMERING) What were you saying?
(TRAIN RUMBLING PAST)
(INDISTINCT)
Come on.
(CAR LOCK CHIRPS)
(HORNS HONKING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GRUNTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(GROANING)
(TRAIN RUMBLING PAST)
(GRUNTING)
Stop him!
Who the fuck are you?
What do you want?
What do you want, God damn it?
I'll kill you!
I don't think so, Alex. Drop it.
Drop it.
- Remember me? Huh?
- My name is Martin Vail.
I don't give a fuck what your name is.
- You got no right doing this to me.
- I have every fucking right!
I'm Aaron Stampler's attorney,
you little shit!
Now, what do you know
about the Archbishop's murder?
Nothing.
Where the fuck do you think
you're going?
Bullshit! Don't fuck With us.
I swear I know nothing.
Well, then,
what were you doing over there?
What were you doing at Aaron's house?
What were you looking for?
- A tape.
- A tape? Videotape?
- Yeah.
- Of what?
Sex stuff.
VAIL: Sex stuff?
What, I have to draw a picture for you?
Who?
Me, Linda.
And Aaron?
Yeah. He shot it, too,
for the Archbishop.
Are you telling...
Are you telling me that Archbishop
Rushman is involved with sex stuff?
Yeah, he called it "purging the devil."
He'd say a sermon for 10 minutes,
and then he'd tell us what to do.
- You're full of shit.
- I don't give a fuck what you believe!
Hey, hey, hey. What? What?
What were you going to do
with the tape?
- What were you going to do?
- Trash it.
I was gonna throw it away.
Just one. One tape. Just one tape.
Yeah. Yeah. One. He'd use the same
one. He'd keep recording over and over.
VAIL: So what made you think
Aaron had this?
(STAMMERING) I don't know.
I thought maybe he got it,
and he went back and killed him.
- I mean, he did kill him, right?
- No, he didn't.
So Where's this girl? Where's Linda?
I don't know.
She freaked out!
She panicked. She split.
I don't know.
I'm not expecting any postcards.
Look at me. Look at me.
Get him the fuck out of here, Tommy.
(STAMMERING)
- Where to?
- A warm bunk and three meals a day.
- You can't arrest me! You're not a cop!
- I used to be. Does that work for you?
- Look who's here.
- Don't get up. Finish it.
- It's a good article.
- You know the rules.
Don't disturb anything.
Don't remove anything.
If you do, it's my ass.
Yeah, mine, too. I won't touch anything.
(RUSHMAN TALKING ON TAPE)
(TAPE FAST-FORWARDING)
Excuse me.
Preach the gospel to every...
Hello.
- What are you guys watching?
- Wait a minute.
RUSHMAN: Go to her. Good.
Now help her. That's it, Aaron. Good.
Linda, help out.
Good. Take off her blouse, Aaron.
That's it. Now help him, Linda.
Isn't that sweet, Linda? Good. That's it.
Now, take him in your mouth.
- Here's motive.
- Aaron,
take her from behind.
- Aaron, take her from behind.
- Jesus Christ.
Thanks.
MAN ON PA: 487113 report to...
- I need to talk to him alone.
- I think there's something
-we should discuss.
- I need to be alone with my client.
Do you trust me?
Do...
(STAMMERING)
Yes, yes, of course I do.
Good. Because I don't trust you.
I'll lay it all out for you.
I'm losing this case.
You know why I'm losing this case?
'Cause my fucking client
is fucking lying to me.
-(STAMMERING) I never lied to you.
- Bullshit!
(CLATTERING)
That's it. No more bullshit.
No more games.
Everybody thinks
you did this, everybody.
I'm the only one who believes you,
and I am that close.
So I want it all out. All of it.
Right now, right here.
Did you underline that book?
Hey, hey. Hey, look at me.
- No, I didn't.
- I don't believe you.
- That is bullshit.
- I told...
I don't fucking believe you!
I saw the tape!
I saw the tape. I know what he did
to you. I want to hear it from you.
No! No! No!
Tell me the whole thing.
Don't fucking do this.
I want you to tell me the truth,
and do not even think of lying.
You fucking killed him, didn't you?
You did it!
- You killed him. You're so full of shit!
- No!
You did it, didn't you?
Tell me the truth. Don't lie to me.
You little fuck! You did it.
You killed him! You son of a bitch!
- You fucking killed him!
- No!
What the hell do you want
from me now?
Quit your crying! I can't understand
a goddamn word you're saying.
You little sissy! You make me sick!
- Looky here. Who the fuck are you?
- Who the fuck are you?
This is my cell, Jack!
Who the fuck are you?
I got you now. You're the lawyer.
- You his lawyer, ain't you?
- Yeah.
Yeah, with your fancy suit.
I heard about you.
Well, my, my, you sure
fucked this one up, Counselor.
It sounds to me like they're gonna
shoot old Aaron so full of poison
it's gonna come out his eyes!
- Where is Aaron?
- Aaron's crying off
in some corner somewhere.
You scared him off!
You've got to deal with me now, boy.
I ought to give you a beating
on principle. Look at me.
You ever come in here and pull any
of that tough-guy shit on Aaron again,
I will kick your fucking ass to Sunday!
- Do you understand me?
- I understand you. I understand.
Aaron gets in trouble, he calls you.
You're the man.
Well, Aaron couldn't kick his own ass.
I mean, you seen him, with the...
(IMITATES STUTTERING)
Yeah.
Jesus Christ, he can't handle anything.
He sure as shit couldn't handle
all that preacher's blood, could he?
If he'd done like I told him,
we wouldn't be in this mess,
but he got scared, and...
Ran off, got hisself caught,
the stupid little shit.
So Aaron did kill Rushman.
Hell, no!
Jesus Christ, where did they find you?
Ain't you been listening to me?
Aaron don't have the guts to do nothing.
It was me, boy.
- It was me.
- It was you.
- It was you. It was you.
- Yes, it was.
He come crying to me like always,
stuttering and whining.
(IMITATES STUTTERING) "I can't take it
no more, Roy. You got to help me.
"Please, please, Roy."
I said, "Shut your mouth, you little girl!
"Grow up. Be a man.
Take care of yourself."
- Be a man, yeah.
- Know what I'm saying?
(SIGHS)
So your name is Roy?
Oh, Jesus, I'm sorry. Yeah.
What is it? Marty?
- Yeah.
- Hey, listen, Marty.
I'm dying for a smoke.
Do you have a cigarette on you?
- No, I quit.
-(CHUCKLES) Fuck that.
I can't live without them. There's got
to be a butt around here somewhere.
Roy.
Roy, tell me about Linda.
- Linda?
- Linda, yeah.
Well, who the fuck cares about Linda?
Well, I care about Linda.
I'd like to know about Linda.
(SCOFFS) That little tramp.
Let me tell you something.
Everybody had a piece of her,
you know what I'm saying?
I mean, she had Aaron
wrapped up so tight,
he actually thought
she was his girlfriend.
It was pathetic. She broke his heart.
So that's why you had to kill Rushman,
because of the sex stuff.
You've seen the tape.
Answer me, you son of a bitch!
Do you think I'm playing with you?
I will break your fucking neck!
I'm going to ask you again.
Have you seen that tape?
I saw the tape.
Yeah, of course I saw the tape.
God damn it, God damn it.
I told him to get that tape.
I said, "Get the fucking tape.
It's motive, you asshole!"
This is going
to fuck everything up, Marty.
Don't you show that
to a goddamn person!
- Do you understand me?
- Yes. Yes.
- Yes. Shit.
- Aaron.
- Damn!
(STUTTERS)
Mr. Vail?
Yeah, I'm right here, Aaron.
(SIGHS)
He did it. The little fuck did it.
How could I have missed that?
- Do I need stitches?
- No.
He didn't do it. Aaron has no idea
what just happened in there.
I kept seeing all the signs, the big ones.
The abusive background,
these repeated blackouts,
the ellipses in thought.
He's ambidextrous.
That's what I was trying to tell you
when you came in tonight.
Look, you may be thrilled by all this,
but I'm fucked. I don't have a case.
It's textbook
multiple personality disorder.
Put me on the stand. I'll testify.
He's insane.
I can't. I can't change plea
in the middle of a trial.
The judge would never allow it.
Besides, insanity is
the hardest thing to prove.
Okay.
My professional opinion?
This is not a criminal
we're dealing with. It's a sick kid.
He's sitting in a cell,
and it's not where he belongs.
You got an aspirin?
(DOOR BUZZING)
(SIGHS)
Come on, Connerman, ask it.
Ask what?
The question
you wanted to ask me before.
I don't understand, Mr. Vail.
"How can you defend someone
if you know they did it?
"How can you do that?
"How can you fucking defend
these fucking scumbags?"
Isn't that what you wanted to ask me?
It is, isn't it?
All those fucking coy questions,
all that bullshit.
Bottom line is,
"How can you do what you do?"
(SIGHS)
You think it's the money, don't you?
The money's nice.
The money's very, very nice, Jack.
You know,
the first thing I ask a new client is,
"You been saving up for a rainy day?
"Guess what? It's raining."
You think it's because I want to see
my face on the cover of magazines?
My 15 seconds on TV? I love it.
I fucking love that shit. I really do,
but guess what.
It's not it.
- You go to Las Vegas?
- Yeah.
I don't go to Vegas.
Why do you think I don't go to Vegas?
Marty, it's late. I think that
we should both just get up and go...
Why gamble with money when you can
gamble with people's lives?
That was a joke.
All right, I'll tell you.
I believe in the notion that people
are innocent until proven guilty.
I believe in that notion
because I choose to believe
in the basic goodness of people.
I choose to believe that not all crimes
are committed by bad people,
and I try to understand
that some very, very good people
do some very bad things.
You know,
when I was working for Shaughnessy,
I did something very, very bad. Maybe
illegal. I was a prosecutor then.
This thing that I did, I was very upset
by it, and I decided to leave.
So I left. I became a defending attorney.
The irony being that everyone
assumes I'm fucking lying anyhow.
So I made myself this little promise that
(SIGHS)
I would reserve my lies
for other than my public life.
You print any of this,
I'll sue your fucking ass.
All right, all right,
so I made a little mistake.
NAOMI: No shit.
What do you want? Want a new suit?
I'll buy you a new suit.
You made a mistake?
You told us the third man did it.
So now you got your third man
and a fourth man and a fifth man...
What are you going to do, Marty?
I don't know. I really fucked up here.
You were right.
So how are you gonna get him off?
(CHUCKLES) I don't know.
What I know is, Aaron did not commit
first-degree murder.
- Marty, he stabbed him a billion times...
- No, not Aaron.
To convict someone of a capital crime,
the State must prove intent.
Roy had intent, Aaron didn't.
Yeah, but the only way to prove that
is to change the plea to insanity,
which we can't do mid-trial, unless
you're planning on a career change.
I could've been mistaken,
but I wasn't wrong.
Aaron is innocent. It's Roy who is guilty.
This kid doesn't need a lawyer.
He needs an exorcist.
Tom, you are so full of shit. You were
not there, and you didn't see it.
He's one sick motherfucking boy, man,
who's been fucked around his whole life
by his father, by his priest.
This kid does not deserve to die,
and it's our job to make sure that a jury
believes he doesn't deserve to die.
- Okay.
- Okay. How do we do it?
By somehow introducing
this whole abuse thing.
- The tape.
- TOMMY: What about the tape?
That's crazy. That gives him motive.
No, it looks like that, but it's...
No, actually, what it does is,
it turns this whole thing around.
It gives concrete documentation
of what Rushman did to this kid.
But we can't put it in. You know that.
But we're not going to.
Oh, fuck!
(GROANS)
- Okay. Okay.
-(CHUCKLING) Good.
(WOMAN TALKING ON TV)
(DOORBELL BUZZES)
(PHONE RINGING)
- Yeah.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Who is this?
- You know damn well who it is.
- Barleycorn's, Marty. Now.
- Janet?
Cute porno. Part of your collection?
VAIL: Hey.
Where did you get it? You steal it
-from the crime scene?
- I don't know anything about this tape.
- You are such a liar.
- Think about it.
- I have.
- Look, if this tape really has on it
what you say it does,
last thing I'd do is give it to you.
It gives you motive.
- You had to give it to me.
- Why?
You couldn't introduce it in court.
The jury would despise you for it,
for dishonoring the Bishop's memory.
But if you get me to show it, motive or
no motive, I'm the one who looks bad,
and you gain sympathy
for your poor little abused boy.
- You think so?
- I hate you.
Don't use it.
I have no intention of using it.
- The usual, Stu.
- STU: You got it.
You're up to even more than that,
aren't you?
I'm not up to anything.
You're opening a door, you think
I'm going to walk through it?
There's going to be a tiger
on the other end, and I don't...
You know who'd be really upset
if you used it?
- I just told you...
- Shaughnessy.
- Fuck him.
- Fuck him?
Fuck you.
Thanks a lot.
All right, if this is not your motive,
what is?
I have motive.
Yeah, what is it?
(SARCASTICALLY)
I'm really gonna tell you.
Well, you better tell the jury pretty soon.
Time's running out.
WAITRESS: Here you go.
You think you've got me.
You think because you know me as
well as you do, you know how I think.
Well, I know how you think.
You know what I'm thinking?
What happened to your face?
I bumped it into a medicine cabinet.
(SNICKERS)
No, Marty,
that was a girl on her way out.
Maybe we should come back here later.
Later? Well, they close in 10 minutes.
No, after.
After the trial.
When we've got nothing to lose.
How can your timing
be so good in a courtroom
and so bad in real life?
I'll think about it later.
I hate you too much right now.
You got a visitor.
YANCY: Here she comes.
- Talk to you later.
- SHAUGHNESSY: Okay.
Janet
Morning.
(DOOR CLOSES)
So where's the tape?
There's some pretty ugly stuff
on that tape.
- Yes, there is.
- Who would've thought?
- Where did it come from?
- Landed on my front door last night.
- No note.
- Vail?
- Who else?
- Clever prick.
What do you think he's up to?
- I honestly don't know.
- Cut the crap, Janet.
You know him pretty goddamn well.
You were balling him, for Christ's sake.
- Where is it?
- At home.
I have some advice for you.
My advice for you, if you really have
aspirations beyond this particular office,
is to pick up that little handbag of yours,
go home right now and destroy this tape
you should've destroyed, like I did,
the minute you received it.
You don't think Vail has a copy?
You don't think there's an original?
It's Stampler that's on trial,
not the Catholic Church,
and if you haven't found another motive
to hang him on, then God help you.
(DOOR CLOSES)
BAILIFF: All rise.
Please, sit down.
Madam Prosecutor.
Miss Venable.
The State calls Thomas Goodman.
Objection, Your Honor.
Prosecution knows full well
that Mr. Goodman is my investigator
in this case,
and under the Work Product Rule,
he can't be compelled to testify.
Permission to approach the bench,
Your Honor?
Granted.
Important evidence has just
come into my possession
which I believe
this witness can authenticate.
That's Mr. Vail's privilege. If Mr. Vail
doesn't want Mr. Goodman to testify,
Mr. Goodman doesn't testify.
Make a decision, Mr. Vail.
Mr. Goodman, have you ever been
to my apartment?
- TOMMY: No.
- By that I mean my apartment building.
Allegedly.
JAN ET: I'm sorry, you're confused.
Either you have or you haven't.
"Allegedly" doesn't figure into it.
I have been there, yes.
- Why did you go there?
- I was delivering something.
For whom?
Martin Vail.
Mr. Vail sent you
to deliver something to me.
- Yes.
- What was it?
A videotape.
Could this have been the tape
you delivered for Mr. Vail?
I have a feeling it is, yes.
The People place
this half-inch videocassette tape
-in evidence, Your Honor.
- So ordered. Bailiff, please index.
JANET: Now, where did Mr. Vail get
this tape, if it is indeed the same one?
TOMMY: He took it from the closet
of Archbishop Rushman.
JANET: He stole it.
TOMMY: No, no, he borrowed it.
Once I made the transfer for him,
I returned it, so...
JANET: Mmm-hmm.
Can you describe for me
what's on this tape?
There was a sermon
by Archbishop Rushman on it,
a rehearsal of a sermon, I should say,
followed by
-a kind of home movie.
- A home movie? Of what?
- Some altar boys.
- And?
- A girl.
- Doing what?
An altar-boy lesson of some kind?
Having sex.
(PEOPLE GASPING)
Quiet.
A porno movie.
-(HESITANTLY) Yes.
- Yes. Now.
How is it, do you think,
that this tape, this porno tape,
was in the Archbishop's closet
in order for Mr. Vail to find it there?
- He was the... The director.
- Who was?
Archbishop Rushman.
(PEOPLE EXCLAIM)
JUDGE: Quiet in the court!
(INAUDIBLE)
JAN ET: And was the defendant
one of the altar boys
performing in the Archbishop's
home movie?
- Yes, he was.
- Was his girlfriend?
I believe her name is Linda Forbes.
Yes, she was.
And did it appear to you
that the defendant was enjoying
performing in this film
with his girlfriend?
No, he does not.
I will not ask you, Mr. Goodman,
if you think we have just
uncovered motive here.
We will decide that for ourselves
once we've all seen the videotape.
No further questions.
JUDGE: Does Defense wish to cross?
- No, Your Honor.
- Court's in recess.
Bailiff, please set up for the tape.
Mr. Goodman, you're excused.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Thanks for the advice.
MOLLY ON TAPE: Mr. Vail said
she was your girlfriend.
AARON ON TAPE: (STUTTERING)
Yes. Yes, she was.
- MOLLY: How'd you meet?
- We was both at the Savior House.
I was an altar boy,
and she was working
for Bishop Rushman.
MOLLY: Doing what?
(FAST-FORWARDING)
Were you sleeping
with anyone else at the time?
- No.
- Was she?
No.
(PHONE RINGING)
Has she been to see you, Aaron?
- Yeah? No, I'm still here.
- AARON: No.
- What?
- MOLL Y: Does that upset you?
(SIGHS)
(HELICOPTER HOVERING)
Okay.
Mr. Vail, are you prepared to proceed
with your first witness?
Yes, Your Honor.
The Defense calls John Shaughnessy.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
The People object, Your Honor.
Mr. Shaughnessy has never been
identified as a possible witness.
- Your Honor, may I approach?
- JUDGE: Yes, you may.
Thank you.
My client is on trial for his life, here.
He's always maintained that there was
-someone else in that bedroom.
- And you think Mr. Shaughnessy
can somehow confirm that?
Your Honor,
the Constitution of the United States
takes precedence here,
permitting the calling of any witness
to promulgate evidence of innocence.
That's clearly stated
in the Sixth Amendment.
It's also profound in Brady vs. Maryland.
VAIL: Mr. Shaughnessy,
do you serve on the board
of an organization known
as the Rushman Foundation?
I have the privilege to be
an honorary board member.
Could you briefly explain the nature
and purpose of this foundation?
The Rushman Foundation was founded
by the late archbishop.
Its purpose is to invest in projects
for the greater good of the community.
The greater good
of the community, okay.
Now, would that be true
in the case of the now bankrupt
- South River Housing Development?
- Yes.
Could you tell the court why the
South River project was abandoned?
There was a difference of opinion
as to the costs.
Wasn't there also
a difference of opinion
between the investors
and the late archbishop himself?
- I don't recall.
- Well...
What kind of money
are we talking about here? I mean...
How much money, Mr. Shaughnessy,
was invested in this failed
South River enterprise?
$60 million.
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
JUDGE: Quiet.
$60 million!
Wow, that's a lot of money.
You and the Archbishop
have been friends for, what, 20 years?
I think it's safe to say the two of you
knew each other really well.
SHAUGHNESSY: That's right.
Were you surprised at the content
of that tape
-that Miss Venable submitted?
- Yes, of course I was.
So you've never heard any allegations,
charges against the Archbishop
during that time?
Not that I recall, no.
No, especially since you were the
State's Attorney for the last 15 years,
it'd be fair to say that you've supervised
all the prosecutions
in Cook County during that time,
especially the prosecutions
of all the prominent figures.
I also have a staff of 1,000
of the best prosecutors...
Yeah, yeah, but as State's Attorney,
it was up to you, ultimately, to decide
who would be indicted
and who wouldn't.
- Yes.
- Yeah. Okay.
Let me just take you back now.
Let's go back to June, 1985.
Do you recall any allegations
of sexual misconduct
-against the Archbishop at that time?
- I don't recall that, no.
No? Do you recall a young man
by the name of Michael O'Donnell
who came to the felony review unit
at your office?
I have no idea what you're talking about,
- Counselor.
- You don't?
This is so confusing to me,
because I have this document here
from the Chicago Metropolitan
Police Department,
and it says that, yes, Michael O'Donnell
spoke to the supervisor of that unit
over a period of two weeks,
explaining to him, in graphic detail,
sexual abuse he suffered
at the hands of Archbishop Rushman.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
JUDGE: Quiet.
Isn't it also true, Mr. State's Attorney,
that you then decided that your friend,
Archbishop Rushman,
was not going to stand trial for any of it?
He owed you big time, John.
You must have been really pissed off
when he pulled out of South River.
What happened? What was it?
He just finally said,
"I can't take it anymore"? He said, "No!"
- JUDGE: Mr. Vail.
- So you and your investors...
-...had 60 million reasons to kill him!
- You little cocksucker!
- JUDGE: That's it. Witness dismissed.
(GAVEL BANGS)
This court's in recess.
Vail, in my chambers now.
That's for Joey Pinero,
you little shithead.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Start looking for a job.
If you think you can use my courtroom
to wage personal vendettas
and settle old scores,
you are sorely mistaken.
I'm striking Shaughnessy's testimony
from the record as irrelevant,
and I'm holding you in contempt
to the tune of $10,000.
So what you're telling me is, I can't get
a fair trial in your courtroom, is that it?
Be very, very careful, Mr. Vail.
You're on dangerous ground here.
Fine, fine. You want me to make
that check out to you, Judge?
Do you want me
to take you off this case?
You're making a mockery of my
courtroom, and I'm not going to allow it.
I suggest you start representing your
client and stop representing yourself.
(FAST-FORWARDING)
AARON ON TAPE: ...do this later?
MOLLY ON TAPE:
No, I want to stay with this for a minute.
(STAMMERING) I'm feeling
my, very tired.
MOLLY: Yeah, I know.
Why does talking
about Linda Forbes upset you?
(AARON STAMMERING)
It doesn't. I just...
- Okay, okay.
- I'm sorry. I 'm sorry.
MOLLY: Hey, you know
What I can do with this thing?
How the fuck should I know?
VAIL: Dr. Arrington, how much time
have you spent with Aaron Stampler?
Around 60 hours.
And what did you find
in the course of your evaluation?
I found that Mr. Stampler suffers from
an acute disassociative condition,
specifically,
multiple personality disorder.
Objection, Your Honor.
Now, Dr. Arrington is only stating what
she herself has personally observed.
- Your Honor.
- Counselors.
- Now, I know what you're doing.
- Will you excuse us for a minute?
JANET: Your Honor, if he wants
to question his client's sanity...
Your Honor, I'm trying to establish
a medical basis for amnesia here.
That is not what he's doing.
He's saying he's crazy.
- Are you?
- No, I am not.
I'll allow you to proceed with
this witness if you're very, very careful.
Absolutely. Yes.
Write down that he said that.
VAIL: All right, where were we?
Now, could Aaron Stampler
have been present during the murder
of Archbishop Rushman
-and not remember it?
- Yes, he could.
Okay. Could you explain that, please?
Mr. Stampler's state at the time
of the offense was such that
his body could be present at a homicide
and yet his mind
would be unable to recall it.
- VAIL: And how is that possible?
- The neurological mechanism
that would make this possible
began with the early abuse
suffered at the hands of his father.
In defense, Aaron's psyche splintered
and helped him to create
two separate personalities.
- Your Honor.
- I didn't say it.
- I did not say it...
- JUDGE: You've been warned twice now.
Do you really wanna pursue
this line of questioning?
And I suggest you think long and hard
before answering.
Your Honor, just one last question.
All right, Dr. Arrington,
in your opinion,
is Aaron Stampler capable of murder?
No, he is not. He is far too traumatized
to express normal anger and frustration.
He keeps his emotions repressed,
which is why he created Roy,
who is capable of such a crime.
- Objection, Your Honor.
- JUDGE: That's enough, Mr. Vail.
The jury will disregard this witness'
last statement, as will the court.
- Thank you very much.
- Madam Prosecutor,
-do you wish to cross?
- You bet I do.
Since you brought it up,
against the instructions of the court,
(INAUDIBLE)
I'm curious to know,
is multiple personality disorder
your primary area of expertise?
It's not my primary field, no.
Is forensic psychiatry
your primary area of expertise?
- No, I'm a neuropsychologist.
- I see.
So you have no forensic experience,
and you're more of, let's say,
an academic?
Then you will forgive
this rather academic question.
I'm driving in my car,
somebody cuts me off.
I think to myself,
"I could just kill that guy,"
but I don't, now do I?
- I would hope not.
- That's right.
Things happen to us. People wrong us,
but we don't all go around
inventing psychopaths
to do our dirty work for us,
now, do we, Doctor?
I'm not suggesting you suffer from
multiple personality, Miss Venable.
- I'm saying Mr. Stampler does.
- Yes, I know. We heard.
You have also testified
that you have met this...
What was his name again?
- MOLLY: Roy.
- Roy what?
- He didn't give a last name.
- I see.
Did this Roy tell you
that he had murdered the Archbishop?
Mr. Vail was alone with him at the time.
I was watching through the window,
but soon after that I was in the room
and saw both Roy
and his transformation back to Aaron.
Did you happen to tape
this appearance of Aaron...
(LAUGHING)
(STAMMERING) I'm sorry. I am sorry.
I just cannot get used to this name.
- Roy.
- Did you?
- No, the tape was off.
- Off?
So you have no record whatsoever
of his appearance.
- No.
Does Aaron Stampler know
the difference between right and wrong?
Yes, he does.
If Aaron Stampler butchered
the Archbishop, would he know...
VAIL: Objection, Your Honor.
If Aaron Stampler
murdered the Archbishop,
-would he know he'd broken the law?
- Yes, he would, but it wasn't Aaron...
Yes, I know, Doctor. It was Roy.
That's all.
No further questions, Your Honor.
JUDGE: Witness may step down.
Miss Venable, if you would like to
re-open the Prosecution's case
and call the State's psychiatrist,
- I will certainly agree to it.
- No, I...
I don't think that's necessary,
Your Honor.
I think we all get the picture here.
JUDGE: Mr. Vail,
are you ready to proceed?
Would you like a recess?
(CAR LOCK CHIRPS)
Roy?
Aaron.
Could you tell us a little about
your relationship
with Archbishop Rushman?
(STAMMERING) Well, he was like
a father to me. I loved him very much.
Why did you love him?
- Why?
- Uh-huh.
(STAMMERING) Well, he saved my life.
He was the only person who ever
treated me like I was worth anything.
(WHISPERS) Stop your whining,
you little girl. Be a man.
Now, we've all seen that tape
that you were in, Aaron.
How did that make you feel?
Did it change your feelings
about Archbishop Rushman?
No. Uh-uh.
He was a wonderful man.
So you didn't feel anger towards him
about being forced to perform
in that tape?
No, he did everything for me.
There wasn't nothing else
I could do for him, and he needed it.
Do you know someone named Roy?
No, I don't.
You heard Dr. Arrington's
testimony about
what she and I saw there at the jail.
Aaron, some pretty strange things
going on there. Do you remember?
I heard what she said,
but I don't remember any of that.
- No recollection?
- No, sir.
Did you kill Archbishop Rushman?
No, sir, I did not.
Thank you.
Your witness.
JANET: Mr. Stampler,
would you like some water?
-(STAMMERING) No, ma'am.
- You sure?
Yes, ma'am. Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Stampler, did you believe
that the Archbishop wore masks?
(STAMMERING) I'm sorry,
what did you say?
Do you think he acted one way
in public and another way in private?
No, I didn't think that.
Isn't that why you underlined
the Hawthorne passage?
Mr. Stampler?
No, I did not underline that book.
- You didn't underline it?
- No, ma'am.
And you didn't carve the numbers
referring to that passage into his chest?
No, no, ma'am, I did not. I told you I...
You loved him.
You loved him like a father.
Even though he made you
and your girlfriend
perform demeaning sexual acts
for his own gratification.
(STAMMERING)
No, you don't understand. He...
There was no other way for him
to cast out his own demons.
- He needed it.
- He needed to get off, Aaron.
That's what he was doing.
That's what he needed you for,
to perform like a circus animal.
- That was your function in his life.
-(STUTTERS) No.
Mr. Stampler, I'm gonna ask you
straight, because I am tired,
and I've had just about
all I can take of this sordidness,
and I wanna go home,
and I wanna wash my hands,
and I wanna forget all about you
and Archbishop Rushman.
Did the Archbishop force you
and your girlfriend and others
to perform sexual acts
while he watched? Yes or no?
- Yes, he did, but...
- Yes. Yes, he forced you.
He forced you using a threat
of expulsion from Savior House
and a life on the street with no heat
and no water and no food.
He put you in front of a camera!
He made you take off your clothes!
And you don't think that
that's another side?
Another face of a man
that we all thought...
- No! No.
- Do you know what I would do
if someone did that to me?
I would kill him. I wouldn't hesitate.
- No.
- I would stab him
78 times with a butcher knife!
I would chop off his fingers!
I would slash his throat open!
I would carve numbers into his chest!
I would gouge out his eyes!
I swear to God.
But that's me.
No further questions, Your Honor.
Where the hell do you think
you're going?
- Excuse me?
- Hey, you look at me
when I'm talking to you, bitch!
(GAVEL BANGS)
JUDGE: Mr. Stampler.
- Fuck you, lady! Come here!
- That's it.
(GAVEL BANGING)
Order! Bailiff! Order!
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
Come here! You wanna play rough?
Let's play rough. Come on. Back off!
- VAIL: Roy! Take it easy.
- Keep coming, asshole.
You'll see if I don't break
her fucking neck.
(JAN ET SCREAMING)
- Roy, come here. I gotta talk to you.
- Fuck you, Marty!
- I'm walking out of here. Now, slow...
- It's me.
(ALL CLAMORING)
(JAN ET GRUNTING)
No! No! Don't you...
(PANTING)
No!
(JAN ET PANTING)
- You okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm okay.
Don't even think of lighting
that cigarette, Miss Venable.
- How's your neck?
- I'll live.
I could call a doctor.
Uh-uh.
Mr. Shaughnessy just called
to inform me there will be no mistrial,
-as if that was his right.
- I can't believe
that scumbag has the balls to call here.
No, thanks.
What matters to me is
what you have to say.
Obviously,
your case has been damaged.
In fairness to the Prosecution,
I would declare a mistrial,
regardless of what
Monsieurs Shaughnessy and Vail think,
if that's what you want.
The Prosecution doesn't wanna try
this case again, even if it could,
which it can't, at least not by me.
And I think I can guarantee you
there's no one
in the DA's office who will,
so it's up to you.
I'm going to dismiss the jury
in favor of a bench trial
and a blind plea of not guilty
by reason of insanity.
- Yes?
- Yeah.
The defendant will be
remanded to Elgin
for an evaluation period of 30 days.
Let them decide
the term of his commitment.
Do either of you have
a problem with that?
JAN ET: Your Honor,
he'll be out in a month.
Take it up with the Legislature,
Miss Venable.
I'm going home.
- Your Honor.
- No, Mr. Vail,
I am not refunding your contempt fine,
and the next time you wanna get
a client off on insanity,
you plead that way,
or I'll have you disbarred.
You okay?
(CHUCKLES SARCASTICALLY)
Am I okay? Do I seem okay?
I get attacked by this sick twist,
I've lost the case, I'm out of a job.
No, Marty. I'm not particularly okay,
but, hey, you won,
justice was done.
Who the hell cares, right?
Congratulations.
You knew, didn't you?
You knew if I went after him,
he'd wig out up there.
Well, I knew he'd come out
if he was threatened.
And who better to do that than me?
You used me.
Yeah, I did. I had no choice.
What did I use, by the way,
that was so terrible?
I knew you'd do your job.
I knew you'd stand up to Shaughnessy.
I knew you'd try to win the case.
Now, what's wrong with that?
I lost my fucking job!
And that's good.
You should've left him years ago.
Christ, Marty, why is it you always think
you know what's right for me?
Because I'm arrogant.
I'm very,
very arrogant.
- You wanna dance?
- No.
- Sure?
- Yeah.
All you have to do is turn around.
(CHUCKLES)
No.
(HUMMING)
(SNIFFLES)
I have to see my client.
- I'd like a minute alone with him.
- Are you sure?
Yeah. I'm sure.
(DOOR LOCKS)
You okay?
(STUTTERS) My head hurts.
You don't remember
what just happened?
- No?
- I lost time again.
Well, I got some good news.
They've agreed to stop the trial.
They're gonna be sending you
to a hospital.
You can get the help you need.
Now, there's a very good chance
you can get out someday soon.
Yeah.
I can't believe it.
- I don't know what to say, Mr. Vail.
- That's all right, Aaron. That's okay.
I knew, the minute
you came into my cell,
I knew everything was gonna be okay.
(STAMMERING) You saved my life.
Yeah.
I got to go.
- When will I see you again?
- Well, that's up to the courts now.
I don't want you to worry, Aaron.
I'm gonna stay on top of this, okay?
Thank you.
All right. You give me a call
if you need to. Okay?
- I will.
- All right.
- Hey, Mr. Vail?
- Yeah.
(STAMMERING) Will you tell
Miss Venable I'm sorry?
Tell her I hope her neck is okay.
Yeah.
- What did you just say?
- What?
You told me you don't remember.
You black out.
So how do you know about her neck?
Well, good for you, Marty.
I was gonna let it go.
You was looking so happy just now.
I was thinking...
But to tell you the truth,
I'm glad you figured it,
'cause I have been dying to tell you.
(CHUCKLING)
I just didn't know who
you'd wanna hear it from, you know.
I mean, Aaron or Roy, or Roy or Aaron.
Well, I'll let you in on a little secret,
sort of a client-attorney privilege type
of a secret. You know what I mean?
Uh-huh.
It don't matter who you hear it from.
It's the same story.
(STAMMERING) I just
had to kill Linda, Mr. Vail.
That cunt just got what she deserved.
But cutting up
that son of a bitch Rushman,
that was just a fucking work of art.
(LAUGHING)
You're good. You are really good.
Yeah, I did get caught, though, didn't I?
So there never...
There never was a Roy?
Jesus Christ, Marty. If that's
what you think, I'm disappointed in you.
I don't mind telling you.
There never was an Aaron, Counselor.
Come on, Marty, I thought you had it
figured there at the end.
The way you put me
on the stand like that,
that was fucking brilliant, Marty.
And that whole thing,
that, "Act like a man,"
Jesus, I knew exactly
what you wanted from me.
It was like we were dancing, Marty!
- Guard.
- Come on. Don't be like that, Marty.
(KEY TURNING IN LOCK)
We did it, man. We fucking did it.
We're a great team, you and me.
You think I could've done this
without you?
You're just feeling a little anger here
because you started to care about
old Aaron. I can understand that,
but, you know, love hurts, Marty.
What can I say?
Hey, I'm just kidding, bud!
I didn't mean to hurt your feelings!
What else was I supposed to do?
Hey, you're gonna thank me
down the road,
'cause this is gonna toughen you
right up, Martin Vail!
You hear me? That's a promise!