[tense music playing]
[gunshot]
[Jesse] Around here,
you're either a guy like me,
or you come from one
of these rich families.
It's pretty much
one or the other.
Regardless, we all share
a feelin' for this place
and these mountains,
and so we tolerate each other.
When tourists come in on their
private jets to stay a week
in their mansions
on top of the hill,
we do what we can for 'em.
Fix that shower,
clean that toilet,
teach that kid to snowboard.
The money's what keeps us here
and this town
from fallin' off the map.
So it is rare for one of us
to do what I've done
and what I'm about to do.
It's fire mitigation.
Keeps the place
from burnin' down.
[swelling music playing]
Well, this is it.
In case you need
anything fixed.
I'll get that bag for you.
Thank you.
[Spencer] There she is.
[Elena chuckles]
[kisses]
-This is for you.
-Oh.
And I think that
is for you, too.
I'm sorry about this.
Oh, it's fine.
So, what else do you think?
I was right.
You do belong here
on a mountain with me.
-[chuckling]
-What's the damage, mate?
Oh, uh, 75.
-Just take that.
-Thank you.
Hey, the guy who bought
this place from,
he was a doctor, I think.
Yeah, he was.
How'd you know that?
I put in that hot tub
a couple years ago.
Needed you last week.
Well, anything breaks,
you need something fixed.
He can fix it.
It's what it says on
his business card.
Oh, I see. Cool.
-Thank you.
-My pleasure.
Take care, you guys.
-See ya.
-You, too.
Didn't you say
this was a cabin?
-It is. It's made of logs.
-[laughs]
Unless you want
something smaller, of course.
It can be arranged. I mean--
Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. I think
this will do just fine.
Uh-huh?
Welcome.
All right.
Let's leave this over here.
Come on in.
Where did you
get all this stuff?
From the previous owner.
He wasn't gonna need all
this shit in West Palm Beach.
And to be fair,
it did me a favor,
saved me gettin' a decorator
to do exactly the same thing.
It's pretty cool, huh?
I'd say so.
Yeah.
Hmm.
That did not come
with the house.
That did not.
That old princess
arrived two days ago.
He did it around
41 at his peak.
Am I supposed
to know who he is?
Come on.
Picasso.
Close, close.
The other Spaniard.
-[champagne pops]
-Wooh!
You know, it's been so weird
here on my own
for the past two weeks.
It gets really quiet out
there, especially at night.
One starts to feel like a 21st
century Jeremiah Johnson.
Sorry.
But it's this old Redford movie,
and I only saw it myself for
the first time the other night,
but basically he plays
this, um, mountain man
that gets besieged
by Indians with painted faces.
Look, I'm not sayin'
we're besieged yet,
but my point is he chose
to be a mountain man,
just like we've
chosen to be here.
It's war paint.
I have some in me, you know?
Native.
And I've got some
terrorist in me.
What does that tell you?
Spencer and Elena
ain't nothin' to fuck with.
[both chuckle]
-[Spencer] Wait.
-[Elena] Okay.
Right. How does that feel?
Okay.
I don't know.
How is it supposed to feel?
Well, you certainly look like
you know what you're doing.
You've been waiting long, mate?
Few minutes, no worries.
[pants]
So, listen.
She's never skied before,
but I need her to ski with me.
How good are you?
I'm magnificent.
[upbeat music playing]
Oh, man, this is so annoying.
Feel that.
What's wrong?
Does that feel hot to you?
Feel it.
Warm enough.
Ah!
Should be fucking scalding
for what I just paid for it.
[Spencer grunts]
Where are you going?
To call the fuckin'
idiots that fixed it.
Actually, call that driver.
He fitted the fucking
thing, didn't he?
He installed this.
Can you call him?
I need to call New York.
Something tells me they're
fucking up as well.
[Spencer]
How many?
I'll tell you what.
If I make the call for you,
I'm gonna need some
serious reciprocity.
Okay, well, just do it.
All right.
Yeah.
Hey.
I just came around the side.
I hope that's all right.
Oh, yeah.
It's fine.
So, what's the problem?
Hello again. Spencer.
Jesse.
Over here.
So, uh, I paid a couple of guys
who promised me
they'd fix this thing.
Have a feel.
Oh, yeah.
You think you can do it?
I'll figure it out.
All right. Now, do me a favor.
If you can't, just say so.
I'll still pay you
for your time.
Hello?
[munching]
Oh, shit.
I think our cowboy's
lookin' a bit perplexed.
Could be how he
looks in general.
-[phone vibrating]
-Mm-mm.
I've gotta take this.
[grunts]
Yeah.
I told you not to say that, man.
-Hey.
You wanna do me a favor?
You know, it's
freezing out here!
Uh, just keep your eye
on that peak.
It'll hypnotize you
and you will not feel the cold.
All right.
Can you check that jet?
Is it gettin' hotter?
I think so.
Yeah.
How's the pressure?
It's gettin' stronger.
What's the J stand for?
It's James, right?
Dad liked outlaws.
Thought he was one.
Mostly he was just a drunk
who liked to break stuff.
How we doing?
He fixed it.
What was the problem?
Pump was clogged.
I unclogged it.
Wow! You would not
believe how much it cost
me to get two experts
to not unclog my fucking pump.
I bet I would.
I'm only gonna
charge you 150, though.
Mostly for bein'
out in the cold.
What do I get?
[Spencer]
What else can you fix?
[Jesse]
Well, I can replace
those rotting boards
on the deck out there.
I didn't even notice that.
Yeah.
Now, I fixed a bunch of
stuff for the previous owner.
Just pretty much looks the same.
Oh, yeah.
Except for that.
[Jesse] Is that real?
[Spencer] Of course it is.
Is it all right if I...
Yeah, be my guest?
I've never seen
one in person before.
-It's a Moreau, right?
-Ding, ding.
[chuckles]
I took art class
back in college.
Oh, you went to college, huh?
Oh, community college
in Weatherford, Texas.
Yeah, teacher said this
bird I was drawing
looked like the rooster
by Moreau.
So, I went down to the bookstore
and checked him out.
Wow.
Who plays?
Oh, I strum a bit.
Not very well, though. You?
Yeah, I strum some.
Go on, then.
Play us something.
All right.
[chuckles]
-Yes! Uh-huh.
-Wooh!
Man of many talents!
Nah, most of us shit kickers
can do a party trick or two.
Yeah. Now, in between your
very nimble guitar playing
and keen eye for art,
tell me something.
Can you fix showers?
-I can take a look.
-This way.
Right.
So this one's fine,
but this one...
How do you feel?
-Ooh!
-Yeah.
-Oh, yeah.
-Scalding, right?
Yeah.
Need a new cartridge.
Switches your hot to hot,
your cold to cold.
Probably just haven't
been replaced since
the house was built.
Well, you get the cartridge
and I'll pay you back,
and then whatever it
costs to install it.
-Sound good?
-Mm-hmm.
Good man. Now, tell me,
can you fix doors?
I've got one downstairs
that needs a new lock.
-I can take a look.
-You can do that?
Let's go.
So there's a guy down
the hill, a Lebanese fella.
He wants all this done and more.
I'm gonna give him your number,
if that's cool with you.
Yeah, sure is.
All right.
Oh, yeah.
And charge him double.
Unlike me, he likes
to overpay for things.
[Spencer laughs]
Hey, thank you for
helping me earlier.
You're welcome.
There you go.
Oh, thank you.
I said 150.
Nope, that's for
the party trick.
Oh. Oh, thank you.
All right.
All right, take care.
Very useful cowboy.
He's the first local I've met
that isn't a complete bellend.
I didn't know who painted that.
Does that make me a bellend?
Furthest thing from, baby.
He did know who it was though,
and he knew his way
around the guitar,
that's for sure.
We can all play something
as country folk.
Oh, yeah, I forgot
you're one of them.
So tell me, what can you play?
Hmm?
You know, I think he
likes you, our cowboy.
[Spencer]
Well, I am very likeable.
I think all the men around
here have got
that hungry look in their eyes.
[Elena]
Should we feed them?
Yeah, I think we should.
How much do you
think I nicked it for?
I don't know, 2 mil.
I don't wanna be nicking it,
it's probably worth that much.
No, I swapped it for a Hockney
that I didn't really love.
And guess who
got the better deal?
[chuckles]
Don't you have to
sell it first to know?
Ah, sometimes just know.
Hmm.
[Spencer] Yeah.
Good, you spoke to them.
What'd they say?
[phone dings]
Mm-hmm.
[tense music]
You've got to be
fucking kidding me.
No, no, no, no,
you know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna fly to LA
today myself,
and I'm gonna show you
how to close these royal twats
once and for all,
and then you will
fucking thank me.
[indistinct conversation]
[Barry laughing]
[man]
That son of a bitch said this is
a fuckin' one-day job!
Fuck it is, dude,
it's a three-day job.
I'm not fucking going
to doing this.
Jesus.
Oh, well, hello there.
Hello!
[laughs]
Hey there.
You lost?
Come on over.
Hey, come on now, we don't bite!
Not much, anyway.
Are you telling me I'm
gonna have to fly commercial?
Good, because
I'm not doing that!
I don't know, Gary,
I'm not a fucking pilot.
Just do your job, man, or
I'll find someone who can.
-Hey, baby.
-Hey.
How was your walk?
Uh, you know, cold, beautiful.
-What's goin' on?
-Bad news.
I've got to go to LA,
see a man about a dog.
What?
That must be
a very special dog.
Not really, an expensive one.
About half a billion.
Why don't you come with me?
I'll only be gone a day or two.
Oh! Uh...
I-- I-- I just got here.
Are you sure?
You just hang by the pool,
Four Seasons.
I promise we'll come
straight back.
[sighs]
Yeah, I...
I'm gonna stay, you know,
work on gettin' to the very top.
Okay.
♪ That old Lincoln
in the rain ♪
♪ And it was not
quite December ♪
♪ When I finally
learned your name ♪
♪ In a coffee shop
in Memphis ♪
[knocking]
♪ Sweet potato
and chocolate pie ♪
♪ 16 months in detention ♪
♪ By God, it's been a long... ♪
-Hey.
Uh, Spencer told me to come
by and fix the door,
and those boards on the deck.
Oh, um, yeah, he's not here.
Okay, you just-- you want
me to come back later?
Um, no. No, come on in.
Not gonna stab me, are you?
[laughs]
We'll see.
[phone rings]
Hey. I'm fine.
Mom, I'm fine.
How much do you need?
Okay, I'll send you
200 as soon as I can.
Mom, I gotta go.
Here you go.
Oh, that's a little
early for me.
Thanks.
Ooh, to altitude.
-[chuckles, shrieks]
-[chuckles]
Altitude.
[sighs]
Mm, that's-- that's really good.
You probably sell that
somewhere, I bet.
I do.
I, um, did.
Just a few restaurants
and bakeries in New York.
No real money in it, though.
No real money in
anything these days.
[Jesse chuckles]
Except one thing.
Where's the money?
Dating rich guys, stupid.
Now, you're easy to miss
till you take those stupid
sunglasses off.
[chuckles]
But you don't miss
much, do you?
Not when I'm payin' attention.
Where'd you grow up, anyway?
Doesn't matter.
Must be from the same place.
[chuckles]
Bet you don't go back much.
Once.
That was enough.
Still too early for you?
Oh, that's not for me.
Believe me, it was,
but, uh, not anymore.
More for me, then.
You said he's in town.
Grand Junction.
Went to see a guy about a dog.
Y'all gettin' a dog, huh?
Hmm.
He's allergic.
I think it's just a saying,
you know, from, uh...
-[both] England.
-Yeah.
[Jesse chuckles]
So you draw, huh?
I scribble some.
You scribble some,
you strum some, too.
That's me.
A little bit of this,
a little bit of that,
not enough for either one.
Just enough for the ladies,
though, right?
No lady?
Nothing serious.
What about you?
I mean, where's the ring?
That's where
the real money is, right?
My mother always said,
"Don't get married,
don't have kids,
and if you're dumb enough
to do either one,
you better have a plan to kill
that son of a bitch."
Smart woman.
[chuckles]
Spencer always says
the money's everywhere.
You just need to know
how to grab it
when no one's lookin'.
Or when everybody is.
They all say that shit,
don't they?
He's all right, though,
compared to most of 'em.
Most of them are dogs.
Spencer is more like a cat,
playing with the mouse
before neatly tearing it up
and eating the good parts.
You just make sure
when the time comes,
you walk out with more
than you walked in with.
And hold on to your good parts.
You do the same.
Here's to gettin' it.
[kissing]
[panting]
[moans]
For the road.
Just once, huh?
Once was enough.
Hey, baby.
-You miss me?
-Oh, I did.
-Oh, gosh.
-Oh.
-[sighs]
-[kissing]
You were right.
I should have come with you.
How was your meeting?
Well, the money's en route,
as they say.
[kisses]
Good.
Yeah.
You hungry?
Yeah, I could do
with some food.
Good.
I'll, uh, fix something up.
-Baby?
-Yeah?
Did the cowboy come and
fix that door downstairs?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, he did.
I forgot to tell
you he's coming.
What about the lower deck?
Oh, uh, yeah.
I'm-- I'm not sure.
So someone's been
drinking on the job?
Oh.
Yeah, I had a beer,
so I offered him one, too.
Oh, that's generous of you.
You know, baby,
we gotta be careful
not to confuse the help.
Okay.
Eat. It's gettin' cold.
[radio]
Last night's dusting turned
out to be quite a bit
more than dusting.
There are seven fresh
inches of snow
on that mountain, people.
So, I suggest you drop
whatever you are doing
and get out there
if you are not already.
That is what I'm gonna
do right after this.
You are listening to KOTO
in Telluride, Colorado.
See you on the mountain.
Hey!
There's some coyotes
yippin' out there.
They get kinda hungry
and mean this time of the year.
Just a heads up.
[knocking]
Baby, a friend
of mine is in town.
Well, he's a colleague, really.
-He's coming over.
-Okay.
-Around 4:00?
You couldn't whip up a cheese
plate or something, could you?
Um, sure. Yeah.
Cool.
Are you gonna close that door?
You're letting
all the steam out.
Cowboy, can you come over?
Boiler's actin' up.
Cheers.
Ah, cowboy!
Glad you're here. Come on in.
Baby, look who's here.
So I've, uh, got some
friends coming over.
-Can you smell that?
-No.
Yeah, see, every time
I go down there,
I get the faint smell of shit.
Come on.
It's your sump pump.
Yeah, probably.
[sniffs]
Now can you smell it?
No.
I can.
Yeah.
When that happens, you just got
to pour water down that pumper.
Well, you do that.
I'm gonna let my friends in.
Hey!
[laughing]
-Tomas!
-Hey. How's it goin', man?
-Good to see you.
-Oh, this place is amazing!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
And, uh, Ginny, right?
Jenette, actually.
But everyone calls me Jen.
Except me.
Please, come in.
-Come in, come in, come in.
-Yeah.
That's the one you like, right?
It certainly is.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Your house is fucking massive.
Trust me, this is pretty quaint
compared to some of
the others around here.
Our pump was actin' up.
Jesse, when you're done here,
come upstairs, will you?
Most able fellow I've met here.
Ah, Elena, darling.
Tomas and Jen.
-Hi.
-Hello.
-Tomas.
-Elena.
-Nice to meet you.
-Jen.
-Pleasure.
-Jen, darling, what
can I get you?
-Whiskey?
-I'll have what she's having.
-Prosecco.
-Cool.
-I love this.
-Thank you.
This is quite a room.
Ah, yeah.
Most of this is from
the previous owner.
Why swap out great cowboy
and Indian shit for
less great, huh?
No, it's perfect.
So is that.
It's a Kandinsky, no?
No, mate. Try, uh, Moreau.
-...skiing so much--
-There we go, ladies.
-Oh, thank you.
-Thank you.
So how much?
Uh, I bought it off some, uh,
bohemian artist
living in the village.
Some Jewish fella,
him and his wife.
He was a-- he was a painter.
His stuff was shit,
but he had that sitting there.
I'm going to hate you. How much?
Half a million.
It's worth two.
-Cheers.
-Fuck.
Is that all or...
Ah, Jesse.
-Stay for a bit.
-Um...
No, no, no.
You're staying. For one.
She looks like fun
to play house with.
She is, but I think
we're past playing.
A bit more Prosecco?
Isn't that right, baby?
-What's that?
-Me and you.
We're past playing.
Never.
[kisses]
[Spencer]
Take it from one who didn't.
Get a solid prenup,
and you're all good, my friend.
The truth is, since bein'
out here,
that whole world seems
so far away.
There's something
real here, man.
People can do things, not
just talk people into things.
This guy over here,
he can fix anything.
He knew that was a Moreau,
knows his way around a guitar.
Ain't that right, cowboy?
Sorry?
I was just telling
my friend here
what a fine guitar
player you are.
Oh, no, I'm not.
You gonna play us something?
-No, I cannot play--
-Yes, you are.
Just imagine we're all
sittin' around a campfire,
one of the guys
has got a guitar.
Yes. Let's do it. Come on.
[plays guitar]
Not that shit.
As skillful as it was,
I want something different.
♪ Here's our secret song ♪
♪ About how we don't belong ♪
♪ To anyone or anywhere
we've been ♪
♪ So meet me on a mountain ♪
♪ Where we can have a drink ♪
♪ Let me tell you
what I really think ♪
♪ And you can text
me anytime ♪
♪ And I'll be about to fix ♪
♪ What ain't even broke ♪
♪ So take a secret,
bury it deep ♪
♪ Maybe you can hide
a thing from me ♪
[music ends]
And that's how we do
it around the campfire.
That's too high of a note
for me not to leave on, so...
No encore?
I've always been kind
of a one-and-doner.
Ah, who knows when to say when?
Wish I did.
Oh, appreciate you guys
letting me have a drink,
and, uh, it's nice meeting
you folks.
Don't forget that
cartridge thingy.
That's comin'.
Thanks for having me over.
-Mm.
-Good night.
That was quite good.
Hmm.
Rather inspired performance,
don't you think, babe?
Mm-hmm.
Anyone hungry?
Okay.
So, what did you think of him?
I mean, he's all right.
He's just a bit of a grasper.
I noticed.
Of course you did.
He can never quite
make the big score.
I mean, he sees it,
don't get me wrong,
just doesn't know
how to grab it.
Which is why he's stayin'
in a pretty solid hotel in town
and not-- you know?
Well, I'm sure you could teach
him how to grab
rather than grasp.
Yeah, I probably could,
but I fucking won't.
[laughs, grunts]
So, come on, baby.
We're gonna take
a bath together,
and you're gonna let me fix you.
[kissing]
Well, how about you
let me fix this--
Hmm.
And then I'll let you fix me?
And if I please you
like I plan to--
[kisses]
It'll be some kind of,
um, you know...
[kisses]
Reciprocity?
Mm.
You know how
much I love that word.
Yeah, I know.
Well, hurry up.
[kisses]
[snoring]
[thud]
[sighs]
[Jesse]
There's always a door open
in these big houses up here.
[gasps]
Once wasn't enough for me.
[kissing, moaning]
[panting]
[grunts]
Elena?
[grunting]
[sniffles]
You don't gotta worry,
you know?
He's smart enough to suspect,
but too arrogant to think
I'd ever fuck the help.
It's you I gotta worry about.
[sighs]
Well, I guess that
works in both of our favor.
If you ever pull anything
like this again,
I just swear to God...
[panting]
Now get the fuck out.
[pants]
What are you doing down there?
Oh, I had to close the door.
It blew right open.
Not the fucking
one he fixed, is it?
No, the one in the gym.
God, it's so windy.
You okay?
Oh, man, I can't believe
I drank so much.
You really put it
away tonight, huh?
This altitude does not
fucking helping us.
Oh.
Come on.
[Spencer grunts, sniffles]
[man]
Called me to tell me that I cut
down a fuckin' live tree.
They got a complaint.
They got a complaint. How?
People aren't even fuckin' home.
Call me again,
I'll fuck your wife.
You won't even know.
I don't know how
you do it, Jess.
What's that?
Drive these rich fucks around.
I mean, don't you got
any fuckin' dignity?
Driving these assholes around?
Fuckin' beta cuck
over there, man.
Fuckin'...
[gasps, pants]
Goddamn you.
I guess you were right.
You do have to worry.
But I'm right, too.
About you and me.
Okay, you need to leave.
Right this minute.
You're not like him.
You can pretend.
I saw you.
You mean you fucked me.
Don't talk like that.
That's what you did.
And it was...
It didn't mean...
Hey.
Cowboy.
What are you doing here?
Got your cartridge.
-Oh, you should have, uh...
-No, I know.
I was just in the neighborhood.
I figured I'd swing by
and see if y'all were around.
I can come back if you want.
No. No.
We can fix it now.
Yeah.
So your song the other day,
went something like this.
It's really nice. I like it.
It's very, um, simple.
But I was thinking
maybe you could add
something like this.
Something like that.
At the end.
It's a trick my Chilean
teacher taught me.
You try it.
Here. Come on.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
[sighs]
You play good.
Thank you.
I hope you didn't think this
thing was just for decoration.
I can't stand people like that.
I mean, I've always
been an excellent student.
I've never had any
trouble gettin' As
or firsts at university,
but, I mean,
I could never give myself to
something completely, you know?
I never had it here
to be an artist.
I had to make money.
I had to.
You know, I didn't grow up posh
like the rest of my classmates.
My dad was from a place
called Lahore.
That's in Pakistan.
Yeah, I figured you were
from, you know,
one of those places.
One of those places, yeah.
India, Yemen, Pakistan,
where they've all got different
shades of brown skin
and they pray on their
knees to Allah!
Allah pak!
[chuckles]
You ever been to one
of those places, Jesse?
I guess I haven't.
Neither have I, except from
the safety of the Four Seasons.
But I have been to places like
the London School of Economics
and Harvard Business School.
They're very interesting places.
Bit boring.
And tad vicious.
I bet.
So you and, uh, Elena,
you met in New York?
Well, I didn't meet
her at Harvard, did I?
Not being rude, but there's
no one there like Elena.
She's a rare breed
anywhere, that one.
You take her to a party, never
looks like she's having fun.
Doesn't wanna get involved
with any of the party girls.
But do you know
what that makes her
to blokes like us?
I think she doesn't know.
She knows everything.
But I really like that.
What about you, cowboy?
Do you like that?
-I don't know.
-Of course you do.
You know, the first
time I met her, right,
she was seein' this, like, blue
blood prick from J.P. Morgan.
I knew him.
And I thought to myself,
"How the fuck did he get her?"
The next time I saw her,
she was off to L.A.,
going to see another guy.
So I told her, "Tell him
that you can't make it,
you got a cold, and let's
fuck off to Lisbon together."
In Portugal.
Last time I checked.
Well done, cowboy.
And that's what we did.
Felt like we fucked
off from everywhere.
We drank some champagne,
and we joined a mile-high club.
Oops. Sorry.
You wanna feel that?
I can feel that.
-You sure?
-Mm-hmm.
[Elena]
Spencer!
The lights are out!
[Spencer]
Yes, I'm here!
Can you fix this, cowboy?
I can take a look.
You got a flashlight, right?
Only on my phone,
and that's charging downstairs.
Not anymore.
So how long does this sort
of thing last around here?
Could be five minutes.
Could be five or six hours.
Dinner's ready.
Are you hungry, Jesse?
Uh, I don't think
there's enough, uh--
Of course there is.
Take a seat.
Looks beautiful.
[kisses]
This is all very exciting.
Don't you think, guys?
You know, I can feel it
gettin' a little bit
cold in here already.
Yeah, it can change
pretty quickly around here.
You know what I think we do?
These things
aren't on in an hour,
we go to the hotel
up the road, and...
[bang]
What was that?
You leave a door open?
I don't think so.
You got a gun?
Why would I have a gun?
Spencer.
Stay.
Stay there.
[Spencer screams]
Hold it.
Yeah, hold it.
It's the Picasso.
Yeah.
[panting]
Hey!
What are you doin'?
You said we take
the painting and go.
You do whatever you want.
I'm gonna look around.
See what else there is to find.
That's fuckin' stupid, man.
We get out of here.
[yells]
[grunting]
[groaning]
Fuckin' stop it!
[pants]
Just stop. Shh! Shh!
Okay.
Okay. Shh! shh!
[pants]
Found us a cat here!
[both pant]
I think we met your
guy downstairs, huh?
Yeah. Real squirrely fuck.
Ran out the door and left you.
Damn it.
Get that fuckin' light off!
-[yells]
-[groans]
[grunting]
[pants]
[groans]
[panting]
Yeah.
Yeah, I remember you.
From the forest that day.
You remember me, too,
don't you?
Don't you?
[Barry chuckles]
How much you wanna bet?
I can wipe that look
right off your face.
You can't afford it.
[both chuckling]
[groan]
-You gotta stop, man.
-Shut the fuck up!
[groaning, grunting]
What the fuck?
[grunting]
[screams]
[groaning]
[grunting]
-Elena. Elena.
-No!
Elena! Elena, it's me, Jesse!
It's me. It's-- Elena! Elena.
It's over. It's okay.
It's over. It's all right.
It's okay.
[panting]
It's all right.
[indistinct radio chatter]
Mr. Sinclair's on his way down
to the station for questioning.
I'm gonna post a car
up the street
for your own peace of mind.
You know, we get burglaries
around here every now and then,
but this is highly unusual.
Footprints go in and out.
Blood trail goes out.
No sign of forced entry.
You, um, you said
you were locked out?
Out the, uh...
Out the back door there.
They, uh,
they came for this painting.
What, uh, what
makes you say that?
Y-- you weren't here, right?
No, but I saw them through
the window there, like I said.
So they came for the
painting and then...
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
Well, it is lucky that
Mr. Sinclair was
here to stop them.
If you want, we can put you
two up at a hotel for the night.
N-- no, no.
We're fine here. Thank you.
Can I make a suggestion?
Get yourself
a good-sized dog,
like a lab or a husky
or a German shepherd.
Most people up here have them.
I'm allergic to dogs.
Last I checked,
it was still legal
to own a firearm around here.
Let's go.
[clears throat]
We should leave.
Do what the fuck you want.
Okay.
How?
You've only got $485 in
your checking account.
Unless you want a fresh
start in Milwaukee.
But how the fuck are
you gonna get there?
A little bit steep
on your budget.
You've had a rough night.
And what did you have?
A fucking pleasant one?
No.
I was nearly raped by
a disgusting little man.
Not pleasant, but
also not my first rodeo.
You had it worse.
Standing out there in the cold,
watched the whole thing go down,
tryin' to wait for the right
moment to make the smart play.
But I guess it never came,
which is why you had to
watch another guy cowboy up
before you could.
Where I come from,
that's pretty fuckin' rough.
You know it was your fucking
cowboy that did this, right?
You fucking know that!
He sent them and then
changed his fucking mind!
But you can't see that!
Fuck!
You know what?
The question is when and why.
Yeah.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
[thuds]
[panting]
The police called.
The name of the guy they're
looking for is Barry Teft.
Sounds more like a fucking
mortgage broker to me
than a rapist.
Barry fucking Teft.
[chuckles]
And the, uh,
big fucker on the floor,
he spent time in
Colorado State Prison.
As did our friend Jesse.
For what?
Jesse?
Oh, just assault with
a deadly weapon.
His name's not even Sinclair.
It's Urick or some shit.
Said he probably
changed it when he got out.
[exhales]
What the fuck you doing?
Hey, Spencer.
I didn't get to these
boards last time I was here.
Yeah, I don't think
I asked you to.
I think you did.
You don't come up here
and tear out my deck
without fucking telling me.
Shit.
Today's the last day
of ski season, isn't it?
How was it out there?
There's still some good snow.
How y'all been since...
Get the fuck out of here.
Now.
Hey, Elena. You all right?
Let me know you need any help.
[man]
Yeah, I remember you
from the forest that day.
Hey, come on now!
We don't bite!
You remember
me, too, don't you?
Don't you?
[Jesse]
You're not like him.
You can pretend.
I saw you.
[sighs]
You know, I always thought
you Americans were
silly with your guns.
But now I think
I'm starting to get it.
Yes, well, tell him if he wants
to bail out now
he has to call me
and fucking beg.
And then we'll take what's
left of his pathetic little fund
and we will use it to
wipe our arses with!
Elena, trust me, I know
what the fuck I'm doing.
Just dump it
and watch it go down down.
[dance music playing]
[muffled music playing]
♪ I think that we both
need to stop this illusion ♪
♪ I've been on
the smooth shit ♪
♪ I've been on the bullshit ♪
♪ I thought that you
knew this ♪
[faint music playing]
♪ I think that we both
need to stop this illusion ♪
♪ I've been on
the smooth shit ♪
♪ I've been on the bullshit ♪
♪ I thought that you
knew this ♪
[indistinct lyrics]
Hey, baby.
You remember this one?
No, maybe you wouldn't.
It's before your time.
[music continues]
Wooh!
[gasps]
Oh, shit.
[pants]
Spencer?
What's happened?
-It's Jesse.
-Jesse?
What's he doing?
He was just staring at me.
Fuck's sake.
I'll call the police.
What?
He's gonna come back, you know?
Why, Elena?
Why's he gonna come back?
What do you mean?
Will the other one
come back, hmm?
No, I don't think so.
But Jesse will.
To collect his reward, maybe.
Yeah.
I mean, what can we give
him that we haven't already?
[scrunching]
Needs more lime.
Squeeze it yourself.
You know what?
I admit it. What you said
the other night was true.
I got caught out.
I didn't see the smart play.
And so I got played.
I'm fucking gutted, really.
I am.
But here's the thing.
They fucking bollocksed it up.
They didn't get
what they came for.
anything, really.
Except one over on
the rich prick
on top of the hill.
You know, baby, I have
spent the last 22 years
rippin' the life
out of other men.
And when you're good at it,
they call you a killer.
And you haven't even
fucking killed anyone.
[sighs]
I know.
It feels fucking good.
And the more you do it,
the more you wonder
what it would be like
to do it for real.
Well, this is your big chance.
I think it is.
You don't wanna miss it.
Yeah.
So I think I'm gonna,
uh, skin up and ski down.
You gonna be all right here?
Yeah.
I'm all right.
[Spencer panting]
[screams]
[Spencer screams]
Fuck.
Help!
[Jesse panting]
[groaning]
[panting]
You're in some shape, mate.
Practically, ran up
that damn hill.
[panting]
[screams]
It'll help.
Probably the only thing
that'll help right now.
There you go. Oh, boy.
[laughs]
[sighs]
-[yells]
-Yeah, I did something similar.
Not quite as bad.
About 10 years ago.
That was it for me.
Probably for you, too.
[Spencer panting]
[grunts]
[Spencer groaning]
You don't deserve her.
And the second I saw you,
I thought, "No way,
not this guy."
I can tell you the type is
thinks everything can be yours
for a deal or a steal.
That house.
That painting.
My song.
A woman.
Fuck you.
You hear that?
Help's on the way.
All you gotta
do is call for it.
You know how to
call for help, don't you?
Help! Please!
Somebody help me!
[chuckles]
You fuckin' idiot.
All right.
Well, you hang in there.
You'll be all right.
Maybe.
[grunts]
[pants]
That's gonna be hard to prove.
That he was there?
That he sabotaged your skis
and that that caused
your accident.
And what about
an accessory to home invasion?
Can we prove that?
We have some witnesses
who saw him
talkin' to Teft and Aldrich
at a local bar a few
nights before the break-in.
We're gonna pick him up.
In the meantime,
I have an officer
posted by the ridge there.
Very reassuring.
And what about Barry Teft?
Are you gonna be pickin'
him up anytime soon?
Yes, sir.
I believe we will.
You believe you will?
Baby, do me a favor.
See the officer out,
and on your way back,
get me my gun from my closet.
Thanks.
[sighs]
[groans]
Supposed to just take
the fuckin' painting
and leave.
[Barry chuckles]
I'm the same as you.
When I see a piece like that,
I'm gonna jump on it.
I beat you to it, didn't I?
[gun thuds]
[takes deep breaths]
I really blew it, didn't I?
What?
My chance.
I was stupid.
[sighs]
No.
You're smart.
You're the smartest.
Just doesn't mean
much around here.
I'm glad you stayed with me.
You should get some rest.
Jerry, I think that maybe
Sinclair's comin' your way.
You might wanna
check on Paschim.
You copy that?
Jerry, you copy?
Look, that one
from the other night,
you don't gotta
worry about him.
They weren't supposed to...
They were just supposed
to take the painting.
Yeah?
And then what?
I don't know.
Fence it.
Sell it.
I just figured
if I could grab it,
like we had said the other day,
then I could...
I could show you that...
...me...
That I could play his game.
You did some time, huh?
I'm not gonna do any more.
I have a dad doing time.
I think he's gonna die in there.
You think or hope?
Tea?
Yeah.
[sighs]
You look tired.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
What am I to you, anyway?
-Just some...
-Mistake I made?
It sure didn't feel
like a mistake.
It felt like...
You know what it felt like.
And I can tell it's
a problem for you.
I know you worked hard
to get here.
Kept yourself to yourself.
You didn't let him or any
of them see shit about you.
You had it in the bag
till you got lonely.
I mean, that's all right.
People do.
I do.
You know, it's hard always
pretendin' to be somethin'
or someone you're not.
Liking guys you don't.
No matter how
good you are at it.
And you are very good.
But even a star player has
to take himself out sometimes,
you know?
Breathe some air.
That's what you were
doin' when we happened.
Just breathing some air.
No mistake.
Oh, fuck!
[panting]
[groaning]
[kissing]
I'm never going back.
[groaning]
I'm sorry.
[panting]
[groaning, panting]
Got you, girl.
You're not that bad, you know?
But you're not so good either.
♪ If I could put it in a box ♪
♪ If I could find it
on a shelf ♪
♪ I would pick it every time ♪
♪ Know yourself ♪
♪ If I could carve it
on a stone ♪
♪ Display it in a square ♪
♪ I would choose
it every time ♪
♪ Be aware ♪
♪ Because you don't
get to do it again ♪
♪ Let me tell you ♪
♪ You don't get to
do it again ♪
♪ Because you don't
get to do it again ♪
♪ Let me tell you ♪
♪ You don't get to do it ♪
♪ Do it again ♪
♪ If I could put it in a box ♪
♪ If I could find it
on a shelf ♪
♪ Yeah,
I'll pick it every time ♪
♪ Know yourself ♪
♪ Be yourself ♪
♪ Because you don't
get to do it again ♪
♪ Let me tell you ♪
♪ You don't get to
do it again ♪
♪ Because you don't
get to do it again ♪
♪ Don't get to do it ♪
♪ Do it again ♪
♪ Let me tell you ♪
♪ If I could carve it
on a stone ♪
♪ If I could display
it in a square ♪
♪ I would choose it
every time ♪
♪ Be aware ♪
♪ Because you don't
get to do it again ♪
♪ Let me tell you ♪
♪ You don't get to
do it again ♪
♪ You don't get to do it ♪
♪ Do it again ♪
♪ Oh, you don't
get to do it again ♪