Good morning, ladies.
Hello.
Hello!
Thank you.
Mmm.
Babe.
I need a second opinion.
Oh. Okay.
What is it?
Um,
it's a Douglas fir parfait.
Oh.
- Darling, what time is it?
- Please.
Please can you just try it?
Hmm.
Okay.
So no gush or trickle or fluid
or unusual amount of dampness
in your underwear?
- Uh-uh.
- Mucus plug?
Who even are you?
Erm, okay.
Fluids?
Didn't you just ask me
that question?
- No, to drink. Have you...
- No, nothing.
Jesus.
Make sure you keep drinking.
Okay.
So as and when you, erm...
You have any...
Yeah, you'll be
the first to know.
Good to go on that.
Just a little more.
- Table five.
- Yes, Chef.
Sauce?
Right,
that's ready for service.
Don't look so terrified, Chef.
- That's fucking majestic.
- Thank you, Chef.
Chef?
Do you need anything?
No, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Leave me alone.
Go back to your station.
So what happens now?
I'm going to recommend
starting with a course
of chemotherapy.
Why not just remove it?
Sorry, I mean, why...
Why can't we just operate?
- Honestly?
- Yeah.
It's too big.
The first thing
we have to do is shrink it.
Slow it down.
Once we achieve that,
then we can operate.
And then... And then what?
Once you recover from surgery,
you'll need to complete
another course
of chemotherapy.
We really don't want to be
leaving anything behind here.
Hmm.
Given this is a reoccurrence,
we need an aggressive
treatment plan.
Okay.
So...
Just to check that I...
It would go...
- A course of chemotherapy...
- Mmm-hmm.
...followed by surgery,
followed by another,
hopefully final...
- course of chemotherapy?
- Correct.
Okay, great.
And what about work?
What about work?
Well, how much time off,
do you think,
realistically,
we should be considering?
What do you think?
Well, given the physical
nature of your profession,
honestly, if you
and your colleagues
can find a workable solution,
I would advocate
stepping back.
Maybe it's time
to finally get a dog.
I read somewhere
that pets, dogs,
are really good for children,
helping them
to cope with, like,
big, life stuff.
Hmm.
Because once they've gone
through the death of a pet,
their ability
to handle all the other
terrible shit goes up.
So...
So you think
we should procure a dog
in order to end its life
prematurely as a way of...
I'm obviously not suggesting
we kill a dog.
Maybe just a really old one.
What...
What would you say
if I said to you...
Erm, I'm not sure...
I know how to go through
all of that all over again?
- Erm...
- 'Cos let's...
Let's just say...
Let's just say it goes to plan
and...
In whatever it is,
like, six to eight months...
Mmm-hmm.
...I receive the all-clear
and it's great
and all of a sudden,
it feels, like, great.
- Yeah.
That'd be great. Agreed, yeah.
But what happens
if it doesn't?
All of a sudden
you're in this weird position
where instead of making
the most out of those...
six, seven, eight,
maybe nine months,
you're gonna realise that
all you did was go bald
and puke your guts up.
Mmm-hmm.
Okay. Yeah.
So you're saying that
in that scenario,
for you it would be...
Erm, more
about quality than quantity?
I'm saying I'm not
particularly interested
in a treatment plan
that accidentally
wastes our time.
I'm saying,
in that particular scenario,
I'd much rather we...
We have six fucking amazing,
fantastic, proactive months...
Than 12 really,
really shitty passive ones.
I'm not saying I don't want
to do the treatment.
I'm just saying...
I want it to be
the right choice.
Knock, knock.
- Breakfast. You got time?
- Yeah.
Kumquats or eggs?
Mmm.
You tell me.
Then dealer's choice it is.
- Nice threads, by the way.
- Oh.
Thanks, Dad.
Hello,
my name is Tobias Durand.
And I'm part of
the Weetabix IT team,
fulfilling the role
of Master Data Steward.
Fabulous.
If you could just go ahead
and tell me
what you had for breakfast
this morning.
Honeyed kumquats on toast.
Followed by
a bowl of Weetabix.
Okey-dokey.
I think the thing
that I enjoy most
about working here at Weetabix
is the feeling of family.
Despite the fact
that we're all of us
part of a very large,
global brand,
there's...
There's still
a real family feeling.
Okay.
Divorce.
Patient number 14.
They needed the bed back.
What's happened
to my underwear?
Oh, I literally have no idea.
This, erm...
This was all you...
All you had on you.
The Chocolate Orange was
pronounced dead at the scene.
Er... Erm...
I'm Almut, by the way.
Almut?
Almut.
Tobias.
So sorry,
but do we know each other?
Oh.
Yeah... No. Erm...
Sorry. I...
I... I ran you over.
Oh.
Patient number 17.
Sorry.
It's all right.
Hello and welcome
to Red Wagon Diner.
Here at Red Wagon Diner,
we pride ourselves
on offering our customers
a taste of the classic
'50s American diner
here on
the great British roadside.
All our burgers are made
to our special recipe
using 100% British beef
and our top dollar shakes
are made
with real dairy ice cream
to die for.
What can I get you?
I work for Weetabix.
As in the breakfast cereal?
Mmm-hmm.
Well, the company...
Sorry. The company also own...
Weetos, Alpen,
Ready Brek. But, yeah.
Wow.
You must be really regular.
Ow, ow.
Um, how... How about yourself?
I'm a chef/restaurant owner.
Oh.
Er, what kind of cuisine
do you, er...
...do?
Er, modern European takes
on classic Alpine dishes.
So, basically, Anglo-Bavarian.
Well, that's the plan, anyway.
Supposed to open
in a few weeks.
How's it going?
Er...
Oh.
Oh, no.
No, it's going fine.
It's gonna be great.
You should come.
No, honestly, I feel like
that's the least I could do.
- Oh.
- And your wife too.
- Darling?
- Yeah?
Yeah.
There is something
that your daddy and I...
Something that
mommy and me want to...
We want to talk to you about.
Yeah.
Something a little...
A little bit important, actually.
- It's a bit serious, though.
- Yeah.
Yeah, a bit serious
- and a bit grown-up.
- Yeah.
A bit serious, a bit grown-up,
a bit important.
Yeah.
So mommy didn't realize it
but mommy's...
mommy's actually
been feeling quite ill.
Got a bit of a tummy ache,
kind of a pretty nasty
tummy ache.
And the doctors
have basically said...
Hi, there! What a delicious
looking ice cream sundae.
Yummo!
My name's Noel.
What's your name?
Ella, and I'm three.
So sorry, we're actually
in the middle...
How would you like
to see me make
this entire bottle disappear?
- Yes, please.
- Noel? Noel, seriously.
- We can't do this right now.
- This is not a good time.
Will you help me say
the magic words?
Noel!
Go... Go away. Go away.
Sorry, it's just not the time.
So...
Where were we?
Mmm-hmm!
That's too much tea.
Can I make you one?
All right, you two.
It's bath time and
it's bedtime for both of you.
No.
Am I gonna have to come
and get you?
- No.
- Are you nodding?
- I'm gonna come and get you!
- Grab Teddy.
What are we gonna do?
Do you want me to...
- Oh, I don't know if I can...
- Oh!
- Sorry, mommy.
- No!
You tricked me!
We're going
all the way. We're going...
I like her best.
- Yep.
- Yeah.
- And I like her best.
- I know you do.
She has great hair,
doesn't she?
You were really great with her
this afternoon, by the way.
Yeah, well...
Yeah, I'm... I'm glad
we decided just to talk to her
instead of killing a dog.
Yeah.
So...
I was thinking...
Maybe, erm,
we...
Should have some sex
before my treatment begins.
Now?
Mmm-hmm.
♪ Oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ Go on, I dare you ♪
♪ I dare you ♪
♪ I can hear it now
Like I heard it then ♪
♪ Singing, oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ Go on, I dare you ♪
I meant to say,
I got the weirdest message
from Simon.
You know,
Simon Maxson, my old boss?
Well, he, erm...
He wanted to know if I...
If I was interested in trying
out for the Bocuse d'Or.
As soon as all this is over,
we're... We're gonna make sure
that you have
the opportunity and the time
to take on whatever it is
you want.
But I really...
I really think that right now
we ought to just slow down
- and focus on get...
- Relax.
I said no.
Just thought
it was interesting,
that's all.
Yes!
Come on.
That was perfect!
That's a perfect throw.
Thank you for joining us
in the countdown to our
New Year's Eve celebrations.
What are you up to tonight?
Are you going out...
- Oh!
- ...to watch some fireworks?
- Staying in with the kids?
- Mmm.
Have you got friends
coming round?
- Mmm!
- Ring in and let us know
- what you're planning to do...
- Thank you.
Mmm!
Oh, fuck! Mmm, motherfucker!
Oh!
They're definitely getting
stronger, you know.
Mmm.
Lasting a minimum now
of 60 seconds
every five to ten minutes.
Great. Thank you.
See you very soon.
That's fine.
- That's fine.
- Yeah?
Yeah. Yeah.
Mmm, hang on a second.
Hang on.
Ooh. Yeah, yeah,
take a moment.
Take a beat, take a beat.
Okay.
Ready?
Here we go.
Sorry.
Shit. I'm sorry.
I'm fine to walk.
Honestly. Honestly.
- Fuck. I'm so sorry.
- Honestly.
Fucking fuckface!
Oh, this is ridiculous!
Very sorry. Sorry.
Oh, fuck!
I'm sorry.
Okay, okay. You okay?
Yeah.
That's it. Well done.
You're doing a great job.
Yes, you are.
Okay.
Well, good news is,
mom and Dad,
the baby's heart rate
is all good.
mom, same goes
for your BP and pulse.
Bad news, I'm afraid, mom,
is that you're still
only two centimetres,
if that.
So, I'm sorry,
but you're going to have
to go back home again
and wait.
I'm sorry.
You wanted
to see me, Chef?
I did, yeah. Please.
Er, actually, would you...
Would you mind
closing the door?
- Oh, yeah, sure.
- Wait, sorry. No, no. Sorry.
- My fault.
- Oh.
Chef, is this about the thing
with the scallops?
What? No, no.
- Oh.
- No.
Tell me something, Chef.
What... What do
you know about the...
Do you need the room?
'Fraid so.
What do you know about
the Bocuse d'Or?
Erm, I mean,
it's like the...
The culinary Olympics.
There is no higher accolade.
Sorry, Chef. We are running
low on celeriac.
Strictly between us, Chef,
and I mean that,
not a word to another soul,
I, erm...
I've been asked if I would
like to compete this year
to represent the UK, and I...
I'd like you to be my commis.
- What?
- But listen.
Holy shit, Chef!
We have two heats
to get through.
And you seriously really need
to consider...
- Chef, I'm in!
- Time. Time, Chef.
You really need
to think about time.
Chef, it's literally
the easiest...
If we make it
to the European heat,
that is three to four days
a week minimum, training wise.
Make it to the final,
that is five days a week.
- Five days, full time.
- Chef, I'm in.
- And there'll be no let-up.
- I'm in. 100%.
Let's get out of here.
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, I'm probably gonna have
to wet-shave you back here.
It's looking a little furry.
Really?
- Oh.
- Lovely.
Yeah, that's the ticket.
I'm jealous. You realize that?
Jay Rayner
just published a rave.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Go on.
- You'll be fine.
- All right, thanks. Bye.
Hi. How are you doing
this evening?
Do you have a reservation
with us?
Er, yeah. Tobi...
Tobias Durand. I don't...
Oh, my God. Mr. Weetabix.
This is so great.
How's the arm? Poor thing.
Oh.
- Yeah.
- Well, listen.
We're so excited to have you
with us this evening.
We're gonna make sure you have
the time of your life.
I have you down
as a table for two, correct?
Erm, no.
Sorry, that's my fault.
Just me in the end.
Oh, don't apologize.
- Follow me.
- Okay.
I'll let Chef know
you're here.
A little something
to get you started.
Oh.
Weisswurst amuse-bouche.
AKA Bavarian white sausage
with a modern twist.
On top, we have for you
a lemon mustard gel. Enjoy.
Thank you. Thank you.
- Hi.
Marks out of 10
for my tiny sausage?
It's 10.
I'm sorry to hear
your wife couldn't make it.
Is everything all right?
Erm, we're actually
not, erm...
Well, I mean...
Technically speaking, we still
are but legally speaking...
we're also...
Divorced.
Mmm.
The back of your neck
is so smooth.
My dad shaved it for me.
Oh, is he some kind of barber?
- Architect.
- Mmm.
Oh, how is the neck,
by the way?
Yeah, it's, erm, get...
Getting there.
I don't think
I've ever had the pleasure
of sleeping with an invalid
before.
Erm...
What?
I suppose I'm a bit, erm,
out of practice.
I'm also just
suddenly aware I...
I don't... I don't have any
kind of prophylactic on me.
Such low expectations.
Also,
by the way, erm...
My staff are desperate to know
if you get free Weetabix.
Well...
I can confirm to you
that on occasion,
I do have access
to complementary
Weetabix, yeah.
- Morning.
- Oh, er...
Adrienne Duvall.
We worked together
back in the day.
Oh.
And it made me realise,
well...
Quite so competitive?
I probably ought
to get going.
Why?
Who says?
I don't know.
Er, you're right.
I don't know why I said that.
I mean, unless you have
shit to do, then...
I have nothing.
But if you...
I mean, have shit to do,
then, you know...
I have nothing.
Thank you.
Hello.
How are you doing?
- Good, thank you.
- Hi.
Right, tasting time.
Are you a cheese person?
Mmm.
Do you like tapenade?
Okay, I'll... Thank you.
- Can I get these, please?
- Of course.
- And do you want a coffee?
- Sure, yeah.
Actually, that's not true.
A lot of it was
decidedly unhappy.
We were starting to maybe
think about children.
Then she got a position
in Sweden, which was...
Great for her.
So then we discussed it
and then we tried it,
me here, her there,
both of us going back
and forth depending.
And then eventually,
she just said, oh,
she didn't want to do that
any more.
I'm sorry.
Adrienne really wanted us
to start thinking
about family.
What did... What did you want?
Erm, I...
I guess there's a world
where...
Kids aren't really my thing.
Come on.
I'm gonna make you
the tastiest eggs
of your life.
Right.
Do you know the best way
to crack an egg?
Always on a flat surface.
What's the thinking
behind the two bowls?
Practically speaking,
it's much easier
to fish out a broken shell
from the one egg
rather than fishing it out
from eight eggs.
Mmm.
The versatility of the egg
knows no bounds.
Oh.
You said something to me,
erm...
Couple weeks ago.
You said... You said kids
aren't really your thing.
That's fine. I mean, no.
Of course, it...
Of course it is. Just, erm...
Truthfully, kids kind of
might be, maybe, or...
Are my thing.
And, erm...
At least I think
they might be, anyway.
And I... I hate...
Hate to even
have to, erm...
It's just diff...
It's just different, isn't it?
You know,
meeting someone at our age.
Whether we like it or not,
the clock is ticking.
I'm sorry,
but what the actual fuck
are you even talking about
right now?
Well...
It would seem to me preferable
to have a moderately-awkward
conversation right now
rather than a completely
destructive one
in five to ten years' time.
Firstly, I'm thirty-four,
not fifty-fucking-five,
so how about
we ease the fuck up on...
On the whole biological clock
bullshit thing?
And secondly,
I don't know, I'm, like,
"Back the fuck off."
And calm the fuck down.
What... What...
What's the rush?
Because I'm worried
that's there's a very distinct
and real possibility
that I am about
to fall in love with you.
I'm sorry,
I'm just not someone
who's interested in making
that kind of a promise.
And in fact, there's this
little bit of me that thinks,
"Fuck you" for even asking.
Hi.
How was work?
Er...
Yeah.
- How was bedtime?
- Yeah. It was fine.
We read Julian Is A Mermaid.
A lot.
So...
You know,
the day of your diagnosis,
you said something to me.
You said that
you would rather have
six fucking fantastic months
than 12...
Than 12 really shitty,
passive ones.
Yeah, passive ones.
At that time,
I was guilty of having
no coherent
or cohesive response
but what you said has really,
really stayed with me.
And I now do have a response
that I would like
to share with you.
Okay.
Erm...
I'm sorry.
"Although...
"Although in the past,
- "you have..."
- Mmm.
Erm...
- What the...
- It's all right.
Take your time.
- I'm nervous.
- It's okay.
Erm...
"Although...
"Although in the past,
you have, erm..."
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- It's all right. Shall I...
I'm sorry.
Here.
Fuck it. Let's do it.
Yeah, let's do it.
- That too much?
- Yes.
In for a heteronormative
penny, in for a pound.
♪ Balanced on desire ♪
♪ I cannot control ♪
♪ These ever-changing ways ♪
♪ So how can I be sure ♪
♪ The feeling will remain? ♪
♪ It'll always change ♪
♪ But everything I am ♪
♪ Is yours ♪
♪ Everything I am... ♪
Pizza.
Er, did anyone order a man
as well as a pizza?
I'll take him.
I, er...
- Weetabix?
- Hi.
- Oh.
- Well.
Welcome to my baby shower.
♪ Find it hard to say ♪
♪ What's going on inside... ♪
Apologies for the, erm...
Interruption?
I saw you the o...
The o... Last week,
I was passing
by the restaurant.
Erm...
And it made me realize,
well...
...two things.
First of which, I was still
quite angry with you
because although I might have
been somewhat insensitive,
you were rude to me,
which, yeah, a lot, hurt.
And the second thing,
I was guilty of
focusing on the wrong,
erm...
...thing, aspect.
Looking ahead
instead of right...
In front of me, at you.
I knew he was gonna do that.
So are you gonna catch
mommy's hair?
Perfect, yeah.
Open your little box.
Yeah.
Aw, that felt like a good one.
- Oh, yeah. Nice and clean.
- That sounded like...
- That's perfect!
- It's nice and...
That's it.
How much hair
do you wanna keep, mommy?
Yeah. Yeah, I got you.
- We're getting chunky now.
- Yeah, just do it.
- We're getting chunky.
- Oh, amazing.
Pat it down, Ells.
Good girl.
Hold that up there for me,
darling. Thank you.
- Well done, girly.
- Oh.
- Oh, lovely.
- Really nice.
- Really nice?
Whoa, okay.
Wow. Wow. Mmm.
Ooh, ooh.
- Aw.
You look beautiful.
Doesn't she look
so beautiful?
Sorry.
- Yes?
- Happy?
Yes.
Anywhere from
200 to 600 seated guests,
access to over four acres
of private gardens.
Wow.
Along with its own
secure car-parking area.
- Marble flooring.
- Wow.
Roman nobles.
Around about 120 guests,
expanding to around about 140
for your evening reception.
And the great hall is licensed
for music and entertainment.
Hear that, Ells?
- Ooh.
- Dancing.
Our conservatory
is licensed for
up to and including
160 guests...
...for a seated dinner.
Or 200...
Touch his bum.
...for a standing buffet.
Fairy lights, optional extra.
Have you seen the ceiling?
Though I should add
that the use of drones
is strictly prohibited.
This one's going
to take 20 minutes,
give or take, then we'll flush
out the system
and get you started
on number two.
Okay, thank you.
Right. Give us a shout
if you need anything.
Will do.
Chefs,
how are we all doing?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Technical bullshit.
Apologies, everyone,
for the delay.
Good news is, audience is in,
ready and raring.
So, er, just a little heads-up
from me.
Erm, I'll kick things off,
a little intro,
little bit about me,
little bit about my role as
Bocuse d'Or UK head coach.
Overview of the rules,
what's up for grabs today,
place at the European
semi-finals,
so on and so forth.
General frenzy-whipping.
Excitement. Good.
Any questions? Excellent.
All right, Chefs. Onwards.
- Hello, you.
- Hi! Hello.
- Good to see ya.
- Yeah.
- Congrats on the star.
- Same to you.
Yeah, well, I think
I'm a little
old hat at this point.
No.
This is Jade Khadime,
my commis.
- And the real deal.
- Hello, Jade.
Well, best of luck out there.
Excellent hair, by the way.
- Oh, thank you.
- Yes.
Er, just gonna pop to the loo.
Oh, fuck!
Chef!
Chef, they're ready for us.
It's fine, honestly.
Honestly, I'm fine.
I'm... I'm... I'm coming.
Chef, are you using?
What?
Chefs' circle of trust, Chef.
No.
No, I have stage three
ovarian cancer.
Do you want to call time
on the whole competing thing?
No, I do not.
Thank you.
Let's do it.
That's okay.
Is that right?
- Yeah, it's fine.
- That's brilliant.
All right.
Best of luck
out there, everyone.
♪ Darling, hold my hand ♪
♪ Oh, won't you
Hold my hand? ♪
Hi.
Penny for your thoughts.
- Hi. Hi.
- So.
I think I like this one
but I suspect I'm pretty easy
either way.
Could I sleep on it?
Yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
What?
What's going on?
Tired.
Okay.
Okay. Huh, mmm-hmm.
Oh, don't forget your, erm...
Waterproof.
- Hello.
- It's us!
Hi!
Okay, I'm gonna buzz you up.
They're here.
All right.
- Mama!
- Hello!
- I love that dress.
- Thank you.
Kind of matches, actually.
Sorry I haven't
brought you anything.
It's okay.
You brought me a baby.
- I brought you a baby.
- Ben, how are you?
Oh, sorry, babies.
Babies want attention. Hi, hi.
- Unbelievable.
- Hi, loves. Come on in.
- Wow!
- Thank you. Wow!
- It goes back so far.
- I know, and I have a bath.
- And a double bed.
- Ah, hi.
Go on.
- You've never been here.
- Really, so grown-up.
Have you? I've just realized.
- It's so cool.
- No, I haven't. No.
My goodness.
Look at the little...
Hi!
Sorry, didn't mean to, er...
- Hi, I'm so sorry.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Good to see you.
- I'm Almut's sister, Leah.
- I'm Reginald.
- That's my dad, yeah.
- Lovely to meet you.
Reginald,
it's a pleasure to meet you.
- It smells amazing.
- Thank you.
- Likewise.
- Hi, I'm Almut's brother,
- Lucas.
- Welcome, welcome.
Thank you, thank you.
Well, it's not my home, but
I'm welcoming everyone anyway.
Hey, I'm the other brother,
Ben.
- Hi. Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
You too.
- Thanks for this.
- Oh, pleasure.
Bea said we had to go
to Salt Lake.
She said, "You'll love it,"
she says.
And so... And so we're there
and it's winter.
It's... It's snowing.
It's beautiful and, erm,
we decide to visit
the Tabernacle.
- I don't know if you know it.
- Oh, yeah.
It's, erm...
Well, I don't even
know how late
and, er,
we've watched the sun go down.
And it's been the most...
You know,
the most wonderful day
of our entire fucking lives.
And I turned to her
and I said... I say...
"Bea, don't know about you,
"but I think this is how
"I'd like to spend
the rest of my life."
No ring, nothing, just...
- Said it.
- And what did she say?
"Don't be
so fucking sentimental."
"I don't need a roomful of
people and a piece of paper
"to know I want to spend
the rest of my life with you,"
- she said.
- Yeah.
- Amen.
So when were you... When were
you all in Salt Lake?
Erm, 15 years ago.
- Give or take.
- Business or pleasure?
What? What's going on?
I... I just happened to be in
a competition that year, so...
Happened, just...
- Don't.
- Competition?
What sort of a competition?
It was, erm...
I used to...
I used to figure-skate.
Erm... ISU World
Championships.
She was unbe-fucking-lievable.
I can't believe you haven't
told these guys this.
- Stop.
- It was, it was.
- Check it out.
- No.
- You have to see this,
- Reginald, it's...
- I'm speechless.
- ...absolutely remarkable.
- Here she goes.
Here she goes. Here she goes.
Oh!
- This is you?
- Yeah, watch this.
Oh!
Oh, my goodness me.
Stop. Stop, stop.
Please. I said no.
I said no.
- You should be proud.
- Yeah, bloody marvelous.
Thanks, mom.
Yeah.
Wine. Anyone for any wine?
You know
it isn't even just you?
Like, honest to God,
no one knows about it.
Thank you.
It was Dad
who got me into skating.
I think he actually really
wanted a sporty child and...
And I suppose
I was his last chance.
And I guess...
He was right to push me
because it turned out
I fucking loved it
and I was really good at it.
And in the beginning,
he would drive me to Swindon
virtually every weekend.
Hmm.
And then when he was ill,
when he was sick, I...
I wanted to help out and...
I took some time off from it.
And then...
After that,
skating without him around
was just joyless.
So you just stopped?
I think it just really
reminded me of him.
You okay?
- What?
- I think I'm gonna be sick.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa. Okay.
I'm cautiously optimistic
we're dealing with
an infection.
But, listen,
once the fluid is out,
we're gonna run some tests,
and if we find anything,
you'll be the first to know.
- Okay.
- In the meantime,
I'd like to get you started
with some antibiotics,
just to help with the pain.
- All right?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Okay?
- Thank you.
- Pleasure.
Tobias, I had a call
from the hospital.
They called to see if I could
come in, and so I did.
Speaking.
They said
it wasn't an infection.
What is it?
I've made notes.
Erm,
they are recommending
either a partial
or a full-blown hysterectomy.
Your note-taking is incredibly
thorough, by the way.
Every cloud...
All right,
so let me just check, I...
- Mmm-hmm.
- Option One would be...
If we ever want
to conceive naturally...
Freeze embryos.
Mmm.
- Followed by...
- Surgery.
So removing one ovary,
not both.
- Followed by...
- Chemo. Shit.
Shit ton of chemo.
- Followed by...
- Shagging.
Or, well, yeah, whatever. IVF.
Oh, I...
I vote shagging, but okay.
Alternatively, Option Two.
Way more invasive
but way lower risk of relapse.
Ovaries and uterus,
they take it.
They take it all.
Okay.
- I think...
- Listen... Oh, sorry.
- No. Do you want...
- No. No, you.
Okay.
I guess...
I think,
unless you think I'm...
Insane, I think I am inclined
to say that I would...
I would like to hang on
to at least one of my...
Fucking addled
cancer-ridden ovaries.
Because, well...
Just because I never,
in a general sense,
saw myself having kids,
doesn't mean
that there isn't a world
where I couldn't see myself,
in time,
deciding to have them
with you.
I'm in remission.
We should do something
to celebrate.
Come on! Come on!
- ...the throne or something.
- What?
No.
That serves you right.
- Everything's great!
- Everything's fine.
Wait, wait,
wait, wait!
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Ooh.
Breathe in.
One second.
Oh, fuck me.
Feeling relaxed and calm.
Almut?
Al? Almut?
Come on,
come on, come on, come on.
Oh.
I'm gonna get a drink.
That is...
Yes, £20 with the fuel.
Thank you. Cheers.
Thank you.
Hiya.
Oh, shit.
- Sorry. Thank you.
- Hiya.
- Hi, how are you?
- Yeah, good, thank you.
- There you go. Any fuel?
- Er, no.
Sorry.
Al?
Al? Al?
Sorry. One second, sorry.
Al?
- Mmm-hmm?
- Hi. Everything okay?
Hmm. Kind of.
- What?
- Erm...
Well, you see, I thought...
I thought I needed a poo.
- Yeah.
- And, er,
- now that I'm in here...
- Yeah?
...I think
I might need to push.
No. No, no. No, no.
No! Okay?
Sorry, but you can't push.
If you let me in, I can...
I can help.
We have biscuits now, Al.
We have biscuits, okay?
- Okay.
- Okay, come on. Let me in.
Oh, no, I can't.
What? Just un...
Unlock it and open it.
I can't. It's not happening.
It's not... It's not working.
Wait.
Sorry. I'm sorry. My, erm...
My partner is stuck
in the, erm...
Do you have the... For the...
The key for the...
- Yeah.
- So sorry, er...
- Thank you.
- Hey, Jane, I'll just...
Okay, Al, we have the key.
We have the key, don't worry.
It's okay. Sorry about this.
- No, no, it's fine.
- Thank you very much.
Okay.
Okay, just...
Just don't push, Al.
Whatever you do,
just don't pu...
Erm, it's just...
Got broken off.
Erm...
- So, Al?
- Yeah?
I'm gonna need you
to stand back, okay?
- What?
- Standing... Standing back
- away from the door.
- Wait, wait, wait. Why?
All the way back.
Right the way back. All right?
- Why?
- I'm so, so sorry.
I think she might be
about to give birth.
- Yeah, erm...
- Maybe...
I'll... I'll... I'm gonna get
Jane, 'cause she'll know...
Okay, get Jane.
Jane? Jane?
Jane, pregnant lady
stuck in the khazi.
- Just bear with me.
- Fine.
The key snapped in the...
- How many weeks?
- Forty.
Huh. Mazel tov.
Okay.
Keep standing back, Al.
- Shall I have a go?
- Yeah, yeah.
No, it's not. Nah.
Okay. Okay, Al,
still standing back?
Okay?
- Hi.
- I can't. I'm sorry.
What...
What do you mean, you can't?
Move. I can't. I'm sorry.
I can feel it.
- No.
- Mmm.
- No, I know, but we can't.
We have to... We don't...
Not... Not here.
- We... We don't... It's not...
- Mmm, listen to me.
- It's not safe.
- It's just coming. It is.
It is. It's coming.
I can feel it. I can feel it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry but I... It's...
This is...
It's it. It's it. It's it.
Yeah, it seems like we have
almost everything we need.
Except for a midwife.
- Except for a midwife.
- Yeah.
Ooh. Ah. Ah.
Is that a push I hear there?
Yeah, I think this might...
This might be a push.
- Do you wanna push?
- Yeah.
- Yes, she wants to push.
Watch your head. Watch
your head. Watch your head.
Understood, yeah.
She... She... She can push.
Al, Al, I'm gonna have
to check again
to see if I can see any
body parts. Is that okay?
I'm not exactly in a position
to say no, am I?
Okay.
- Yes, I can see the head.
- Wait, what?
- What? Tobias?
- Shh. Erm... Sorry.
- Wait, no, I'm sorry, no.
- Tobias? Tobias?
Sorry, wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Okay, listen to me.
You've got this.
- A head?
- Sorry, sorry.
I'm gonna put you on
speakerphone.
Hold on one second.
Can you, can you, can you...
- Dig deep, babe.
- I got it.
- Thank you. Sorry, still here.
- Hello?
Can you say
that last bit again, please?
With each contraction,
place the palm of your hand...
Listen,
you're doing brilliantly.
...against the vagina
and apply firm
but gentle pressure
- to keep baby's head...
- To keep baby inside?
- No.
- No, Christ!
- No, please do not do that.
- No.
You do not want to keep
- the baby inside.
- Right.
You want to apply firm
but gentle pressure
to keep baby's head
from delivering too fast
and tearing.
Sorry. Sorry. Understood, yes.
Understood.
- Oh, my God.
- Do you understand?
Yes, yes, got it now. Sorry.
How is mom doing now?
How's mom doing now?
Oh. Tell her it feels like
a huge fucking lump
between my legs.
She says it feels like she's
got a lump between her legs.
- A huge fucking lump.
- I'm sorry.
A huge fucking lump
between her legs.
Yeah.
Is there anyone else
there with you?
Yeah, we're actually...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
I don't know their names.
- Er, Sanjaya.
- Sanjaya.
- Jane, hi.
- Hi.
Could one of you
do me a favour
and go and make sure...
...the front door is unlocked
and open?
Yeah. It's a...
It's a petrol station.
Yeah, it's a petrol station.
You just walk straight in.
Ooh, I can feel it,
I can feel it.
The head, it's coming.
It's coming.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
Whoa-ho!
Lean into me. That's it.
There's a face!
I mean, a head.
There's a head! It's great.
Head's out.
- Oh, my God!
- You're amazing.
Yeah, she's doing great.
She is. She's doing great.
You're doing great.
You're doing so fucking great!
Oh, my God!
All right, yes!
Got the shoulders.
Shoulders are out.
That's it.
Yes. That's it. That's it.
Ah. Oh. She's out.
- Yes, yes! You did it!
- Oh! Oh, my God. She is?
That's great.
That's fantastic.
Is baby crying, Dad?
Is baby breathing?
Both.
- Both.
- We did it!
- Wow!
You are incredible.
What I need you to do now,
is get a clean towel
and gently wipe
and dry baby off, okay, Dad?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Nose and mouth first.
- All right?
- She's gorgeous.
- Yeah, okay.
- Can I see her?
- Yeah, she's coming.
Can you put that towel
underneath for me?
Can I see her?
I have to see her.
- She's coming. She's coming.
- Oh, my God. There she is.
Thank you, Sanjaya.
- Hi.
- That's your mommy.
That's your mommy.
I can hear her. You did say
"her", didn't you, "she"?
Her. She.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Congratulations, Mom and Dad.
Now, I need you to make sure
baby is wrapped in a towel,
okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
- Can you do that for me, Dad?
Ah.
Without pulling the cord
too tight,
I want you to put baby
in mom's arms, all right?
Al, Al, Al.
And I'm gonna need you
to make sure
that mom and baby
are kept warm, okay?
- Yeah.
- Hi.
- I've got you.
- Yeah.
Oh, my God. Hi!
Oh, she's beautiful!
Thanks, Jane.
Shh.
Dad, I've got some good news.
Ambulance should be with you
any minute now, all right?
Okay.
In the meantime, contractions
might start up again, okay...
Do you want the... Yeah.
...because mom's got
to deliver the placenta,
so I'm going to need you to
try and keep her nice and calm
- and warm. Okay?
- Yeah.
Okay, I can do that.
Yeah.
Happy New Year.
...Happy New Year...
Not only have we been
unable to shrink the tumor,
but in fact the disease
seems to have metastasised.
Which means, I'm afraid,
we're still not in a position
to operate.
But there are plenty of
reasons to remain positive.
Other treatment options
are still available.
Failure first time around has
almost no bearing whatsoever
on the likelihood
of second-line success.
It's fine. I'm fine.
I'm okay. It's okay, honestly.
Yeah.
It's okay not to be okay.
It's a lot.
You've been through a lot,
both of you.
Gosh. Christ.
Sorry.
Oh, my God. Are you sure?
Not exactly haute cuisine.
Thank you.
Oh. Thanks.
What did you go for?
Twix.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
- What about you?
- Bounty.
When in Rome.
Meant to ask, erm...
I have a feeling my 4:00
is gonna overrun.
I don't suppose
there's any chance you might
be able to do pick-up?
Erm, only if
you have the time.
- Definitely.
- Thank you. That'd be great.
Pleasure.
Okay, so that is
15 minutes over.
Fuck.
Sixteen.
Fuck, fuck. It's fucked. Stop.
It's fucked. It's... We're...
We're still far
too fucking slow on the prep.
And this whole
sous vide situation
- is fucking killing us!
- All right. All right. Easy.
Let's take five.
No, I don't wanna
take a break.
I don't wanna take five.
I wanna go back to the start.
I need to look at the plans.
I need to look at the timings.
I need to figure this shit
the fuck out.
Sick of this shit!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's take a break.
Let's take five.
Right, what's next?
- Octopus?
- Yep.
Where the hell were you?
You said you were gonna
- do pick-up.
- I was in the restaurant.
- Oh, my God.
- No.
You weren't in the restaurant,
cos I spoke to Skye.
She didn't know where the hell
you were either.
Was everything okay
with the... With the pick-up?
No, not particularly.
Jesus.
I was this close to calling
round A&E departments.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Erm...
I'm in training
for the Bocuse d'Or.
Hmm.
- Beg your pardon?
- Not... Not the final.
Just the Euros.
We, erm... We won the UK heat.
How long?
- Huh?
- How long have you been
prioritising fucking cooking
instead of getting better?
Er, the UK heat
was back in October
and the, er, Euro qualifiers
are coming up soon.
Do... Do the hospital know?
Did they, erm...
Did you... Please.
Please. Please tell me that...
That they, erm,
and that you...
What difference does it make
if they know?
Oh, grow up, will you, Almut?
You have cancer.
You have cancer, Al.
No, you grow up,
you fucking dick.
The difference
this could make is...
It's vast.
Why?
Why are you taking the risk?
- Isn't it obvious?
- No, actually, it's not.
- Not to me.
- I'm... I'm not exactly
gonna get the chance again,
am I?
What is that supposed to mean?
In what reality...
It means I'm not
particularly interested
in dying with fuck all
to show for it.
Oh, okay.
So we're not...
We're not enough for you?
Is that...
Is that what it is?
Award-winning chef
cum-former
figure-skating nutcase...
No, now
you're just being mean.
No, no, no. No, I'm not.
I'm... I'm honestly...
I'm trying to understand
what it is that motivates
an otherwise perfectly sane...
Of course you factor
into my thinking, you fuck!
Okay, so, then,
I don't understand.
I'm sorry.
But, I really...
Honest to God, I don't.
Maybe... I mean, Jesus!
I mean,
did it ever occur to you
that maybe I don't wanna just
be someone's dead fucking mom?
I mean, at this point
nothing terrifies me more
than the thought of having her
having nothing whatsoever
to remember me by.
And it's like there's this...
This bit of me
that is fucking desperate
for her to know
that I didn't just give up.
And wouldn't it be
quite the thing
if maybe one day she decided
to look back on this time,
she actually chose
to look back
on this entire godforsaken
episode and thought,
"Wow, that's my mom"?
I don't...
I don't want my relationship
with Ella
to be solely defined
by my decline.
Or maybe
I actually just can't bear
the thought
of being forgotten.
I'm not sure which is worse.
Wanting us to remember
your achievements
is one thing.
Wanting us to somehow remember
your achievements
that we have absolutely
no fucking knowledge of...
Okay, I get it, I fucked up.
I fucked up. Please stop.
Please.
Please stop going on about it.
When is it?
The thing?
The European qualifying,
what... Whatever?
June.
June?
June the, erm...
It's the 5th and 6th of June.
Oh, right.
I'm so sorry, Tobias.
I am.
Aerodynamic, innit?
Chef, I think
I might be about to throw up.
Oh, shit. Erm, do you...
Do you have a buck...
Can I have a bucket?
Like a cup, or...
Okay, there you go.
Okay.
- Better?
- Oui, Chef.
Sometimes, Chef,
inside just wants out.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- Let's do it.
♪ I get a good feeling, yeah ♪
♪ Get a feeling that I never
Never knew before ♪
♪ I get a good feeling, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, oh, sometimes... ♪
Please welcome
the United Kingdom,
Almut Bruhl and Jade Khadim.
Come on, England!
I can't hear you!
Impressive start
with a plate presentation.
Please welcome Norway.
Vigo Hansen and Soren Hansen.
Come on, you Brits!
Ready, go.
Here we go.
United Kingdom.
Start!
That's your mom.
- Team UK! Team UK!
- Go on, Team UK!
Come on, GB!
Okay, let's get them out.
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, coming.
Here we go.
- Thank you.
- Well done.
Good.
Let's go, mom!
Let's go, Almut!
Whoa.
Go, go, go...
Team United Kingdom,
thirty seconds to finish.
Let's go, Almut!
- Keep going!
- Down to the wire, guys!
Couple more seconds. Come on!
Ten, nine, eight...
Seven, six, five, four,
three, two, one.
Yes! All right!
- All right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah.
One, two, three.
- United Kingdom!
- Well done, well done.
She did it. She did it.
I did it.
Amazing.
I love you.
Chef?
I'll see you soon, Chef.
Oh. Hi.
Come on.
Let's go.
Ready? And we're off.
Turning.
It's good.
Ooh.
Ooh!
- Okay. Watch mommy.
- Okay.
There she goes.
Bye, mommy!
Bye!
Mwah!
Okay.
Let's put them on the table, yeah?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cos it's egg time.
Hi, Belinda. Hi, Barry.
How's that look?
- Good?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- In the basket.
- Yep.
In the basket, please.
Check that one for me, please,
egg-checker.
How many eggs do you want, darling?
Five.
You can have as many
as you want. Five is good.
- Yep.
- Oh, yeah, check that.
- Yep. Yep.
One, two, jump. What a jump!
Okay, do you remember
the best way to crack an egg?
Always on a flat surface, yeah?
- Yeah.
- And then in there.
That goes in there.
You want to try?
You got it. You got it.
Open that a bit there.
Ah, yeah, you did it.
Stop.
Perfect.
No shells.
There's no shells?
- Okay, so next...
- Yeah?
Bye-bye.
Bye.
♪ My defense is down ♪
♪ I want you to surround me ♪
♪ Anytime I go out ♪
♪ You're still the only sound
that I hear ♪
♪ You've taken me
to higher ground ♪
♪ I'm never coming down ♪
♪ Even when we're in a crowd ♪
♪ It's like
there's no one else around ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ Hope the way
I feel tonight ♪
♪ Is the way I ♪
♪ Feel ♪
♪ For life ♪
♪ Is the way I ♪
♪ Feel ♪
♪ For life ♪
♪ I know it gets hard ♪
♪ We both know
we're still learning ♪
♪ Still learning ♪
♪ Let your troubles out ♪
♪ They will never
be a burden ♪
♪ You put your trust in me ♪
♪ I'll show you I deserve it ♪
♪ All I ever need ♪
♪ Is right under
your surface ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ Hope the way
I feel tonight ♪
♪ Is the way I ♪
♪ Feel ♪
♪ For life ♪
♪ Is the way I ♪
♪ Feel ♪
♪ For life ♪
♪ Listen to me ♪
♪ Oh, me ♪
♪ There's something
I've not told you ♪
♪ I'm on your team ♪
♪ Your team ♪
♪ But I can't
always coach you ♪
♪ There's no in-between ♪
♪ Between ♪
♪ I want the truth only ♪
♪ Could you love me wholly ♪
♪ I know it gets hard ♪
♪ We both know
we're still learning ♪