- What was that?
- Nothing.
- Okay, just give me one little hint.
- No. No hints.
We're almost there.
Okay, I'm going to take this off.
No, no, no.
Hey, you said you like surprises.
Yeah, I do. When I know what they are.
You're going to love it.
Promise.
- Yeah. I already love the view.
- Ha-ha.
♪ Love is a burning thing ♪
♪ And it makes a fiery ring ♪
♪ Bound by wild desire... ♪
All right. Here we are.
♪ I fell into a ring of fire... ♪
Watch your step. Watch your step.
I can't see.
Okay. Move forward. Stop.
Now taking it off...
Now.
Are you kidding?
How? I didn't even know
this place was open yet.
I pulled some favors
and I got us on the list
for opening night.
Wow. Uh...
Are you sure I'm dressed all right?
You look like a million bucks.
Come on.
♪ And it burns burns burns
The ring of fire ♪
♪ The ring of fire ♪
Hey!
Don't steal coins from the fountain.
It's bad luck.
- Sorry, sir.
- Go on.
Smile.
- Here's your ticket.
- Thank you.
Hello, sir.
- Would you like a photo?
- Thank you.
Oh...
Watch your step, everyone.
You coming?
Uh, we'll take the next one.
Ah, come on. We can fit you in.
Thanks.
Going up.
Oh, excuse me.
Sorry. It does that sometimes.
Some fun facts
about the Sky View Tower.
It's 494 feet tall
and weighs over 9,000 tons.
It's made of steel
and reinforced concrete and glass.
And even more impressive,
the entire project
was completed five months
ahead of schedule.
Is that a good thing?
Wow.
What did I tell you?
- Fancy.
- Yes?
May I help you?
We have a reservation. Campbell.
Oh, I'm sorry,
but we're already over capacity
for opening night.
We cannot accommodate you.
If you wouldn't mind
just stepping aside.
Thank you so much.
It's okay. I worked it out with Jake.
Is he here? I could speak with...
We let Jake go this morning.
Thank you so much.
- What's going on?
- One second, one second. Um...
Sir, I know you're a very important man,
but you think maybe
you could help me out...
Please.
You're tearing me apart.
But I'm sorry, I can't help you.
Now, if you wouldn't mind...
Oh, Mr. Fuller! How nice to see you.
We have a lovely table for you.
Thank you. This way, please.
- Let's go to the bar.
- What?
Just act natural.
Wow.
Wow. Look at that view.
Mm-mm.
What?
Oh, no.
You're scared of heights.
What? Oh, no. I'm just...
I've just never been this high up
before.
I'm so sorry. This night's
turning into such a disaster.
I really wanted it to be perfect.
Hey.
It is perfect.
Because I'm with you.
You okay?
- I think I'll live.
- Yeah?
Hey, look, free champagne.
That's my favorite kind.
Coming right up.
♪ Got the feelin' I'm a-fall in' ♪
♪ Like a star up in the blue ♪
♪ Like I was fallin' off Niagara ♪
♪ In a paddle boat canoe ♪
♪ I got to feeling I'm a-fall in' ♪
♪ And it's all because of you ♪
- Okay.
- Um, I'll be right back.
Excuse me. Where's the ladies' room?
Other side of the dance floor.
♪ I thought that love
could never touch me ♪
♪ Yeah, I was riding high ♪
♪ And then my ivory tower toppled ♪
♪ And then I tumbled from the sky ♪
♪ I got to feeling I'm a-fall in' ♪
♪ Lover, you're the reason why ♪
♪ You're the reason why ♪
Thank you.
We'll be right back.
Hi, sweetie.
Is everything all right?
I'm fine. Thank you.
How far along are you?
What?
Oh. No. I'm not...
Um...
I don't know, exactly.
Maybe one or two months.
That's wonderful news.
Isn't it?
I haven't told my boyfriend yet.
Does he love you?
Yes.
Then he won't let go.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Bye.
Okay. It's almost over.
Okay.
Oh.
There you are.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I think so.
Come on.
Let's get some fresh air.
- I really need...
- Sorry, I wanted to...
Uh... You go first.
Okay.
Um...
I was going to do this at dinner,
but seeing as we have this view...
Hey!
Don't throw that penny.
It could kill somebody.
Oh, I'm so sorry. Of course. Yeah.
Fat ass.
Um... These past few years...
have been absolutely magical.
And that's, uh... that's because of you.
Iris, I want to spend
the rest of my life with you.
You mean with us?
What?
Sorry.
I...
I'm the luckiest guy in the world.
What? You're not upset?
Are you kidding me? No, this is...
- this is incredible.
- Really?
We're going to start a family.
Um... So, will you?
Oh, uh... Yes.
Mm, uh...
- Is it too tight?
- Uh... It's perfect.
Hey. Let's go celebrate.
♪ Well... ♪
- ♪ You know you make me wanna ♪
- ♪ Shout ♪
- ♪ Kick my heels up and ♪
- ♪ Throw my hands up and ♪
- ♪ Shout ♪
- ♪ Throw my head back and
- ♪ Come on now ♪
- ♪ Shout ♪
♪ Don't forget to say you will ♪
♪ Don't forget to say yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Say you will ♪
♪ Say it right now, little baby ♪
♪ Come on, come on ♪
♪ Say you will ♪
- ♪ Say it, oh ♪
- ♪ Say you will ♪
♪ Come on now ♪
- ♪ Say that you love me ♪
- ♪ Say ♪
- ♪ Come on now ♪
- ♪ You know you make me wanna ♪
- ♪ Shout ♪
- ♪ Lift my heels up and shout ♪
♪ Throw my head back and... ♪
♪ Shout, shout ♪
- ♪ A little bit softer now ♪
- ♪ Shout ♪
♪ A little bit softer now
A little bit softer now ♪
♪ A little bit louder now
A little bit louder now ♪
- ♪ A little bit louder now ♪
- ♪ Shout ♪
- ♪ Hey-hey-hey-hey ♪
♪ Jump up and shout now
Jump up and shout now ♪
♪ Everybody, shout now
♪ Everybody, shout, shout
Shout, shout, shout ♪
♪ Shout, shout, shout
♪ Raindrops keep falling on my head ♪
♪ But that doesn't mean ♪
♪ My eyes will soon be turning red ♪
Paul! Grab my hand! Pull up!
- Hold on!
- No!
Stay back!
- No, stay back!
- Wait! Help!
Paul! Grab my hand!
No!
Subtitle | www.movieddl.me
Everyone down the stairs!
Out of my way! Children first!
Single file!
Oh my God!
To the elevator!
Excuse me, ma'am.
Please. I need to get to the controls.
Move!
Let me in.
Please, sir. Step back.
We're already over capacity!
I swear to God, move!
Let me in! Ah!
Help, please! Please!
Grab on!
Help!
Hey.
Come here.
Well...
I realize vector multiplication
is scary,
but it's not that scary.
All right, that's it for today.
We'll start prepping
for the final next week.
Ms. Reyes.
We need to talk.
Yeah.
We're going to start a family.
Don't throw that penny.
It could kill somebody.
Everyone down the stairs!
Oh, this dream is ruining my life.
Mine too.
Every night, Stef.
God, I'm not getting any sleep.
Shit, I'm sorry.
Um, can I tell you something?
Yeah, what's up?
So, the woman in my dream.
Her name is Iris, right?
Okay.
That was my grandmother's name.
I, uh... I think I'm dreaming about her.
Are you serious?
Yeah. The thing is,
I never even met her.
I don't even know if she's alive.
Okay, well...
either go home
and find out about Grandma
and hope that stops the dreams,
or stay here
and die in your sleep for real.
Because I will murder you.
I'm sorry.
- Yeah, yeah, okay.
- Love you.
Yeah. Love you too.
- Go home.
- Yeah.
Quietly.
Okay.
- Hey, there she is!
- Hey, Dad.
Welcome home, sweetie.
So glad you're here.
- Yeah, me too.
- I missed you so much.
I know.
Oh, so great to see you.
- Thank you, thank you.
- Let me take that for you.
Hey, sorry.
Charlie took your room a while ago
and my files are in his room,
so I made up the pullout for you.
Is that okay?
Yeah, yeah.
No, that sounds totally fine.
Uh, hey, do we still have that box
of Mom's old stuff?
It had, uh, some photos,
like an address book
with phone numbers in it.
Uh, why do you want that?
Oh, it's not a big deal.
I just thought I saw it
lying around here somewhere.
Stefani, what's going on?
Okay, this is going to sound
really, really weird,
but I just need to find Mom's mom, Iris.
Uh, okay. Yeah, that is weird.
And you know,
I got rid of those boxes years ago
after your mom left.
Oh, hi, Charlie.
Hey.
Um, "Hi, Stef. How are you?
It's so nice to see you."
Yeah, sure.
Uh, I'm going to the cousins'.
Whoa. Now?
Look, your sister just got home.
- I thought we...
- Well, I had plans.
Actually, you know what?
I can drive you.
I was wanting to see them anyways.
It's fine.
Hey. If you're going
to see your cousins,
please don't talk about Iris
to Uncle Howard.
Yeah. Yeah, no problem.
All right.
- Bye. Love you.
- Love you too.
Charlie?
Charlie... Can you just take
these out, please?
Ow. Stef!
I'm trying to talk to you.
What's your problem?
What?
You haven't said anything
this entire time.
Wha...
Stef, why are you here?
I mean, you only come home for holidays.
Okay, I have to tell you something.
But you have to promise not to tell Dad.
What, are you pregnant?
No, I'm not pregnant, Charlie.
- I don't know.
- Why would you even...?
That's not... I mean, you're in college.
Okay, can you just promise me
you won't tell Dad?
- Why would I tell Dad?
- It's serious, Charlie.
All right.
Okay. Um...
I am on academic probation.
Whoa.
What? Charlie, stop laughing!
If I don't get my grades up...
It's kind of a big moment for me.
This is kind of funny.
Straight A's. You're a class president.
Miss Valedictorian
is failing out of school.
Charlie, it's not funny.
If I don't get my grades up,
I will lose my scholarship.
Oh.
- That blows. Sorry.
- Mm-hmm.
What happened?
I mean, I can't sleep.
Every time I close my eyes,
I have this same recurring
nightmare about Iris.
Our grandmother. I don't...
I mean, it has to mean something.
I don't know.
I dream weird things.
I dreamed a hot dog ate me last night.
What? That is...
Like the hot dog was eating me.
Okay.
Dude, can you just do something?
Dude, calm down, all right?
- We'll find him.
- Just move a little bit.
I can't pause, all right?
It's an online match. Are you serious?
- I have to look under this.
- Can you do me a kindness? Fuck off.
You remember
what happened last time?
It's a ranked match!
- What's going on?
- I can't find Paco.
Dude, again?
Wait, who's Paco?
No way! Hey, cuz!
Oh my gosh. Hey, can you help us look?
And just watch your feet
where you're stepping.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
I just...
I got to talk to your dad first.
What the fuck you doing home?
Oh, dude, she's flunking out of school.
- Charlie.
- Hey, welcome to the club.
Erik, dude, have you looked anywhere?
Paco's not upstairs!
- Oh. But look who's down here.
- Hi, Julia.
- Oh my gosh. I'm so sorry...
- How you been?
- Charlie!
- Jules!
There's my little Romeo.
So, wait, how did
the promposal with Jenny go?
- Dude, she said yes.
- Oh my God. Stop. Okay, wait.
Who's, uh... Who's Jenny?
Oh, he met her in junior lifeguards.
Junior lifeguards?
Charlie, I didn't know
you were doing junior lifeguards.
You didn't tell me that.
Okay, so what are you going to wear?
Um, I'm just going
to keep it simple.
- You know, black blazer...
- Okay, yeah, yeah.
- ...but with like a fun bow tie.
- I like it.
Stef! Stefani! Oh my gosh!
- Hi, honey.
- Hi, Aunt Brenda.
- How long are you here for?
- Not long.
Is Uncle Howard around?
Yeah. Yeah, he's out back. I'll get him.
Howard! Stefani's here. Come in!
Great!
You look a little tired.
Is everything okay?
- Oh.
- Stefi! Look at you!
- Hey!
- Come here, come here.
Oh, sweetie.
Oh, so good to see you.
Hey, are you hungry?
I was just gonna make some lunch.
No, actually.
I came here
because I wanted to talk to you
about your mother, Iris.
I know you don't
like to talk about her...
There's not much to tell.
Hey, kids, come on, lunch!
It's just that I've been having
this recurring nightmare about her.
Oh, honey.
It's probably just stress.
You should try Melatonin.
Okay, but the weird thing is
I've been dreaming about a real place
from 50 years ago.
It was like a restaurant
called the Sky View.
You know what it is.
Did Iris tell you about it?
What did she say? Did she say anything?
Maybe if I could talk to her...
Talk to who?
Oh, Stefis dreaming about Grandma Iris.
- Ooh, Psycho Granny?
- I thought she was dead.
Well, she's dead to us.
Yeah, Stefi.
Iris Campbell is a very deeply
disturbed woman. End of story.
Look, if I could just talk to her,
then maybe
I can get these dreams to stop.
- Stef, just drop it.
- I don't get it.
- What happened that was so bad?
- For one thing,
she's the reason
that your mother is so screwed up.
- What?
- Look, I just don't want to
talk about this anymore. Okay?
Uncle Howard, please.
I just need to know.
Look, Stefi.
After our father died...
Iris just snapped.
She wouldn't let us go to school.
She locked us inside the house.
She obsessed about all the horrific ways
we could die.
And eventually it got so bad,
I mean, so bad,
that the State came in
and they took your mother and I
away from her.
But it didn't end there.
She tracked us all through foster care,
and when the kids were born,
she started sending us
these horrible letters
that were full of obituaries
and these disturbing pictures
of dead bodies.
We had to move
so she couldn't contact us anymore.
So, uh...
Do you still have
any of those letters though?
Stefi.
Listen to me.
That woman is a sick
and dangerous person.
And for your well-being and your safety,
stay the hell away from her.
Uh...
I found Paco!
Oh! Thank God!
I'm sure he'd love to be
in the living room right now.
- He was in the pantry.
- Come on, guys. Let's go.
How did he even get in there?
I need you to help me.
You heard your uncle. Just let it go.
Just let it go.
You don't understand.
My whole life is falling apart
because of this dream.
And not only that,
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
Please, you are the only person
who can help me.
Howard would never forgive me
if I put you in touch with Iris.
Please.
Whatever you do,
do not look in the bottom drawer
of the dining room cabinet.
Hi. Um...
I'm here to see Iris Campbell.
Did you not see the signs?
Uh... Yeah. Yes, I did, but...
Then get the fuck out of here.
No visitors.
I'm your granddaughter.
Stefani.
Empty your pockets.
Phone, keys, everything.
Well, I'm not dangerous.
It's not you I'm afraid of.
Uh...
Come in slowly.
Shut the door. Quick, quick, quick!
Don't move.
Oh my God.
It really is you.
I can see your mother in you.
Hi. I'm Stefani...
Stop! Stop. Don't move.
Not until I tell you.
Trying to trick me, aren't you?
Getting me
to let my guard down.
I...
There you go. Come on.
Come here. Sit.
Okay. Um...
Sit.
That's it.
So, how is Darlene?
- Your mom okay?
- Oh. Uh...
No. Uh, I don't know.
She, uh... she left when I was ten,
so we don't see her anymore.
Oh.
But you saw my letters.
That's why you're here, right?
No. Um...
I'm actually here because
I've been dreaming about the Sky View.
- What?
- Yeah.
Yeah, every single night
for the past two months.
It's the same dream.
In it, you're on a date,
but then the dance floor breaks
and then there's an explosion
and then you...
Fall. And die.
Yeah. Yeah, everyone dies.
It wasn't just your dream.
It was my premonition.
Years ago, at the Sky View,
I got a glimpse into the future
and saw what Death was about to do.
I was going to do this at dinner,
but seeing as we have this view...
Hey! Don't throw that penny.
It could kill somebody.
Oh, I'm so sorry. Of course.
Fat ass.
These past few years
have been absolutely magical.
And that's all because of you.
No, no, no. I...
This isn't right. I...
Is that a no?
Everyone's going to die.
No, the whole building
is going to come down.
Are you serious?
- The penny.
- Iris?
- Give me that!
- What the hell, lady?
- Give it to me!
- What are you doing?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
♪ Well... ♪
Iris?
- ♪ You know you make me wanna ♪
- ♪ Shout ♪
- ♪ Kick my heels up and ♪
Move!
- ♪ Throw my head back and ♪
- ♪ Shout ♪
- ♪ Come on now ♪
♪ Don't forget to say you will ♪
♪ Don't forget to say yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Stop playing! Stop playing!
Everyone needs
to get off the dance floor!
The glass is about to break.
Everyone needs to get off now!
- Ma'am.
- Wait! No!
Get off the dance floor!
- Iris!
- You need to get off!
Get off!
I saved a lot of lives
that night.
Lives that were never meant to be saved.
They closed the restaurant after that.
Said it needed additional renovations.
But it never reopened.
Eventually they tore it down.
Wait, so you stopped the disaster.
Yes.
But Death doesn't like it
when you fuck with his plans.
So, over the years, he came back
and he killed everyone
who was there that night.
Including my Paul.
Wait a minute. I'm sorry. Did you...
Did you say Death came back?
He's a relentless son of a bitch.
Won't stop until he finishes the job,
but I taught myself
how to see him coming.
To anticipate his every move.
I've been keeping him at bay
for years now.
But now he's got me. Cancer.
Oh. Uh...
- Believe that shit?
- Sorry.
Got the diagnosis two months ago.
Wait, that's when
I started having my dream.
See? It's a sign.
Okay, but why am I dreaming
about what you saw?
Maybe my cancer
passed my premonition onto you.
Maybe it's fate's demented
sense of humor.
Who the hell knows.
What matters
is that when the Universe speaks,
you pay attention.
I see you, you fuck.
- Um... Who are you talking to?
- Death.
He thinks I'm distracted
because you're here.
I have to teach you
everything in this book.
It'll take some time
to learn the basics,
so you'll need to stay here.
Stay here?
The outside world is too dangerous.
I haven't stepped out there in 20 years.
In here, we can be safe.
Oh.
See that?
Yeah.
This is all my research.
My life's work.
Look, I'm sorry. I can't stay here.
I have to get back to school,
but, you know,
I'll come back and I'll visit.
No, I'm sick!
I won't be alive that long.
You can't leave.
Don't you see?
Death is coming for our family.
Uh...
You don't believe me.
No. Um... I think I made a mistake.
I think it was probably just a dream.
No, wait. At least take the book.
Stefani!
Stefani! Stop!
Look, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have come here.
This book is a lifeline.
It will show you
everything you need to know
to keep our family safe.
You still don't believe me.
Step back.
What? Why?
Seeing is believing.
Hey, Stef. Her face
really explode right in front of you?
- Erik! Just leave her alone.
- I'm...
It's my bad, Stef. I'm just curious.
Hey. How are you holding up?
I'm sorry, Uncle Howard.
You were right about Iris.
I... I never should've went there.
Honey, there's no need to apologize.
I'm so sorry you had to go through that.
She said something to me
before she died.
She said Death was coming
for our family.
That's crazy, right?
Oh my God.
I can't believe it.
I emailed her.
I just didn't think she'd show up. I...
Come on.
Is that, um...
Is that Mom?
Yeah.
Darlene!
- Wow.
- Um...
I can come back.
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
Come on.
Get down here. Come here.
Think she'll come
to the barbecue?
Stef. Hey, wait up.
If she's going
to Uncle Howard's house, then I'm not.
You can get a ride with Dad.
Uh...
You're not even going to talk to her?
Come on.
You don't remember her like I do.
- Just give her a chance.
- Why?
Charlie, she abandoned us
and now she rolls in here
after all these years,
and wants to act like nothing happened?
Yeah. Because who would do that? Right?
Wait. What?
- Nothing. Forget it.
- No.
No. What's that supposed to mean?
I tried calling you
so many times and nothing.
Same with Julia.
You used to be best friends.
You don't even talk anymore.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I've just been distracted
the last couple of months
because of this nightmare.
Okay, but what about before that?
It's been like this ever since you left.
You're mad at Mom,
but you haven't been around either.
I'm not like her!
Okay?
I'm not crazy.
Yeah, you're right. You're not crazy.
You just don't care.
Now you got it. Watch out for splinters.
Hey, there she is!
Hey!
Come here. So glad you made it.
You know, I didn't think
you were actually going to come.
Thank you for inviting me.
Of course. Come on in.
Hey, everybody! Come on! Come on over!
- I made cookies.
- That's great!
- Can I try one?
- Yes, of course.
- Does this have peanut butter?
- Yeah.
Are you trying
to kill my brother?
- Oh my God. Bobby's allergic.
- Yeah.
I totally forgot.
I'm so sorry.
You know, the most important thing
is that you're here, so...
Uh, Bobby Bartender, drinks!
Drinks all around!
Family.
You don't get to pick the one you get,
just got to love the one that you got.
Now, our mother...
she lived alone
until the day that she died.
And her death should
be a reminder to all of us
to enjoy life
and spend the time
that we have together.
Because we're not going to get any back.
- I love you guys.
- Aw.
Cheers to that! Cheers!
This is strong.
What did you put in there?
Julia? Oh, Jules!
Are you all right?
Oh my God.
There was a bug in there. Ugh.
Extra protein.
You on?
Oh.
- I got it.
- I don't think you've got it.
Oh, it's coming.
Actually, I'm starting
a new life guarding job.
- That's great.
- Yeah.
Charlie!
Get up here!
Jeez! Whoa!
- Erik!
- Ma, grill's ready.
Mm.
Mind if I join you?
Have a seat. Take a load off.
Oh, yeah. There we go.
It's quite the setup
you've got here.
Well, I wanted the kids
to have a happy childhood.
Unlike some people I know.
You're not talking about us, are you?
- Oh, no.
- We had a great childhood.
- Mm-hmm.
- I mean, look at me.
I turned out... fabulous.
Yep.
Huh.
Howard.
- What?
- Come on. What is that?
It looks like a house key to me.
Come on.
You know we've got the spare room.
I know.
And it's got to be better
than bouncing around trailer parks.
I don't think this is a good idea.
It's never too late for a second chance.
I'm sorry.
They're better off without me.
Pick up, pick up. Come on.
Okay, wait,
you bounce me or I bounce you?
You're bouncing me,
you're bouncing me.
Hey, Dad!
Come show us your back flip!
- What? No, no, no.
- Yeah, come on, Uncle Howard!
- Come on, Howard!
- Howard! Howard! Howard!
Help him up, help him up.
Thank you.
- Oh, yeah!
- There you go.
Stop stalling.
What's the worst thing
that could happen?
All right. Here we go. Watch out.
Wait! Stop!
- Oh, nice catch, Aunt D. All right.
- All right, here we go.
- Okay, Dad.
- Let's do it.
- Stay away from that edge.
- Come on, Uncle Howard.
There you go. Just like college.
Yep, nice.
- Mom, you watch this?
- Careful, Howard.
Not taking it out of there.
That's cheating!
Hey, Stefi!
- You made it!
- Stefani.
I'm glad you decided to come.
Now watch the master.
Now the whole family's here!
I'm okay. I'm all right.
Whoa, good.
I'm okay. It's okay.
It's all right. Whoa.
The former things
have passed away.
Neither shall there
be mourning nor pain.
And he shall wipe away
every tear from their eyes.
And death shall be no more.
Hey.
What is all this stuff?
Okay.
I found these papers in Iris's book.
They are obituaries and articles
for the people who were at the Sky View
on the night
that Iris had her premonition.
Each one of these people went on to die
in some weird and messed up way.
And not only that,
they all died in the same order
as Iris's premonition.
Hundreds of people
were supposed to die that night,
but Iris... Iris stopped the disaster.
So, Death came back for them one by one.
Since there were so many survivors,
it took years for Death
to get to all of them.
But eventually it got to Iris.
I mean, she was the last to die
in the premonition.
It was her and a little boy.
But she was prepared.
She single-handedly held off Death
for decades.
Stefani, sweetie,
I don't think this is
the appropriate time for this.
Yeah, I mean,
none of this even has anything
to do with us, right?
- No.
- Why are we even here?
No, it has everything to do with us.
I mean, because Death took so long
to make its way through the survivors,
these people went on to have families.
Families that they never should've had.
So Death took them too.
I mean, don't you see this?
Death is coming for us
because we were never supposed to exist.
Okay, so, what,
everybody in this room
is on Death's "hit list"?
- Bobby, stop.
- That's what she's saying.
No, Dad and Aunt Brenda are safe
because they're not
part of Iris's bloodline.
Okay. Following the pattern...
Death makes its way
down each branch by age.
So because Uncle Howard was the oldest,
it'll start with his family first.
- Meaning, Erik, you're next.
- Go fuck yourself.
Then it'll go for Julia, then Bobby.
Then it'll come for our branch,
starting with Darlene,
then me, then Charlie.
Charlie.
You buying this?
I don't know.
This is so messed up.
I mean, you're turning our dad's death
into some kind of fucked up
conspiracy theory.
- What is wrong with you?
- No, no, no.
No, it's not a conspiracy theory.
Stef, enough.
- We're all going to die!
- Stop!
I can't listen to this
for one more minute.
That crazy woman's nonsense
has caused enough pain and suffering
for this family.
Hang on.
Aunt Brenda, please just listen.
For God's sake, leave it alone.
Okay, in Iris's book
she mentions somebody
who cheated Death and survived.
Stefani.
- Come on.
- Erik. No, wait.
- I'm worried about you.
- Stop it.
- Let me take care of this.
- Come on, Bobby.
- Brenda.
- Let's go.
- Brenda, I'm sorry.
- No, no, no.
- I didn't know.
- Please.
You believe me, right?
- I'm sorry.
- Julia.
Look, I love you.
But sometimes I really hate you.
I know how convincing
all of this can be.
But it's not real.
How can you say that?
I know Iris taught you all of this.
Don't let my mom's beliefs
derail your life...
the same way they did mine.
Thank you so much for that advice,
but I really don't need a mom anymore.
All right, open wide.
All right, good.
This is going to pinch, all right?
You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- Five, four, three...
...two, one.
Good job.
Ready to hit the club.
Need you to lock up.
And don't touch any of my liquor.
No, no, you didn't say anything
about locking up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You didn't say shit about closing, dude!
Yeah, cry me a river.
I hope you burn in hell!
Do you believe that shit?
My old man just died.
I come in as a favor to that asshole
and now he wants me to lock up.
- You know what that is?
- Mm-hmm.
You know what that is?
It's inconsiderate.
Anyway, you're all done.
Mm-hmm. Thank you.
Of course. Hey, five-star review, yeah?
Like and subscribe and all the things.
♪ No
I can't forget this evening ♪
♪ Or your face as you were leaving ♪
♪ But I guess that's just the way ♪
♪ The story goes ♪
Oh, goddamn it.
What the fuck?
Come on.
Okay, okay.
Okay, come on.
Shit!
Charlie, wake up. Charlie, wake...
Charlie, wake up!
I've been trying to call Erik all night.
He's not answering me.
I don't know where he is. I'm worried.
I'm sure he's fine.
Well, have you heard from him?
I'm going over there.
I need to check on him.
And you're coming too, Charlie!
It keeps going to voicemail.
Is that him?
My friend just said the tattoo parlor
burned down last night.
What?
Stef, Stef, Stef!
Ow! You trying to kill me?
Erik?
Oh, yeah, no, of course it's you.
Dude!
We heard about the fire.
We thought you were dead.
I'm fine.
Oh my God. Are you okay?
I was so worried about you.
Yeah. The firefighters said
I was lucky as fuck
that I was wearing that leather jacket.
Barely got burned.
Ruined my favorite jacket though.
- What is this?
- Oh, yeah, check it out.
I got branded.
Sick, right?
You like it?
You said you were asleep.
You were blowing up my phone
like a goddamn stalker.
- What did you want me to do?
- No, I don't get it. You should be dead.
Right. Yeah, yeah.
Or, you know, maybe...
maybe Death's not actually
coming for our family.
Because that
would be fucking crazy.
Jesus!
Shit!
Or maybe I'm invincible.
Erik.
Erik!
- Yeah?
- Erik, wait.
- Stop, just wait, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Just because Death
didn't kill you last night,
doesn't mean that you're safe.
Stay away from that tree trimmer!
Is it going to move on its own, Stef?
Is that what it's going to do?
It could fall.
And stay away from these kids.
I'll take my chances.
Stef, how's a couple kids
with a soccer ball going to kill him?
I mean, I don't know.
The trimmer could fall
and hit the leaf blower guy
which causes him to...
blow stuff into the kids' eyes
and then kick the ball into his face.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Soccer ball to my face?
That does sound deadly.
I should be more careful.
- Hey!
- What's up?
What happened to you?
Charbroiled by Death, apparently.
- Kiki, that looks really bad.
- Yeah, it's fine.
No, wait. Let me see that.
- Erik, just stay away from the truck.
- Stop.
- Oh, what, this truck?
- Stop!
- Oh my God.
- Please.
This truck right here?
Please just
listen to me for one...
But it's such a beautiful truck.
Please. Stop, stop.
Don't touch...
- Mwah!
- Erik, get away!
Stop!
- You like that?
- Can you just...
Oh my God.
Oh! Uh-oh.
Oh, Erik's tempting Death again.
What's going to happen?
- Stop doing that!
- What is going to happen?
- Nothing at all.
- Please, just...
How about that?
Look,
I'm just trying to help you.
- Okay.
- Try less.
Yeah. Honestly, we're so done
with your garbage.
- Can you please...
- Okay, for the 1,500th time,
no one gives a shit about
your stupid little Death curse, okay?
So take a hint and leave us alone
because Death's
not coming for our family!
Julia!
Shit.
- Julia!
Stop the truck! Stop the truck!
- Stop the truck!
- Hey! Hey!
Stop the fucking truck!
My sister's in the garbage!
♪ What doesn't kill you
Makes you stronger♪
♪ Stand a little taller♪
♪ Doesn't mean I'm lonely
When I'm alone ♪
♪ What doesn't kill you
Makes a fighter♪
♪ Footsteps even lighter... ♪
Help!
- Julia?
- Stef!
Give me your hand!
I got you!
Don't worry, you're not next!
Whoa! Whoa!
- Help!
- Hey, stop! Stop!
- Stop!
- Stop! Stop!
- My sister's in the back!
- Stef!
- I'm so sorry, sweetie.
- Dad.
We should've believed you, Stef.
No, I...
I screwed up the order
and now Julia's dead and it's my fault.
Guys, look. What happened
was traumatic and awful.
- It's not anybody's fault.
- Marty, please don't.
It's my fault.
Mom, it's not your fault.
It is my fault.
Stefani, you were only wrong
about the order
because there is something
you didn't know.
Erik isn't Howard's biological son.
I'm sorry. What are you talking about?
And Stefani, I didn't believe you,
so I didn't say anything to you,
and now my little girl is dead.
I don't understand.
What, you had an affair?
Your father and I were
having such a hard time...
but it was good because I got you.
I got you out of it.
Who's my real dad then?
Who's my real dad?
It doesn't matter
because Howard loved you so, so much.
Who is it?
Who's my real dad?
Jerry Fenbury.
Jerry Fenbury?
Yes.
Oh, shit.
- No, no, no!
- Erik.
Jerry fucking Fenbury?
You don't know
what we were going through.
Oh, God! What, is this why
he always wanted to play catch?
Oh my God.
Okay.
All right, so, that means that
if it's going in the right order that...
I'm next, right?
You got to help me, Stef.
Bobby, I don't...
I don't think that I can.
I mean, I thought I did,
but I don't know...
No. But you can.
I mean, you predicted
exactly what was going to happen.
You just got the order wrong
because you didn't
have all the information.
- Charlie.
- What do you mean "predicted"?
She saw everything.
The trimmer, the blower,
the soccer ball.
It was like they were pieces to a puzzle
and she just had to put them together.
- You know what I mean?
- Is that true?
Darlene, please.
- Do not encourage this.
- Marty.
I mean...
I mean,
it's everything in Iris's book. It's...
It's like an equation. It's math.
Stefani, if you can see
how all of this fits together,
we might have a chance.
Stop. Just stop.
You devastated this family
when you walked out.
But we've been okay without you.
I'm begging you
not to traumatize our kids anymore.
It's real this time.
I'm going for a walk.
I need some air.
I can appreciate that
our family is clearly going to need
some counseling in the future,
but can we focus on the fact
that we're all about to die, right?
I mean... I mean, Stef,
didn't you say that... that Iris...
knew someone
that cheated death or something?
Yeah, um...
In here, somewhere, it says...
that, uh... Right here.
"JB found someone who survived."
But it doesn't say anything
about who this JB was or...
Wait a minute. I know that name.
My mom used to write me letters,
and she sometimes would talk
about a friend of hers named JB
who worked at a hospital.
Hospital.
Um... um...
Something, uh...
Something River Hospital.
Uh, Deep River.
Uh, Peace River Hospital. Clear River...
- Hope River?
- That's it!
Shit, it's like an hour away.
I'm going. I'm going to go find him
and talk to him myself.
Well, I'm coming with you.
- Me too.
- Okay. Yeah, yeah, let's go.
Bobby, uh...
What?
You need to stay here with your mom.
It's safer.
Yeah, fuck that.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not staying here by myself.
Well, it's too dangerous
on the road for you. You can't.
No, I read Gammy's Death Book, okay?
All right?
I mean, there's like a thousand
house-related deaths in that thing, man.
You can trip down the stairs,
fall down a toilet or something.
I don't know, but I'm not...
No way. I'm not staying here.
- Hang on, hang on.
- Hey, okay.
- Okay.
- Too fast.
Okay, okay.
We'll go slow. We'll go slow.
I'm going to go open up the truck.
- Charlie, check the back.
- Got it.
Okay.
Be careful.
The step's slippery sometimes.
Oi!
Any of you fuckers do a nut check?
Excuse me?
You made cookies in that thing
with peanut butter in them
just a few days ago.
This poor bastard
so much as even touches a nut,
his throat is going to close up
tighter than...
You understand.
Where's the peanut butter?
- Cabinet above the sink.
- Thank you.
I'm so sorry, Bobby. I just...
Yeah.
Hey. Okay.
All clear.
Thank you. You're a good brother, Erik.
- Nut check.
- What?
- God!
- Stupid.
It was good. I get it.
Let's go. Come on.
It's only going to get worse.
Goddamn it.
Wait! I'm coming with you, bro.
Someone's got to protect you.
Dad's calling. Again.
Tell him we just
went for a ride with Mom.
He's not going to believe that.
At least it'll buy us some time.
All right.
If Death doesn't get us, your dad will.
I always keep them where I can see them.
I mean, you could've just
had the real thing,
but it's okay,
not everyone wants to be a mom.
Is that what you think?
That I didn't want to be your mom?
Look, I was raised by a woman
who taught me to see Death everywhere.
I thought I could put it behind me,
but then when I had you
and your brother,
all I could see were
a hundred different ways
that you and Charlie could die.
I didn't want you to leave the house.
I would freak out on you guys
over nothing.
One day I looked at your face
and I saw the same scared little girl
that I was growing up,
and I knew that if I stayed,
I was going to ruin your life.
I have no idea if I did the right thing.
But I'm here for you now.
It's okay.
I'm right behind you.
Hey. Now you see, buddy. We got you.
The front desk is this way.
Oh. Hi. We're looking for JB.
And who are you?
The front desk told us we could
find him down here. Is that you?
That would be me.
William John Bludworth.
But my friends call me JB.
I've been waiting for you, Stefani.
Charlie. Darlene.
But no Howard. No Julia.
So, which one of you is next?
Hi.
I was sorry to hear about Iris.
She was a special woman.
How did you know her?
She saved my life.
When?
At the Sky View.
My mother brought me
with her to work that night.
JB, honey, I told you,
you got to stay back there
while I'm on stage.
I wasn't
supposed to be there,
except, of course, to die.
- ♪ You know you make me wanna ♪
- ♪ Shout ♪
- ♪ Kick my heels up and ♪
- ♪ Throw my hands up and ♪
- Stop playing! Stop playing!
Everyone needs to get off
the dance floor!
The glass is about to break.
Everyone needs to get off now!
Wait! No!
Iris!
You were the last to die.
You were the little boy.
Correct.
So, all that time,
she wasn't just protecting our family,
she was protecting you too.
Years later, she tracked me down.
Helped me see the truth.
We traded ideas.
I helped her fortify her cabin.
We became friends.
I even helped her
get the best medical care I could,
considering her condition.
Iris said that you found somebody
who stopped Death and survived.
Yes.
Uh, and how do we do that?
There are only two ways.
By killing or by dying.
If you take a life,
you get the time that person had left.
What? No!
I... I'm not going to kill someone.
Maybe we should let the guy finish.
And to truly break the cycle,
you have to die.
What... What does that mean?
A long time ago,
a young woman named Kimberly Corman
found herself on Death's list.
Just like you.
And when her turn finally came,
she died.
Flatlined.
But her doctor managed
to bring her back,
and that broke the chain.
- All right, then. We'll do that.
- What are you talking about?
Why didn't Iris try that?
It's risky.
And if you fuck with Death and lose,
things can get very messy.
Wait. Hang on, hang on. Okay, wait. No.
There has to be another way.
Please, you have to help us.
For years, people have been
coming to me for advice.
Well, I'm tired. I'm done with all that.
And now, I'm sick just like Iris.
There's no running this time.
Fact is, you're all going to die.
And after that, I will too.
Now that my old friend is gone,
I'm retiring.
So, what,
you're just gonna leave us here?
- Wait, wait, wait!
- Dude, we need your help.
Where are you going?
I intend to enjoy the time I have left.
And I suggest that you do the same.
Life is precious.
Enjoy every single second.
You never know when.
Good luck.
Well, that's fantastic.
- No. No.
- Bobby.
No, that... that can't be it.
No. No, there...
There has to be something here.
There has to be another answer.
Stef. Stef. Stef, he gave us an answer.
Bobby's got to die.
Erik!
Are you fucking insane?
We're not killing Bobby!
Whoa, whoa, am I the only guy
that just listened to that dude?
There's only one way.
We kill Bobby, we resuscitate him,
and then boom,
you're all off Death's list.
Congratulations.
There has to be something else, right?
I mean, there has to be
another solution, right, Stef?
No.
No, there's...
there's nothing else we can do, okay?
It's over.
Hey.
Stefani, listen to me.
You got to trust me on this one, okay?
She's giving up on you,
I'm not going to.
Look, Iris found a way
to hold Death off for decades.
- So will we.
- I trust that guy.
You trust that guy?
- He was...
- This one that...
He was awfully charismatic,
and you know that as well as I do...
Uh...
Erik and Bobby are gone.
Shit. Shit!
I don't think I like this.
Hey, dude,
we're in a hospital, remember?
There's doctors everywhere.
We kill you, they bring you back,
everybody's safe, we're heroes.
Dude, that is literally
the opposite of keeping me safe.
What's the alternative, huh?
You want to kill someone,
take the time they have left?
How? How do you even know
how many years they have?
- No. No.
- No. Not good with that.
- Well, I mean...
- No.
- No, of course not.
- We wouldn't do that.
- No, we would never.
- Don't touch those babies.
Look, bottom line...
...flatlining is your best option.
What do you have to lose?
- Okay.
All right, how would we even do that?
Well, see, I've got an idea.
But it's a little nuts.
Your allergy is deadly, right?
Yeah.
Well...
Hey, dude, wait.
No, look, all right? If I'm going out,
it's not going to be on those...
what, unsalted bitches, all right?
Give me those.
Nice choice.
Oh, you got to be kidding me. Come on!
- Hey.
- Stupid!
- All right.
- Come on!
You know, maybe this is a sign,
so we can just...
Okay. Hey, dude,
maybe we can just bail now.
No, I'm not giving up.
- What the hell?
- Can you help?
It's all right. We work here.
Maintenance. It's fine.
Put your headphones back on.
Dude, it's going to fall.
It's going to fall.
- Oh, my! It's falling!
- Did you get it out?
I can't hold it!
It's going to fall!
Easy work.
Now what?
Come with me. Come with me.
What?
Hey, hang here.
I got to get something.
- Wha...
- Don't move.
What are you talk...
Okay. Don't move.
No, that's... that's cool.
I searched the bathrooms.
They weren't in the RV?
No. Look,
if Erik was trying to kill Bobby,
where would they be?
I don't know, but there's a million ways
to die in a hospital.
Can I help you? Excuse me.
No, uh... just here to see my Nana.
Lovely day today.
Got much time left?
I think so.
Be sure to remove
all metallic belongings and devices
that could interact
with the MRI's powerful magnet.
- Hey, dude, Charlie's trying to call...
- Here, man, give me that.
Here, come on. Sit down. Sit, sit, sit.
What the hell?
No, I'm not sitting in that.
Well, I've got a great idea.
Okay, there's an ER down the hall.
So, as soon as you flat line, boom.
I'm going to wheel your ass down there
and they're going to
bring you right back.
Hey, where's your EpiPen?
- Uh, it's right here.
- Give it to me.
Why?
- What is that?
- Dude, give it.
Give it. Listen, the whole idea
is you have to die.
Remember, this keeps you alive. Now sit.
- Dude, we need to hurry. Come on. Go.
- All right, all right.
All right, eat up.
Hey, man, um...
The plan's great,
but you know, if it doesn't work out...
It's going to work, Bobby.
Yeah.
Yeah, but you know, just in case,
and I die for real...
will you just, um...
Will you look after Paco?
Yeah, yeah, of course I'll look after...
Dude, I'm just saying,
turtles live to be like 100 years old,
and it's a lifetime commitment.
Look at me. Look at me.
Brother, I'm not going
to take care of Paco
because you are going to be okay.
Me and you?
We are going to fix things
for everyone right now.
Look at me.
I promise you
I'm not going to let you die.
Technically, I'm going to let you die,
but I'm going to bring you back.
- Dude, it's not funny.
- I'm just fucking with you.
Come on.
You got this.
Oh my God.
What?
That's really good.
It's very good, I know.
So, what, okay, other than good,
what are you feeling?
Nothing.
You got to be kidding me.
What, are you telling me
you're not allergic anymore?
- I don't know, man.
- That's just perfect, isn't it?
- Maybe I grew out of it.
- What, grew out of it? Fuck!
You know, I don't have a plan B exactly.
Hey, you're doing it.
Yeah, yeah, you're doing it.
Bobby, you're doing it.
Hey, I'm here with you.
I'm here with you.
Hey, hey. I can't give you that, okay?
Bobby, Bobby. Hey.
Hey!
Please.
Bobby, this is all part of the plan.
Just calm down.
Bobby, in the wheelchair!
Try calling them again.
This is the only way we can do...
Aah! Fuck!
Oh my God. Are you okay?
Yeah.
Why... Why is Erik dead
if he's not related to Iris?
When you fuck with Death,
things get messy.
We have to get out of here.
It's not safe.
And go where?
Nowhere is safe.
Except Iris' cabin.
She was able to survive there
for decades.
Yeah, and then she got
her face blown off.
She only died
because she left the cabin.
Outside is dangerous,
but inside is the safest place
that there is.
You're right.
It's the only place
where we have any advantage.
So... So we just lock ourselves
in a cabin forever?
Not you.
Me.
Mom, you can't leave.
We just got you back.
If anybody's going to live
in that cabin, it's me.
And as long as I am alive,
Death can't touch you.
- Mom.
- Let me do this.
He'll never let you
get there on your own.
But I can see him coming.
We have to do this together.
Okay.
Let's go.
Yep.
Okay.
Watch out!
- You should drive.
- Yeah.
Holy shit.
Look at this place.
It's going to be impossible
to get through that gate.
He's about to make a move.
I don't know what it is.
We need to get you inside now.
Okay.
Wait. Wait, what?
Go!
Stef!
- Stef!
- Shit!
Okay. Let's get inside.
Okay.
- Shit.
- What?
- I can help.
- No, no. Don't wait for me.
- Just get inside.
- Stef.
If you get inside, I'll be safe. Go.
Okay. Come on.
Mom.
Get down!
Fuck!
Mom? Mom!
Wait.
Okay, okay.
Mom? Oh my God.
Don't worry about me.
Go save your sister.
I'm going to stay alive as long as...
Stef!
No! No!
Oh my God. Are you okay?
Yeah.
Just breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
How?
Charlie. What happened?
You're okay.
You died, and I brought you back.
You brought me back.
We're safe now.
Mom?
No. No.
She saved us.
Let's go home.
All right, I'm ready.
Well, there he is.
Wow. Okay, Charlie.
All right. Give us a spin. Mm-hmm.
Oh. Mm-hmm.
You look really good.
I have a great stylist.
Come on, we're going to be late.
Where's Jenny?
I think she's still inside,
getting ready.
Here, let me fix this.
I'm really happy
I could be here for this.
Me too.
Ow.
You okay?
Yeah.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Could I have one cookie, please?
Charlie.
- Looking sharp.
- Thank you, sir.
Stef, I want you to meet Jenny's dad,
Dr. Reddick.
- Hey. Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
You too.
We just adore Charlie.
And I understand
he's quite the lifesaver.
Oh, yeah. You heard about that.
He, uh, brought me back from the dead.
Mmm.
Huh?
Yeah.
- What?
- Well, technically you weren't dead.
What?
Well, I mean, if you were unconscious
and Charlie got you breathing again,
then your heart didn't stop.
But regardless, way to go, Charlie.
- So she wasn't dead?
- Exactly.
She was lucky Charlie was there.
Yep.
Everything happens for a reason.
Jenny!
Sweetie,
you look like a million bucks.
Stef.
Run!
Oh my God, that was close.
- You okay?
- Yeah.