To tell you the truth,
I never was much for the holidays.
It'd been forever
since I'd known a holiday...
since I'd seen my family...
since I'd been with a girl,
since I'd driven a car.
You see, cars are what put me here:
Iron Mountain, maximum security.
I was riding a hard five
for grand theft auto.
Meanwhile, my esteemed raping
and murdering colleagues...
were up for parole at three.
World works like that sometimes.
All the time, in my experience.
That's me, Rudy Duncan,
menace to society, on the left.
The guy on the right's
Nick Cassidy, my best friend.
Back then, we were both looking
at three days to a new start.
That's what you talk about in prison.
How you're gonna get it right.
How you'll never make the same mistakes.
We walk outta here, we hit that road...
what's the first thing you're gonna do?
Hot chocolate.
- What?
- That's the first thing I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna go out and get myself
a mug of hot chocolate.
And a piece of pecan pie.
That's right. A piece of pecan pie.
Yeah.
She's gonna be out there, man.
She's gonna be right there waiting.
She got us a motel on Highway 5.
Lock ourselves in the whole week...
drinkin' wine, takin' baths, man.
Yeah.
You know, Nick,
all those pictures she sent?
You sure that's really her
in the pictures?
I did hear sometimes these girls send
pictures that's not really them.
It's like their prettier cousin
or somethin' like that.
Why you gotta say a thing like that, man?
- I'm just sayin'...
- Why you gotta say a thing like that?
I'm just sayin',
maybe I should take her out.
Spend a day or two with her.
Make sure she's the right girl.
Just a day or two. Maybe a night or two?
Whatever it takes. Just make sure
you're gettin' the right merchandise.
- You know?
- You know what?
Enjoy your hot chocolate, Rudy.
I think I'll take my chances with Ashley.
Yeah, I figured. I figured.
- Hold it up close.
- Pop gate three.
Oh, shit!
- What's up?
- Alamo's back.
Don't look like he missed the sunlight.
Bro, I'm fucked.
Pincher said he thinks I'm the one
who ratted him out for beating up Creed.
'Cause I was there, he thinks
I'm the reason he ended up in solitary.
Fuck, Rudy.
Move out!
And stop!
Move in!
Listen to this.
"I've made my list
and I've checked it twice.
As long as you're naughty,
it's gonna be nice.
All that gets me through the day is to
close my eyes and imagine holding you...
kissing you, touching you.
Because I know I'll feel
at that moment...
I've found the reason
for my whole entire life."
She sounds pretty mature for 25.
Yeah!
You grow up in Detroit,
you get matured real quick.
Yeah. Either that
or those pictures are 10 years old.
Sure as hell don't
make me miss Millie Bobeck.
Guess I owe Millie, though.
If I hadn't been rolling her...
I would've never ended up here.
Yeah. You hadn't have cracked
that guy's head open...
you never would've found true love.
Jealous.
You know, Nick,
what if she sees you and, you know...
you just don't do it for her,
you know, I mean physically?
She just... It's not there.
What are you gonna do?
Well, me and her, we got a connection.
Jesus Christ.
Get this fuckin' shit out of my face.
You should've written
to that magazine, Rudy.
I should've, yeah.
I'm gonna walk outta here.
I'm gonna walk right into a relationship.
And you, my friend, will walk out
with your bus fare.
Searching for the drunkest skirt
in the room.
That's right.
"Morning, gorgeous. More eggnog?"
Should've written, Rudy.
You'd have got yourself a girl.
Yeah, should've done a lot of things.
All I want is just
to make it back to Sidnaw...
sit down for Christmas dinner...
sleep in my old bed...
watch some ball games with my old man...
eat leftovers for about six months.
I thought you hated that place.
Some of my dad's Christmas turkey.
Yeah, what makes you think
your dad'll forgive you?
Well, he said I'd pay for it.
You know?
Me and my easy money.
That's what he called it.
After wasting five years
of my fuckin' life...
I'd have to say the guy had a point.
Five years, man.
I did my time.
I just want to go home.
Keep the line movin'.
- What's this?
- Holiday Jell-O.
- What's this shit in it?
- Swallow it and you'll see.
Just so you know...
this man and I are outta here in two days.
So while we're inhaling London broil
and lobster bisque...
you're still gonna be standing here...
smelling up the mystery cream fuck.
Who's in prison now?
- Alamo, man, it wasn't me.
- Back in line!
- It wasn't me.
- Two days, man. Come on.
Remember how her brother's
a truck driver down there?
I'm thinkin' he might be
able to get me some work.
What work, security?
I'm through with that shit.
Ashley's right.
I gotta start doin' something
I got a stake in, get a business going.
I don't know, man.
I been in the business world.
Hot-wiring cars, Rudy,
does not qualify you as a small business.
"Chop-shop consultant"
doesn't work on a resume.
I always wanted to be
the boss of something, you know?
Have people working for me.
Man, what's wrong with you?
Monsters... in the gelatin.
- It's just a roach, Zook.
- Yeah, it's protein. It's good for you.
Monsters... in the gelatin!
Calm down.
There are monsters in the gelatin!
Hey, Zook! Sit the fuck down!
Monsters... in the gelatin!
Look at this shit!
Hey! Jesus!
Sit down!
Son of a bitch!
You eat this shit!
Get down! Don't move!
Stay out of it. Stay out of it, Rudy!
- You want some fucking monsters?
- Eat this, cocksucker!
Two days, man.
Fuck!
Don't move!
We had nothing to do with it!
Rudy, watch out!
Cassidy's down! Cassidy's stabbed!
Ashley. I gotta be there.
Oh, my God!
- Rudy, Ashley.
- You're gonna be all right.
- Hold on, hold on.
- Ashley's gonna be there.
Guard! Jesus, guards!
Nick, you gotta be-
Guard! Guards!
Jesus Christ.
- Nick. Nick! Nick!
- Get him outta here now!
Nick! Nick! Nick!
Nick! Nick!
Well, at least he won't be comin' back.
You need some company tonight, Rudy,
you just give me a holler.
Shut the fuck up!
You gonna take that from him, Rudy?
You gonna do something, Rudy?
Yeah, I want some company too!
Open outer gate.
Your world and welcome to it,
you dumb fucks.
Don't be a stranger now.
We'll keep the lights on for you.
Over here!
Hi!
Over here. Hey, how you doin'?
"And all that gets me through the day
is to close my eyes...
and imagine holding you, kissing you...
touching you."
Don't do it, Rudy.
Don't you fucking do it!
Jesus Christ.
Are you Ashley?
I'm Nick!
How's your coffee?
It's good.
Geez, it's got to be about
10 degrees out there.
The radio said negative five.
- Negative five?
- Yeah.
I don't think it's negative five.
The radio said.
Well, windchill, you know,
is probably what they meant.
Windchill factor.
Yeah.
Look, Ashley, I'm sorry.
I was scared that
I was gonna walk out there...
and you were gonna take one look at me
and just... turn around.
I was scared I was walkin' into heartache.
All those letters, those words,
and you have a picture in your mind.
I was scared you'd see me,
and I just wouldn't be that...
picture that you had in your mind.
I figured you walked outta there
and saw my clothes or something...
and you just walked right the other way.
You know, maybe you saw
my coat or my hair...
Hey, I like your coat!
Maybe you-
Maybe you saw me and I didn't-
Ashley, no. That was me.
I thought you said
you had curly hair.
I do. It's very curly.
When it gets long, it's really curly.
But I cut it short.
I can grow it back out again, if you want.
I can get it pretty bushy.
No! No, no, no.
I want you to be who you wanna be.
Do that again.
What?
Smile like that.
Come on. One more time.
God, I have been dreaming
about that smile...
for so long...
Ashley Mercer.
You're better than the pictures
in my mind, Nick.
You're real.
Can I ask you somethin'?
Is this the first time
you ever done somethin' like this?
Look at you.
You're so pretty, sweet.
Why were you writing to a guy,
some con, you don't even know?
I told you, Nick. Remember?
Tell me again.
All the guys I've ever been with...
they never wanted to get to know me.
Who I am... inside.
They just wanted to... get inside.
A guy like you, Nick.
God, I mean, six months
before you could even touch my face.
I figure a guy like that...
is gonna have to work
to get to know me some other way.
But when I read what you wrote to me...
I said:
"Here's a guy they say
is a criminal, but he's not.
Just protected his girl.
Somebody got killed,
but he's not a killer...
'cause he did what he had to do
to save somebody.
And the world just
didn't see it that way."
State of Michigan, anyway.
You wrote me some wonderful things, Nick.
It wasn't all me, you know.
Yeah, it was all you.
The guy I was in with, you know, he helped
me with some of the romantic stuff.
He's a good guy, actually. You'd like him.
I'm talkin' about the heart,
not the words.
Yeah, well...
some of the heart might've been his too.
Yeah?
He should've signed his name.
Then he'd be here right now.
Merry Christmas! Ho, ho, ho!
- Merry Christmas, Santa!
- Leave Santa alone!
Provisions, Nick.
- What?
- Provisions!
Oh, we are going to be naked,
drinking cold champagne...
but we are not leaving that motel room
till after New Year's.
Okay, well, I think we got enough stuff.
Come here. You need a coat.
No boyfriend of mine is gonna walk around
in a negative five degree wind chill...
without a good-looking goddamn coat.
But you already got me all this stuff.
I didn't get you anything.
Nick, you got out. You're here.
You're my Christmas.
It's $200, Ash.
I know! But you forget where I work.
- Beauty and fragrances.
- Yep.
Fifty percent off, my friend. Ho, ho, ho.
Just till the holidays, Nick.
We'll let her have her holidays.
Then we'll tell her.
Attention, shoppers...
- Hey, Nick.
- Yeah.
You know what I was thinking?
What?
Well, after our little holiday hideaway...
maybe instead of going back to Detroit...
we can go gambling.
Don't you think that'd be fun?
You know, drive up to that Indian place
you used to work at.
I don't know about that.
What are you talking about?
I haven't gambled in forever.
I got some luck, you know?
Blackjack, Nick. Blackjack I'm good at.
And they'd give us some free games,
wouldn't they, since you worked there?
I worked security.
I don't think they're gonna be rolling out
the red carpet for me.
Yeah, slots... Whoo! Baby,
am I good at slots. You don't even know.
It would be so much fun. Come on.
You can't be good at slots.
You just pull the handle.
No, but we'll walk in there
like high rollers.
You know, it'll be fun.
Look, Ash, we're not going anywhere
I used to work. Okay? That's it.
Okay. I'm sorry. I just-
You know, I thought
maybe you had friends there...
and you'd like to see them.
It's okay. Look, you know,
I've been in prison for two years.
Those guys really don't want to see me.
Trust me.
Well, they don't know
what the hell they're missing.
I'm gonna tell them not to bother us
for the rest of the year.
When I get back in that room, you better
be wearing nothing but a candy cane.
I have no gifts to bring
A gift to give a King
I've got a girl—
Hi, Nick.
Shit!
I owe you a drink!
Welcome home, Nick.
Look, man, you don't know me.
Oh, I know you.
- I know you real well.
- You can't.
The hell I can't.
- Watch out, baby!
- Ashley!
I'm bringin' in the tree!
Looks like somebody's
been havin' some fun.
Hey, sis, happy holidays.
You bastard! No!
- Take it easy. Don't hurt her.
- Right. Sorry, Monster.
So...
this is the guy you've been waitin' for,
the man of your dreams.
Gabriel, what are you doing?
I read a lot about you, Nick.
Gabriel, what are you doing here?
I read you're a man of some knowledge.
Gabriel.
A man of some travels.
Look, man, I'm not him.
Whatever you want from Nick,
you got the wrong guy.
Nick?
No! No!
Who are you now?
I'm not him, man!
She just thinks I'm Nick. I'm not him.
Put him in the truck.
Wait a minute!
I was in the joint with him.
That's how I knew about him and her.
I took his place.
You what?
Okay. I got out. Nick didn't.
I knew about her letters,
and, Jesus Christ, man...
whatever you want from Nick,
I'm not him, okay?
I just wanted to be.
You're not Nick Cassidy?
No, man, I just shared his cell.
But you were saying you were.
Yeah.
So you could get with my sister.
So you could get down her chimney.
Yeah.
And you think tellin' me that's
gonna help your cause.
No!
No! No!
Is this him?
Please don't hurt him, Gabriel. Don't!
Is this the fucker you been writin' all year?
Don't! Please, don't.
- Is this Nick Cassidy?
- Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Well, he better learn
to give you some respect.
- Get her outta here.
- No!
No!
Man, they got a shitload of cookies.
Take 'em.
What about the tree?
You want the tree?
Yeah.
I read your letters, convict.
Don't play no reindeer games with me.
He read your letters.
One day I wasn't there, and he came in.
Jane tried to stop him,
but he read your letters.
What letters?
He knows you worked at that casino.
What?
Oh, my God, you set him up!
No, no, I didn't. I didn't.
When did you decide to do it, Ash?
After which one of his letters?
What, the 40th? The 50th? The first? What?
- No, Nick, you're not-
- Look, I'm not Nick!
Okay? You thought you'd fuck him over?
Shit! Guess what? He fucked you!
Because I never worked in any casino,
and I can't help you because I'm not him!
No, you don't understand. I love you!
Jesus Christ!
Hey, hey, watch your mouth.
It's Christmas.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
My brother has killed people. I know this.
You don't know him. You don't know
what he's capable of. He will kill you.
If you keep telling him
that you're not you, he will kill you.
Says here the retail industry
does 50 percent of its business...
between December 1 and December 25.
That's half a year's business
in one month's time.
It seems to me an intelligent country would
legislate a second such gift-giving holiday.
Create, say, a Christmas Two,
late May or early June...
to further stimulate growth.
Ever since you been goin' to night school,
you been giving me headaches, Jumpy.
Christmas Two.
"My sweet, sexy Ashy-lashy.
I have been dreaming of you constantly...
and knowing you are out there
makes these walls...
not seem so close
or so strong or so cold.
Someday I'm gonna take you
up by Lake Superior.
Before I went in,
before goddamn Millie...
I used to work up at this casino...
working security.
I used to watch for people
stealin' chips, counting cards...
getting piss-drunk, that kind of stuff.
I ndian place. Easiest job I ever had."
You're a good writer, Nick.
I give this writing... an A-plus.
You just tell us what we need to know...
and you two kids,
you get to go live happily ever after.
You give me little nieces and nephews.
Listen to me, man.
I never worked at a casino.
No, Nick.
Just shut up.
That guy who wrote that letter?
That's Nick Cassidy.
I was in the joint with him.
He rode a two-year manslaughter bit...
for killing some guy who was bothering
his girlfriend in a bar.
He's dead. He wrote those letters.
He worked at a casino.
Me? My last job was at a Quick Lube.
I did five for lifting cars.
That's it. He was my cell mate.
That's how I know him.
I'm not him. I'm sorry about your sister.
I just got out of the joint.
I just wanna—
I don't know anything.
I don't remember anybody.
I just wanna go home.
Bury this guy.
- No. Gabriel, no.
- What?
Gabriel, you promised.
I promised that when he helped us,
we'd be gone.
When he helped us.
This guy doesn't wanna play.
No, you promised me!
And you promised me
you'd get your sweetheart to help!
He'd rather die... than be with you.
He'd make a fucked-up boyfriend anyway.
Bury this guy all over the place.
No. No! Gabriel, no!
Shut up!
Don't get no blood on my shoes.
All right, all right, all right.
What do you want to know?
About the casino, the Tomahawk?
Jesus Christ, what do you wanna know?
Six months writing love letters,
my pen pal fucks me over.
Thanks for the stamps, Ash.
All right. What do you wanna know?
Everything.
Nick, I love you, baby.
Nick, I love you.
Hey.
She said she loves you. Say something.
I had better sex in prison.
Throw him back in the rig.
Monster, he's not the guy.
Whole time you were drivin',
he was tellin' her he's not the guy.
He's not the guy.
I understand why he'd tell us
he's not the guy...
but why would he tell her
that he's not the guy?
Maybe he's not the guy.
Look, if I went in the joint with a library card,
I'd come out with a library card.
The man who wrote those letters
loved Ashley, boys.
He lived for her.
Where's she work?
What?
Wrote you a hundred letters, didn't she?
Where's she work?
Lindstrom's, beauty and fragrances.
What's her middle name?
Samantha.
What'd they call her in high school?
Bam-Bam.
- What'd they call her in college?
- What college?
- What's her greatest fear?
- Brother.
Wrong. It's drowning.
Wrong. It's her brother.
That's love.
It's time to start talking...
Nick.
Time to start telling tales.
Get him up here.
No, no, no! Fuck that!
Nick doesn't do anything
till Nick gets something for Nick.
You got it? I want some hot chocolate.
You wanna hear about some job of mine?
I wanna see some goddamn hot chocolate...
and some pecan fuckin' pie!
Sure nice pie.
So, when you worked there-
You knew the place-
Okay.
You know what?
I could really go for some onion rings.
You said talk. That's all you said.
Gabriel, you said you wanted to talk.
Shut up!
You just said you wanted to talk to him.
You can't choose your family, Ash.
Unlike friends and lovers,
that does relieve you...
of the burden of worrying you chose wrong.
- How much money is in that casino?
- Hard to say.
Well, take a guess.
Five million?
Jesus.
- You wrote Ash a letter with a story...
- Come here.
About working Christmas Eve.
About how they send
half the security guys home.
Nobody's comin' in and out.
And the rest of you are gettin' shit-faced.
That a true story or not?
Christmas Eve.
We're taking down that casino, convict.
And you're the guy
that's gonna tell us how.
That's what we can see.
Now, you tell us what we can't see.
Where the private doors go...
where the alarms are,
what the upstairs looks like, all of it.
That's not the Tomahawk.
What the hell are you talkin' about?
What's this, the cage?
I mean, the cage is over here.
This whole thing's mixed up.
- That's what it looks like, Romeo.
- Since when?
I mean, what's this?
That's the prime rib buffet. $5.99.
Buffet? Buffet is over here by the bar.
I mean, this map looks like it was made
by a bunch of retards. It's all wrong.
Stop it.
It's my map, you little shit!
Now, we cased the place. We saw it.
Yeah, and I worked there, for a year.
The map is kinda messy, Monster.
They must have remodeled the place.
- What?
- Big guy, the boss.
- The guy that ran the place, was in charge.
- Jack Bangs.
Jack Bangs! Was always talkin' about
giving the place a makeover.
Must've gone ahead and done that
while I was in the Mountain.
I mean, this thing's all changed around.
I can't help you with this.
I don't know where security or anything is.
I have no idea.
Look I don't care about
the pancake breakfast.
You wanna know about money, right?
Okay. Where you got the buffet down here?
That used to be Bangs's office.
And he kept a safe in there.
And that safe had all the money
that he was skimming in there.
- And it was called the powwow safe.
- Powwow safe?
Yes, powwow safe.
'Cause he was stealing money
from the tribe.
The guy had thousands in there.
Millions probably.
Millions? In the powwow safe?
Millions.
But, I mean, you know...
it's just that now you tell me
his office is moved.
God knows what else is different.
You know?
The security.
You want me to show you what goes where.
I have no idea!
Well, I guess we don't need you then.
Well, not necessarily.
Because, if you get me inside,
then I know where the money moves.
I know the security routines.
I know their signals to each other.
I know how they operate.
You get me in there...
then I can work with this map,
and I can tell you if anything's changed.
Wrong, convict.
You walk in there, they recognize you.
So what?
If they recognize him, they'll remember him
when the job goes down.
- They won't recognize me. Trust me.
- Why not?
'Cause you're gonna get me a disguise.
Look, I give you the wrong information,
you shoot me, right?
I mean, it's pretty simple.
Now, you got two choices...
You can either get me in there...
I can take a look around and case
the joint, check out security...
and I can tell you
if I can work with this map...
or you can just shoot me right now.
Wait a minute. What's this?
What happened to working together?
- You rather be back in the Mountain?
- Might as well be.
You don't get 50 channels in the Mountain.
Tomorrow you got singin'
for your supper to do.
I've always looked on
Christmas as a good time.
Help yourself.
Sure, take that. I don't need it.
It's the only time when people
open their hearts freely...
the only time when men
and women seem to realize...
that all human beings
are really members of the same family.
Damn it!
Nick. Nick.
Let me help you.
Get your own room, Ashley.
- Let me help you.
- Get your own room.
He said when you come out,
he wants to talk to you. That's all!
I thought he meant after New Year's,
back in Detroit.
But you knew what he wanted. Right?
I thought we had more days.
For what? What are you gonna do?
Talk me into helping?
What, did he promise you
some of the money?
- No.
- Shit, you should've at least gotten that.
Get your own fucking room.
Christ, you know how I hate him.
You know how I feel about my brother.
How fucking stupid are you?
What did you think's going to happen?
This thing's gonna be over,
and he's just gonna let me go?
He's going to shoot me
in the back of the head like this.
Or I'm back in prison for the rest of my life,
and that's it for me.
This is my life too, you know.
This is not just about you.
You think he's just gonna let me walk?
You think he's not gonna
take this out on me?
I'm in this too, and I'm really scared.
Please!
Oh, Jesus.
Nick. Nick.
Do you remember all those letters
you wrote me?
About me and you against the whole world?
We can still have that.
We can have it all if you just
give him what he wants.
Why do you have to keep fighting him?
Why can't you just give him what he wants?
Why?
God!
You know, it's just my luck.
I finally meet a boy that I'm crazy about,
and my brother wants him worse than I do.
What do you want from me? Sympathy?
I don't feel bad for you.
Why didn't you tell me
your brother was a criminal?
Gabriel knows some guys
in Miami and New York-
Guys that he helps get guns to Detroit.
That's it. That's all I know.
- That's who he's working for on this one?
- No.
He doesn't want to work for anyone.
Well, what's the last
place they took down?
What?
Monster and his merry men-
What's the last place they robbed?
Who they ripped off. What did they do?
I don't think they've
robbed anywhere before.
They drive guns.
They've never done a robbery?
Really?
Nick.
- We can get out of this.
- There's no "we," Ashley, okay?
- Hey!
- We get rid of them and we-
Get your own room!
Go! Leave!
Fine.
But if I told you what he wanted,
you would've been gone.
You would've gotten on that bus,
and you would've stayed on it.
And if that makes me selfish,
then I am selfish.
If that makes me a liar... God— I am a liar.
But I have been dealing
with my fucked-up brother...
and his fucked-up friends
for way too long.
And I am stronger than him now.
Because he showed up for money...
and I showed up for love.
Sing it to somebody who gives a shit.
You're so quick to make me your enemy?
Then tell me something, Nick.
Tell me—
What did you show up for?
What did you really want?
With me?
No. Miss, miss, miss, miss.
Oh, man.
Well, well.
- You still got the touch, Monster.
- That's right.
Look what Santa's dwarves
have brought you.
What do you say to Santa's dwarves?
It's elves, bro.
You say "Thank you."
A cowboy.
You're sending me into an I ndian casino
dressed like a cowboy.
- Thought this through entirely?
- It was that or a ballerina.
Well, I mean, I'm gonna need some money.
It is a casino.
Ten bucks?
What am I gonna do with 10 bucks?
Don't tip.
Look, if we're gonna
be workin' together...
you shouldn't send me in there like the
Lone Ranger with 10 bucks to throw down.
You want me to not get noticed.
Not gettin' noticed costs at least
a couple hundred.
Ante up, boys.
Don't lose.
Yeah. Do I get, like, a country-western name,
or are we just gonna—
You get recognized,
you get a country-western funeral.
Come on. Come on.
Get your hands off me!
Are you ready to go gamblin', darlin'?
Here. She is now.
All right.
You all keep an eye on my guitar now.
Who's robbing who here, Gabe?
Get in there and watch them.
Jumpy.
Nick, you're making it
really hard to apologize.
Is that what you're tryin' to do?
Say it with car keys.
Nick, a lot of relationships start out like this-
you know, family problems?
Save it, Bam-Bam.
Hey. I think I liked you better
when you were in prison.
Yeah? Is that why you keep trying
to put me back in?
Well, I just think you were a hell
of a lot more understanding.
Well, I was a different person then.
As I was saying, boys...
there's an "S" word I'd like
to throw into the conversation here...
because it's a big part
of what's going on, a big element.
The "S" word.
It's a serious matter
with serious effects...
so I'd just like to get it out there,
throw it out there...
so that we can know about it,
talk about it, hear it...
maybe even do some things about it.
- Mr. Bangs.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
Snow.
Are you with me here, boys?
Now, I'm talking big-time, grade-A...
God-quality, S-N-O-fucking-W snow.
Now, look, you guys hired me
because you wanted Las Vegas quality.
I brought it to you.
You wanted Las Vegas press.
I gave that to you.
But I cannot give you Las Vegas profits...
until you people get together
around a campfire...
smoke a pipe, and do some kind
of fucking spirit dance...
about this goddamn snow.
We understand the Paiutes' casino
saw a profit of $ 12 million last year.
Don't talk to me about the Paiutes, okay?
I have it on very good authority
they're cooking the books.
The Wyatolla reservation made 17 million.
All right, look.
Keep this under your feathers, boys...
but it just so happens that next week...
I'm bringing in a great lounge act.
Three Russian broads.
They all look like Meryl Streep.
They can juggle anything— your house,
your car, your mother-in-law.
Mr. Bangs.
We're doing the right thing here-
Mr. Bangs, the tribe is concerned...
that many of your new ideas
are not bringing in any new revenues.
I'm putting liquor into drinks.
I'm paying 10 times odds on craps...
and I got the girls showing 16% more skin.
And by the way,
you show me another buffet...
that offers both Coke and Pepsi.
Don't even bother looking,
because it doesn't exist.
Okay, so, now,
what else do you people want me to do?
So, does it look remodeled a lot?
Yeah. Yeah, it does.
They did a lot of work.
This restaurant here is the main expansion.
And they moved the games around.
The big guy's office—
They did a hell of a job with that.
Hell of a job.
Do you know that guy?
Yeah. That's Mike.
Mike. He works here.
Spend some of your brother's money.
I'm gonna go look around.
I was just thinking maybe you fellas
would like to stick around—
You know, try the $5.99 prime rib.
Thank you.
Couple of rum and Cokes, please.
You want that rum and Coke
or rum and Pepsi?
Did you keep going?
Bear.
Bear, give me a bottle of any goddamn
thing you got. Come on, hurry up.
Cheap low-balling
two-dollar fucking bettors.
I can't go back to Vegas, Bear.
I can't go back. They'll kill me.
- What does the tribe want?
- What do they want?
They want their roads paved
with gold is what they want.
Talking to me about the fucking Paiutes.
The Paiutes are on the interstate, okay?
There's nothing I can do about that,
my friend.
And I certainly didn't pick this spot
for your reservation.
- Neither did we.
- Yeah, yeah.
Thanks a lot.
Hey, how you doing, cowboy? How are you?
- Good. Great.
- Jack Bangs is the name.
Hey, listen. Listen, Hopalong,
you look like an intelligent fellow.
Let me ask you something.
Do you think that upstate Michigan...
needs another roadside casino, or...
do you think that upstate Michigan...
needs an international gaming destination?
- What do you think?
- Roadside casino.
How'd you hear about us? Radio, TV, cable?
Prison.
Place your bets, please.
I can't go back to Vegas.
We won! We won!
Oh, fuck.
What the hell was that all about?
Nothing, man. He just wanted to know
how I heard about the place.
Just fucking throttle down a little bit,
all right? Ease up off me.
You're welcome.
Oh, my God. I'm sorry.
Jesus Christ.
I'm sorry. Here, hold this.
What are you doing?
Security's not all that changed.
Let me just go clean this up, all right?
- What was that?
- His face fell off. Take this.
Hey, baby.
Give me one of those.
- How are you?
- Fucking freezing.
How long you work here?
Five years... since it opened.
How long since your makeover?
My what?
I'm taking about the place...
The remodeling, moving everything around.
Tomahawk's been the same
ever since I started, buddy.
It's the losers that change.
Lying motherfucker!
Go, kid, go!
Hey.
Shit.
Come here!
Oh, man, it's yourjacket.
You can have it.
- He gave me a hundred bucks.
- Shit!
- What the hell happened, man?
- The man fucked up!
This building is the same from day one!
It hasn't been changed!
Monster, he was talking
to the manager inside there!
There he is!
Go, go, go, go!
Come on! Get him back!
Keep on running, Romeo! Keep on running!
As fast as you go, we'll get there!
We're truckers, motherfucker!
We drive for a living!
Help! Help! Help!
He thinks he's gettin' away.
Shit!
No!
Come on. Come on!
We gotta get to those trees.
Oh, shit!
Come on! Get 'em outta there! Come on!
Come on!
- Is she all right?
- All right, all right!
All right!
At the rate you're goin', I'm gonna have
trouble considerin' you family.
Hey there! You folks need some help?
- I say, you need some help?
- Get outta here, man!
- Shut the fuck up!
- Get the fuck outta here!
Well, if you need some help-
Gabriel, no!
Gabriel, he won't hurt us.
He won't remember us. Don't do it.
Shut the fuck up!
No!
Oh, God!
Jesus. Please.
I'm just a farmer.
I got a wife and family.
I got a hunger...
and a headache.
Hey, Monster.
Here they are! Come on!
Get out of here. Get out of here.
Nick the Trick.
Master of disguise.
I'm surprised you never escaped
from the Mountain.
What? Yeah. Never tried.
Well...
in the spirit of the season, convict...
I'm gonna give you a chance.
I understand you're unhappy.
It's been kind of rough.
You need a little guidance.
You're like a wanderer...
who's just lost his way in the night.
So we're gonna have a little contest.
We're each gonna get one of these.
Yeah.
Whichever one hits closest
to the bull's-eye gets what he wants.
You land closer, you get Ashley.
You kids get to go free.
I land closer...
then we start getting your help.
May the man who really wants it win.
Yeah?
Shit.
You got something to say to me, Nick?
Two out of three?
"What's this? What's this?
This isn't the Tomahawk.
No, no. I've never seen this before.
They must've given the place a makeover.
Yeah. The buffet was over here.
The blackjack was over here.
The bar used to be over here.
I don't know. I can't help you.
I have no idea. I have no idea."
Something tells me you're not being
totally honest with me.
What'd you tell that casino manager?
Nothing. Nothing.
You were talking to him.
What'd you tell him?
Nothing.
He thought I was some gambler. Nothing.
Maybe something about a robbery?
No, man. I swear to God.
Jesus Christ, man,
He thought I was some gambler!
He didn't know me, man!
He didn't recognize me! Jesus Christ!
I've been driving rigs
a long time, convict.
Worked for people who wouldn't keep me on
unless I was driving 15 hours a day.
Tell them I was tired, shit,
they'd just hire someone else.
A thousand miles by sundown,
or the gang don't eat come sunrise.
Shit.
And every road...
every mile...
it's nothing but moms and pops...
and car-seat kiddies
giving me that look to go to hell...
and get off their happy goddamn highway.
So...
So I have worked...
and I have slaved...
and I have waited...
for the highways to split open
and for the rivers to roil...
and for God in the heavens to reach down
and show me some sign of my reward—
To grant me with my gift...
and say to me, "Gabriel, my son...
you are done with the road."
Well, convict...
that gift was granted.
Look, man, I swear to God.
He just wanted to know
how I heard about the place, that's all.
He didn't know it was me, Gabriel.
Gabriel, he didn't know it was me.
Please.
Man, Monster,
just don't start trying to hit me.
Nick...
I've been trying to hit you.
Because I do not deserve
to be in some shit-bag motel...
in the middle of bum-fuck Michigan...
throwing darts at a worthless...
fucking convict!
You know something?
My little sister-
She deserves a world better than you.
Tonight, we're going to take
one more look at that map.
And this time...
you better have something worth saying.
Oh, my God.
Jesus Christ. What happened to you?
What did you do to him?
Hey!
What did they do to you, Nick?
Jesus Christ.
What the fuck did you do to him?
Bastard. Get out! Get out!
Just get out!
Oh, my God. Nick, are you all right?
Let me see. Let me see.
Oh, God.
- Come here.
- Damn.
Come here.
Had some... points to make.
Okay. Baby.
We're going to get you
out of these wet clothes. Okay?
Oh, God.
Okay.
Okay. Come here.
- Come here.
- Jesus.
There you go. Okay.
All I wanted to do was
to make it back to Sidnaw...
just have some of Mama's gravy,
you know...
and some of Aunt Lisbeth's
cranberry cakes.
She makes them
with real cranberries.
It's really good.
We'll get there, baby.
- Jesus.
- We'll get there.
Just rest. Okay?
You saved my life, Nick.
You could've run, but you didn't.
You saved me.
I saved you 'cause I love you, Nick.
Why did you save me?
The guy I was in with...
Rudy, the car thief?
Sometimes I read him your letters.
I mean, I know they were private, but...
you know.
I'd read them to him, and he'd...
get this look on his face.
I swear, I think he imagined
you were writing to him.
And I know sometimes, I think...
he fell in love with you too.
You gave a couple of guys hope, Ashley.
Oh, it was a good thing.
We're gonna get out of this together,
I promise you.
Ash?
We're gonna need one.
What?
A gun.
We got to find a way to get me a gun.
What?
And I'll need to be
inside the casino when it happens.
I can't just be outside drawing some map.
Nick, what are you talking about?
We need to find a way
to make me a part of this.
A part of what? A part of them?
Look, Ash,
if we're helping them with the robbery...
we got to be doing more than walking away.
Like that's winning, like that's some kind
of Christmas fucking bonus.
You mean take the money?
Yeah. Take the money.
Look, you want him out
of your life for good?
You want a real New Year
to look forward to?
If we're gonna do this,
then we ought to do it.
It's Christmas, Ash.
I think we deserve a present.
Start singing, Nick.
I have no gifts to bring
A gift to give
You want to keep fooling around?
Yeah. You want to keep playing?
Come on, let's get it on!
- Let me go!
- Calm down.
You want to keep playing?
I got a toy for you.
Let me get my toy.
Yes. Let's play!
- Hey, man. Hey.
- Shut up!
Now you get your pussy ass over here
and do what the fuck you're told!
Now when you're spoke to,
you listen and answer.
It was a joke, anyways.
All right.
What you want to do...
is get to the top level up here.
Okay? And you do that
through this door on the western wall.
You want to get to the security,
and then from the security...
you get down into the cashier cage
and then you go into the count room.
Now, there'll be a guard in there,
but he doesn't have a gun.
The door's accessed by a keypad.
The cashier will know the code.
What about the powwow safe?
That's upstairs.
You'll want to get to that.
We're gonna get to the powwow safe.
That's good. We're gonna get there.
What you want to do is,
you got to get a guy in the cage...
and a guy on the floor
and somebody up top.
Then you need a sweeper on the side...
a lookout out front...
and somebody watching the back.
So, that's... How many is that? Six.
We got five. Keeping Ashley outside.
But you need six.
No.
Look, man, I'm not making this shit up,
you know?
You go in there with five guys...
you're gonna either leave
an exit or an alarm unguarded.
- No.
- I know what I'm talking about.
Raise your hand if you've
ever done a robbery before.
Anyone? Anyone? Who's done a robbery?
Raise your hand.
Okay.
I have.
You need six, Gabriel.
You do. What are you gonna do about it?
All right. I want a drawing
of that security level.
Every door, every guard, every ashtray.
Yeah. All right.
So, six guys, that's six guns.
No way.
Well, what am I gonna do?
I'm no threat without a gun.
- No, you're not.
- What's the matter, Gabriel?
Isn't this what you wanted him for?
Areas of expertise?
No guns.
Well, you know, fine. It's up to you.
What you've got to figure out is how you're
gonna get up to that security level...
without anybody knowing anything's wrong.
I can tell you right now,
going in there with A.K.s and ski masks...
ain't gonna do that.
Well, that part, Nick...
was planned out the day
I read your letters.
Oh, yeah. What?
We're all gonna dress up like cowboys?
No, no, not cowboys, Nick.
Not on Christmas Eve.
You gotta be kidding me.
'Tis the season, convict.
Ho, ho, ho.
Coming up at 11:00
on the Channel 5 news, these top stories.
The search intensifies for a Michigan man—
Here's your Picasso.
Reported missing this morning
on the Tallahassee Lake.
- Investigators suspect foul play.
- It better be.
Also, lottery fever—
How long have you guys been going out?
- Set us up with free drinks.
- Oh, yeah.
Shit!
Only guy in the gun club
who doesn't keep a gun in his truck.
Shit!
Fucker decided to build him
a silicone tongue...
so that the boy could talk.
Now, you ever see a motherfucker
with a breast-implanted tongue?
This guy I'm talking about— black-ass lung
is the least of his problems, man.
He had so much smoke
comin' out of his skin, people would say...
- "Hey, where's the barbecue?"
- Yeah.
No! No!
No. Get away from me, goddamn it.
Get off me! Just get off me.
You heard what I said.
Stay away from me!
No. You stay away from me.
Stay the hell away from me.
You want me to scream?
I'll fucking scream. I swear to God.
Listen. I was trying to stop him.
You just about killed me.
I wasn't shooting at you.
I was just trying to stop him...
put him down,
shoot him in the fucking knees.
I'm a good shot. I wasn't gonna kill him.
Yeah. You're such a goddamn good shot...
that who went through
the goddamn ice?
Hey, I didn't put you on that ice.
- You would never have been there-
- I just about goddamned died, Gabriel.
Baby, I know that.
When I saw you fall,
I could've put the gun in my mouth...
and pulled the trigger then.
I know you have to be with him...
but it is killing me.
Gabriel, we just have
to keep doing this and-
I'm gonna cut out his heart.
Is he ready for that?
He's helped us do the map.
He's done what we need.
We don't need him anymore.
I don't trust the little fucker.
We can do this without him.
I'm gonna kill that motherfucker tonight.
No.
Jesus.
You drive me crazy, you know that?
- Hey—
- No. You listen to me...
because we have to be smart about this.
The more he wants me,
the more his help's for real.
He's manpower. That's all he is.
He's just more manpower.
Gabriel, he wants to help now.
He wants to rob it. He wants to rob you.
He wants the money?
No, baby.
He wants me.
Your little sister.
If only Ma and Pop-
Could see us now.
- Hey.
- What?
You told me this guy would play
the game by the numbers.
Well, from where I stand, the only thing
he's been doing right so far...
is fucking my girlfriend.
I don't want you with him.
When I'm with him, I'm wanting you.
All those letters
to all those goddamn cons...
are finally gonna pay off.
So don't get crazy, okay?
'Cause it's working.
He's our money man.
- We finally found one, didn't we?
- Yeah.
Oh, baby.
- See you later, assholes.
- Who's Jumpy calling?
- Ex-wife, probably.
- Which one? All the ex-wives he's got...
he's probably gonna have
to take down three casinos.
You track down Gabriel?
Nah. He's with his girlfriend,
making up for lost Nicky time.
Come on. Hey, let's go get a drink.
I should go and check on Romeo.
Go smile on the motherfucker in love.
Shit.
You know what? I'll meet you in the bar.
Fuck.
Come on, give me something.
If I can fucking hot-wire cars,
I should fucking hot-wire a hotel door.
Yeah, there we go.
Damn.
Who's slamming doors?
How you doing?
Shit.
Damn.
Hey.
Nick.
Where should we go?
Huh, baby?
When we're gone from here...
when we can do anything...
where should we go?
I don't know about you. I'm going home.
We go together, remember?
Wherever.
Well, I'm going home.
Tomorrow's Christmas Eve, my love.
My love.
Tomorrow's Christmas Eve.
And your charges, sir.
Happy holidays.
That's for the hundred bucks
worth of pay-per-view.
That's for the 200
you took out of the minibar.
- That's enough.
- It was on my credit card!
I figured since you guys
were paying for the room-
So...
you wanted a weapon, convict?
No! Don't!
Well, now, look at what Santa's dwarves
have brought you.
What do you say to Santa's dwarves?
It's elves... Santa's elves.
You say, "Thank you," motherfucker.
You hang around with criminals,
you end up making a lot of plans.
But all the jobs I ever pulled,
all the cars I ever stole...
no plan ever went down
the way it had been drawn up.
My plans to escape never worked,
and being on parole...
going to the police wasn't an option.
What's the matter? You nervous?
Right now, you're just a truck driver.
You haven't done anything wrong yet.
If you do this, you're gonna spend
the rest of your life wishing you hadn't.
Thanks for the reminder, Nick.
Relax.
Have a drink.
Ain't that your thing?
Hey, hey! Thirsty!
This diversion you're doing-
You'd better do it just the way
Monster planned...
or there ain't gonna be
no more rest of your life.
And all through the house,
not a creature was stirring.
Why don't you send
most of your boys home, Ed?
Tom, why don't you go spend
Christmas with your family?
Don, you can shove off.
Merry Christmas, Jack.
- Good to see you again.
- Nice to see you.
Nobody even comes here to cheat.
Ho, ho, ho!
Hello!
Eggnog for everyone. Santa's here.
Good to see you.
Merry Christmas. Merry Christmas.
And we'd like some money, please.
We're here to win money.
Do you have any money?
How you gentlemen doing tonight?
Very good, Captain,
except that we're out of work.
Seasons greetings.
He's from Lindstrom's. I'm from Save-Away.
How you doing?
No more toys for the kiddies,
but we do have charitable donations.
All right, fellas, in?
Hey, sweetheart, how you doing?
- Eleven.
- I'm fucking freezing. What can I get you?
- Twenty-one.
- Oh, Jesus. You just hit from my card.
I'm sorry, mister.
- Dealer has 18.
- And look at that, Grandpa.
Yeah. I'm gonna win your sled.
Save-Away.
Over here.
I saved you a seat. Play my hand.
- Lindstrom's. How you doing?
- Aren't you gonna take those beards off?
No, I'm not gonna take these beards off.
This is my lucky beard. Mind my beard.
Watch out for this guy.
He's a fucking jinx.
Okay, Santa number three,
what can I get you?
Could Fat Man With Flying Horse
get quarters, please?
- Watch my bank.
- All right.
Five. Nine.
No way. Pop, goddamn it,
you're hitting from my card. No.
- You don't even know what it is.
- He doesn't hit.
Why don't you go find a chimney
somewhere and fall in, huh?
Son of a bitch! You are killing me here.
That's the way it goes.
- There's two more coming.
- There you go.
That's what I like to see.
Now, that's the spirit.
Jack, is there a union
for department store Santas?
Hey, who the fuck knows?
Then go get another table! For old people!
You're old! You're taking Santa's money!
- There is no other table.
- Then I'll open another table!
What kind of a people cheat Santa Claus?
- What the hell are you doing?
- For God's sake!
- Security!
- That was Santa's money! You took it!
- You're cheating me!
- Hey, pal! Come here, buddy!
Lay down, pop. It's all right.
- Come on!
- Stay down.
Santa Claus is kicking the shit
out of your guards.
The security room-
Right at the top of the stairs. Right, right.
Take a right. Security room.
Fuck.
That fucking convict. Geez!
Turn off the fucking alarm!
What the heck?
Get away from the desk!
Drop 'em!
Put the guns down!
Get down!
Put the guns down! Put 'em down!
Christ!
Here it is, motherfucker.
I don't like you!
Your piss is all you need, Romeo.
Get up! Get the fuck up! Everybody!
It's the only time-
Cuff 'em. Cuff 'em! Come on!
Oh, no.
Oh, no, listen, no.
No. Please don't do this here, okay?
Please don't do this to me,
all right? Listen.
Look, let me tell you something.
This is just not
another card club, all right?
This is the Tomahawk Casino.
We're an international gaming destination.
We're in guidebooks.
Show's over.
Move, Goddamn you!
These guys aren't fucking around.
Let's move.
Get in there.
Go ahead. Just do what my friends say.
They're a little bit...
disturbed.
What's the security code
for the count room!
Code? What code? Just use the key!
- Nick said code!
- Who the fuck is Nick? Who's Nick?
- Drop your guns!
- Throw your guns down! Show your hands!
Drop that gun!
- All right, all right, all right!
- Drop it now!
You motherfucker!
No guns in the count room!
- Fuck you!
- Put 'em up in the air!
Fuck you!
Shit!
No guns in the count room!
Forget about him and get the money!
Forget about him
and get the fucking money!
Forget about him.
There's no future for people
like you and me, Nick.
The places we come from—
bland towns, mill towns, small lives.
No future, just more of the same.
You want a future,
you got to stand up and steal it.
Oh, my God.
The powwow safe!
I want the powwow safe! Where is it?
I can't move back to Las Vegas.
I do not give a shit about Vegas!
The money is in the car.
Let's get out of here right now.
- He won't tell us where it is.
- What?
The powwow safe.
Remember Nick Cassidy?
Security guard named Nick Cassidy?
Yeah, Nick Cassidy. Where is he?
Gabriel, we have enough money.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
Where is he?
Not Nick Cassidy.
Nick Cassidy worked for me two years ago.
Cowboy.
Hopalong.
That's the story of your life, Ash.
You fucked the wrong guy.
Rudy Duncan, honey.
We still gonna spend Christmas together?
- You fucking bastard!
- Hey, hey, hey.
No! Goddamn it!
You are lucky, convict.
You're gonna be spending Christmas
with the birthday boy himself.
Wait a minute.
There is a powwow safe, all right?
There is a powwow safe.
I did time with Nick Cassidy, right?
Some shit he told me.
Some shit I remember.
He told me the manager keeps a secret stash
in his office... a powwow safe.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- No! There is no safe!
- He's stalling us! There's no safe!
- He said it one time!
I overheard it. There is a powwow safe.
He's been stalling us from day one.
There's no safe.
- There's a powwow safe. I heard it.
- Then where the fuck is it?
Behind the liquor cabinet.
Oh, Jesus.
Hey, hey.
- Get up.
- Oh, please. Please.
- Get up. Open it.
- I can't go back to Vegas.
I don't give a fuck about that!
Get up! Open it!
Hurry up!
Oh, God. I can't go back.
Pow... wow.
Powwow.
Hey, Santa Claus! Welcome to the Tomahawk!
Oh, shit.
Yes!
Get up.
Yeah. Yeah.
God is good.
Now...
what do you say...
to Santa's dwarves?
You say, "Thank you."
Never make the same mistake twice.
You just did.
The wrong guy.
We took the place down with the wrong guy.
Is this Christmas, huh?
Is this Christmas?
God bless us, every one.
Come on.
Smart, aren't you?
So smart. You're smarter
than everybody, huh?
Powwow safe.
A little gift for us in the powwow safe.
Well, I got a gift for you.
From Pug and Merlin and Jumpy,
you son of a bitch.
You're going where they went.
And they're gonna find you there,
and they're gonna kick your fucking ass!
You feel smart?
You think you're lucky?
Well, let's see how lucky you are!
Come on!
Here's how lucky you are.
You got out of the Tomahawk,
into your car...
made it halfway to Canada
until you caught some ice on the road.
Get down there!
Take a look.
By the time you hit
the bottom down there...
the whole car was burning like a comet.
Must've burned up all that money too.
Was it your idea, Monster, or was it hers?
Well, she told me about
the convict magazines.
Had to figure there'd be some guys
in the pen with some useful knowledge...
with nobody to talk to
and nobody to listen...
so...
we just stocked up on stationery.
It's a hard life being a trucker's girl.
Baby. Come here.
- I saved your life.
- You shouldn't have.
He really loved you, you know that?
Nick. He really loved you.
Who wouldn't?
Maybe this is where
you wanted him, Ashley...
Some stranger at the bottom of a ravine
with a burned-up heart.
Maybe.
But it didn't happen...
because what you did for him...
- you made him the happiest he'd ever been.
- Shut up.
Get up. Come on.
Get in the car.
Hey. Hey!
Gabriel.
Don't go getting all noble with me, Rudy.
Guy takes a shiv for you,
you go chasing his girlfriend?
Don't talk to me about greed.
What? What did you say?
I said don't talk to me about greed.
No, not about that—
about you said a guy takes a shiv for you.
I never said anything about a shiv.
How'd you know there was a shiv?
You said it.
You said the real Nick died saving you.
No, I didn't. I said he died.
- I never said how.
- Yes, you did.
No. I never said how. I said he died.
You said he was stabbed.
I said he died. I never said how.
You said he was stabbed,
that he took a shiv—
A knife, a shank, whatever.
Ash?
How'd she know there was a shiv?
How'd she know?
Jesus Christ.
Men.
Merry Christmas, Rudy.
We made it, baby.
Oh, yes, we did.
We made it.
Got a little messy, but...
I'll tell you all about that
once we're on the road.
For your information...
I never fuck the wrong guy.
So, Rudy...
I want you to meet Millie Bobeck.
Remember Millie Bobeck, don't you?
My girlfriend before I went in.
Worked at that bar in Motor City
where I manslaughtered what's-his-name.
See...
Millie here...
she used to serve drinks
to these gun-running truckers.
Real big talkers...
scheming about a real score one day.
Two years in the Mountain,
man, what the hell?
Why not let her get friendly with 'em?
Tell 'em her real name was Ashley.
Tell 'em about this idea she had...
about writing guys in prison.
Find a sucker who could
show them a sure thing.
You know...
they would've never done it
without you, Nick.
I mean, Rudy.
I always wanted to rob that casino, Rudy.
Way back when I worked there.
What better way than to get
some guys to rob it for me?
Paid the Alamo a hundred
to put the shiv in me.
He's a lifer, man. What does he care?
He was supposed to stab me
in the yard later that day...
but when that food fight started, man...
I couldn't believe it.
The slash across the ribs,
the homemade blood capsule...
gets you a nice, warm hospital bed.
Paid a guard to spread
the word I bought it.
And once the wound healed up...
got out of the Mountain this morning.
Tonight, I am a rich man.
Get in the car.
Keep your gun on him, honey.
How'd you know I'd do it?
Because every time
I read her letters, Rudy...
you listened.
Besides, man...
even if you hadn't taken the bait...
we'd have still had a shot.
She'd have just had to convince them
they could do it alone.
What do you know?
Good old Rudy came through.
Good old predictable Rudy.
Goes for the easy money, every time.
Five Santas walked
into that Tomahawk, Rudy.
That's what the witnesses will say.
So, we gotta have five Santas
not walk out.
Gotta have five.
How many things could have gone wrong?
A thousand?
You think we don't know
what a long shot is?
My girl Millie was steering you, man.
You fucked it up,
she would've cut and run.
They'd be looking for Ashley Mercer.
Whoever she is.
Six months of telling you
Tomahawk stories.
Guess now you know why.
You gave them the confidence
to walk in there, Nick Cassidy.
That's all we needed you to do.
You said some nice things about me, man.
Appreciate it.
You know what? You're right.
I do love her.
And she-
she loves me.
You had that part right all along.
It's Christmas, sugarplum.
Let's light up the tree.
Shit.
Write me.
Shit. It's like ridin' a bike.
Like ridin' a bike.
Good-bye, Rudy, my man.
Nice spending... time with you!
Rule one- never put a car thief
behind the wheel!
No!
Five Santas walked
into that Tomahawk, Rudy.
That's what the witnesses will say.
So, we gotta have five Santas
not walk out.
Gotta have five.
Rudy.
Rudy, you and me, man. You and me.
We can split the money, huh?
Rudy, that whore, Millie Bobeck?
You think I was serious about her, man?
I was gonna kill her!
You gotta believe me.
You gotta believe me, I swear it.
- Believe me!
- Believe this.
Rudy! Rudy, help me!
Rudy!
All I wanna do
is make it back to Sidnaw...
sit down for Christmas dinner...
watch some ball with my old man...
sleep in my old bed...
have leftovers for about six months...
eat some of that Christmas turkey.
Like I said, I never was
much for the holidays...
until now.