CINEMA FUND
VOL'GA.
NMG Studio
(Wind Blown)
(Footsteps)
(Dog Barking)
(Grunts)
(Grunt)
(Gunshot)
(Wind Blown)
(Vehicle Approaching)
THE RAGE.
(Car Door Open)
(Car Door Close)
(Engine Revving)
(Door Open)
Get out.
(Spitting)
(Thud)
(Exhales)
(Door Close)
(Engine Revving)
After you taught me lessons,
the whole body hurts.
- Maybe, you'd carry me?
- Obviously...
(Footsteps)
Okay, let me go.
Just let me go! I'll go myself.
(Footsteps)
Let go! What are you doing?
(Thud)
(Exhales)
Here's my buddy, Dima Nifontov, lying.
He died when he was 27.
Missing him?
Just wait, you'll feel it.
Don't be in a hurry.
Let go! Bitch!
Another Dimon lies here. Tereshonok.
He managed only to 26.
And here's my best friend lying.
Kostya Grishkov.
Feel how soft the ground is here.
It's fluffy! Do you want to lie down?
And Kostya is lying, no claims...
(Spitting)
What a fool you are.
(Exhales)
There are twenty guys lying here,
friends of mine...
...none of them survived their thirties.
At least you can be proud of yourself,
you're a centenarian.
They didn't know what they were in
for when they put that shit in their veins.
And you see everything clearly.
I get my wisdom from YouTube.
Do you also want to die
with a syringe in your vein?
No, I want to be like you.
Quietly in my bed, surrounded by
beloved children and grandchildren.
So I didn't bring you here for nothing.
- Let's go.
- I can go myself!
Yourself you can only
put syringe in your vein.
(Footsteps)
(Ominous Music Playing)
(Car Passing By)
(Suspenseful Music Playing)
(Engine Revving)
(Car Passing By)
(Car Door Open)
Here you are! I've called several times.
Has the phone gone dead?
(Car Door Close)
Hello!
(Chuckles)
Have you brought the asshole?
- Well, he's actually my son.
- Yeah...
(Knocks)
(Car Door Open)
Get out, your majesty.
A real skinny guy, just like mine.
- This bag is for you.
- Okay. Oh...
I forgot the keys. Just a sec...
Misha!
Give me the keys from the second half!
- Come on, be quick, it's freezing.
- I'll go and get them myself.
(Footsteps)
What's this place?
Your motherland.
We'd better put the car into the garage.
I'll do it right now.
Should I take anything?
- Take the bag.
- Okay, right.
Let's go.
(Car Door Close)
(Footsteps)
(Door Open)
Come in.
(Footsteps)
You've heated it up like a sauna.
Everything for the dear guests.
Hey, where're you going?
We go barefooted there.
Take the shoes off.
(Footsteps)
You'd get some water.
(Thud)
- Yura.
- Eh?
- Here's ammo.
- Okay.
Wow, Igor, as always, thank you!
- Look, hot is here...
- Go, set the table.
But it's ready.
Come on, make yourself comfortable
and join me.
This bed is yours.
The mattress here is softer. Try it.
What can I do to get you to take me back?
(Thud)
(Creaking)
(Clanking)
(Clatter)
Dad, what are you doing?
What have you done?
- That's it. -What have you done?
- Are you nuts?
Am I a dog or a slave?
(Thud)
From now on it will be like this:
(Clatter)
- We sleep, exercise in the morning...
- (Groaning)
...pack up and go to the taiga...
(Groaning)
...there's a hunting lodge there,
there you won't have to be handcuffed...
(Groaning)
...but here it'll be like this.
(Clanking)
(Exhales)
You're nuts,
it's you who must be handcuffed!
Get out! I've got nothing!
- Lie down!
- Don't you touch me!
(Clanking)
(Exhales)
(Thud)
Let go! Let go, I told you!
(Clatter)
(Exhales)
There's fresh air...
...game, melt water...
(Clatter)
You'll like it.
Give me the sneakers, my feet are cold.
Put the blanket on.
(Clatter)
I had my last dose yesterday.
Do you get it?
It's gonna be a hell of
a night of withdrawal!
You'll make it... You'll make it.
(Exhales)
(Footsteps)
A forced detox.
(Thud)
Freak... What a freak you are.
(Dog Barking In The Distance)
(Engine Revving)
(Door Open)
(Door Close)
(Exhales)
Why don't you eat the shaved meat?
I'd better eat hot first.
Ah, that's right.
(Clatter)
He's spending all days like this.
All summer long he saved up,
of course, I added to it...
...and he bought a used
one through the Internet.
(Clatter)
Now that's it, the kid's gone.
(Thud)
Forbid.
(Gasps)
It's no use. As soon as I leave
the house he goes back to playing.
When mother comes back from the shift,
let her sort it out herself.
(Clatter)
And what about yours? How's he?
I took him to all sorts of clinics.
(Clatter)
I went to all sorts of
witches and healers...
...prayed for him, ME!
Lit the candles. Nothing helps.
I only saw him once,
two years ago, at Julia's funeral.
- Is that when he started?
- No, he started earlier.
That was what got him down.
- (Clatter)
- (Exhales)
In the evening...
(Exhales)
I come home, he's not in.
He's not answering the phone.
Of course, I am up all night and worried.
And in the morning...
(Music)
I open the door...
(Exhales)
...and see him lying in the stairwell...
on a rug.
(Sobbing)
Beaten, dirty, like a mangy dog.
(Music)
You know what?
You're right to bring him here.
That's right.
You know, how good our land is.
It's healing here.
(Spritz)
- Come on.
- (Thud)
(Exhales)
(Clanking)
(Thud)
(Gasps)
(Pulsation)
(Clatter)
(Gasps)
- (Gasps)
- (Thud)
(Gasps)
(Suspenseful Music Playing)
(Screaming)
Look, Yura...
(Clatter)
The cops have pinned me down.
- Kidding?
- What is it like here?
Some customs officers make you pay...
...and others catch you.
That’s the system. My turn has come.
Good thing a friend warned
me that they are coming...
...to arrest me on Monday.
- Wait. Arrest where?
- Arrest to prison.
I'll sit out a couple of years,
get some sleep...
...read some books, think about life.
No, that's not discussed.
But I have to break Vova first.
So until they find me,
I'll be in the taiga with him.
Will you help us?
Of course I will!
It hurts you think I wouldn’t!
The potatoes are about to be ready!
Misha, shut that crap down...
...go talk to Uncle Igor,
at least you’ll learn a thing or two.
Dad, 15 minutes more, please.
Mine used to sit at the
computer at night, too.
Then he switched to heroin.
(Clatter)
Misha, turn that bloody thing off!
(Wind Blown)
(Vehicle Passing By)
(Engine Revving)
- Why so long?
- Traffic jams, damn them.
- Let's go look what's there?
- No, thanks.
I'll stay here, near the cars. But you go.
Follow the tracks, you can't go wrong.
(Engine Revving)
(Footsteps)
There must be two of them.
They went to check the
station in the morning.
And in the evening their bosses told
me there hadn’t been a word from them.
Keep silence for a moment.
(Wind Blown)
(Suspenseful Music Playing)
(Footsteps)
So what's there?
(Cock A Gun)
(Footsteps)
(Suspenseful Music Playing)
Have you found both?
I have.
What a creature - he gutted them both!
(Wind Blown)
But there were two wolves, too.
Were they having a party or something?
Strange wolves: attacked during the day,
gutted and abandoned.
- We should declare a quarantine.
- Really? Quarantine?
Is that Wuhan?
Rabid wolves don't gather in packs.
If these two are rabid, there will be more.
(Suspenseful Music Playing)
(Sighs)
Hi.
- Waiting for me to get up?
- No, just sitting.
(Coughs)
Dad...
I've been thinking all night long...
I understood you're right.
(Exhales)
It's great you've brought me here.
I felt it was the right thing to do.
It was like looking into the mirror.
And what did you see there?
Everything...
So much shit...
There was also meanness,
nastiness, hatred...
I won't tell lies any more, dad.
I do want a doze, but I won’t... Honestly.
My word to you.
Great.
- Let's go home.
- Of course, we'll go.
After all the shit goes out of you.
So that you look into
the mirror with joy...
...seeing no shit in it.
And what if it doesn't get out?
I'll beat it out.
(Door Open)
Come on, Misha, come on. Get on with it.
(Grunts)
I can't.
You'll make it, son, you'll make it.
Come on, raise your axe and chop.
- I can't!
- Did I warn you? I did!
- Chop this bloody crap!
- But dad!
Chop it now, I said!
(Thud)
Why are you pushing on the guy?
I'm gonna come now and
chop your hands off myself.
Now!
(Sobbing)
- (Thud)
- More!
(Sobbing)
More! Come on!
That's right! Well done! Well done!
You, bastard! Bastard!
Now we'll live normally!
- Don't you feel sorry for the boy?
- That'll teach him.
Why are you standing here! Get out!
When are we leaving?
Igor, listen...
Maybe you'd better keep
Vova here for a while, eh?
They say a wolf gutted
someone at the tower last night...
...and they called the cops from the city,
they're now processing...
There's no way to leave the car there now.
Then we have to go
right up to the winter hut.
On your car?
No way, we won't make it, we tried.
Maybe, forget this hut?
The air is clean here too,
the other half is yours!
Nadia is fine with it.
She'll always cook you a hot meal.
No. The snowmobile will take
us straight to the winter hut.
Really? It's over an hour's trip.
It's already thirty below
zero and will be more.
Vova is weak, he won't make it,
the taiga doesn't like the weak.
- I can't wait.
- Igor, don't make a fuss.
Let's wait until morning.
Damn...
Come on, I'll show you how
I got the snowmobile ready.
(Thud)
Got a new track,
straight from Japan, thank you.
The bearings have been changed,
the slides are new.
(Thud)
- I'll go to Vova.
- Okay.
I'll start it up and warm it
up again in the meantime.
(Sighs)
(Footsteps)
You, asshole! Give it to me!
- It's mine! I'll die without it!
- Give it to me, I say!
Give it to me!
Bitch!
(Coughs)
You sly, bastard.
Should I scan you now?
(Thud)
(Groaning)
It's your own fault.
Give me some, I beg you!
For Christ’s sake, dad, give me a tiny bit!
I'll die without it, do you hear me?
Give me just a tiny bit, I beg you...
In mercy's name...
You're my father,
I won't make it through another night.
I'll help you, don't you worry.
Wait a minute.
(Sobbing)
Dad, one last time.
Last time!
I promise you, I won't ever do it again.
I need it now to survive, please.
I beg you, dad!
(Sobbing)
- Take it, you'll feel better.
- I won't! Let me go!
It's a painkiller. You'll feel better.
I won't!
Don't you think I haven't tried?
Oh, you, fool, what a fool you're...
(Sobbing)
(Engine Revving)
Yura, turn it off.
Can I take your TV until night?
Sure, you can.
I'll go to the shop to buy some
more liquid for a quick start.
It's freezing, I feel.
Maybe you have something
more powerful than Ibuprofen?
I'm afraid he'll be yelling so loud
that all the village will be here.
Go to Olga Savchenko
to the house number 17...
...she's a paramedic,
she might have something.
(Footsteps)
(Door Close)
You are a scum.
And you're scum's son.
(Groaning)
So, what d'you want to watch?
- Your funeral...
- I see.
[from the TV] Good morning!
There you go.
You have pictures like that in there...
...when you're high, don't you?
You should try it yourself to get a
better understanding of the issue.
(Sobbing)
(Ominous Music Playing)
- Is anybody here?
- Who's there?
- Hello.
- What d'you want?
My name is Igor.
Timofey and I go hunting together.
I see. Come in.
(Door Creaking)
(Grunts)
- Isn't Timofey home?
- He still hasn't come back from hunt.
Do you have some strong painkiller?
The back is aching harshly.
Better if it's with codeine.
It's the only thing that helps.
Where should I take it?
I only have paracetamol.
- And I buy it for my own money.
- Could you at least prescribe it?
No, we can't. We're strict about it.
(Grunts)
What's going on again? Lyosha!
Osokin, bullying again?
I'll tell your mother everything!
Enough! Enough, I said!
Go home, now!
(Door Close)
(Footsteps)
[from the TV] Kite flying,
tossing and turning...
...hide and seek, balls,
quack and jump rope.
And simply, and simply,
and simply jump ropes...
Mom, please... I don't need borscht...
(Sobbing)
Let me make a call. They'll bring some.
(Knocks Doors)
Igoryok!
Do you hear me? Come out.
(Door Creaking)
- Take it.
- Oh, thanks.
Hard to get them without a receipt.
- How is he?
- Hard.
Come with me, I'll close the gates.
(Footsteps)
There's no one at the tower any more,
so we'll go in the morning for sure.
Great.
If I don't make it now,
there'll be no other chance.
- And mine has run away.
- Really?
Yeah. He must be staying
the night with Turhin family.
- Father of the year?
- Yes.
I feel really worried.
(Thud)
It's good we're leaving tomorrow.
I won't hear much from Nadya.
- But you meant well.
- (Door Creaking)
(Exhales)
Yes...
There will be much talk just
of it in the village tomorrow.
(Gasps)
But that's no worry.
I'll buy him something necessary.
(Grunts)
Wait.
Go inside, quick!
Come on, faster!
Faster!
(Grunts)
(Groaning)
- (Groaning)
- (Grunts)
(Grunts)
(Door Open)
I'm about to die.
(Thud)
(Grunts)
Wolf! Gut him!
- (Groaning)
- (Grunts)
(Thud)
(Gasps)
- What was that?
- A wolf.
- Has he bit you?
- What wolf? What a wolf is it?
Rabid wolf.
Have you brought me here
to be gut by wolves, right?
(Gasps)
(Dogs Barking)
Yura!
(Footsteps)
The wolf has attacked.
- And what's with Yura?
- Dead.
- I killed the wolf.
- Don't let the children come here.
Vova is yelling.
I ask you to be patient.
You just have to be patient.
(Sobbing)
- (Sobbing)
- Be quiet.
(Sobbing)
- How did it attack?
- Right from the darkness.
Has anyone called the cops?
- Dad?
- Don't let him come!
- Dad...
- Hold him, eh!
- Get him away.
- Dad! What's with him?! Dad!
- Dad!
- And you, man, how'd you get here?
I'm his neighbor.
We planned to go hunting together.
(Vehicle Approaching)
And how did you kill it?
I got so scared. Don't even remember.
It was all so quickly.
(Footsteps)
I broke it by accident today.
Yura and I planned to
put a new frame tomorrow.
- I see.
- So what can I do?
Officials will come,
then we'll decide something.
What do you want from me?
Captain, Sir! Can I have a moment?
Come on, break it up. It's all over.
What?
He killed the wolf in the house, not here.
- Meaning?
- The wolf jumped into the window.
He killed it there,
then brought outside and put near the body.
- I don't know why.
- Come.
(Footsteps)
Can we go inside? It's uncomfortable
to write the report outside.
- Yes, go to that half.
- No, we'd better go here.
We'll leave everything as it is there
for the crime investigators from the city.
Otherwise, they'll be resent, okay?
Sure.
(Door Open)
(News Broadcast On Tv In Background)
Come in, sit at the table.
Can you turn down the TV?
Can't hear anything.
(News Broadcast On Tv In Background)
(Footsteps)
(Gasps)
- What's that?
- It's my son.
He's a drug addict. He has a withdrawal.
(Gasps)
Is he down there in the
basement or something?
I told you, withdrawal...
Open up!
(Door Open)
(Sobbing)
(Siren Wailing)
Roman Vasilievich,
meet the ambulance, or they'll.
- And what should we do with him?
- We'll sort it out.
Meet them, please.
(Footsteps)
Get him out from there.
(Gasps)
There.
(Sobbing)
The towel.
Thanks. Thanks. Take me from him.
- Handcuffs.
- Listen, captain. It's my son.
- Don't listen to him. He's nuts.
- Shut up.
I'll now take the heroine
from the pocket and show you.
Lies. He's lying!
I'm waiting until the withdrawal's over.
It's wrong to take him now, do you get it?
He's lying! He's lying! He's sick
in the head, he's just torturing me.
I've been bitten by a wolf! Look! Look!
They know how to lie when they want a dose.
- It's a cut from a nail.
- I'll get rabid.
- I have to go to town!
- Okay, enough!
Put the package onto the fridge.
- And take the handcuffs off him.
- You don't get it, Captain.
- It all just looks...
- Take the handcuffs off...
- Where to?
- For the key.
Thanks. Thank you so much.
He's a psycho... he wanted to kill me.
(Footsteps)
- Are you nuts?
- Here's 200 000.
He's my son, captain.
I want to save him.
When the wolf attacked,
I hid him in the basement...
...so you wouldn't find him.
That's my son.
If I let him go, I will lose him.
(Gasps)
Man, you're incredible.
Do you understand what 200 000 is here?
That is why I am offering
you two hundred thousand.
Anybody here would sell their
hand for that kind of money.
- Do you know how it hurts?
- Kill the pain. Take it.
If I'd take it... I'd...
- It's wrong to do this to people.
- He does it to all people.
He must be put in prison to understand.
Rare people understand
anything new in prison.
I'll pray for him.
My brother was a drug addict.
I told him: "You'd go cokehead".
He's gone totally stupid.
Is to silly to understand anything.
There's no way to save them.
Just make it so that no one hears him.
Where are you going?
- What are you doing?
- Put the TV on.
Are you selling me to him?
Are you out of your fucking mind?!
You, bastards!
(Door Open)
(Engine Revving)
(Clearing Throat)
(Footsteps)
Good evening, sir!
We have another rabid wolf.
Are you breeding them here?
What is the forestry department doing?
- The area should be quarantined.
- That's our forester right there.
Your forester is not doing a good job.
- Get people out of here, Captain.
- Yes, sir!
- What was there in the house?
- Wait a bit.
Break it up, men. Go home.
Girls, dear,
you must have got frozen already.
Major, Sir...
(Dog Barking In The Distance)
One more. Major!
Get into my car, fast!
(Dog Barking In The Distance)
They're coming, they'll help you now.
(Sobbing)
There it is. Creature... I've locked it up.
- Dima?
- Yes.
I went out when I heard dogs bark,
and saw it jumping at our dog...
...I was so stupid to try to fight it off,
I hardly ran away.
Drive up close to the barn.
(Engine Revving)
Come on, come on.
Enough.
(Thud)
(Crackling Noise)
(Suspenseful Music Playing)
(Bleat)
- (Grunts)
- (Gunshot)
(Grunts)
- (Grunts)
- (Gunshots)
(Bleat)
(Door Close)
(Dog Barking In The Distance)
So what?
Done.
Well done, yeti.
Look... and what's there with that guy?
The drug addict...
Come, I'll explain.
(Footsteps)
I've given you a bonus here
for your excellent shooting.
Here's fifty for you.
Let's mind our own business.
Did you sell the man for that money?
He's a crackhead.
Either you go and detain him yourself...
...or I tell the Major.
What a fool...
Really, you don't need money in the forest.
And I live with people around.
But it's just not very human of you,
Abyzov.
A fool you're, forester.
It's three months of calm life.
I don't need money in the forest.
Okay. I'll deal with it.
You should. And I'll keep an eye on it.
(Door Close)
(Engine Revving)
Hey!
That man took a tied up kid
somewhere on a snowmobile.
- Took where?
- To the taiga. Where else?
He's got him right out.
He was yelling! Drunk or something.
Right. You blocked his car.
- Let's follow them. -Where?
- At night? To taiga?
If they get stuck,
they won't make it till morning.
It's their fault. Where the hell they go?
(Engine Revving)
It was you who made him do it.
If you don't go, I'll go to the Major.
(Phone Chimes)
Here is a romantic evening.
(Engine Revving)
Did you really plan to put me to prison?
Why not? A great idea.
You'll have a flat, and a car and money.
How many dozes you'd get for my off-roader?
- (Dogs Barking)
- Enough for a year?
- There's someone behind.
- Who?
- Hurry up! Step on it!
(Vehicle Passing By)
Is the guy a real addict?
(Engine Revving)
He could have killed
for real for such a doze.
Reload.
Please.
Ammo is in the glove box.
- We'll get stuck in there ourselves.
- We won't, the ice crust is solid.
What a day, and most importantly...
...I promised my wife
I'd be back for dinner.
You've got only five rounds here.
I didn't mean to go to war.
God willing,
there will be no more firing today.
(Engine Revving)
(Wind Blown)
(Grunts)
Sit!
(Gunshots)
(Grunts)
(Howling)
(Groaning)
(Engine Revving)
(Howling)
Here we are.
(Exhales)
Come on.
(Gasps)
Stop.
What's that crap?
(Door Creaking)
Bear slippers.
(Gasps)
Here, help me with the light.
You're sickhead.
You're totally sickhead.
(Thud)
Everything...
everything just for you, sonny.
How will we manage here?
There's everything here.
(Gasps)
What the hell is going on here?
Masha and the Bears?
(Coughs)
I hear a car.
(Engine Revving)
There he's, looking out of the window.
- Drive closer. -No.
- If I drive down, we won't go up.
- Wolves are there. Wolves!
- What's he saying?
- I hear damn nothing.
- Wolves are here.
- That's why he's yelling.
- Wolves, wolves...
(Engine Revving)
- Come here.
- No, we won't come out.
Turn the car off,
I can't hear a fucking thing.
- There're wolves there.
- No one is here!
Come here, quick!
(Cock A Gun)
(Dog Barking In The Distance)
(Grunts)
(Gunshots)
(Gunshot)
(Grunts)
Fucking hell!
Have you killed it?
You did it, forester!
(Footsteps)
Have you blown out the tyre?
- We have to start the car.
- Ask him to start it.
(Cock A Gun)
I've run out of rounds.
Are you kidding?
I see,
you've also given yours away generously.
There's a curse on me today.
There's a pheasant shot,
but it's in the car.
(Grunts)
It reacts on us.
We must leave,
otherwise it can break the window out.
Move your feet, why standing then?
(Door Creaking)
- Has it bitten you?
- No, it's just torn the jacket.
It hasn't got to the skin.
- There's no signal here.
- We are going back, aren't we?
- Leaving?
- No. The tyre is blown out.
We'll put on the spare and
get you out of here in the light.
We'll stay here.
Aren't you afraid other wolves can come?
- Are you alive?
- So far so good.
- I need to go to town.
- Is the withdrawal over?
It's from stress.
(Squeaking)
Why is it so dirty here?
We must start the car,
otherwise we'll go nowhere tomorrow.
Yes, it's forty degrees below zero.
(Cock A Gun)
It seems, someone sat in a siege here.
It was locked from the inside.
And there were bear slippers at the door.
Quiet!
(Suspenseful Music Playing)
Okay. Okay.
- What's there?
- Yes.
(Suspenseful Music Playing)
(Shivering)
Man, what's up?
Hey, what's...
(Grunts)
(Gasps)
Man, what's up?
What's up with him?
Rabid...
(Gasps)
Put the light out!
Where to?
(Clatter)
Man, easy, easy!
Abyzov, give me the handcuffs!
Quick!
(Groaning)
- Here you go! - Tie him up.
- (Groaning)
(Gasps)
Easy, man! Easy. Here!
Easy, easy! Hop! Quiet, man!
- Done.
- What's that?
Is it all contagious around here now?
No, if you don't put your
fingers in your mouth.
What are we gonna do with him?
He'll die soon.
One or two days left.
How did he even survive
in this freezing cold?
He's recently stopped stoking.
This must be Timofey Savchenko.
I visited his wife this morning.
She's been waiting for
him for the last three days.
She won't be happy...
What a dumbass you are...
(Screaming)
Shut up, you...
(Coughs)
We now have two wards.
It hurts. Give me the pills.
(Coughs)
We need to finish the wolf in
the car and get out of here fast.
- Why sit here?
- How? We've got no more rounds.
We'll open the door, it'll jump out,
and we clamp it like this and kill.
And what if it bites?
Look, we'll kill it. We are three.
These two are surely of no help.
The only thing we have to decide upon is...
...who's holding the door
and who's killing the wolf.
One was enough for me.
Pay them so that they go together.
That's what you always do.
(Chuckles)
Well, yeah,
you could give a little extra for courage.
I'll finish it off.
(Gasps)
Just need to know with what.
(Door Open)
You make the stake,
and I'll look for a shovel.
(Suspenseful Music Playing)
(Door Close)
Oh, let's take this one.
(Footsteps)
You picked the wrong health resort.
(Thud)
Give me the axe.
(Suspenseful Music Playing)
(Thud)
So you're not at all afraid
of the rabid wolves, right?
I'm more afraid of people... in the city.
(Thud)
Enough. Don't make it too thin.
Or it will break.
(Suspenseful Music Playing)
Is it dead or what?
(Ominous Music Playing)
- Just be slow, do it slowly.
- I got it, I got it.
(Suspenseful Music Playing)
Come on!
(Door Creaking)
(Grunts)
Bitch!
(Door Close)
(Gasps)
Hey! Hey, come here!
Faster! This hunter!
Come here, faster!
(Gasps)
What a night...
(Door Open)
(Engine Revving)
And you, lie here for now.
(Ominous Music Playing)
It's still there...
(Gasps)
- It's there...
- Who?
(Gasps)
The bear.
It'll come here.
(Ominous Music Playing)
(Gasps)
Olya... Call Olya... Call Olya...
That's it. He'll die till morning.
Call my Olya.
He seems to feel better,
he started talking.
It's always so with rabid people.
They seem to feel better before death,
but then... they must lie down.
Maybe we should give him some painkillers?
It won't help.
And maybe give him your drugs?
They're there in the car.
There's a bear somewhere there.
I saw the trails.
So, we now have a bear
for a company, right?
- Yes.
- And how would we kill it?
With a shovel and an axe?
- (Grunts)
- (Thud)
(Ominous Music Playing)
(Crackling)
You don't like wolves, do you?
No one, who knows wolves deeply,
likes them.
And how do you know them?
I wanted to show off when I was 16.
Went hunting the wolf alone.
Why the wolf?
Because wolf is the tzar of the taiga.
While I was aiming at one,
another went behind my back.
I dropped the carbine and climbed a tree.
Tied myself with a rope and waited.
The next day they found
me by the footprints.
(Exhales)
I lost three toes, frost-bitten.
I respect any beast in the taiga.
But after that night,
I have a score to settle with the wolves.
- How many have you already killed?
- I haven't counted.
- You have.
- 23.
There're still many wolves in the taiga.
(Thud)
Enough putting more every five minutes.
The heat is going down the chimney.
You're a pain in the arse with your drills.
- The master of the taiga...
- Why are you such a piece of shit?
We came here because of damn you,
hell knows why.
You should have declared
quarantine after the first dead.
I do not impose the quarantine...
...but the Region Hunt Management
and the regional administration do.
(Crackling)
- But you're a cop.
- So what?
You could have driven through
villages and warned people.
Yes, I could have,
people are my responsibility.
Beasts are your responsibility.
And you seem to be failing.
I see how you cope.
Only when you are given extra money, right?
- What are you...
- Sit down!
Otherwise, I'll break your nose.
Just try.
(Thud)
Has your son been long on that crap?
I started two years ago.
I can share my experience.
No thanks, I am a moonshine expert.
You know how many moonshine
experts are there around the country?
- And what are you addicted to?
- To money...
Money gives adrenaline.
It's normal for a man. It's not a drug.
- What do you know about drugs?
- They kill people.
- Or make people complete idiots.
- And thus you can handcuff them?
No other variants have been invented yet.
So, you think, it's all so easy, right?
It's easier to stick yourself
with a syringe, of course.
And for us to seek for you,
run after you, catch you...
...beg you, rescue you and then bury you.
(Clatter)
(Thud)
Heroin...
They usually start smoking at first.
But then the scenario is always the same.
(Sobbing)
What are you doing? Put your clothes on.
Here are the veins of the junkie.
I'm not super tight yet,
and I only have them here and here.
(Sighs)
If there are no veins there already,
you can inject anywhere.
For example, here.
Here is also a great place...
...between your toes and on your hand...
...you can even go in the head...
...you can do in the cods...
right under the balls...
...and if it's really fucked up,
or if they're checking veins...
...you can do it under the tongue,
right in the mouth...
(Tongue Clicking)
(Gasps)
And you think you can get a junkie...
...who's willing to stick needles
everywhere to get high to quit?
Should I give up on you?
Anybody can be negotiated with,
just not a junkie.
You should all be locked up.
Yeah, sure.
(Gasps)
In the 1950s there was
an experiment in America.
Mice were put into a cage and two
trays of water were given to them...
...one with heroin and
one with clean water.
After a while, the mice began to
drink only the water with the heroin.
- It's an addiction.
- Yes, that's what they decided.
The war on drugs
started all over the world.
(Sighs)
Then in the 1980s in Canada, one dude...
...Bruce Alexander,
got suspicious about this experiment...
...and decided to do his own.
He built a park for rats.
A huge one, with slides,
holes, swings, ponds...
(Sighs)
...put 20 rats of both sexes in it...
...filled the park with
different kinds of food...
...and put two water trays with
heroin and with clean water.
The rats tasted the heroin water,
but then didn't drink it;
they drank the clean water.
That's how they found
out the heroin was cut!
(Sighs)
It turned out that addiction
is related to living conditions...
...and the way you are treated.
So, it's all my fault?
Who cares whose fault it is?
You don't want to understand anything...
You don't want to see that it's the system.
The same system that's putting you away.
And you're part of the system,
putting me away.
(Sobbing)
(Footsteps)
(Clearing Throat)
(Suspenseful Music Playing)
(Thud)
(Sighs)
Where did you put them?
- What are you filming?
- I'll send it to you to have a look...
- ...when you get normal.
- Put the phone away!
(Sighs)
Varya, give me 2000, please!
Varya, are you grudging 2000?
You see, I feel like shit!
(Sighs)
Where's the money?
- Where's the money, Varya?
- I don't have any cash.
Bitch!
(Sighs)
(Sobbing)
Haven't I given you money?
Haven't I given you gifts?
Damn, I am taking them back.
(Sobbing)
(Yelling)
(Sighs)
I knew you'd fuck me over, bitch.
(Coughs)
Put it away!
Let's go to your mom?
Can we go to your mom to hospital?
Are you stupid? You think I'm going
to my mother like this now, don't you?
(Sighs)
It's not you now.
You'll look later and realize it's not you.
Why are you moaning,
why are you moaning, bitch?
Vova!
Is it your mother dying?
Go away!
(Sobbing)
- What are you doing, Vova?
- Give me the phone!
Give me the phone!
(Sobbing)
- Go away, please!
- Bitch, I wish you'd shut up.
- I cut myself, it's bleeding.
- Please, go away.
Where's the money, bitch?
(Sobbing)
Why have you closed there?
Varya, I feel really terrible.
Varya, give me some money and I'll go away.
Please, go away.
- Please, go away.
- Bitch, I hate you!
(Sobbing)
Where's the money?
(Wind Blown)
(Sighs)
(Clatter)
(Birds Chirping)
(Door Creaking)
(Creaking)
(Birds Chirping)
(Door Open)
(Exhales)
Hi, gray.
(Door Close)
(Clatter)
Please... Please...
Please, please...
(Clatter)
(Sobbing)
(Exhales)
Thanks...
(Gasps)
(Ominous Music Playing)
(Dog Barking In The Distance)
(Gasps)
(Ominous Music Playing)
(Clatter)
(Engine Revving)
(Grunts)
Where's Vova?
(Gasps)
(Grunts)
I'm so...
(Footsteps)
(Growls)
(Grunts)
(Yelling)
Go.
Stop! Stop!
(Growls)
(Yelling)
(Cock A Gun)
(Growls)
Hey!
(Gunshot)
(Growls)
Let's put him on the table.
(Clatter)
Damn!
(Thud)
- (Thud)
- (Gasps)
What a fool you are...
(Thud)
Easy, easy... Easy, easy.
Shit.
Easy, easy...
Sh, sh, sh... hold on, hold on...
Sh, sh, easy, easy...
That's it, that's it...
That's it, that's it... Easy, easy.
(Gasps)
Easy...
That's all. That's all.
(Gasps)
He died because of you! Do you get it?
Because of you, bastard!
And mom died because of you.
(Growls)
- I don't feel the pain!
- Shut up, scum!
Shut up, you, both.
You tease him by shouting.
(Growls)
He must be taken to the hospital
to get the rabies vaccination.
Kite flying, tossing and turning...
(Growls)
...hide-and-seek, balls...
(Thud)
It still tries to come in.
If it breaks in here,
we'll climb out the windows.
- We'll set it on fire in here.
- And what if it follows us?
We don't have any chances outside.
And here...
Here we have some, because it's tight here.
(Growls)
You'll distract it with fire.
The main thing is to
get it on its hind legs.
And then the stake might come in handy.
Is it gone? It's gone, isn't it?
(Gasps)
(Growls)
(Thud)
(Gunshot)
(Growls)
Break the window! Run!
(Yelling)
Run, I said!
Dad, come on, go to the window!
Why are you standing?
Come here!
(Growls)
- (Growls)
- (Yelling)
(Growls)
(Yelling)
(Gasps)
Wait. Everything will be okay.
I'll get you out of here.
- (Gasps)
- (Coughs)
(Coughs)
(Gasps)
The winter hut will burn down,
you have to go.
(Gasps)
It's minus forty at night here,
you'll freeze.
We'll go together. Let me look.
Go up through the forest.
You'll get to the mountain pass there.
Press it. Press it harder.
Wait a bit.
(Gasps)
We'll go together.
I'll get you there, they'll heal you.
You'll go alone, otherwise you'll freeze.
Come on, slowly.
(Gasps)
There was plenty of time before...
...but I couldn't talk to you.
And now I wanna talk...
...but there's no time.
We'll have enough time.
(Ominous Music Playing)
(Gasps)
(Wind Blown)
(Grunts)
Do you remember,
you told me how mother gave birth to me?
Do you?
Tell it once more.
Dad? Can you tell me?
Okay, I'll do it myself.
She was giving birth...
...and you were standing
behind the wall in the hall.
She'd been screaming
for about four hours...
...she couldn't give birth.
And you were giving advice
about breathing or not breathing.
The doctors wanted to
kill you for that advice.
And then she said:
"Bring me a meat pie."
I'm not going into labor yet,
I'll have a meat pie.
They sell such tasty meat pies down there".
Can you imagine?
I was born 4,6 kg.
My mother knew I had to be
fed because I yelled in bass.
And I grew up skinny.
Dad?
Don't you die, okay?
I'll never ever take drugs anymore.
Never.
I promised it so many times.
But now it's really the last time.
Why are you silent?
Dad?
Dad, what are you doing?
You're kidding, right?
Come on, get up. Get up, dad!
Get up, dad!
Just a tiny bit to go yet, do you hear?
Get up, you, bastard!
I'll beat that crap out of you!
Do you hear?
If I managed, you can, too.
Dad, please, get up! Dad!
(Sobbing)
Get up, dad, please!
(Vehicle Approaching)
(Ominous Music Playing)
(Engine Revving)
(Door Open)
Here we are.
(Wind Blown)
Hello, dad.
I won't ask how you're doing.
You're good, I know.
It's been a year since
I stopped taking drugs.
So your trick worked.
(Wind Blown)
Varya and I decided
it's time to have a baby.
I want a girl.
(Wind Blown)
Damn, it took me so long to rehearse,
what to tell you.
And now it seems I have told everything.
(Wind Blown)
So what? Have you discussed everything?
What's he saying about the baby?
He says it's a great idea.
(Wind Blown)
- I'll go and swim.
- Meaning?
Directly.
Are you nuts?
The water is freezing cold. You'll drown.
Vova!
I won't drown here.
Dad taught me to swim here.
Why didn’t he teach you
somewhere in Thailand or Turkey?
In July here it's usually...
...warmer... by two degrees.
Vova, it's a really bad idea.
- Really?
- Really.
- Then come with me!
- No, Vova! Vova! Vova!
Vova!
(Birds Chirping)
(Peaceful Background Music)
(Waves Splashing)
[tatoo inscription: NO PAIN]
(Peaceful Background Music)