Here! Here!
Over here!
Guess what?
I'm not!
Stop!
What's wrong, sweetie?
Mama! I got mud on my knee!
Now it's a house!
Hello, Lynette, this is
Investigator Sharon Wright
from Cash Express Loans.
Please, please, please call me back
about your outstanding loan balance.
If I don't hear from you soon, I need to
escalate this to our repossession team,
and I do not want
to have to do that.
Investigator Sharon
Wright, Cash Express Loans.
888-555-0113.
If you're feeling the
pinch, you're not alone.
Numbers released by the Fed today
are confirming continuing inflation,
rising rents, and an
ever-concerning...
Ken. Come on.
It's a big day. We're closing
on the house, remember?
-One more minute.
-Get up. You say that every morning.
One University of Washington
economist put it this way...
Mom, get up.
...fundamentals of the
American economy are breaking,
especially in the job market
and the housing market.
People are actually being paid less
than they used to for the same jobs.
Middle wages are going
down thanks to inflation.
A hundred dollars used to
get you a lot of groceries.
Now you're spending twice that and
your bags are less full than before.
Economists believe it's
not just food prices.
According to new numbers,
the majority of all renters spend over
a third of their income on housing.
30% of Americans say they could
not pay a $1,000 emergency expense.
The consequences could be
disastrous, including eviction rates,
job losses, and mental
health difficulties.
Don't look at me like that.
Ugh...
Who can sleep with your
horse feet clomping around?
Don't sleep out there and then
you won't have to hear me.
Don't be an asshole.
It's too early to deal with
your constant criticisms.
We're meeting David at the attorney's
at 2:30 to sign the papers.
So you can't be
late. Do you hear me?
Yeah, okay. You don't need to
remind me every two minutes, okay?
If we don't put the money
down today, we'll be evicted.
Do you understand?
-Mom? Do you understand?
-Hey, Mommy.
Hi, babe.
Come here.
Mm. How did you sleep?
-Really good.
-I like that.
-Ken, where's your other shoe?
-What?
So you gotta pick up the check
from Chase on the way, right?
-Of course, I got it. Thank you.
-Okay. 2:30.
Come on, Ken.
Coming up here on
Portland 90.7 FM,
we're taking your
calls all morning
to know if you're feeling
the squeeze in this economy.
No sugarcoating it, folks.
Everything's going up
except our paychecks.
-Latest numbers from the Fed confirmed...
-Are you excited for the house?
-Oh, yes.
Uh, great times.
You know what it means to
own a home, don't you, Ken?
It means Social Services
can't take you away again.
Yeah. And I can
paint my bedroom red.
If you're homeless,
or live in a motel,
or are even just struggling,
everyone assumes that you deserve it.
It just takes one raise in rent,
one missed shift at work, and
anyone could be right here.
Everyone thinks,
"They're homeless because of
something they've done." Well, no.
Sometimes it's just like one slip-up,
one big bill coming in, and boom,
you're evicted, you're living in
your car, and there's no way back.
It's rare, but it's not. For
every one person who finds a home,
four more are forced out of
theirs. Think about that.
And if you have an eviction on
your record, nobody'll rent to you.
I think Americans are trained
from birth to hate poor people.
Even poor people hate poor people.
That's the DNA of this country.
We have wages falling,
prices going up,
housing completely
out of control.
It really feels to me
and to a lot of others
that the fundamentals of American
society are just breaking down,
especially when it comes
to jobs and housing.
"Working homeless"
ought to be an oxymoron.
And here I am living in my car, and
showering at the YMCA, and just...
You're gonna be okay
while I'm at work?
Will you ask about
the job at the bakery?
Yeah. I'm gonna ask him again.
I'm with you. For the rich,
Portland is this huge success story.
Rents are skyrocketing,
investments, luxury developments...
Life's great for
property owners...
Ah, it's a big day for you, huh?
Yeah. Though until it's
signed, I'm like, ugh.
-Just can't even...
-Mama doing all right?
Yeah, you know. She's a total
fucking mess like always.
Mm.
All right. Hit it.
The manager's here, Ken.
Come on, you gotta go.
Did you ask about the job?
Yeah, I... I did. There's
nothing right now.
Syrup on the side this time?
-Uh, no, top.
-No, side.
-No, top.
-Yesterday you said side.
-No, I did not say that.
-You can't change your mind all the time.
-Five dollars.
-I don't care.
-"Thank you."
-Yeah, give me.
Morning, Kenny.
-Ken, I'll be done in three.
-Okay.
In the end...
the differences between Monetarist and
the Keynesian approaches are just...
...differences in opinion on
how to maximize economic growth.
She looks like Hillary Clinton.
The driving force here is...
-He needs full-time care.
-Yeah, I know. That's under control.
-There are facilities for that.
-We're just in between facilities.
Find one. My
classroom is not it.
-Yeah, I get it.
-Um, my name's Kenny.
-Okay, but Kenny can't be here.
-Yup, we know that.
-You know I was bullshitting her, right?
-Yeah.
-You're not going back to that place.
-I'm not going back.
-Never.
-No.
-We're getting a house now, Ken.
-Cool.
Do I look okay?
-You look good.
-You think?
Mama better be here.
Why do I feel so nervous?
I... want you...
I want you to be,
you know, strong.
Strong and just be yourself,
and just be adorable.
There's this... Here she is.
Hi, David. I'm so sorry. We got
held up in traffic. It was...
-It's fine.
-Yeah, um...
-Oh, this is Kenny, you remember?
-Of course.
-Hey.
Uh, this is Mike
Gregory, my lawyer.
-Hi.
Hello, Mike.
Uh, thank you for the money off
and the extension that you gave me.
Of course! My dad would've
wanted you to have it, so...
Doreen's not with you?
We need both of you
to sign the loan.
Uh, of course. I mean, she
texted me to say, um...
Uh, she should be here.
It's probably minutes away.
Um, thing is we don't have a lot of time.
I have to go see a property in St. John's.
No, she's coming. She's
coming. I'll call her.
Uh, sure.
Stressful. I guess I don't
know what I expected.
Um, okay, I feel like
we've tried and tried here.
It's just...
-Hi, listen...
-Where are you?
I'm... I got, like,
held up. Where are you?
I'm at the attorney's office.
Uh, well, you're gonna have
to tell them I can't make it.
I... I can't talk about
this right now. Sorry.
Are you serious?
Mm, gotta... gotta go.
Is, uh... Is Doreen
gonna make it?
It's Doreen. You
know what to do.
...Sharon Wright
from Cash Express...
It's Doreen. You
know what to do.
Denise called in sick, so I'm
covering until you arrive.
Try not to be late...
Oh no. We're so fucked.
What is that?
It's a car.
Whose car?
Mine. Bought it.
Passed that dealer on the way to work.
They were having this Mazda Madness sale.
-You're not serious.
-I saw this beautiful white car.
So I went in, I hustled
them, and I got a great deal.
So instead of coming to the
attorney's office like we planned,
you left work, went to a car
dealership, and you bought a car?
Yeah, pretty much.
How much was that?
Um, I put 25 down, so my
monthly is almost nothing.
$25,000?
It's my money, right?
You just spent our whole
down payment on a car?
Well, I'm allowed to
spend my own money.
-Working at Fred Meyer till I drop dead.
-Do you have any idea what this means?
I've been saving for years, so I thought,
why not do something nice for myself once?
Why would you do this today?
That money is for the house.
I'm gonna go inside,
I'm gonna grab a Coke,
and then I'm gonna grab Kenny
and take him for a drive.
You didn't turn up because
you were at Mazda Mania?
-Really?
-It's Mazda Madness.
Mazda Madness, then?
We're gonna be evicted.
Do you understand that?
I mean, have you actually lost your
mind? We don't have anywhere to go.
We're gonna be out on the
streets. What do you not get?
I'm really sorry. It was
a shitty thing to do.
And I'm... I'm a
really shitty mom.
I know you're upset, and
that's the last thing I want,
but honestly, I didn't tell you
because I knew you'd be upset, and...
"Upset"? I just had to beg David
to give us till tomorrow...
David's a crook.
His loan is a shitty loan, and
the house is shittier still.
Everything's falling apart here.
Oh God. They're gonna
take Kenny away.
-I knew you'd act like this.
-Fuck, fuck.
Okay, listen to me, okay? I
told you I'm gonna do it up.
I told you I'm gonna fix
it up. Gonna make it nice.
Gonna make it so nice.
Because that's the point.
We'll never get another
opportunity like this.
This is our only
chance. Do you get that?
There's another offer. He's
gonna take the offer tomorrow.
-Do you understand that?
-I cannot.
-They'll take Kenny away.
-I'm not doing this with you now.
-Please just give me the keys.
-No. I'm not giving you the keys.
I am not having this
conversation right now!
Stop fighting!
I'm gonna take it back. I'm
gonna do all of the talking.
-I'm gonna tell them you made a mistake.
-But I haven't made a mistake.
You have. You have. Just give me
the keys. Just give me the keys.
-Give me the fucking keys!
-Hey!
-Give me the fucking...
-Stop fighting.
I hate when you fight!
Hey, babe?
Would you like to go for a
ride in my brand-new car?
-Oh God.
-So cool, Mom.
Okay. Okay.
But this... Mom,
this is about Kenny.
This is so cool.
Come on. We'll go to
Dairy Queen and celebrate.
We'll be homeless, and you'll be
living in that fucking Mazda, Mom.
-You wanna buy the house?
-Kenny will go back in that care home.
Get it on your
own. God love you.
-You go for it, okay?
-You know I can't get a loan on my own.
-You know that!
-Yeah, and whose fault is that?
And I'm gonna be out on the street
again. Is that what you want?
How long have you kept a job before you
blow it and you freak out at everybody
and start threatening
people and throwing shit?
I'm sorry. No, come
on. I'm begging you.
Please. Do not do this.
I'm begging you. Please.
Let's just take it back, okay?
I will go to the
dealership, tell them...
Can you not? Fuck off.
It's done. It's signed.
That's the contract, okay?
It's over, it's done.
Let go. It's over.
Oh God. Fuck.
Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna get the $25,000.
You are insane, and you
have lost your mind.
You've lost your mind.
Kenny, she's lost her mind.
Okay, just don't forget to pick
Kenny up tonight from Mona's, okay?
This is David Claremont
from Portland Real Estate.
Leave a message and
I'll call you back.
David, hi, it's Lynette.
Um, I'm sorry about today.
I just, um, I have something
I wanted to talk to you about.
It's kind of urgent. Would you
mind just giving me a call back?
Thanks.
You okay?
-You're late again! It's 6:30.
-I know, Tammy.
-I know. Sorry, I got caught up...
-Whatever.
I just wish you wouldn't be such a
slacker and be on time once in a while.
-Something happened.
-Not my problem.
-Can you grab that food order there, sis?
-Yeah.
-Hi, David.
-Are you backing out?
No, it's just that the bank is fucked
up and they didn't get the check in time
and we might just need a bit more
time because it's a weekend tomorrow.
Okay, enough already. I've
been more than generous.
I know. If you could just...
I know that you have, David.
You know that I know that you have. I
just need a bit more time, that's all.
-I just need one more day.
-Lynette, stop!
9:00 a.m. tomorrow morning.
If all the money is in my account,
we have a deal. Otherwise, it's off.
-$25,000 by 9:00 a.m.
-Okay.
-Last chance, Lynette.
-Yeah. Tomorrow.
Fuck.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
No.
Can I have one?
-Cody.
-I know.
-Scott, hi.
-You called?
-Yes.
-You free to meet?
Yes, I can, actually.
I'm free, that's right.
The usual place, okay?
Yes, that's great. We
can definitely do that.
-Fifteen minutes?
-Thirty.
Sure.
Right over there.
Help yourself.
-Where are you going, girl?
-I've gotta...
-No way. No.
-It's Kenny. I've gotta go.
-I'm so sorry.
-It's always Kenny!
-Hi.
-Hey.
Hi.
-Never seen you not dressed up.
-I know.
I thought I'd mix
it up a little bit.
It looks, um, good.
I was surprised you called.
You never called me before.
-No, I know. I never do.
-It was actually good timing.
I had the evening free.
That's great. I'm so pleased.
So why'd you call?
Well, I, um...
-I had this idea for us I'd like to share.
-Idea? Okay.
Is it a sexy idea?
-So, okay. So, you know...
-You know what? Let me get you a drink.
-Excuse me!
-Yes, hi.
-Two tequila on the rocks, please.
-Sure.
-Idea.
-Yes, an amazing investment opportunity.
I live in Kenton.
You know that area?
-From the news sometimes, yes.
-Yeah.
Yeah, I know,
right? It's so...
I live in a place there,
and the guys decided to sell it to us
for $40,000 under the asking price,
which I thought was a good...
-It's a really good deal.
-Okay.
-We got this one shot of getting us...
-Who's us?
My mom and my brother.
Oh, um... Yeah, you
should go for it.
Yeah, the thing is, is that
we lost the deposit on the...
Here you go. Two tequilas.
Thank you.
-Salud.
Yeah.
All right, so the thing is what?
Well, the thing is we had this deposit,
and it kind of went wrong today,
and I just wondered
whether maybe, um...
I wondered if you might be able
to, uh... lend me the money.
The, uh, $25,000.
For the house?
Yeah, no, but
through your company,
'cause I know you're really
good at this stuff, and...
Wait, are you joking?
You're joking, right?
I wouldn't ask you
if it wasn't...
I just really, I just...
I just need a bit
of help right now.
-Was wondering if...
-No.
-If you could ask people at work.
-Yeah, no.
Maybe there's a way
you can maybe...
I'm not looking to find a way to
work out any deals with you, Lynette.
Sure. Yeah.
Look, listen. Listen.
I like you.
Okay? I do. We have a
lot of fun together.
But I don't want to know that you live
with your mother and your brother.
You know?
Like, I pay to have a good time,
not to talk about that stuff.
Yeah?
I have enough worries as it is.
My kids always asking for stuff,
never saying "thank you" ever.
-You know?
-Yeah.
-You okay?
-Yes.
-Yeah, I'm great. I'm really great.
-Yeah?
-Still okay to go up to the room?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. Always.
Okay.
Here's, uh... the $500.
And I'm going to double
it as a parting gift.
It's been fun these
past few months.
It really has.
Good luck with the house.
Yes, honey. We'll talk about
it when I get home, okay?
Say good night to the
kids. Okay. Love you.
All right.
Fuck.
Shit.
Hey, Lynette, crazy question.
Did you see my key
fob in the room?
What the fuck am I doing?
Shit.
Fuck.
I know you've taken
my car, Lynette.
Call me right fucking
now! I mean it!
Call me back!
-Hi.
-Lyn-Lyn!
What are you doing here?
-I missed you.
-Hi.
What's going on? I thought
you were the delivery guy.
Oh! All right. Come on
in. Make yourself at home.
Oh my God.
This better be good. My Lyft's
gonna be here in five minutes.
-Is this where he's got you now?
-It's Robert's old bachelor pad.
You know, I'm making it my own,
and... I mean, look at this view.
Didn't have this at the last
place. Do you want a drink?
There's a whole
bunch right there.
-Yeah.
-Make me one too.
To what do I owe this
pleasant surprise?
I need to ask you something.
Ah-ah-ah-ah! No, no, no!
Don't touch those glasses.
They're Robert's. If you
break it, he'll kill me.
There's clean ones
above the sink.
Anyway, I wish I could stay
and get drunk with you,
but I was, like, ten
minutes late last week.
He does this thing that
my grandma used to do.
He, like, won't tell you why he's mad,
but they'll just, like, look at you
like a fucking chihuahua in the middle
of taking the biggest shit of its life,
like all cockeyed, like...
Like, it's actually quite
menacing and terrifying.
Can't stay long. I gotta
pick Kenny up anyways.
Why are you acting
like you're his mom?
Trying to prove you're a good
little girlie or something?
-Fuck off.
-Well, I'm just saying, you do too much.
Fuck. You smell bad.
You look like shit.
Do I? You have no idea.
Did I tell you I just
got back from San Diego?
He had some Senate stuff
to do in Corona Del Mar.
We stayed at the
Hyatt. Two rooms.
We're still doing the whole,
like, being discreet thing,
even though everyone knows we're
together, including his wife,
which is a whole 'nother story, but
I'll tell you that another time.
We're not gonna stay
at the Hyatt anymore.
They say the beds are Tempur-Pedic,
and they're so clearly not.
They're, like, cardboard.
It's false advertising.
You grew up sleeping on a couch,
and now you're complaining
about a fancy bed at the Hyatt?
Oh, you know what, Lynette? Fuck
you. I told you that in confidence.
God, you always bring...
You're so annoying!
Ugh, this shit
doesn't even come off.
I'll do it.
Can you open this?
-Can you hurry? I really have to go.
-Okay, Gloria. I've got a problem, okay?
And you know that
three grand you owe me?
I really need it tonight 'cause Doreen
fucked up the plan to buy the house.
I need that money back, okay?
-I knew she was gonna do that.
-Gloria.
Gloria, I'm serious.
-Look at this.
-Fuck.
Look at this.
Giovanni Versace.
That's how the Italians say it.
What do you think? Should
I wear this tonight?
It's kind of springy.
Gloria, I really need
my money back tonight.
-Nope! I'm not doing this now.
-I'm serious. We're gonna be evicted.
-You understand?
-My car's downstairs. I'm not doing this.
I'm gonna be turning fucking
tricks in my car again.
Ugh! You're literally
fucking up my vibe right now.
-Ugh.
-Babe...
Oh my God.
Did Robert put that there
to watch you change?
No, don't be crude.
I put it there. I prefer this version
anyway because he doesn't talk back.
-Do you, Bobby? That's my boy.
-Oh my God.
Anyway, you're just jealous
because my man is going places.
Yeah, jail.
Although I'm kinda stressed 'cause I
don't think he finds me sexy anymore.
Here. Can you put this on?
That must be hard, but I'm not
here to talk about your sex life.
I'm here to talk about
the money you owe me.
All right, Lynette, take the
stick out of your ass, okay?
You can't show up unannounced and start
emotionally blackmailing me for money.
That's what you did to me six
months ago when I bailed you out.
Lynette, I was in jail.
That situation is not this situation.
You're the only number I know by heart.
Like, that's just the way the
chips fell. Like, okay? Relax.
Take one look at me. How long do you think
I'd last at Columbia River Correctional?
-Yeah, not long.
-Okay, exactly. That settles that.
Unbelievable.
Gloria, come on.
Can you not ask Robert
for the fucking money?
Ask Scott.
I did. He said no.
He doesn't even call me
anymore. You stole him from me.
Well, it's ended now, so...
Whatever. I know you definitely
got way more than $3,000 off him,
so let's call it even.
Can't you ask those two
other guys you're seeing?
What the fuck, Lynette? I'm
not seeing them anymore.
Well, last week you were.
Now suddenly you're not?
What are you, the fucking feds?
Jesus Christ, Lynette. Do you know
what would happen if Robert heard you?
He'd throw me out! I'd be
back dancing at Mary's.
Give me my money
and I will fuck off!
-Ugh! My car's here. I can't do this.
-I'm gonna be working the streets, Gloria.
-You're unbelievable!
-Kenny's gonna be taken away. How...
Ugh!
Really bad time, Lynette!
My car's downstairs!
Will you stop shouting at me?
I am asking for my own money.
I can't just materialize $3,000
in the middle of the night!
What the fuck do I look
like, Bank of America?
I can't be your personal fucking ATM
machine every time you need money.
You know what? You told me
to mind my own business!
So you know what? I'm
minding my own business.
Maybe that's why nothing's going
right in your fucking life.
Maybe you need an
attitude adjustment.
Ugh! You see, now I feel
bad. Now I fucking feel bad.
You want the shirt off my back? You
want the wig too while you're at it?
You know what, Lynette?
Friends don't keep score.
Next time I do something nice for
you, I'll make sure to keep a tally.
How's that?
You know what Robert would do if
he knew I had the code to his safe?
It'd be so bad.
Oh my God.
He'd throw me out
of here so fast.
Five hundred. Take it or leave
it, that's the best I can do.
No! Five hundred? No,
I need the three grand.
Lynette, why are you doing
this to me right now?
My car is here!
Do you know what? It's fine. I'm
gonna work it out. It's all fine.
-I'm being crazy. He still likes me.
-Yes.
Okay, want me to drop
you off somewhere?
I just need a second.
Can I stay for a minute?
That'd be great, actually, because
I have a package on the way.
Okay. And don't forget
to double lock, okay?
Love you! Bye!
Cody.
Cody?
Hi.
I was waiting for you. I
just had a question for you.
-I'm supposed to be catching my bus.
-No, I know. It'll take one minute.
What's up?
I've been really fucking dumb, okay? And
I put some money in my safe ages ago.
And, um...
Uh, you know the digital ones?
-You know and you put the code in?
-Yeah.
And I put it wrong three times
tonight, and it's locked.
I wondered if you knew
how I could get it open.
-Call a locksmith?
-I tried. It's too late.
I don't have time.
I need it tonight. Do you
know how I might override it?
How would I know that?
-Because...
-Because?
-Well, I thought you might know how to...
-Why would you figure that?
I just thought you might know how to get
into the safe because you did time, right?
I did time? Who told you that?
Tammy told me that.
Fucking Tammy.
-Well, do you know?
-No, uh, look.
I'm not gonna lie. All this shit sounds
pretty fucking sketchy right now.
-I'm just asking. I just...
-I'm gonna catch this bus, all right?
Fuck!
Cody? Cody.
Cody, I'll give you $200 if
you just come and look at it.
Cody, I will give you
money. I will give you $200.
Just come and have a look at it.
Just have a look.
-What kind of safe did you say it was?
-It's just... What do you mean?
It's just a Home Depot one.
Where is it?
It's at my apartment.
It's three minutes from here.
What's in it?
It's just my money that I need
to get out of there right now.
Cody, I'm asking for your help.
All I'm asking is for you
to come and have a look.
-Just to look at it.
-You got a boyfriend?
-Mm-mm.
-Roommate, nothing like that? Live alone?
I live alone.
That's good.
So?
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I can
look at that for you.
-Just look at it?
-For four hundred.
-Four hundred?
-Yeah.
-That's cool?
-Four hundred. Let's do it.
-Does that work?
-Yeah, I'm down.
Yeah, that's good.
It's, um...
This is a nice place
for a bartender.
Thanks.
So this is, um...
Yeah. What do you think?
That ain't from Home Depot.
Um...
Can we get it open?
How am I supposed to know that?
Well, I mean, can we not just...
Can we, um, force
it open somehow?
So you'd want me to break
it in? That's it, huh?
No, it's not. I'm
giving you $400, so...
Four hundred to look at
it, and I looked at it.
To look at it? Okay. We're not
breaking it open. It's mine.
It's yours?
-Yes!
-Just like this apartment's yours?
Yes.
-And you're sure of that?
-Yes, I am.
Really?
It's my roommate's.
Your roommate's? You
told me you lived alone.
It's my ex-roommate's.
So she moved out, she left her safe,
and she left all your shit in there.
-Yes, okay?
-That's what happened, huh?
-You're sticking with that?
-Yeah.
Lynette, cut the bullshit.
Tell me the truth.
It is my girlfriend's, okay? It
is my girlfriend's apartment.
It's her boyfriend's safe that
I need to get the money out of.
And I need to get it out tonight.
And that is the fucking truth.
It's for my family.
It's for my family, all right?
You really should have
told me that before.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have lied.
I need this, Cody.
I can't believe I'm
doing this again.
Look, the only way to...
The only way to open up that safe is to
let someone drill through the layers.
-Drill through the layers?
-Yeah.
Can we not get them here?
You could if you want the whole
building to know what you're doing.
Can we not do it quietly?
Luckily I got a drill with
a fucking silencer on it?
No. There's no way.
We gotta take it out.
It's not gonna be cheap, either.
How much?
Eight hundred.
You wanna do it or not?
Mm-hmm.
-I have to.
-But you're good for it, right?
Yeah, it's in the safe.
You know, you better
not be fucking with me.
Mm-hmm.
I'll make a call.
Okay, Lynette, I get it. I
shouldn't have laughed at you.
Just bring back the car,
and we can discuss it, okay?
Do not be late getting
Kenny at Mona's.
Mona has an early
thing tomorrow.
This is an automated message
from Rose City Loans.
Your account is seven weeks past
due, and a payment needs to be...
Lynette, this isn't funny.
You know that's my wife's
car. Tell me where it is now.
You fucking piece of shit!
If you've done anything to that
car, I'll fucking kill you!
Hold it.
Thanks.
You guys moving out?
Yeah.
Gentrification.
-It's the worst.
-Yeah.
Yeah, one second, one second.
One second.
You gonna get that?
-Where are we going?
-South on 82nd.
What's your place like now?
-My place?
-Yeah.
-My home?
It's a bit rough. It needs
some stuff done to it.
I got like 12 hours to
get this money or I'm...
I'm past due on everything.
No one will rent to me on my
own, because... You know...
That sucks.
Where do you live?
Way out.
-It's all I can get on what Tammy pays.
-Hmm.
Two hours by bus.
You got family?
Not anymore.
So this guy is okay
to open this thing?
I mean, we're gonna
find out, right?
And we just take the money I'm
owed out of the back, right?
Close it, and then
we can just...
bring it back.
-Bring it back where?
-Back to the apartment.
-The apartment?
-Yeah.
It's right here.
What's up?
Hi, Mama.
What's going on, Mama?
Love you.
Make sure she's not alone, please.
And make sure this shit is down.
-You ready?
-Yep.
Let's go.
Carl, wake up, wake up, wake up.
So it's your safe, and you
forgot the combination.
What's in it?
Just my money.
-Your money?
-Yeah.
Okay.
Let's get it.
Keys.
Carl, help me with
the garage, please?
Get your shit together.
Come on. I'm serious. Come on.
Did you carry this all the way
over here with this skinny bitch?
-God damn.
-Come on. This way.
Ooh-whee!
That's a lot of fucking
money, if you ask me.
God damn.
Interesting...
What the fuck is
that, Carl? Huh?
No.
That ain't it.
Well, you know what we gotta do.
Gotta go old school.
-No, don't smash it up like that. Don't...
-Shut the fuck up.
Don't do that. Fuck.
Do not... It has to go back.
Yeah, one more, baby.
There she is.
God damn!
What do we got here?
Yep.
What the fuck?
Whose safe did you
say this was again?
It's just mine.
-Yours?
-Yeah.
-It's yours, huh?
-All this is yours?
-Yeah.
What do we got?
Got some nice male Rolexes here.
A lot of cash, and we
got a lot of cocaine.
-How do you know her, buddy?
-A girl from the bar.
A girl from the bar?
-Mm-hmm.
-Hmm.
-Carl.
-Yeah.
The fuck you bringing
that shit to me for, bruh?
-What the fuck are you doing?
-That's your shit, huh?
Fuck you, it's mine. It's mine.
-I just want my money, okay?
-That's what you want?
If you wanted your money, then
where the fuck did this come from?
It's a...
It's a what?
-It's a what?
-It's a...
-It's mine.
-Excuse me?
-No, it's not.
-Give me my shit now. Give me my shit.
-Whose safe is it?
-Fuck you.
-Give me my shit!
Bitch, who the fuck
you steal this from?
It's a girlfriend's of mine.
-Whose is this?
-Dude, what the fuck, man? Easy!
I told you. It's a fucking
girlfriend's of mine.
It's a girlfriend's now, huh?
Now we're getting to the truth.
Just tell me where the
fucking safe is from.
-She's an escort.
-An escort?
Yes, she keeps it
for a business guy.
He's not gonna know.
-How the fuck do you know that?
-He's not gonna care.
-Yeah?
-She's just an escort.
She keeps it for a business guy.
Why the fuck did you
bring it to me, huh? Hmm?
Fucking bitch.
They're trying to
motherfucking play us, Carl.
What the fuck you doing?
Get the fuck off me!
-Give it to me!
-Give me my fucking bag!
Fuck.
Ow!
Fuck! Give me the bag!
Damn it!
Stay back.
I'm gonna fuck you up!
Carl!
Shit!
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Listen to me! Listen to me!
Oh fuck.
I'm gonna kill you!
You are dead!
Shit, shit...
You are dead, bitch!
Oh God.
Get the fuck out of here!
Listen. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Run!
Cody!
Get the fuck in!
-Pull over.
-What? You gonna be sick?
-Hey, pull over.
-All right, all right, all right.
You all right?
Lynette. Relax, okay?
-Relax?
-Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Oh my God. What am I
doing? What the fuck...
We got the money, right?
Are you gonna answer that?
Have a shot.
Take the edge off a little bit.
Take the edge off?
We're alive, right?
Whose fucking safe
was it, anyway?
Just some politician.
Which means he can't come looking
for it. Not with the drugs.
That's good.
So you gonna count it?
-Can I ask you something?
-Depends.
When did you get out?
What did Tammy tell you?
-Tammy?
-Talking Tammy.
-You want to know what Tammy said?
-Yeah, what'd she tell you?
-She just said that you robbed someplace.
-Mm.
-That's what she said?
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah, but it's not the full story.
-What's the full story?
I was set up.
-You were set up?
-Yeah, that's the full story.
Who were you set up by?
-Some girl.
-Some girl?
-Yeah.
-Oh.
Supposed to be one thing,
ended up being another thing.
Mm-hmm.
That's life, isn't it?
It's, uh...
How much?
What?
How much is it?
It's about $19,000.
Nineteen grand?
That's a lot of cash.
You gonna take the rest
back like you said?
Nah.
No, I need it. I need it for
the house I told you about.
We were supposed to close
on it today, and I...
If I don't get it by
tomorrow morning, I'm fucked.
I just...
want to have one win, you know?
I've hurt a lot of people
that I care about and...
done some really bad
things, and I just...
I've just...
come way too far not to, so...
Yeah.
I just...
I just need... I just fucking...
need only four grand more.
Four grand, huh?
Mm.
What you laughing about?
Um...
You don't, uh...
You don't know anyone who
would take a Mercedes, do you?
-What, now you got a Mercedes?
-Yeah, I got a Mercedes.
Let me guess, belongs to
the dude with the safe?
-No, different guy, actually.
-Different guy? Jesus.
But it's his wife's, so I don't
think he's gonna report it,
because he'd have to
tell her who took it.
I think I can get you that four
grand if the Mercedes is real.
-You could get four grand right now?
-I can get four grand.
I gotta see it first.
-Make sure you're not fucking with me.
-Mm.
You show me the money,
I'll take you to the car.
Let's do it.
We have to go to my
place to get the cash.
Where are you? I'm at work.
Mona is freaking out.
Kenny's over there crying.
You were supposed to be there hours
ago. He thinks you're not coming back.
-Fuck.
-Why do you keep pulling this shit?
I'm sorry, it just... it
won't happen again, Mona.
-Don't worry about it.
-It was a really...
-Messed up day at work, and I just...
-Mm-hmm.
You know, it was...
It was tough today.
I love you, Mona.
I love you too, Kenny.
See you soon.
Ken, I'm sorry, babe. I just...
I had a crazy day at work.
And it was, you know... Tammy
was just the worst, and...
You... Do you forgive
me for being late?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
You had a good time?
Okay, there's a guy in the car that...
we're gonna drop him off somewhere quick.
-And then we're gonna go eat, okay?
-Is he a stranger?
No, no, he's a...
He's a cool guy.
-Really, really?
-Yeah, he's cool.
-Really cool?
-Yeah, he's a cool guy.
-Yeah?
-He's a really cool guy.
-Okay!
-He's cool, this one, okay?
This one's cool.
Be cool, Ken.
-That's my seat.
-In the back, babe.
Uh, this is... Uh,
this is Cody, Kenny.
-Hey, Cody.
-What's going on?
Doing good.
Uh, Cody is your boyfriend?
No, he's just a... He's
just a guy that I work with.
Cool.
You got a girlfriend, Kenny?
-Yeah.
-You got two girlfriends, haven't you?
-My man! What's their names?
Erica, Azica.
-One of them broke it off though, no?
-Got your heart broken, Kenny?
Yeah. We have been
together the whole time.
But the problem is
about, you know...
somebody else broke
it off from us.
That's shitty. I feel you, man.
-Kenny's a DJ.
-For real?
-Yeah.
-Yes, I am.
-What's your DJ name?
-DJ Kenny.
DJ Kenny! Okay.
-Or Kenny the Rapper sometimes.
-All right.
-You got bars?
-Yeah.
♪ I want to say yo, yo
Uh, Cody is so cool ♪
♪ And king of how
he chill with bros ♪
♪ And doing like a
show, oh Uh-oh! ♪
That was cold, DJ!
Gimme dap. Gimme dap.
-Told you he was good.
-Yeah, that's fire, man.
I gotta play something.
I gotta hear it.
-Got the...
-How you work this shit?
-You need an adapter for it.
-What is this?
You need to upgrade
this shit for real.
Do you know a guy?
You know I always know a guy.
-♪ To take the dank out of the baggie ♪
-♪ I got five on it ♪
♪ Got it good ♪
♪ Grab your 40,
let's get keyed ♪
♪ I got five on it ♪
Fuck. Chill out.
♪ It's got me stuck... ♪
Lock the door.
Lynette, why do I have
to keep calling you?
It's 2:00 a.m. Kenny
should be in bed.
Where are you? Mona said that
you had someone else in your car?
What are you doing?
Oh fuck.
You scared me.
-Can you open the door?
-Did you get it?
Yeah. How's that?
All right.
Is that it?
Yeah.
Why is the door open?
Because I panicked.
Fuck, I can't believe
it's still there.
-You got the key?
-It's in the bag.
All right, all right.
I showed you the car. You
gonna show me the cash?
You want $4,000 for
a stolen Mercedes?
Yeah.
You know, after everything
we did together...
you ever think of me?
You didn't even
give me the $800.
But I was... I was gonna
give you some money.
Yeah, but you could've
done that back at the deli.
Why didn't you?
Well, because...
Mm.
Because we made a
deal on the car.
Look, there's a new deal.
I want half.
Half the cash.
You want half of the...
-But the car's worth so much more...
-I want to split the cash.
A stolen fuckin' Mercedes. You have any
clue the danger you're putting me in?
What are you talking about?
You offered four grand.
Want your four grand? Look,
this is what your four grand is.
-That was fucking bullshit?
-Yeah, it was fucking bullshit.
I've been lying to you like
you've been lying to me.
-Calm down.
-Lynette, split the money.
-That was not the deal.
-It's only fair.
-The fucking car is worth 50 times...
-After all the shit we've done?
I don't give a
fuck about the car!
-I need this.
-What do you need it for, huh?
I need money too! I got nothing!
-I told you I needed it.
-I got a shitty parole job.
You know what? Fuck your house!
Now I want the whole thing.
-No.
-Yes.
-No. That was not the deal.
-Give me the fucking bag.
-Give me the fucking bag, Lynette.
-Fuck you.
Give me the fucking
bag, Lynette!
Leave my sister alone!
-Don't...
-Give me the bag!
-Leave her alone.
-I'm not fuckin' with you.
-Leave my sister alone.
-Shut the fuck up, Kenny.
Please don't do this.
-Give me the bag, Lynette!
-No, I need it!
-I need it!
-Give me the fucking bag! Give me the bag!
-Don't do this!
-Give me the fucking bag!
-Don't do it!
-Give me the fucking...
Give it to me!
Why are you doing this?
Leave my sister alone!
Jesus fucking Christ.
Okay, okay, okay.
Kenny, it's fine.
It's fine. Don't worry.
Okay, okay, okay.
You made me do it. You
know you made me do it.
Fuck you!
Fuck you...
Fuck you, Lynette.
I am worried about you.
So much.
Why... Why you have
to act so crazy?
Ken?
Uh, he'll have the pancakes
with syrup and butter.
-But can you put the syrup on the side?
-Yeah, I can do that. For you?
Just coffee, black. Just
make sure it's on the side.
-Yeah.
-Thanks.
Do you remember when Daddy used to go
to that place and he met that busboy?
What was his name? He used
to speak Lithuanian with him.
He used to love speaking his own language.
You remember that? What was his name?
Dominykas. Do you remember?
Remember I wanted us to go on a
trip there? I wanted us to, um...
go get a couple of
passports and run away.
Get us the hell out of here.
Kenny.
Kenny, look at me.
Cody was not a good
guy. He was a bad guy.
He wasn't a cool
guy. I got it wrong.
And he was trying to steal the house. The
house we've lived in our entire lives.
Is that what you want?
I miss my dad.
I know.
I know you do. Dad left
us, Ken. You know that.
Okay? And, um...
I still love you.
But I can't stand it.
-What? What can't you stand?
-A lot of shit stuff.
Yeah, okay, well, I got angry.
I got angry because he was
trying to steal from us, okay?
He was trying to steal from us.
That's why I got angry.
I know that. Dad told
me to protect you.
You're supposed to be
my big brother. Are you?
Yes.
You're my big brother, okay?
I'm your little sister.
Are you gonna be in this with me
or not? You gonna help me or not?
I am the man of the family,
and I'm going to help you.
You're the man of the family.
That's why me and you are
gonna do this together.
-Yes.
-We're in it together.
We're gonna do it for the
family, and know what?
We're gonna fuckin' do it.
We're gonna go together and
get the fucking money, okay?
-Okay.
-We are?
Yes.
Hello?
Hi, is Tommy there?
Um, who is this?
Just tell him it's Lynette.
What the fuck? Wait there.
Now, look who it is.
Long time, huh?
What brings you here, Lynette?
You still sell stuff?
-You see the store standing, don't you?
-Yeah, maybe.
Whoa.
Whoa! Not here.
So you must be the famous Kenny.
-Yes, I am.
-Yes, you are.
You know what? Here,
check this out.
-I am Zoltar...
-Awesome!
Yeah? You ever played one?
-Uh, yes, I have.
-Hey. Let's go.
Old-school pinball. You don't
need tokens or anything.
It's... You know how to play?
-Uh, yes.
-You do?
-Yes.
-All right.
Come on over and let
Zoltar be sharing...
I just gotta talk to Tommy
for five minutes, okay?
Jesus Christ. What the fuck?
Where did you get this?
Loose lips sink ships. Isn't
that what you taught us, Tommy?
That's fucking good.
Who is that upstairs?
That's none of your
fucking business.
And if you gotta know,
that's my girlfriend.
Nice.
It's your girlfriend, really?
You don't get to
come to my place,
middle of the night, and
start giving me shit, Lynette.
Just like all the years you gave
me shit? Five years of shit?
I never wanted you to
live here. You begged.
I begged because I was a kid, and I
was fucked up. That's why I begged.
I was looking for help, Tommy.
You weren't that much
of a kid, were you?
-Fuck you.
-Lyn?
Lyn?
-What's up?
-You okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Two minutes, okay?
-Okay.
Cool. Be out in a second.
How many of those girls have
you had upstairs since me, huh?
I don't do that anymore.
You don't make your girlfriends
sleep with other guys?
You know, I was...
You know, you had me so fucked up, I
thought I was in love with you, Tommy.
What you made me
do... was wrong.
A long time ago.
I did what I did to get by.
I was 16.
So how much are you gonna pay me
for that? How much is it worth?
It's a fucking half a kilo.
I do not have six grand
just fucking laying around.
So you don't have cash anymore,
like you always used to,
when I was upstairs?
You can find someone
that's gonna buy it.
-No.
-Yes you can. Right now.
I do not have to do
fucking anything for you.
This is the least
you could do.
Take your coke.
Look at you.
I'm really fucking sorry.
My guy'll give you three.
No, I need four.
It's the middle of the
night. You know someone else
who's gonna give you more money
for your coke, go to them.
Okay, what's the address?
His name's Blake. You know
those houses in Meadow Vale?
Up in the hills?
How could I forget?
Ring the gate when
you get there.
I give this to you
on one condition.
I don't want you to ever come here again.
Don't call, don't show up. Nothing.
You got it?
You should take these.
They belong to you.
Show yourself out.
You don't get to pretend
it didn't happen, Tommy.
Kenny, come on.
Okay.
It's okay, Kenny.
She looks innocent.
She's not.
You were right, Tommy!
-She's wild.
-How much to take her upstairs?
You weren't that much of
a kid, though, were you?
...that much of a kid...
I don't want to hear.
You take good care of
my friend here, okay?
He already paid.
He's paying, so
you be real nice.
-I don't like it here.
-I know. It's okay.
It's me and you, yeah?
I'll call you who
the fuck you are!
You act like a bitch, I
call you a fucking bitch!
Why the fuck did I
even bring you out?
Bitch, why would I stay home
with you, you dirty-ass bitch?
Start making my
friends richer...
Okay, meet here, yeah?
-Are you sure?
-Stay right here.
Alone at last.
Away from all those
horrid people.
Care for a drink?
No.
Oh, do you mind the
shoes on the rug?
I try to keep it clean.
Uh...
I mean, I'll just stand here.
Did you know there's
421,000 units of bacteria
on the single sole of a shoe?
-Here you go.
-No, I'm all good. Thanks.
Well, it's right
here if you want it.
So... tell me.
Friend of Tommy's?
How should we do this?
You want to see the stuff?
No, no, no. I trust you.
I don't know you, but I trust Tommy.
I mean, how do you want to get paid?
-PayPal?
-No.
OnlyFans?
-I'm a very good tipper.
-No, I need cash.
Cash, yeah.
Probably best not to have our
fingerprints all over each other.
Cash it is.
Don't worry.
I got it right here.
What did we say?
-$2,000, right?
-I agreed with Tommy $3,000.
$2,000 is for the coke.
You know what? Now
it's gone up to $4,000.
So you can give me the money or
I can get the fuck out of here.
Four thousand.
Tommy said you were fucking
wild back in the day.
I'm sorry, what?
Tommy said you used
to be pretty wild.
When I was 16, yeah.
So is this like a
trip down memory lane?
The money, and the drugs,
late-night parties.
I just want to know,
are you still wild?
Careful. Because you seem,
like, a little bit still wild.
Look, I'm... I don't know
what you think is happening.
I don't care what Tommy said.
That's not... That's not it, okay?
Not gonna argue. Give
me the fucking money.
Clearly, you know what
it is. Here you go.
Oops, it slipped.
It's yours.
$1,000.
$2,000.
What? It's yours.
Some over there.
Good girl.
And $4,000.
-Get out of my way.
-I'm not in your way.
-Yeah, get out of my fucking way.
-Look.
-I'm not doing anything. I just need...
-Just get out of my way.
-I just need to know that you're calm.
-Move out of my way.
-Okay, I will.
-No.
-I'm gonna move.
-No, don't do that.
-Careful.
-Do not do that.
Don't scratch. I
pay extra for that.
Do not do that. Do
not fucking do that.
Stop fucking touching me! You
think you can fucking buy me?
You think I'm fucking
trash? That what you think?
You think because you have
money, you can buy me.
-Jesus!
-You aren't gonna fucking touch me!
-You understand that?
-Oh my God! You're fucking crazy.
Crazy? Fucking crazy?
Want to see fucking crazy?
Fucking touch me!
Don't fucking touch me!
You weren't that much of
a kid, though, were you?
Shh.
There's no rush.
Yeah?
I don't want to go
upstairs with him, Tommy.
Take your dress down. Come on.
-Stay back.
-Okay. You got your money.
Shh.
Calm down.
No!
Fuck! Fucking bitch!
Kenny?
Kenny!
Where are you?
What the fuck?
Is that glass? Is it...
What the fuck...
-Where's my brother?
-Put the glass down.
She fucking attacked me!
She stole my fucking money!
Relax. Fuck...
Don't fucking touch me!
-Get her.
-Don't fucking touch me!
Put it down, bitch.
Hold her down,
man! Hold her down!
-Lyn!
-Kenny!
Lyn! Leave my sister alone!
Somebody fucking stop
this psycho bitch!
-I'm sorry.
-Are you... Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Hey. Sorry.
What the fuck, man?
Get the fuck out of my house.
I got the money,
baby. I got the money.
Let's go home.
Let's go home. Okay.
Okay.
It's over now. Get
some sleep, Ken.
Good night?
You take good care
of your brother?
Yeah. I spent the night getting
the money that you blew on the car.
All $25,000.
And we're out of time.
So please, please get dressed.
And come with me
to sign the loan.
Please.
Hold still.
Even your dad hated this house.
This isn't some
magical place, honey.
It's just all we could afford.
Be still.
Okay, that one's done.
If we don't...
If we don't do this right now,
we're gonna lose the house.
Okay?
-So I'm begging you.
-Sweetheart, I'm not... I'm too tired.
-I'm not having this conversation.
-I'm begging you.
-We're both tired, okay?
-Lynette, I know you don't wanna hear it.
But I don't want that loan,
and I don't want this house.
-Don't.
-Please, I'm begging you.
-I hate this house. I'd like to burn it.
-I'm begging you. Please.
That's what I would do.
Too many memories.
You were never serious
about buying it, were you?
This entire time,
you've watched me...
You've watched me...
You watched me do what
I do and what I did,
and you still, you said nothing.
I tried to tell you.
You wouldn't hear.
No, you didn't. You bought
a car instead of telling me.
Because I can't have you
screaming and freaking out at me.
I'm not! What do
you mean, screaming?
I'm not that person anymore.
I'm not that person.
I don't do that anymore.
-You know what? I'm...
-I don't do that. I'm not...
I'm picking glass out
of your back right now.
You just don't want to live
with me, that's what it is.
You don't want to
live with me, do you?
Oh, Jesus.
You don't.
You...
Okay. Okay, you know what?
You know what? It's fine.
Get some shitty
apartment. You go do that.
-Kenny's gonna come with me.
-Kenny's not gonna go.
-He's afraid of you.
-Yes, he is. Kenny loves me.
Of course he loves you,
but he's scared of you.
Kenny needs me. He knows that I
would never do anything to hurt him.
Is that right? So where'd
you take him tonight?
I am his mother, Lynette.
I have been taking care of Kenny his
entire life since before you were born.
Well, you know what? I
will fight you for him.
Is that a joke? Are you kidding?
And what are you gonna say?
That you tried to kill yourself?
That you sleep
with men for money?
You... You become violent,
that you can't hold down a job?
You would fucking love that,
wouldn't you? You'd love it.
You'd tell them you have
a fucked-up daughter.
You know, you forgot
all about Kenny
when you ran away and
moved in with Tommy.
And I was fine being his mom then,
right? You were happy about it then.
Don't you dare! I was just...
I was 16! I was trying to be with
someone who actually loved me.
-How did that work out for you?
-It didn't work out because I couldn't...
I couldn't...
I didn't... I don't...
You don't think... You
don't think I know...
You don't think I know who I am?
You have no clue.
Where were you?
I needed you when he...
I needed you to...
I just needed my mom.
I can't save you.
I can't help you, so...
Shit.
You can keep blaming me, but
you're a grown woman now.
You want to blame me? Go ahead.
You're like that thing at
the bottom of a toilet bowl.
You just, like, suck
everything down with you.
I can't do this anymore.
I made plans with Mona. Kenny
and I move in there next week.
Yeah.
Hey, Lynette. It's David.
I am so sorry.
I've changed my mind.
I've taken the higher
offer from the other buyer.
I gave your family
all the chan...
-Hey.
-Hi.
Kenny, I have to go
away for a while.
I'm gonna come back and visit you
as soon as I can, okay? I promise.
I love you.
I really love you.
I'm gonna think about you every second.
Gonna love you every minute of every day.
Okay?
You are my little sister.
And I will always
be your big brother.
-Yeah.
-And I will always protect you.
Yes, you will.
Okay.
I'm gonna have to go to bed now.
You have to go to bed?
-I have to go to bed.
-Okay.
Mom.
You asked me what
I did last night.
I fought.
I fought for this family.
The only way I know how.
But I guess you said
what I needed to hear.
So... thank you.
And now I need to fight for me.
Take care of Kenny.
He needs his mom.
Maybe this is our
chance to get it right.
Lyn.
♪ Wall eyes ♪
♪ Ceiling felt too high ♪
♪ Nights were
falling down skies ♪
♪ Was no look in the eye ♪
♪ Subtle moments of past ♪
♪ What a wondering time ♪
♪ Come back ♪
♪ Swallowed over the stage ♪
♪ Turning into the rage ♪
♪ Wondering what
forced the age ♪
♪ Towards tomorrow ♪
♪ Come back ♪
♪ Was wild and unsure ♪
♪ And naked and pure ♪
♪ Come back ♪
♪ Turning into over my mind ♪
♪ Jumping on tenuous time ♪
♪ Come back ♪
♪ Moments of faith ♪
♪ Turning out late ♪
♪ Come back ♪
♪ Or does anyone care? ♪
♪ Ominous state ♪
♪ Come back ♪
♪ Neighboring love ♪
♪ Won't stay in the home ♪
♪ Come back ♪
♪ Moments of fire ♪
♪ Can turn the
car on back home ♪