Please, get me to a hospital!
I can't breathe.
You know what? If you were smart,
you would stop talking right now.
Sue me. I just know that women
should never work for women.
How can you say that?
Because they're always threatened.
Especially if you're beautiful,
and they're not.
Fine! You never had a fight with your boss?
Never. You know why?
Because he's a man.
Can we please drop this?
I just want to go home and kiss my son.
Honey.
See, you have to mention
that you have a child and we don't.
-There's my point.
-Erit, I didn't say anything of the sort.
Don't apologize, it's genetics.
Women are always competing
with each other.
That's why you're having problems
with your boss.
-Because she's a woman.
-Exactly.
Women should work under men,
men under women. That's it.
What about men under men?
That's fine, too.
I mean, they can deal with it.
-Can we go now?
-Either of you guys want another drink?
-We're good.
-Shot? Double?
Women can do amazing things.
I am one. I know.
But even I would never work for me.
That we can agree on. Good night, Mick.
We are in a bad mood.
She's got a point, bro, you know.
I'd much rather work under you than her.
That's nice. I'd rather work under him, too.
You'd rather "work" under John?
You have a problem with that, too?
No! Why would I have a problem
with your Iittle sexual innuendo?
What is up your ass tonight?
So I should just sit here while you come on
to my husband right in front of me?
Lara, if I wanted your husband,
I would have him, Iike that.
How? You couldn't possibly show him
more of those tits.
-You know what your problem is?
-Okay...
My problem is your brain
is as big as those tits.
-Baby, this is your fault!
-Huge, exactly!
This is your...
If you had half a brain,
we wouldn't be having this conversation.
Baby. Let it go, Iet it go, Iet it go.
-Good night, brother dear!
-Good night!
-She's completely full of herself.
-Don't try and agree with me now!
I don't even think
she's a member of the dental profession.
Shut up!
She probably can't even
spell "anesthesiologist."
-The woman's a complete fraud.
-We went to her office party, you idiot!
And I believe she hit on me
that night as well.
You are completely delusional. She didn't
even hit on you in there. I just don't Iike her.
I understand your point of view. I really do.
I agree with you.
Somebody who Iooks Iike that should not
be allowed anywhere near oral surgery.
You are an asshole!
You're sitting in the chair,
you're trying to stay calm,
and you got them things
hanging in your face...
-So, see you next weekend. AII right?
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Good night.
-Bye.
-Bye!
Bye!
Oh, gee.
Look at this.
-Now you say go.
-Go!
Smash.
AII right, squeeze in.
You know, you can't do this every morning.
It's way too corny.
Come on. Smile.
It's just till he's 18.
-A present.
-Oh, great. What's that?
You hate brushing your teeth
and that brushes them in 30 seconds.
I Iove brushing my teeth.
Don't believe everything your mother says.
-What time's your Iast class?
-3:00.
But I got some papers to grade.
Can you pick up Luke?
After yesterday,
I probably don't have a job anyway, so...
Was it wrong of me
to call her a useless cow?
I think bosses admire
that kind of frank exchange.
-Did you call your dad?
-When?
Birthday, yesterday!
Yeah, I sent him some freshly cut flowers,
Iittle pink roses.
I sent him a handmade card.
And I finished that quilt I've been sewing
since spring.
You are completely impossible.
Did you notice what I got for my birthday
this year? I got a grunt.
Mom said, "Happy birthday, sweetheart,"
and Dad went...
It was just... It was a beautiful moment
in my Iife. I teared up.
Ever think that somebody has to be
the bigger person here?
Now I want you to remember this
for the custody hearing,
how Mommy is always
scolding Daddy, okay?
Can you remember that?
You know, how are you gonna feel
when Luke grows up
and doesn't call you on your birthday?
And now she's trying to drive a wedge
between us.
-I give up.
-And now she's abandoning you.
Hey, buddy, do you wanna try
and knock him over again?
You ready? Line it up.
-Line it up now and you say go.
-Go!
I got it.
Pittsburgh Police.
This is an arrest warrant for Lara Brennan...
-Arrest for what?
-...and a search warrant for the premises.
-Hold on!
-Lara Brennan?
-You touch me again, I'm gonna arrest you.
-Hold on.
-Stay where you are!
-This is my house!
-Lara Brennan?
-Yes!
I will arrest you.
You're under arrest for the murder
of EIizabeth Gesas.
-Calm down!
-I got my kid in the kitchen!
What are you doing?
Arrest her for what?
-Turn around!
-Mommy!
-John! John!
-You have the right to an attorney...
Go get Luke. Go get Luke.
-...understand these rights...
-Luke!
It's okay, buddy! It's okay!
-Mommy!
-Luke!
It's all right. It's okay!
Daddy! Daddy!
-Daddy!
-What's wrong? What's wrong, buddy?
What's wrong?
I got you.
Well, you can stay in here
as Iong as you sleep on this side of the bed,
all right?
You Iittle snake.
I don't know why I keep falling
for the same old trick.
You have your tricks, don't you?
Hey, go to sleep.
Go to sleep.
-But Sam is your friend, right?
-Not at Iunch.
-Why, does he steal your food?
-No.
-Did he say something mean? About Mom?
-Yeah.
-Did you hit him?
Good. Where'd you hit him?
On the playground.
Wow! That must have hurt.
Hold it there, son.
It's a toy.
Thank you.
Hey. AII right.
And the other arm.
Don't worry about the car.
We'II get it back Iater, okay?
Hey!
Hi, honey!
Hey.
You won't give Mommy a kiss?
Can Mommy please have a kiss?
Rat-bag. Give your mom a kiss.
-Is Daddy reading you my Ietters?
-Every night at bedtime.
Yeah?
You smell so good.
What are you gonna build today?
You gonna build a fort?
A door? Or a castle?
Hey.
Was he scared going to school?
No. I walked him to his class,
gave him a kiss, he just walked right in.
Didn't even turn back for a wave.
Look at his friends!
And his desk.
-How was your first day?
-Excellent.
Half the class stayed awake, you know.
-I talked to your mom.
-When is she coming?
She's having a Iot of trouble
with her business, so...
Well, it's only been a couple of years,
I'm sure she'II get around to it.
Have you heard anything?
About the appeal?
Yeah, and I've just decided not to tell you.
-Remember what Meyer said.
-Don't.
It can take months for a court
to make a ruling.
I saw that woman. She was there.
She couldn't have just disappeared.
Meyer is Iooking for a new investigator.
Her coat snagged my purse,
and I felt that button pop,
and they're blind if they can't find it.
He's gonna go through
all the evidence again.
That's great,
because we're not quite bankrupt yet.
We're fine.
How you just Iie and Iie.
But you're so handsome.
Can you do me a favor?
I don't know, I'm kind of busy.
I need you to run for governor.
I can do that.
You can change this rule
about no conjugal visits,
'cause I don't think
I can Iast another 20 years.
Hey.
I'm okay.
-I'm okay.
-Everything is gonna be all right.
I promise.
You think he'II ever kiss me again?
I need you to stand up.
Tag, you're it.
Luke! Let's go, yard ape.
Hey.
-Have fun?
-Yeah.
She's kind of crazy, that Iittle girl, right?
Time to go, Carrie!
No!
He didn't even read the thing. Half the time,
I'm telling you... We'II get him in there.
What happens if we find the woman
who was Ieaving the parking Iot?
The PCRA has been rejected.
No new evidence can be submitted.
Not anymore.
It was a robbery.
And if they had used her credit card,
we could have argued that.
I'm... I'm sorry.
John...
This sucks.
Okay. That's that.
AII we have now
is the Supreme Court, right?
John, in the Iast 30 years,
the Supreme Court
has not heard one murder case.
No decent Iawyer
would even file the pleadings.
So, all I have to do is find an indecent one?
That shouldn't be too hard.
I'II file it.
But I need you to do something for me.
What?
I need you to Iook at the evidence
and forget that Lara's your wife.
I've seen the evidence, Meyer.
I'm not saying judge her innocent or guilty,
I'm just saying Iook at it.
Her co-worker sees her Ieaving the scene,
the victim's blood is on her clothes,
her fingerprints are on the murder weapon.
And then we went out to dinner.
How do you do that
if you just killed somebody?
That would make her a psychopath.
-And the fight...
-Is Lara a psychopath?
-The fight in the office?
-Everyone fights with their boss!
But this one ended up dead.
So what you're saying is that
you never believed in her innocence?
-How can you say that?
-What are you saying, Meyer?
I'm saying that it no Ionger matters
what we believe,
Lara is not getting out!
And you have no idea
how much I hate to say that.
I will find someone to file the pleadings.
John.
John, come on. John!
John!
John! For Christ's sakes!
Come on.
We'II find Scout, okay?
Thank you.
"And give a big hug to Pengui,
Little Pengui, Kiki and Opossumy.
"Lots and Iots of Iove, Mommy."
Should we write her back?
Can I have a quarter?
Can you have a quarter?
Yeah, but you know you can't spend these.
Because they come from the cottage
where Mom and I used to take you
when you were a baby.
Then can I have them all?
Sure.
My wife, Lara Brennan,
she was sent up here.
-Brennan, B-R-E-N-N-A-N.
-I'm sorry, but she can't have visitors.
That's ridiculous. I have to see her.
-Lara! Lara!
-I'm sorry.
You can't go down there!
-You can't be in here!
-Hey, hey, stop. Stop right there.
-Where you going? Hey, come back here.
-Lara!
-Sir!
-What the hell is going on?
-My wife attempted suicide.
They brought her up here.
I have to see her, please.
-She's not allowed visitors.
-So why isn't she in the ER?
-Because she's a transfer from County Jail.
-Just two minutes, please.
Two minutes.
Okay.
Thank you.
Two minutes.
So, The Life and Times of Don Quixote.
What is it about?
That someone's belief in virtue
is more important than virtue itself?
Yes, that's in there. But what is it about?
Could it be about
how rational thought destroys your soul?
Could it be about the triumph of irrationality
and the power that's in that?
You know, we spend a Iot of time
trying to organize the world.
We build clocks and calendars
and we try and predict the weather.
But what part of our Iife
is truly under our control?
What if we choose to exist purely
in a reality of our own making?
Does that render us insane?
And if it does,
isn't that better than a Iife of despair?
It's a course that investigates what
drives men to be free, no matter the cost.
Some other teacher had dibs on Papillon?
You escaped from jail seven times.
What do you want to know?
How you escaped when no one else could.
Balls and a Iittle Iuck.
No prison in the world is airtight.
Each one has a key. You just have to find it.
How do you do that?
A Iot of Iooking.
Especially at things
that break up the daily routine.
Guards get comfortable
doing the same thing day in, day out.
Something happens,
that's when they make mistakes.
When you see it, you have to be ready.
You have to have the entire plan
already in place,
even before you know
how you're going to get out of jail.
Escaping is easy,
the hardest part is staying free.
You have to know where you're gonna go
and how you're gonna get there.
You have to know how they plan
to catch you, where and when.
Well, how the hell
are you supposed to know that?
You pay off someone who knows.
And a Iot depends on
if the prison is in the country or the city.
City.
Where are you from?
Pittsburgh.
Pittsburgh's tough.
So many bridges and tunnels
they can block off.
From the time they make the call,
the police can have the center of the city
sealed tight in 15 minutes.
How can they be so exact?
After 9/11, Homeland Security
made every city have a Iockdown plan.
Downtown Pittsburgh, Philly, Boston,
Minneapolis, 15 minutes.
They can do D.C. in under 10.
Within 35 minutes, they can have cops
at every tollbooth on the interstate
and be running rolling stops
on the secondary roads.
They won't have your photograph yet,
but they will have your description.
What if you can't get out?
Thirty-five minutes is not a Iot of time.
Then surrender.
Because they will shoot you on sight,
along with anyone else you're with.
Stay far away
from the train and bus stations.
Forget the local airports.
Leave from another state.
Second, identity.
It's easy to find fake papers,
harder to find ones
that will get you through an airport.
You'II need a passport, a driver's Iicense
and a social security number.
If you have to rent a car,
find a place that will take a cash deposit.
They'II still run a credit check,
so use a real person's name on the ID.
Third, destination.
You want somewhere
that doesn't attract American tourists.
Think Yemen, and you get the idea.
And money, you'II need a truckload of it.
Everything's expensive,
hotels, travel, information.
How much?
Enough to last at least five, six years.
You run out of money,
you run out of friends.
But before you do anything,
you have to ask yourself if you can do it.
Can you forget about ever seeing
your parents again?
Can you kill a guard?
Leave your kid at a gas station?
Push some nice old Iady to the ground
just because she gets
between you and the door?
Because to do this thing,
that's who you have to become.
And if you can't, don't start,
'cause you'II just get someone killed.
How did you get caught?
I gave myself up.
I couldn't take wondering when someone
was gonna come through the bedroom door.
So, what do you have in your pocket?
Good Iuck.
No prison in the world is airtight.
Each one has a key. You just have to find it.
How do you do that?
A lot of looking.
Especially at things
that break up the daily routine.
And on the left, the Allegheny County Jail,
now the largest jail in the world.
There have been three escape attempts
of which no one has made it out alive.
If you look to the right, south side...
"On the first Ianding, which was as small
as the necessary turn of the stairs allowed,
"there was a niche in the column,
about half a yard wide,
"and in this niche, the prince felt
convinced that a man stood concealed.
"He thought he could distinguish
a figure standing there..."
25, 26, 27,
28, 29, 30.
Good?
And money, you'll need a truckload of it.
Everything's expensive,
hotels, travel, information.
It's gonna take our selection.
Then we're gonna wanna use
our magic Iasso tool
to get the door out of the background.
Hey.
Identity. It's easy to find fake papers,
harder to find ones
that will get you through an airport.
-OxyContin.
-$10 apiece.
Give you five for $40.
Hey, I need some passports.
Piss off, man! Beat your feet.
Okay, boy!
You got to pay upfront for the passports, yo.
-I can do that.
-You know the Hotel Lafayette?
It's on Main Street. When you get there,
go to the bar, ask for Harv.
What's your name?
Tell him Mouss sent you.
Harv? I'm Iooking for Harv.
-Are you Harv?
-Yeah.
Mouss told me to come and see you.
He did, did he? What do you want?
Three passports, a driver's Iicense,
and a real social security number.
How do you know Mouss?
He babysits my kid.
Okay, follow me.
-You got the photos on you?
-Yeah.
-How much?
-$1,500.
If I ever see your face again,
you're gonna Iose an eye.
Yeah, it was stupid. I fell off the bike.
You mean the bike that's been in our garage
for two years?
Put your head back.
Some guy made a crack about Lara.
So that's what you do now? You punch
everybody who thinks she's guilty?
What's that supposed to mean?
It means it's important what you believe,
-not what somebody else...
-Really?
-Do you believe, Mom?
-Why are you trying to start a fight?
Come on, buddy. Let's go. Where's his bag?
-Why are you doing this?
-No reason.
I just stupidly thought that the people
who Ioved her
would actually believe she's innocent.
My mistake.
Stop this!
Go give Grandma a kiss.
Come on.
Does your face hurt?
A Iittle.
Did you hit him back?
No, I... I didn't.
That's okay.
Okay, buddy?
I'm Iooking for someone
who does high-end IDs.
Passports, social security cards.
Get out of here.
Yeah?
I was at the bar.
I know what you are Iooking for.
I'm deaf, you idiot. I read your Iips.
What do you need?
Passports, driver's Iicense,
a social security number
that'II take a credit check.
$3,700.
That's too much.
It is if you never get them.
I need photos and $1,000 in advance.
-I'II bring them Wednesday.
-Hey, not here.
I don't want you coming back here again.
Parking Iot of Don's. Eckert Street.
Under the bridge, 2:00.
If I'm not there on time, Ieave.
Put your thumb right there.
-Thanks. That's all I need.
-Thank you.
I'II just be a few moments.
GIasses?
Yes.
Yeah, I found myself falling asleep
grading papers.
When?
I guess about a year ago.
A year ago.
Look at you.
How can you do this to yourself?
I am hopeless without my wife.
I can't even ride a bike.
Sorry about the house.
I won't know where to picture you.
I close my eyes, I see Luke in his bedroom,
and you on the sofa by the window.
I won't know where to picture you anymore.
Show me where the bullets go.
Hi, it's John.
Luke's not feeling too well.
So I'm gonna pick him up
and take him home, okay?
I need Carl to cover my 3:00 class.
Thanks.
You ever gonna answer
your goddamn phone?
You were supposed to Ieave.
I need them.
You notice that guy was a cop?
Just give me the money.
You want this too much.
You're gonna fuck it up.
Hey, Mr. Brennan.
Today I'm gonna show you
how to make a key that can open any lock.
It's called a bump key.
First thing you need to do
is you need to find a key
that can fit into the type of lock
that you're trying to open.
Here I have a key
that fits into my front door,
but I just changed the locks,
so it won't open.
First thing you need to do
is secure your key,
take a metal file and go through and
start taking those mountains and valleys
all the way down
to the lowest possible setting on the key.
The bump key works
by momentarily bumping those pins up,
so that for a split second,
the chamber is cleared of pins
and thus, able to turn and open.
-Here you go.
-Don't touch that.
-Sorry.
-Trying to do my job?
So you are where in here?
I'm in the middle there.
In the middle. Can you point to yourself?
That's me.
There.
So that's not you back there
by the elevators.
No, no, I was around here somewhere.
You wanna tell me what's going on?
You want me to tell you?
Yes.
Do you know what a bump key is?
Sorry?
If this was you,
you might wanna think about
what's gonna happen to your kids
if both their parents end up in prison.
Dad?
Dad!
Yeah, bud.
Yeah.
Thanks.
So we arrested his wife, and now
we're gonna charge the man with vomiting.
He's selling the house. Or he has a buyer.
In this market? Lucky man.
Can we possibly go do police work now?
I don't know how you managed
to stay single this Iong.
Dad, can I have my cookies?
-You hungry? You want a sandwich?
-No.
-There you go.
-Thanks.
Carrie!
I'm sorry.
She's just already got it all figured out.
Nicole.
-I remember.
-Really?
I remember your daughter.
Well, she's hard to forget.
Luke was supposed to bring this home.
He has his father's memory.
It's for Carrie's birthday party.
PIease, come. I'd Iove to meet your wife.
She won't be there.
It's complicated.
I understand. With me, too.
Carrie, come on, Iet's go.
We're gonna grab a bite to eat.
Would you Iike to come?
-No, I don't... We're kind of...
-Busy?
Come on. We owe you for the cookies.
Well, that's true.
And I did make those cookies myself.
And Iearned how to pre-package them.
Come on, Luke.
So, do you trade off time with Luke?
No, Luke and I are together full-time.
Wow. I guess that's why I see you so much.
She'd Iike nothing better than to be here,
with him.
Lara, she... She misses all this.
I guess it's all about priorities, isn't it?
No, she's not Iike that.
She's in prison.
-I don't tell most people.
-I understand.
She's innocent. She didn't kill that woman.
Good. I mean...
I'm sure she didn't.
We really should be going home.
Okay.
Thank you very much for the invitation.
We'II try and make it.
That would be great.
-Goodbye. Luke!
-Bye.
Come on.
Carrie, come on!
-Hey.
What's wrong?
What is it?
No.
They can't move you without notice.
Three days isn't notice.
I was only here through the appeal.
We knew I was going to a prison.
No, no, I don't have two weeks.
I gotta close the escrow tomorrow.
Well, the title hasn't even been cleared yet.
I mean, there's no way I can...
How much can they give me?
Nothing!
What are you doing here?
I've got class.
You be good, okay?
Thanks.
Are you okay? You're okay?
-Are you okay?
-What are you doing?
You almost killed us!
I'm so, so sorry.
You're out of your mind. You don't Iook.
Get away. Get away from us!
Hey.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Is it Luke?
-No.
-What?
I... I asked Meyer
to Iook into not having you moved.
I told him that traveling that distance
would be a hardship on us,
that Luke was already having problems
at school, which is true.
I haven't been spending
enough time with him.
You haven't?
No.
Jesus, John.
You really are too much.
Luke is having a hard time,
because Mommy's in jail for murder,
not because Daddy doesn't spend
enough time with him.
Your father was right. You really don't
Iive in the same world we do.
That's nice, that the two of you talk.
What world do I Iive in, Lara?
Well, I don't know, John,
but it's not the real one.
The one in which I'm in here
for the rest of my Iife.
So don't be talking to me about fantasies
Iike there's some happily ever...
We good here?
Yes. Sorry.
Now you're gonna sit here all Iong-faced,
Iike you Iet me down.
I mean, what do you want me to do here?
You want me to make you feel better?
Got it.
I'm sorry.
Now you're apologizing.
You really are a gem.
-What do you want from me, Lara?
-What do I want from you? Nothing.
You're already too perfect.
You know,
you never even asked me if I did it.
-If I killed her.
-Because I know you didn't.
Well, then you'd be wrong.
I'm done.
Sir, you can't stand there.
Sir, I need you to Ieave the building now.
Sir?
-What?
-Shut up.
I don't care what you say or how you say it.
I don't believe you did it.
And I never will.
I know who you are.
And I promise you
this will not be your Iife.
Shut up!
-I don't know what's going on, man.
-You done?
Everybody is out.
I gotta get back to Jimmy.
Back away! Back away!
Drop the gun! Drop it!
Put the dog away!
You shoot the dog, I'II kill you!
-You want the police here, asshole?
-Good idea!
Get in, get in, get in!
-You, too!
-I'm not getting in there!
Get in there!
Get in! Get in! Get in!
AII right, Iock it. Lock the door.
-Move!
-You are dead.
-I didn't do anything.
-You brought him here!
I didn't bring him!
On your knees! On the floor!
AII right. Where's your money?
Here. It's worth it to get rid of you.
-Where's the rest?
-Here.
-Take more.
-Where do you keep your money?
I'm gonna give my money to you. Yeah.
-I'II shoot you.
-You can't even shoot a dog.
-I'II kill you both!
-No, I'm gonna kill you both!
-Just give him your money!
-Keep your dead bitch mouth shut!
Give him your money!
Jesus!
See? You ain't gonna kill me.
This is the worst you could do?
Go home.
I'II come, I'II find you and I'II kill you.
You're wasting some good shit there!
Yeah, good shit.
High alcohol content.
What are you gonna do?
You gonna burn me out?
Yeah. That's what I'm gonna do.
Jesus Christ!
This is a meth Iab, you idiot!
No.
It was.
Tell me! Where's your money?
My kid is upstairs!
-Get up!
-Jesus!
Get up!
PIease.
PIease, Iet me go, please.
Anybody here?
Don't Ieave me here.
I don't wanna die here.
PIease!
PIease, get me to a hospital!
I can't breathe.
PIease.
I can't... I can't...
Get out of my way.
-What do we have?
-A freaking miracle.
Meth Iab in the basement,
the house still standing.
Should be just a crater.
We know him?
AIex Gaidar,
history of violence and drug trafficking.
He have a kid?
Neighbor said wife Ieft with him Iast year.
Big surprise there.
And this blood,
they type it all yet?
No, but someone Ieft through
the back door bleeding.
Zone Three found a gunshot victim dead
on a transit bench.
Hey.
I've just come to pick up Luke.
He's sound asleep.
Yeah, I've just come to get Luke.
John.
Are you all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Hey, buddy.
Wake up, bud, we're going home.
So, what do you say?
Thank you, Grandma.
I think you should give Grandma a big kiss.
-I'm too tired for kisses.
-Buddy.
That's okay.
I'II get Iots of kisses next weekend.
We want to take him
to the Fall Festival in Kutztown
where the CIydesdales are.
-See you.
-Bye.
Bye.
Hey.
-Bye, Grandpa.
-Bye.
Goodbye.
Bye, Mom.
Bye.