Everything I have said and done
has been in the hands of God.
I was born to do
this, I am not afraid.
Everything I have said and done
has been in the hands of God.
I was born to do this.
I am not afraid.
Everything I have said and done
has been in the hands of God.
Everything I've said and done
I was born to do this.
I am not afraid.
-Oh, hey.
-Hey.
Why are you sitting over here?
What?
You can't read?
It's not coming.
You gotta walk, man.
-Sorry.
-See ya.
Thanks.
Hi. Hi there.
Excuse me. I'm lost.
I'm looking for a White Sands.
My girls are about to
get out of practice.
You can't look it
up on your phone?
Well, my phone died and one
of my girls took the charger.
I think you know how that goes.
You know, I left a
really big meeting
just so I could
get here in time.
Dressed like that?
Oh, you're funny.
You're funny.
I know White Sands isn't far.
You've gotta take the
interstate to get there.
Um, I'm not totally sure though.
I'm not from around here.
Hey, hang on a second.
I got an idea.
How about I compensate
you for your time?
Just doing my good
deed for the day.
You know what?
Speaking of good deeds,
can I offer you a ride?
I mean, where do you need to go?
I'm okay. I'm
waiting for the bus.
You can't be waiting
out here by yourself.
Just come on.
I'll give you a ride.
Look, you got nothing
to worry about.
I am not a creep.
I'm just, I'm a dad.
Um,
what happened here?
Oh, yeah.
I need to get that fixed.
Straight?
-Yes.
-Okay.
So what time were you
supposed to pick them up?
Oh, we got time.
I thought you said
you were in a rush.
Do you smoke around them?
You like to ask
questions, don't you?
Everything I have said and done
has been in the hands of God.
I was born to do this.
I am not afraid.
Everything I have said and done
has been in the hands of God.
Um, I can just get
off at the next light.
-No.
-I can walk from there.
-Yeah.
-I can.
It's really close.
Okey dokes.
-You just passed it.
-Aw.
You follow directions
as good as you smell.
No wonder your so lost.
Oh, whoa. Take it
easy little missy.
Where are we going?
Relax, have some of this, okay?
Don't be a big baby, just...
It's, it's good.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
It's all right.
Help you relax.
Everything I have said and done
has been in the hands of God.
I was born to do
this. I'm not afraid.
What was that?
It's a quote from Joan of Arc.
She led the French to
battle against England
and then became a
Saint for her actions.
Right.
Wasn't she burned alive?
She was.
She also killed an awful
lot of men before that.
See, you indeed, are correct.
I have nothing to worry
about. Only you do.
What are you doing?
Everything I have said and done
has been in the hands of God.
Dear God, what have
you made of me?
Have mercy.
Have mercy, have
mercy on my soul.
Why don't I feel bad about this?
Why?
Why do I feed on this?
Is it my burden to carry?
My gift?
My curse?
Why?
Why have you made me this way?
Oh wow, how darling.
Where have you been?
I've been waiting
here for hours.
You have not just
been waiting, Jules.
We've been dancing.
-She gave me weed.
-Oh.
We were waiting for you
though, to do the peyote.
Okay, Gigi.
Oh, come on.
She knows I'm joking.
Better not drink the tea
tonight though, sweetie.
What?
It smells delicious in
here, what you cooking?
Beef stew.
So, are you just gonna
ignore my question?
Where have you been?
The poli sci exam.
We were supposed to study.
I was waiting for you.
Waited for me?
-Yeah.
-Where?
You know the Goats Cafe.
The Goats?
Yeah.
You said to meet
you at the house.
So why didn't you text me?
Oh, I was zoned out
and my phone died.
Gigi, did you give this girl
the upper or the downer?
'Cause she's 21
questions over here.
Hmm.
Maybe she's more
the ketamine type.
No, I'm just scaring her.
All right, fine.
Let's just eat.
Pre-code films were
whole other thing.
Hollywood in 1931 was a radical
bed of progressive ideas.
And women, women were
just a femme fatale,
or the ingenue, or the
doting wife or the victim.
No.
Women were whole people.
Emancipated from the
harness of how a woman
is supposed to behave.
Now, my mom, Clare's
great grandma
was a Hollywood
screenwriter Oh really.
In the '60s and '70s, yeah,
and she did this one
spaghetti western
and that is how I
got into acting.
And I even taught little Clare.
All my favorite screen
combat moves, didn't I?
You never told me that.
Oh!
By the way, I'm sorry for
missing our study day today.
It won't happen again.
Dude, don't sweat
it. We're good.
Um, well text me
when you get home?
Always. Bye.
Oh, and Clare?
Goats was closed today
for a private event.
See you tomorrow.
Hey, there.
Fuck off.
Jesus.
Bob, how many times
do I have to kill you?
Clare Bleeker.
New day, same habit.
Whatever this is, can we just
reschedule it for another time?
I really need to sleep.
That's a big negative,
my auburn vendetta.
Oh hey, that'd be a great
assassin name for you.
Nobody hires me to
do what I do yet.
Um, Bob, what is this?
What are you doing here?
I am here representing
the last itsy bitsy piece
of your conscience.
Really? Because I don't
feel bad about what I do.
No? Not even about me?
Thought we were pals.
No, I'm in college.
You're decomposing.
I remember our first encounter
like it was yesterday.
What are you doing down there?
Oh, I'm not doing much.
You know, just...
Are you drunk?
Yeah.
Yes, I have been drinking.
Can you get up?
Oh, I can't.
Okay, I'm gonna call
someone for help.
No, no, no, no.
Please, don't, don't.
Don't call anybody, yeah.
Just give me a hand.
Oh, thank you.
You wanna talk about it?
30 years.
30 years of marriage.
I never even looked
at another woman.
I never thought about
another woman, I never cared.
I find out that she cheated
on me my whole life.
Stepped on and, and,
and taken advantage of
and taken for granted
and over and over and
over and over and over.
I never thought.
I never thought that
she would do that to me.
I'm sure you'll find
somebody that cares about you
the way you deserve.
I'm sorry.
Oh, oh, okay.
Okay, getting too tight.
Okay.
Stop, stop.
Get off me!
No, no, no, no, no.
Please, please, please.
What is your point?
Why? Why are you haunting me?
You slipped and fell and broke
your dumb head open, okay?
So you can't be my conscience
uttering its last dying breaths
or whatever you just said.
I'm here to warn you.
About?
The man you murdered today.
Oh, please don't tell me I'm
gonna start seeing him too.
He did not act alone.
Be mindful of what
you say tomorrow.
To whom?
Be mindful.
Okay, thank you
for being useless.
Goodnight, Bob.
You're still here, Bob.
I don't know.
I heard the detective
on this case
is like a sexy fox.
Who cares? This whole
thing is so psycho.
When Theresa went missing,
they didn't do half the crap
they're making us do right now.
Wait, the girl went missing?
Wait, who's the guy?
I don't know, but look,
see these two girls
from our school, they were
the last people that saw him.
And they told me, pretended
like he needed directions
to help pick up his daughters.
Men should never
ask for directions.
Fact check. Homie
had no daughters.
-Classic.
-Shocking.
-Just trifling, you know.
-There's a girl missing?
These girls are so cool.
They don't even hear you.
So a girl went missing?
Yeah, it was last
year, Theresa Holmes.
She was so kind,
she was talented.
Okay.
She was in other people's
boyfriends is what she was.
Okay, sis.
Well it wasn't her
sis of her sis?
Anyway, they found traces
of GHB and fentanyl
and a flask in his car.
So those girls dodged a bullet.
-I knew it.
-Knew what?
Um, oh in my head, in my head,
I was thinking about something.
God you are so hot
but so weird Clare.
So did they say anything else?
No, but I mean, it had
to be after school hours
or they wouldn't be
interrogating us.
Interrogating?
Wait, is that what's
happening here?
Yes, Einstein.
What do you think we're in
line for, a juice press?
Oh my God, I need an alibi.
-Why?
-I invoke the Sixth.
It's the Fifth, Amity.
And you're not gonna do well
in there without an alibi
for yesterday afternoon.
Can you be my alibi?
-You're so cute, but I can't.
-Why?
Firstly, you wouldn't be
able to bear the pressure
of a cross-interrogation
and would likely end
crushed by the web of lies
of your own making.
Secondly, a false
testimony in a murder case
is a federal charge.
Third of all, you don't
actually think they're looking
for a suspect amongst us, right?
I don't know.
Juliana LeBlanc.
Here.
This is ridiculous and
a dumb waste of my time.
By the way, I knew
it was the Fifth.
I mean, I was so,
so obviously joking.
It's just like Juliana needs
to get off her high horse.
You know? She thinks
I'm not smart,
but I always get the
last laugh in the end.
Remember that, Clare.
So a juice press is so 2012.
Anyway, it's like, who's
standing in line for a juice?
Wait, why don't you
wanna tell anyone
where you were yesterday?
Because it's private.
Clare Bleeker.
Yeah, good luck with that, kid.
Let's hope Juliana is as good
a friend as she says she is.
Clare, this is
Detective Timmons.
Miss Bleeker is one
of our newer student.
She's an East Coast transplant.
Oh yeah, where on
the East Coast?
New York.
What got you moving here?
Dead parents.
Um...
I'm sorry to hear that.
All right, Miss Bleeker,
I don't wish to take
too much of your time,
but can you walk us
through your day yesterday
from about 2:00 PM to 8:00 PM?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, um...
Started at school.
Yeah.
Then I went to the bus stop.
Which bus? The
bus up on campus?
It's not coming.
Yeah, yeah.
On campus.
And what happened next?
I was reading a
book and I went home
and had a study
date with my friend.
Which friend was that?
LeBlanc.
Um...
And then, then...
we had dinner with my...
I had a study date...
-Clare.
-Grandma.
-Detective to repeat it.
Clare.
Sorry?
I said you can go.
Okay.
Well, you know where to
find me if you need me.
You have pets?
No, just bad habits.
Well, it's like I always say.
Don't.
- I'm just saying- - Don't.
I didn't think it went that bad.
Yeah, right.
It went fucking amazing
because I blacked out
and I have absolutely
no recollection of
what I just said.
Ah, don't say, oh, Uncle
Bob didn't warn you.
Well, look who it is...
Clare Bleeker.
Um,
I'm sorry, what,
what is your name?
You're funny.
Amity told me you were funny.
Amity's ex, ah...
Cool. I, I have to go.
Wait, where to?
You need a ride?
No, I...
uh...
yeah, actually, yeah. Yes.
Yeah, and then just right
up this street is my house.
...homicide case.
So what happened with you
and Truman earlier today?
...tragically found dead.
-Huh?
-In the hallway.
I saw you guys, looked
like some tension.
Oh, that kid is whack.
He deserved it.
Why did he deserve it?
Well, it seems
like police arrived
at the scene this morning.
Amity didn't tell you?
Tell me what?
He's been identified
as Joe Morton.
Look, all you need to
know is he did something
he regretted and he
won't do it again.
...a targeted attack.
Targeted attack?
Well, this is me.
Investigators are trying-
That was easy and painless.
So maybe we'll hop in again.
Thank you.
Hey, Clare.
Look, I know you're new in town,
but I'm throwing
a party tonight.
Would you wanna come?
Not with me, not with me.
Just you or others if you want?
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah. Why not?
Awesome.
And just can you
do me one thing?
Just, don't tell
Amity I invited you.
I just don't want
it to be a thing.
You know what I mean?
Okay.
All right. Dope.
I'll see you tonight.
All right, party!
I'm gonna come by about seven.
We'll get ready together.
It's gonna be awesome.
I don't know how
you girls do it.
I, ah, gosh.
This is both painful and
difficult at the same time.
Wow, Bob, you've been
dead for only a month
and you've already summed up
the entire female experience.
Okay, stop that. I cannot
let you do this anymore.
This is painful.
Close.
Okay, stay still.
Bob, where do you go
when you're not like...
Here?
Yeah, like why aren't
you in heaven yet?
Are you on some type
of heaven probation or?
Why do you ask?
Just wondering if you'd seen
my mom and dad by any chance?
I have not.
I think about them
a lot actually.
I know that what
I'm doing is right.
I can, I just feel
it in my soul.
But then I think maybe
they're up there looking down
and saying, normal
Clare Bleeker is enough.
Maybe they're up there thinking
that they want
normal Clare Bleeker
to have some normal fun.
No more killing.
I am the result
of a fallen world.
But has to give light,
last endure burning.
What's that smell?
Regrets.
This is good.
See, this is the
acceptable kind of trouble.
Juliana meeting us here?
No.
Why?
Because I didn't tell her.
Why not?
Bob, why try to kill the
mood with all the questions?
Okay? This is a night for
us to get out and be normal
and be social.
Bob and Clare, Bob and
Clare. Are you with me?
Okay? Watch me, be normal.
Hey, you, you.
Mm.
Oh my God.
No. No more. No, I don't.
You photograph
disgustingly well.
Emphasis on
disgusting by the way.
Didn't expect to see
you here tonight.
Same.
Well, I'm here on a work night.
Just a mere and humble observant
of this wild fucking
human display.
Hmm. What kind
of work is that?
Well, I'm actually,
I'm working on a series
titled Demented Debauchery of
Intoxicated College Students.
-Oh.
-It'll make for like an edgy,
pricey coffee table book
somewhere, I don't know.
Glad to be collecting dust
in some old dude's house.
What makes you think
you made the cut?
Clearly, I am the cover.
I'm just demented
debauchery at its finest.
Wow.
So what brings you here on
this delectable evening?
A ghost of a dead
mailman that haunts me
told me to do it.
Better tell lover boy I
come with the package.
Get it?
So what else did this ghost
tell you to do, Clare?
I'd rather not say.
Let's just drop the
ghost. Drop the ghost.
-Shall we, you wanna go inside?
-Fuck the ghost
for the rest of the night?
-Yeah.
-I'll be your ghost.
-Yeah, he's not cool at all.
♪ Let me go ♪
♪ Some faces I know ♪
♪ Doesn't matter where I go ♪
♪ I see you ♪
♪ Would you tell me
about the dream again ♪
♪ The one of learning
how to breathe ♪
♪ At the garden of the seas ♪
♪ Is only you and me ♪
♪ Would you take it
out of me again ♪
♪ Do you hear me ♪
Do you know where
the bathroom is?
It's upstairs.
You want me to wait for you?
Okay.
Cops are here! Cops are here!
Why is Timmons here?
Is anybody up there?
Need your IDs out.
Fuck.
What the? What the fuck?
Whoa.
Uh, hi.
What's up, but?
How'd you find my room?
That's your room?
Yeah, I didn't know that.
I checked all the doors,
but they were all
locked and yours wasn't.
So, yeah you know, the cops.
I was trying to hide.
This is pretty annoying.
Yeah.
It's just a noise complaint
but people inevitably bring
drugs to these things.
So, cops stay a lot
longer than they should.
What are you hiding,
Clare Bleeker?
And why are you even in there?
Are you running from the cops?
Everybody started
bolting, so I did.
All right, well look,
make yourself comfortable
'cause it's, it's
gonna be a while.
You know, half my
nicotine addiction
comes from manual fixation,
which I don't get from vaping.
I have to go.
Wait, are you sure?
Yeah, I have to be home.
Look, I would not risk
that if I were you.
I gotta get home.
No, I couldn't get
anybody tonight.
Death is more welcome
here than you.
Next!
-Next.
Hey, Amity.
How are you?
-Clare, wish me luck.
Actually, don't
you say break a leg
'cause we're in the theater, so.
What part are you
auditioning for?
Myra. Obviously,
the female lead.
You know what? You
actually have a Helga vibe.
Clare Voyant.
You see what I did
there with your name?
It's supporting but.
I actually related a bit more
to the two male protagonist.
You would.
Yeah, also he die's
after the first act.
The only thing you're
projecting is vomit.
Next!
Amity, I wanted to
just talk to you
about something
pretty important.
Okay? Shoot.
What was your relationship
like with Wade?
Why?
Did he ever say anything
or make you do anything
that felt forced?
What are you asking me?
If he put you in a position-
Why are you all of a
sudden curious about Wade?
Did he ask you out?
No, I barely saw
him the other night.
The other night?
Like at his party?
So you went to my
ex's party without us?
Do you know how
sketchy that sounds?
Amity-
We're trying to prep.
Okay, you shut up!
Amity, it wasn't like that.
That's exactly
what Theresa said.
What does Theresa have
to do it with this?
Oh God.
I'd rather pass a kidney stone.
Next.
I have to audition.
Amity, darling.
Mwah. Mwah.
-Mwah. Mwah.
Finally, a true thespian
in the sea of dilettantes.
They're all Philistines.
Entre vous.
A girl went missing?
Yeah, it was last
year, Theresa Holmes.
Have you seen my text?
My phone's been off.
I'm just gonna get to the point.
There is something
really, really-
I thought you were gonna get
straight to the point, Clare.
Okay.
I found photos of Amity
that I don't think
she wanted to taken.
And there was another
of a missing girl,
she went missing last year.
And then I found photos of you.
-What?
-You were unconscious.
Well, I don't do drugs
and I don't drink.
So frankly, I don't know
what you're talking about.
I know what I saw.
I'm trying to help you.
Has Wade done anything or said-
Wade?
It was in his room, the photos.
So you did hook up with him?
What? No, I didn't
hook up with him.
Clare, listen, I
like you and all,
but you just got
here six months ago
whilst I've known Amity
since middle school.
Now, I don't give a damn
that you hooked up with
her ex or whatever-
- I didn't hook- -
It doesn't matter.
But if you think I'm not
keeping track of all the lies
you've been spewing
regularly, you are wrong.
What lies?
Goats Cafe, Clare, or the party
you didn't think of
inviting your friends to.
-Oh my God. This is different.
-And now it turns out you were
Wade's bedroom.
You're a little
dishonest, Clare.
This, this is what matters.
You're smart, you're pretty,
but you're dishonest.
- This is- - If you
really think there's
something wrong, then why
not just go to the police?
Hmm?
Precisely.
Later, Clare.
Mr. Edwards.
-Uh-uh, no ma'am.
-Ah, Mr. Edwards?
Not today.
Auditions are over. No.
-But Mr. Edwards.
-Director.
Director Edwards. I have
this proposition for you.
Mm.
Because someone as
riveting as yourself
should not settle for
just small town production
of a spell binding
piece of literature.
Your vision is Broadway or-
We're working in here.
Carry on.
Because you're like, then
you're just this true feminist.
You're a trailblazer,
Mr. Edwards.
Can I assist you?
No, I don't babysit.
But I did come up with
the best idea right now.
It just popped into my brain.
Gender is a construct.
So you can play the
male lead, Sidney Brule.
Oh, great idea.
Opposite Amity Liston.
And if you are late
ever again, you're out.
Move it.
-Okay, great.
I'm out of here.
I'm off the clock.
Miss Bleeker, may I
have a word with you
in the dean's office?
Yeah, of course.
Clare, do you remember
last time we spoke
that it was about Joe Morton?
Who?
The man who was
murdered in his car.
Oh, right. What about it?
Well, the victim's only
witnesses recently testified
that they saw a
redheaded girl waiting
at the campus bus stop
the day of the murder.
But what time exactly did
you get home that night?
Forgive me I'm,
having a little deja vu here.
Ah well, let's see.
The bus was late.
I was reading a book and
I lost track of time,
and then I went home.
I had a study date with my
friend, Juliana LeBlanc.
And then we made dinner
with my grandma Gigi.
And then I just went to bed.
Well, we spoke with your
grandmother earlier today.
Hmm.
She said you were
three hours late.
Okay, and?
And Juliana didn't mention
that when we interrogated her.
She must have forgot.
Doesn't really seem
like a relevant detail.
Buses aren't hours
late, Miss Bleeker.
Outrageous, I know.
What a waste of my time.
But I didn't see the guy
that you're talking about.
So, I'm sorry I don't have
more intel for you detective.
But that's not a crime, is it?
No, it's not, but giving
a false testimony is.
And for some strange reason,
you and your two closest friends
all have murky testimonies
on the day a man was murdered.
Am I being detained, detective?
No, you can go.
But Clare, let me be clear.
You have a three-hour
gap in your alibi.
I will find out why.
Detective Timmons, do you know
how many women have gone
missing in this town
in the last 30 years?
53.
54 with Theresa Holmes.
In a single town in the
course of only three decades,
my brain, just, I-
How does something
like that go unnoticed?
How does so many
women go unnoticed?
Clare, you're being naive,
if you don't think we're
aware, people go missing.
It's what keeps me up at night.
And it's the reason
why I warned you
the first time I saw you.
But something tells me
that you're withholding
pivotal information here.
Unless this guy
has something to do
with these missing girls.
I think my job is done here.
I'm allowed to leave, right?
There's the door.
He can't have anything on me.
He can't. He can't.
Because if he did, he'd
already have me detained
and I didn't leave any
DNA evidence behind
because they had already had me.
Hmm.
How would I bring up
all these missing girls?
Timmons just doesn't
say anything.
He literally didn't
It's like, why
doesn't anybody care?
People tend to not want to
talk about that kind of stuff.
What does that mean?
The ugly stuff in the world.
They wanna pretend
it's not there.
Well, what does that mean to me?
Well, like, we should just
go on living our lives
while all these
girls are missing?
Why am I even
talking to you, Bob?
Well technically, you're not.
Timmons,
he's always watching so I
can't really do anything.
But on top of that right,
I'm just jeopardizing
all of my friends.
You don't really have
any friends left, do you?
There's Juliana, there's
Amity, there's something
that's not right about that.
And then you've got Wade, Wade.
He's got this so many photos.
Look at her. How did
they get in his room?
Why does he have them?
I need to figure
out this puzzle.
I need to put all of
the pieces together.
It'll work out.
But, but I can't, I can't.
Because I shouldn't. I
shouldn't be doing this.
I can't be doing this because
I've done too many things
and they're going to resurface
that I've done in the past.
I don't know what to do.
I need to know what to
do. What do I do, Bob?
What do I do? What do I do?
You have to finish
what you started.
I can't. I can't.
-You have to go back.
-I can't.
You have to go back to
the house on Oak Street.
Like Joan of Arc?
Like Joan of Arc, guided
solely by my visions.
Joan burned, Clare.
Something so evil,
it infects all of
those who touch it.
Death trap is a Chinese box
of moving parts that makes
you question everything
that you just learned.
Who is an ally?
Who is not?
Who is a murderer?
And who is a victim?
I'm gonna take this great play
and make it extraordinary
by casting Clare Bleeker
as the male lead, Sidney Brule,
What?
The washed up writer who's
desperate for a second chance.
And Amity Liston will
play Clifford, the young
and plucky student who Sydney
is trying to steal the play
of death trap from.
I'm an ingenue.
Uh-huh.
And Wade, you will be
playing Sydney's wife,
the clingy Machiavellian Myra.
So I get to play
Clare's clingy wife?
Mm-hmm.
Sexy.
What?
Miss Liston.
I just-
Whatever it is you
are channeling here,
I need you to save
it for the stage.
Okay?
Rehearsal time, it's
indeed where this belongs.
Indeed.
Now, donde esta,
mi psychic Helga.
Helga?
Hey. Hey. I'm here. I'm here.
Sorry, I was working on a film-
No, no, no, no.
I do not tolerate tardiness.
Be gone.
Are are, are you
serious right now?
Deadly. Out.
Okay, okay, okay.
And that is what we call acting.
See what I'm doing there, kids?
Helga, Helga, Helga, Helga,
please come back.
We miss you already.
Please take a seat
and use your psychic
abilities to make sure
that you never, ever,
ever disappoint me again.
Or you'll be out like
me from the closet.
I can't wait to get started
so I can watch Helga die
a very slow and
excruciating death.
Wow, Clare here is clearly
overcompensating for her lack
of talent by method
acting, which I Stan.
Okay.
Bravo, Clare.
Bravo.
Now everybody, up, up, up.
Use our instruments people.
A five, six, seven, eight.
To the right, to the left.
To the right.
The tip of the tongue,
the teeth, the lips.
Clare.
Clare, what happened?
Clare, what's your problem?
Hey, hey, wait.
Don't come near me.
You're actually insane.
What the fuck? You're
a nut job, fuck.
[Tires squeal]
So?
So what?
So what is our plan?
There is a curfew in place.
That is the plan.
A curfew.
What does a curfew
do in this situation?
It is a necessary precaution,
given the extreme
circumstances that we're in.
The only person right now
who is in extreme
circumstances is Juliana.
If we don't do
something immediately,
she's gonna disappear like
the rest of the girls.
There's gonna be a vigil.
We'll go to the vigil.
What, what does
a vigil do, Gigi?
We should be out
looking right now.
And what is with the coffee?
You don't even drink coffee.
It's to keep me up,
while you sleep.
-Are you serious?
-Yes.
Right now, anything could
be happening to her.
I hear you talking
to yourself at night.
Detective Timmons says I
should take particular care
with you because of your
fragile state of mind.
But is he insinuating
that I'm crazy?
No, it's not like that.
-Is that what you think?
-No, that's not what I think.
But you've been
through a lot, Clare.
You've seen some
horrifying things.
And I know that you
sneak out at night.
To do what I have no
idea, but it has to stop.
From now on, it is
home, school, home.
-Until when?
-Until I say so.
What was this doing
in your drawer?
-Protection.
-Oh, come on.
What is this for?
What is it you do when
you sneak out at night?
Tell me.
I can't tell you.
I can't tell anyone.
Jesus.
You are grounded.
I'm not your child, Gigi.
No, you're not.
Because I had to bury my
child with my own hands.
I'm not gonna bury my
granddaughter also.
Clare!
Oh my God!
Clare, you have to
promise me something.
You'll never tell anyone what
you did in the woods today.
Okay?
Even if you saved a life.
It will haunt you, Clare.
It will change
your life forever.
And not everyone
will understand you.
Not everyone will
see you as a hero.
You have to bear
this secret alone.
But whenever you
feel like you need
to take this burden off your
shoulders, you come talk to me.
I'll always be with you
when all goes dark.
Mom?
Please grant me strength.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
please grant me strength.
Please do not abandon me.
Holy Mary, Mother
of God, please,
please grant me strength.
Please do not abandon me.
Holy Mary, mother
of God, please,
please grant me strength.
To thee, do we cry
poor children of Eve,
to thee, do we
send up our sighs,
mourning and weeping in
this valley of tears.
Please, Holy Mary mother of God.
The blood, it won't come off.
Help me carry this burden,
I can't do this anymore.
I'm not strong enough.
I belong nowhere.
Show me the way,
make me your vessel.
Please do not abandon me.
Pray for us sinners now and
in the hour of our death.
Amen.
Help me.
Who are you taking
the photos for?
Clare, please don't do
something you may regret.
Who are you taking
the photos for?
Okay, look, I'll answer
whatever question you have,
but you need to
put the knife down.
No.
Who are you taking
the photos for?
I don't know what
you're asking me.
Photo that you took of me
the night of the party.
Why did I find it in
some stranger's basement?
Hmm? What was it doing there?
Who are you selling
these photos to?
-Your, your photo?
-Don't act fucking stupid.
You know what I'm talking about.
Look, my camera was stolen
the night of the party.
Okay? When the cops
came, all right?
All those photos
that I took are gone.
Literally, I didn't get a
chance to download them.
I lost-
-Are you lying to me?
-No. Look,
every single photo I
took that night is gone.
Including yours.
I'm working on film again.
What do you know about
the house on Oak Street?
Who told you? Was
it, was it Wade?
What about Wade?
He thinks I took some
promiscuous photos of his girl
when I didn't even know what
I was walking myself into.
Okay? And I don't even
think Amity did either.
I was just answering some
stupid photography ad,
to make some cash.
Okay? I didn't even
go back. That's it.
Did you take this photo?
No, but I recognized
the background.
That's the house.
Are you friends with
my granddaughter?
Do you know my granddaughter?
Mrs. Newberry, right?
Yeah, we didn't get a chance
to introduce ourselves.
My name is Truman.
You're friends with
my granddaughter?
Oh, yes, yes. I know Clare.
And where is Clare?
I haven't seen her since...
Since what?
She told me she was
with her friends.
She's not home and
she's not here.
So, so where is she?
Where is she?
Where is my granddaughter?
I can't lose her too.
I can't lose her.
Hello?
Have you seen my
friend, Juliana LeBlanc?
She went missing three days ago.
Have you seen her?
I'm sorry kid, I haven't.
Are you sure?
Can you take
another look please?
'Cause I've been searching
all night and I'm so tired.
Can I use your bathroom?
It'll be really
quick, I promise.
Uh,
where is it, your bathroom?
On the left.
And can I get a glass of water?
I'm so thirsty.
Yeah.
Here you go.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Gibbs needs more
product within two days.
Raw stuff.
Younger.
You can't seem to understand
this is a process.
It takes time to
get these girls.
We run a business, Randall,
and you're behind on delivery.
Either you're in or you're out.
Well things have
been a bit backed up
since the Joe situation.
Gibbs was sorry to hear
about your brother.
Yeah, well he did all
the pickups, you know,
and now I'm running
this thing all myself.
What about the
recruiter we got you?
Whose idea was that?
Hold on.
Hey.
Whoa, whoa. Oh, hello.
Hi.
There she is.
You're not gonna believe
what just knocked on my door.
She showed up looking
for the other one.
The van will be at
your place in an hour.
Better have them both on it.
Hey, the guys are coming.
I'll send you stuff ASAP.
All right, listen up.
Girl in the bed's done.
All right? She's got
pick up in an hour.
Meanwhile, I caught another one.
So she's gonna need some
pictures, she needs video.
And I'll tell you, if
you get done early,
you can have some fun with her
before the van picks her up.
Okay? Have at it, let's go.
Hey, take the braids out.
Little messy.
There you go.
Yeah. All right. Clear out.
There we go. There we go.
Oh, it's good.
Randall, can I get
her for the video?
All right. Hey, I'm done.
Okey dokes. Bring her on.
Showtime.
Hang on a second.
I'm getting a vision.
You two look good together.
Why don't we spice
up this video?
Maybe introduce some product
testing to the package
and get a bidding war going on.
Put on a mask and
get camera ready.
I ain't getting paid
enough for this shit, man.
-I'll do it.
-Yes! Yes!
What's wrong with you, Justin?
Jesus Christ.
Hey, Randall. How much
did you give her, man?
She can't even
stand up straight.
I can't pick up the girl.
You want me to reset
the lights by the bed?
No, just pull the horse over.
Let's go.
Everything I've said and done
has been the will of God.
What? What did you say?
I am not afraid.
I'm not afraid.
I was born to do this.
Hey Randall, I don't
like this, man.
You are so high.
Everything I have said and done
has been in the hands of God.
I was born to do
this, I'm not afraid.
Come on you-
Let her go.
Why should I?
I won't have mercy on
your soul if you don't.
On my soul?
Let her go.
Help! Help!
We're down here.
Oh!
Help, help us, please.
We're down here.
Please help us.
I'm so scared.
Please, please, please,
someone help me.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck happened here?
Randall, Jesus Christ, man.
You had one job.
You fuckin' piece of shit.
Clare.
All right, let's try to
all walk outta here alive.
Shall we?
Tell him to let her go.
Do it!
Go on.
Put the scissors on the
floor and pass them to me.
That was fair.
And I'd say we're
even now, don't you?
Where do all the
girls go, Timmons?
Hmm?
How much do they go for?
By the way, I loved
killing your brother.
I have to go get Timmons.
Clare, please, please,
please, don't leave me.
I have to.
Please, don't leave me, please.
Fuck.
There, there, there, there.
You're safe, you're safe.
No one's gonna hurt
you. I promise.
Hey, hey, hey, you're safe.
Gigi.
Gigi,
I know you're mad and I'm sorry
but you're never gonna
believe what happened.
You have to see what's on TV.
...versity town has been
discovered to be the nest,
of a human trafficking
We found Juliana!
Operation that has run
for more than 40 years.
A local college
student, Juliana LeBlanc
who went missing three
days ago, was found alive
inside the basement
of trafficking ring
leader, Randall Morton.
Mr. Morton and his brother Joe,
had previously been convicted
with bail years prior.
When another student
came to this house
looking for her friend,
she walked into the scene
of a gruesome death,
-Gigi!
-that miraculously,
-You're missing it.
-Juliana was spared from.
What happened?
It, it was really scary.
I...
The door was open
and then I could hear yelling
coming from the basement.
And then I went in and then
I was like walking-
It took such courage
for this young lady to
walk into the wolf's mouth.
But her action saved
her best friend's life.
Stay tuned for more information
on the Pickmann Flats
trafficking case.
We'll be right back
after a short break.
Oh, don't worry, Clare.
She got to die peacefully
in her own home.
Well, not too peacefully
since she had a heart attack
the second she realized
I was after you.
Remember, I tried to
make a deal with you,
but you had to go all
Rambo in that basement.
You could have spared
your grandmother's life.
All they do is take from me.
They take from me.
What? What? What
are you saying?
I cannot hear you.
The last thing I have is...
...gone.
I have nothing.
Are you here to kill me now?
Clare, I think there's
been a misunderstanding.
I'm not here to kill you.
I don't want you dead at all.
I want you to work for me.
No, with, with me.
See, as you rightfully
pointed out,
you have nothing to live for.
No family members left,
but you are a weapon.
Oh my God, Clare, we could
make so much money together.
I'm telling you,
you'd be set for life.
Ah.
I would never.
Never.
I expected a little resistance.
See, I've done some research
on you, Miss Bleeker.
Your father left when
you were in fifth grade.
Mom had a rare heart condition
that went undiagnosed.
She died when you were only 14.
After that, you moved from
New York to Connecticut,
from friends' houses
to boarding schools
until you ended up here.
But it appears that
wherever you went,
somehow a mysterious
surge in murder cases
made to look like suicides
or accidents happened.
I know you killed Joe Morton.
I know you're responsible
for the mailman's death
and virtually every
other unsolved murder
in the cities you've lived in.
Join me, Clare.
Or it's only a matter of
time until you get caught.
I can protect you.
Detective...
I believe in what I do.
I hope I get caught.
Hey!
You had your chance.
What has to give light
must endure burning.
What has to fight must
endure destruction.
Burn.
Cheryl, you made it.
Thank you for coming.
Are you loving?
-It's great, man.
-I know I'm, phenomenal.
Pumpkin.
-Hi, Cole.
-We're so glad you made it
and that you're doing all right?
Yes, of course.
Front row, honey.
Where you belong.
-Yeah.
I'm watching you two, trouble.
Hey, pull it together people.
Oh my God, oh my God.
Oh my God, you! I can't!
Okay. There are reviewers
here for Christ's sake.
Do you have my tape measure?
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
-Okay.
-Amity, Amity.
Can you stand still please?
-Yes.
-This fit you fine last week.
Maybe I'm losing weight.
Not in the trunk.
Ah!
Okay, Do I look
manly enough for you?
No.
Ah, Clifford's ready, we
open in five. Let's go!
Five! We can't be
late. Move it. Move it.
Props, props, props.
Please stop me from putting
this in someone's face.
You, perfection.
Yes. I love it. Meow. Meow.
Come on, OMG.
There are reviewers here.
They are totally judging me.
We are going to hell.
Curtain!
Oh my God, I am like
bringing down the house.
Forever.
Forever and ever.
Forever, no.
Here, why don't you
take some of my flowers?
I have like way too many.
Look at Wade.
At least we don't need
him to finish the play.
But we do need you.
So, hurry up.
It's opening night.
Hey, break a leg, Clare.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Hi, Clare.
Where have you been
this entire time?
I could have used
your help, you know?
Gigi's dead.
I know,
but she's, she's here.
She's, she's watching over you.
And she wants you to know
she's very proud of you
and so are your parents.
But there is one last thing
that you have to do and
you can only do it now
We're about to go.
This is pretty
disastrous timing, Bob.
The Tale of Oak
Street isn't over.
What?
The code is 1713.
Code for what?
Gibbs needs more
product within two days.
Raw stuff. Younger.
What about the
recruiter we got you?
He thinks I took some
promiscuous photos
of his girlfriend.
Juliana thinks I'm not smart,
but I always get the
last laugh in the end.
Remember that, Clare.
Break a leg.
Everything I have said and done
has been in the hands of God.