[keyboard clicking]
[eerie music]
Cool. Okay, compose yourself.
Okay.
Greetings everyone, I...
Greetings everyone,
I'm Anya. Whoa.
Greetings everyone, my name...
Greetings everyone.
Hi, I'm, no. Hi, I'm Anya.
Mind. No, greetings, greetings.
Greetings.
Okay.
Greetings everyone, I'm Anya.
Welcome to Mind Body Spirit.
Mind Body Spirit is so much
more than a fitness channel.
It is a journey
to self discovery,
and aligning our
mind, body, and spirit
is the closest we can
get to our truest selves.
But in order to
make that discovery,
we've gotta be
willing to take risks.
So get ready to step
outta your comfort zone.
Go for it. Be brave.
Don't become a lost soul
floating through the void. Woo.
Like me, before
my morning coffee.
[chuckling]
My grandmother gave me
this house in her will.
She passed away
about a year ago.
And I never really
got to meet her.
Didn't really know
her that well.
But, you know, it
really felt like a,
the universe telling me to
make a change in my life.
So that's what I did. I
moved out to California.
I left my old life
behind. Yes, thank you.
And I took a risk and...
so can you.
I promise, if you stick with me,
then we will go to
places you never imagine.
Shit.
I promise, if you stick with me,
then we will go to places
that you can never imagine.
We will recharge our
minds, reclaim our bodies,
because our bodies
are the places
that our spirits call home.
You ready?
Today, we are going to dive
right into a balancing posture.
So, we're going to
meet in Savasana.
No, no, Tadasana.
♪ Tadasana
Meaning in Tadasana,
standing posture,
we're going to root our
feet into the ground,
lift one knee up to the heart,
stretch all the way back,
squeeze those inner
thighs, engage that core.
And if you discover
that you are a little bit
limited in flexibility,
don't let that hold you
back, just go with the flip.
Now, if you start to
lose your balance,
which will probably happen,
you know, just
get right back up.
Like my friend Kenzi says,
"Practice make powerful."
Okay, I guess I need
some practice here too...
Shit. Ow!
Damn it!
Stupid.
You gotta do it. You gotta
do it. You gotta do it, Anya.
No way.
That's definitely a door.
[grunting]
[door creaking]
Fuck it.
Oh...
So, welcome to my
grandma's hidden pantry.
[Anya coughs and clears throat]
I will just put this down here
on the weird candle bread.
Okay, that's weird.
[Anya panting]
Oh, Jesus. [light
bulb explodes]
Nope, I guess not.
[Anya panting]
Yikes.
Whoa.
What the fuck?
Oh, geez!
Oh, Jesus, fuck!
Okay.
[clanging]
Hello?
[Anya shrieks] Shit.
Verasha.
"For my Anya."
[speaking Russian]
Greetings everyone,
welcome back.
The passage-
The passage that I was
just reading to you
was written to me by my
grandmother, Verasha.
I was never allowed to meet
her. My mom never let me.
Family drama.
I, I never knew that she was
a teacher, a healer like me.
'Cause it runs in our blood.
This house is the place
that her spirit called home.
I guess I just,
I never realized how much
of her was still here.
Hi grandma.
So she dedicated this
journal to me. I don't know.
She wanted somebody in our
family to know what she did,
where she went.
She spent her lifetime
reconnecting with her Slavic
heritage, my heritage,
collecting rituals like this.
A lot of it is in Russian.
She translated some of it
and then phoneticized some
other passages for me.
"The path to self-discovery
is paved with doubt."
But every step you
take brings you closer
to who you really are.
To not be afraid in this
journey, in this life,
you are not alone.
"Whenever you are lost, you
can find yourself here."
I wish you knew how much
those words meant to me.
How much she's inspired me.
I mean, she just, she
experienced so much.
I just...
I wish...
I wish I could be like her.
And someday I will.
But right now, I
am here with you.
So let's get moving, shall we?
We're going to start
in a balancing posture.
Don't be afraid. I am
right here with you.
Root your feet into the ground,
float one knee up to your heart,
and kick it back behind you
as you lengthen
through your spine.
And if you fall, you know,
just get back up, right?
It's called practice
for a reason.
Woo. Alright, hold here for
a couple of deep breaths in.
[deep exhale]
Digging into that heel.
One more. In.
[deep exhale]
And as you come
back to your feet,
don't just plop down, float
your knee back to your heart,
and then let it drop
back down to the ground.
And that's it. You did
it. Great job, everyone.
Thank you so much
for joining me.
Thank you for listening to me,
and I really hope we can
really become one mind,
one body, one spirit together.
Yeah.
Cool.
This is KenziFit.
You ready to sweat?
[upbeat music]
If you wanna unlock your body,
you have to unleash your mind.
Don't listen to that voice
inside you that says you can't,
because you can.
Why meditate when
you can "sweatitate."
[upbeat music continues]
Only on KenziFit.
[computer dialing tone]
Hi baby.
Hi, Lenka.
Anya, you know,
I hate that name.
Your grandmother
always called me that.
Hi, Lenny.
Come on, we can do
better than that.
- How about "mom?"
- Sure.
That was fun. Did you call me
just to give me a hard time?
You told me to call
you once I got settled.
So you're settled.
Is this news?
- Mom...
- I'm just asking.
You're so far from home.
No friends, no family.
Grandma's family.
Verasha is dead, Anya.
Boris! Enough! [dog barking]
Okay, fine. Your grandmother
was family, but...
Go on.
She wasn't the woman
you think she was.
Boris! Boris! [dog barking]
You know, you've always told
me about who she wasn't,
but you've never actually
told me who she was.
You never told me
she was spiritual.
I can't tell you about a
woman who was never around.
That's a pretty heavy
pour, sweetheart.
Verasha only came back
when she needed something.
All she did was take
and take and take.
And now she's
taking you from me.
Jesus, mom, she hasn't
taken me from you.
If anything, she's
given me a place
to finally figure
myself out, you know?
And you can't do
that here at home?
I, I can move my things
out of your room.
I'm not coming home, okay?
I've literally spent all that
I have just to get out here.
Anya, I know that.
I just wanna make sure that
you're safe, that you're okay.
I'm okay.
Good. I just wanna help you.
Yeah, well then you should have.
[dog barking]
This fucking dog.
Boris, you get out
of here right now!
Asshole! Quick!
Did you ever think
that maybe grandma
felt like she had to
leave to find herself?
And why would you say that?
Because she said
so in her journal.
I see. Is that
what you believe?
It's, it's not about
what I believe.
That's what I have to do.
That's what I am doing.
Anya, I just, I just don't
want you to waste your life
obsessing over your grandmother.
Obsessing? I am
not obsessing, mom.
That's not what I meant, baby.
You just, you get
so lost in things.
And I am not there
to pull you out.
I know what I'm doing.
Of course, you do.
But listen, if you wanna find
yourself, go find yourself.
Go anywhere. Just
not, not there.
None of us knew
that place existed.
Yeah, well maybe she
didn't want you to know.
Maybe all of this was
always just for me.
Maybe she saw herself in me
in a way that she
could never see in you.
Oh, Anya, I promise you,
you are nothing like her.
- Goodbye, Lenka.
- Anya-
Hey guys!
Oh my God. I'm sorry. Reflex.
- That's okay.
Do your thing, girl.
Yeah, no, totally. No worries.
Okay.
Welcome everyone, I'm Anya.
And today we have a
very special guest.
This is Kenzi Duffert.
Oh, I, I don't use that
name professionally.
- Fuck! Oh, I'm sorry-
- No, that's okay.
- I'm so sorry.
- That's totally cool.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
Thank you for doing
this with me again.
Yeah, of course, chigger.
Your mom said that you
were really struggling,
so I'm happy to help.
- Yes, thank you.
- Yeah.
Okay.
Welcome everyone, I am Anya,
and today we have a
very special guest.
This is KenziFit.
- Hey guys.
Kenzi and I grew up together
and we recently reconnected
when I moved out here.
And I'm just so excited to
partner with her on today's video
and to really learn about
how she's connecting
with her fan base.
I'll be guiding you
through my 10 minute total
body takeover strength flow,
a little bit of yoga, a
little bit of lifting,
and a lot of sweat.
So get ready.
Okay, how do you
normally kick things off?
Um, well, let's, I don't know,
I kind of keep things
pretty loose, you know,
and it's all about
the discovery process.
All my things are about-
Ah ha. So how do
you kick things off?
Process.
Well, usually I start talking
about how I'm feeling and-
- Okay.
- Yeah.
First tip.
Right.
No one gives a shit
about how you feel.
People only care
about themselves.
They want structure,
not a therapy session.
So you gotta be fearless.
- Fearless.
Um, you're also going to
want to build your brand.
Something that
helps you stand out,
you know, find your thing.
Oh, um...
What about, what about this?
- Oh, God.
- This is my grandma's.
And she was like collecting
all these rituals
from our homeland and it's...
Um, I mean, that might
be a little too obscure.
People want things
that they know,
but like with a little
extra personality.
So remix some yoga flows,
pepper in some Sanskrit.
Yeah, I know.
I just, I don't really feel
comfortable teaching a language
that I don't actually
speak, you know?
Fake it till you make it.
Listen, people don't really care
as long as you seem authentic.
But this is authentic.
No one wants to read old books.
Look, you wanna be
successful, right?
Yeah. Yes.
So, how many videos
have you dropped so far?
I just started recording them.
I was gonna, I was gonna
release them all when I'm ready.
Okay, so you haven't
put anything out yet?
Well, no, I just, I didn't
want it to seem like bullshit,
I wanted it to be true to me.
Okay, well, you're not
gonna get any views
if you don't have
anything to watch.
Oh girl, that is not even
a tip. That's just a fact.
Okay.
Oh shit, I have to teach
a class in like an hour.
Can we do this?
Yeah, absolutely.
- Like now-ish.
- Okay. Yep. Cool.
Namaste, bitches.
We're getting started with
two hand front race swings.
Thirty seconds starts now.
[deep exhale] And up!
And up!
Keep that core tight!
Feeling the burn, Anya.
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah, this is intense.
- Yes. Get it, girl.
- Woo. Wow.
- Woo.
Up and up! Squeeze
your glutes.
- Squeezing.
- Up to the sky.
Smile through the pain!
Okay.
Hi everyone. Ugh.
Hey, hi. Greetings.
Namaste, whatever.
Everyone has this voice
inside of themselves
that really feels like
their truth, right?
But then there's all
these other voices
that are telling you
that that truth is a lie.
And...
maybe they're right,
but it's really hard to know
which voice to listen to.
But the most important
thing is that we make space
for ourselves to listen, right?
So in the interest
of an open mind,
we are going to do a
mindful meditation.
Find yourself in Sukhasana.
You know what? Nah, forget that.
Just sit however you want, but
make sure you're comfortable.
Feel yourself connecting
to the earth. [deep exhale]
Lengthen your spine.
Soften your eyes.
Inhale into your belly.
[deep inhale]
Exhale. Let it all go.
[deep exhale]
Inhale into your belly.
[deep inhale]
Exhale. Let it go. [deep exhale]
And in. [eerie music]
And out.
And in.
And as you continue this rhythm,
clear your mind of the chatter.
Quiet every voice, but your own.
And in.
And out.
Keep it going. Inhale in.
Exhale. Let it go.
One final breath in.
Exhale, let it all
go. [deep exhale]
[Anya coughing]
Shit.
Hello.
And sometimes your
meditations get cut short,
but you know, that's okay,
because it's all a part
of the journey, right?
And I don't know about you,
but I really felt like I
was finally given the chance
to listen to myself.
So I hope you did too.
[Kenzi] Hey guys, KenziFit here
with my daily dose
of damn good advice.
Never be afraid of how
powerful you really are.
Discover the power
you have inside you.
Don't wait for the universe
to give you a sign.
Discover it for yourself.
Click the link below to
sign up for my new discover-
[crickets chirping] [dog
barking in the distance]
[door slams]
[eerie music]
Whenever you are lost, you
can find yourself here.
Last night I realized
Verasha was trying
to tell me something.
Everything that I
was looking for,
my path, my answers,
they are all right here.
This is a traditional
Slavic ritual
called "prisoyedineniye"
or "the joining."
It is a month long
daily practice
curated by my ancestors
generations ago
meant to join the
soul back to the body,
the ultimate
spiritual centering.
My grandmother, she saw
how this culture takes
and takes and takes and
never gives anything back.
So she found something in
the history of our people.
I know that these videos
started out as one thing,
but I truly believe that
they can be so much more.
I don't know how
to speak Sanskrit.
I am an influencer
imposter living a lie.
And I don't know how
far I'll have to go
to start living my truth, but...
this feels like the first step.
For years, I was a
slave to caffeine.
Working on Wall Street,
I would drink like
12 espressos a day.
But when I went on a
business retreat in Bali,
I tried Chamisal
tea. [relaxing music]
It fueled my mind and my body
in a way I had
never felt before.
And I knew it was my job
to bring that
experience to the world.
So I quit corporate life
and turned my liquid
capital into liquid dreams.
This is RthNrgy,
a sacred blend of earth's
greatest treasures.
The hollowing,
the cleansing,
the many,
the expansion.
These are the core pillars of...
the joining.
I know this might all
seem a little strange,
but, it's like I said, discovery
is all about taking risks.
We gotta be fearless, right?
We're never gonna
know how far we can go
until we go there.
[distant thunder rumbling]
The first step to finding
yourself is finding your voice.
♪ La la la la la
[laughing] No, I'm
sorry. Ignore me.
Was a joke, don't ignore me.
Hey guys, welcome to
day one of our practice.
We're going to be kicking
off our journey with...
the hollowing.
It is an incantation,
a guided vocal chant,
meant to bring the
voice back to the body,
and really open us up
for what's about to come.
I know it might feel
a little bit silly,
but you know, just
trust your voice,
listen to your voice,
love your voice.
I will be following Verasha
and you will be following me.
Everyone inhale in.
[deep inhale]
♪ I am
♪ Oh, I am
[creaking]
Did you hear that?
Well, I'm sure my neighbors
heard something. [chuckling]
Well done, everyone. That
was great. Really awesome.
I hope you take
your voice with you
into the rest of your day.
And until then...
[deep inhale and exhale]
Day three, y'all.
Like Verasha says,
"Strong body, strong mind.
Find the shape that fits you."
Verasha's recipe,
[blending roaring]
a healthy body is
a receptive body.
If this is as far as you
can go, that's great.
It's only day six.
Just push yourself a
little further each time.
And remember,
make space in your body,
make space for your spirit.
Oh shit. Cheers.
I am receiving this.
[chair scratching
on the wooden floor]
The cleansing.
So, now that we've hollowed
out a space within us,
we are going to clear
out all the crap
that's stuck down inside.
So the next phase
of our practice
is going to be kind of
like a detoxifying purge.
It's really all about
getting rid of anything
and everything that
no longer serves us.
Don't freak out.
This is a very, very
common holistic practice.
It is called a throat
cleanse. You can look it up.
It's kind of like a nasal
cleanse, which I've done before.
Not a big deal.
All you do is you take a string
and you swallow it on
down in your throat,
and then you take it back out.
And that's it.
Okay, here we go.
We're gonna do it.
[gasping]
[eerie music]
[gagging]
[Anya vomiting]
[heavy breathing]
[vomiting]
[eerie music]
[creaking]
[door creaking]
Yikes.
Well, that was rough.
I definitely feel lighter.
Spiritually, not so much,
but physically, you
better believe it.
I know I talked a big game
about really taking risks
to discover yourself,
but I think the only
thing that I discovered
is that I can keep throwing up
even after my stomach
is completely empty.
Maybe I missed something.
Maybe I did it
wrong. I don't know.
Maybe I'm not ready for this.
So today
I am going to stick
with what I know.
A classic seated vinyasa flow.
So find a comfortable
seat on your sits bones,
and...
lengthen through your spine,
lifting away from the ground
out through the
crown of your head.
Lifting, lifting, lifting.
Lifting,
lifting, lifting,
lifting.
[distorted eerie noise]
Jesus.
Okay, so something
just happened there.
I don't know what it was.
Maybe it was just a feeling,
but it definitely felt powerful.
And listen, yeah, maybe I am
crazy to keep going with this.
Definitely not not crazy.
I have discovered something
powerful in these pages,
in this practice,
something beyond me.
That is where Verasha went,
and that is where
she wants me to go.
And I, I've gotta be fearless
in order to get there.
It...
Otherwise, I'll just end up
right back where I started
and...
I hope you can understand,
and I hope you're still with me.
[blender roaring]
[eerie music]
Hi.
Right, day 12,
the next part of our practice
is called "the many."
But there's only
half a page here.
It's like a poem or a
riddle or something.
"The many selves
share only one mind.
And you can't see the truth
when your thoughts are blind."
Blind eye.
Come on, Anya, get burned.
[glass shattering]
Oh, geez.
Okay, so, the many.
The journal says that this is
a remedy for the cleansing.
Kind of like an herbal
elixir to heal the body
and expand the mind.
So, okay, "you must
consider your many self"
all facets of your being.
"So you might see
yourself as one whole."
So essentially, you gotta relax.
[kettle whistling]
So I know that most of you
don't have a mystery
bottle of tea leaves
hiding around in your dead
grandma's secret crawlspace.
But you know, you can use
any kind of herbal remedy
that you have,
maybe some CBD, whatever
mellows you out.
Last time I did shrooms,
I was at the zoo,
and I cried for like six hours.
Let's hope that
doesn't happen again.
Cheers, Verasha. Cheers to you.
Here we go.
Ugh. Woo.
Ah, gross.
Okay.
Gross.
I definitely do feel a
little calmer though.
So, yes.
The next thing that we
have to do is we have to...
So the next...
next thing...
[distant thunder rumbling]
[groaning and panting]
[thunder rumbling]
[sinister laughing]
[sinister screaming]
[thunder rumbling]
[sinister laughing]
[phone ringing]
[Lenka] Hello?
Hello.
[Lenka] Anya, are are you
all right? It's so late.
Anya, are you all
right? It's so late.
[Lenka] Anya, is that you?
Who am I speaking to?
- Who am I speaking to?
Anya, are you, are you there?
Anya?
Hello?
Anya? Anya, are you there?
Mom?
[Lenka] Anya? Honey,
what is going on?
- We're okay.
- We, who's there with you?
I'm, I'm okay. I
don't, I don't know.
I just had a bad dream.
It's, it's nothing.
I'm sorry I called.
[Lenka] Are you
sure you're okay?
Who is there with you?
Grandma.
[knocking at the door]
Hey, thank you so
much for coming.
[Kenzi] Yeah, for sure.
Oh...
we've been redecorating.
[Anya] I guess so.
Kinda looks like
my grandma's house.
Thank you.
So how are the videos going?
I'm really excited to show
you what I've been working on.
I can't wait.
Jesus, Anya, have
you been eating?
I've been focusing
on making space.
Well, maybe you make space for
a Caesar wrap or something.
Look, are you, are you
sure you wanna shoot this?
Why?
You look not great?
I'm fine.
Okay.
[creaking]
Is someone else here?
No, it's just us.
Hi everyone, welcome back to
Mind Body Spirit, I'm Anya.
It's day 17. Let's get
started with today's practice.
And I'm Kenzi from KenziFit.
Right.
Do you wanna start over again?
No, not really.
And this is Kenzi.
She'll be joining us
for today's practice.
The expansion, the joining.
Wait, sorry.
Can, can we stop this a second?
I, I thought this was
gonna be like a flow.
What, what is this?
This is Verasha.
- What the fuck is a Verasha?
- My grandmother.
- Okay, can we cut?
- Why? What's wrong?
I'm, I'm not doing whatever
this is. This isn't my thing.
Yeah, I know. It's my thing.
Okay, great for you, I guess,
but like this isn't
on brand for me.
Like, what even is this?
- Hey!
Whoa. Chill. Jesus,
Anya, look at yourself.
I have been looking at myself
more than you ever will.
What the fuck is your deal?
I'm just trying to help you.
I don't need your help, cunt!
You know what?
Good.
The only reason that I am here
is because your mom begged
me to come and check on you
and make sure you didn't try
to fucking kill yourself again.
I don't need to be a guest
star on your shitty video diary
that nobody's gonna
fucking watch.
I actually have a following.
I actually help
people feel good.
I'm not just... [snickering]
I am not just sitting around
in this stupid fucking room
starving myself
and getting lifestyle tips
from the book of the dead.
Who the fuck do
you think you are?
Your whole entire fucking career
is built on the backs
of people like Verasha,
people with the fucking fortitude
to go out into the world
and experience real shit.
You, you bounce your tits
around doing some jumping jacks,
and you think that you're
changing people's lives.
Are you fucking kidding me?
You consume other
people's cultures
and then shit them back out
into leopard-neon spandex.
Kenzi, you're a
fucking colonizer!
- Oh my God!
- This is real.
This is truth. This is my
heritage and I am living it.
Oh...
my fucking God!
Anya, are you serious?
Colonizer?
You need a fucking Taco Bell.
At least back when
you actually ate food.
I mean, what?
You seriously think that
your weird fucking grandma
traveled the world?
She probably never even
left this fucking house.
Just some sad old lady
getting drunk on Vodka
and making up stories because
her family abandoned her.
Keep your fucking
Siberian bullshit.
Fuck you, fuck your
grandma. Have a great life.
I am done with this and
I am so done with you.
And I am taking this with me.
Hey!
Get out!
- What the fuck, Anya?
- Get out.
Get out!
You fucking psycho!
[door slams]
[screams]
[bones cracking]
[eerie music]
[Anya breathing heavily]
[computer dialing tone]
Anya, what is the
matter with you?
Why haven't you called me back?
Kenzi's mom said you
two got in a fight.
Yeah, I'm sorry. I, I
meant to call you earlier.
I just-
I've been so worried about you.
I almost called the police.
Mom, I'm sorry. Okay?
You look sick.
I, I need help.
Okay. Okay. I'll get the
first flight out there.
No, mom, I need help
translating something.
- No.
- Mom, please.
I said no.
Please.
Anya.
Mom, please.
I don't, I don't
know what I'm doing.
What has she done to you?
I, I don't know.
I don't know. And-
Anya, this is why I never told
you about your grandmother.
The day I heard Verasha died,
all I felt was happiness,
because I knew she would
never come back for you.
Jesus, mom.
- Anya, come home, please.
- Okay.
I am sorry, mom.
I am so sorry that I
didn't listen to you,
but I need you to
translate this for me.
But I need you to
help me for once,
because if I don't find
a way to finish this,
then I will never escape it
and I can't keep running.
So please, please tell
me what this says.
Show me.
So...
she translated most of it
and, and phonetized some
other places, but not this.
And it looks like it's in
the same alphabet, I think.
It might be just a
different dialect or...
- Anya. Anya.
- What does it say?
I, I can't, I can't say it.
- Mom, please tell me.
- Anya.
- Anya, I can't say it.
- It doesn't make
any sense - What?
It's, it's, it's some
sort of ancient tongue.
It's barely even Russian.
I don't know what this is.
Anya. Anya, please come home.
You fucking bitch.
I've been lying to you
because my grandmother
has been lying to me.
You see this symbol, the
top of all the ritual pages?
Yeah, I thought, I thought
that it was like a, a flourish
or a signature or something.
But...
it's not.
It's a fucking key
to what's hidden in these pages.
These aren't words of wisdom.
It's fucking backwards
black magic bullshit.
This was never meant
to cleanse my spirit.
This was meant to
destroy my spirit.
It was meant to
destroy my spirit
and make room for hers.
And I...
followed blindly because it's
easier than facing myself.
[screaming]
[eerie music]
[deep heart beating]
Verasha, please, please,
Verasha, you don't have,
you don't have to do this.
Please, please.
No, please, please.
[screaming] [eerie
music continues]
Hey guys, it's
Kenzi from KenziFit.
Frown Lines looking fierce.
Clear the years away with
Renuyu, age defying day cream.
Handcrafted with
natural ingredients
to leave your skin feeling
fresh and you feeling younger.
Click the link below and
enter promo code Kenzi
for 10% off your order.
Renuyu. Feel new.
Look new. Live new.
Absolve your skin.
Hi Kenzi, this is Anya speaking.
I can't tell you how sorry I
am for my behavior earlier.
I feel so ashamed.
To be perfectly honest with you,
I think a lot of that anger
came from a place of jealousy.
I mean, you're just so
worldly and wise and kind.
And sometimes, sometimes,
sometimes I feel
like I can't compete.
There's this little
voice inside of me
that just won't let be myself.
And I just wanna
tell her to let go.
It's okay.
But until then, I sincerely
hope you can forgive me.
And as a sign of good faith,
I would love to have you over
to record some more videos
and bury the old hatchet.
Wishing you wellness my friend.
Namaste.
[knocking at the door]
Are you filming me?
[Anya] Yes. Is that
all right with you?
Yeah, sure.
Holy shit, are you
okay? What happened?
[Anya] Oh, this.
I hit my head while I was
rearranging some furniture.
It looks like it hurt.
[Anya] I'm fine now.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't
have said, I mean earlier.
I'm sorry.
[creaking]
Do you wanna sit?
I am sorry for
getting so heated.
It's just...
being this, this perfect person
is just so fucking
stressful, you know?
I completely understand.
And I'm sorry too.
I shouldn't have
said those things.
Are you sure you're okay?
I feel fantastic.
I truly do.
I...
I guess I have to thank you.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
You know, I don't really agree
with the way you handled things,
and I was pretty
fucking upset with you.
But what you said,
it wasn't bullshit.
We're all just borrowing,
stealing, I guess,
just like taking
pieces of things
and making them our identity
without really thinking
about where they come from.
And I guess,
I guess I just don't really
know who I am without them.
You're you. That's
all you can be.
I mean, I put in the work.
It's not like easy,
but I'm not, you know,
special or whatever.
But you are.
How hard did you hit your head?
[both giggling]
I am glad you're here.
I'm glad I am too.
Okay, so what exactly
did you have in mind?
It's a guided meditation.
I practiced it on my
own a few nights ago,
but it's supposed to be better
when someone else
is guiding you.
Cool. You, you
wanna do an intro?
I recorded an
introduction earlier,
but perhaps we can say "hello."
Okay. Yeah. Cool. Kick it off.
Welcome back everyone
to Mind Body Spirit.
We have a familiar guest today.
Hey guys, KenziFit here.
I will be guiding you
through a meditation.
And Kenzi here, will
be my first recipient.
Find yourself in a
comfortable corpse pose.
Whatever feels best to you.
- Okay.
Allow your back body
to sink to the ground.
[deep exhale]
Let your belly rise
and fall with a breath.
[deep exhale]
Sink deeper with every exhale.
In
And out. [deep exhale]
In...
- Oh. Okay.
- It's okay.
And as you relax,
your partner will gently reach
your arms out to your sides,
extending away from
your ribs, [deep exhale]
allowing your breath to
fill into your lungs,
reaching their full
capacity. [deep exhale]
In
And out. [deep exhale]
Continue with this rhythm.
[deep exhale]
In
And out. [deep exhale]
This is really nice.
So how long should I-
[Kenzi shrieks]
[heavy multiple thuds]
[tense music with a heavy beat]
[door slams]
[sinister music]
I am ready to
receive all of you.
[quivering]
[gasping]
[bones cracking]
[screaming]
[sinister scream]
[cellphone vibrating]
- Hello?
- Anya? Jesus, are you okay?
[Lenka] I have been
calling you nonstop.
[Anya] Oh, don't worry.
I'm fine. I slept well.
I feel rested now.
[Lenka] That's a relief.
It's, it's good to
hear your voice.
[Anya] Hmm. It's good
to hear your voice too.
[Lenka] What happened
with the journal?
[Anya] Well, I put
that behind me.
[Lenka] Oh, good.
Good.
Anya?
[Anya] I was trying so
hard to be someone else
that I finally found myself.
I think it's time
I come home, Lenka.
[Lenka] I look forward
to seeing you again.
I love you, Anya.
[sinister music]
[heavy beat sinister music]
[heavy beat sinister
music continues]