Please, help me!
Help!
Please!
Get me out of here!
Help!
Get us out of here!
Please!
Oh God!
Water!
Get out now. Move. Come on, come on.
Come on, hurry.
The backpacks. Move it, fast!
We’re getting out!
- At last! Thank God!
- Quick!
Get up. Get down!
Where’s he going? Where?
- Let’s see what you’ve got. Take it out.
- Come here. Come here.
- Take it out! Give it to me.
- Come on, that’s it.
Go on, get out.
- That chain, don’t play dumb.
- Give me the boots.
- Show me what you’ve got.
- I don’t have anything!
- You, bastard, give me that jacket.
- Got your wallet there?
- Don’t play dumb, idiot.
- Come on, come on.
- You too, I saw you.
- Hands up. Let’s go, quick.
Up, up. Let’s go, fast.
- Take them off. What you got?
- You, give me that backpack.
- Give it! Come on, bastards, move!
- Quick, quick!
Is that all?
Want anything else? All good?
Ok.
Hey, no!
- I need a glass of water.
- No.
You can’t be here.
Let’s go.
STOP
- Well… thanks.
- Good luck.
Hey.
Would you give me a ride?
I’m going to San Francisco.
I’m headed the other way.
Alright, ok.
STOP
How did you get here?
- I crossed through San Antonio.
- How?
With the money you left.
Call your mom, she’s worried.
Yes, but you tell her I’m fine.
- I’ll call later.
- I’ll tell her.
- Ok.
- Thanks.
Alright, hug.
Hugs, take care.
- Your dad?
- Yes.
- How is he?
- He’s fine.
- Hand me the plates.
- Yes.
I’m glad to see you.
You found her.
Yes. Thanks.
What will we eat?
Italian food.
- Want me to help?
- No.
I want to spoil you.
- Ok. So what do I do?
- Nothing.
…after crossing the border in Laredo, Mexican authorities reported that,
at 2:45 p.m. on Monday, a truck passed through a checkpoint
of the Border Patrol in Encino, Texas.
A camera recorded the driver, identified by authorities
as a U.S. citizen, driving toward Cotulla.
And finally it stopped about 235 kilometers further ahead,
on a day with temperatures close to 38 degrees Celsius.
The alleged driver was identified
by the U.S. Department of Justice as Homero Zamorano.
- What do you have against Mexicans?
- Nothing...
It’s not, it’s not that I have anything against Mexicans, but I think...
I think we should help Americans. That’s all.
Well, your wife doesn’t seem to care either.
Sure, but she hasn’t attended these meetings in a long time, so it doesn’t matter.
Jake, are the ones living in Mission Mexicans or Americans?
Mexicans.
Son, if you don’t approve your sister’s project,
we can finance it from another company account.
I’ll propose something, Jake.
I’ll make a program you do like.
First sign Mexico’s budget for next year.
Half the money from my programs is deducted in taxes.
Oh, approved.
Do you want to go with me to Mexico next time?
Don’t exaggerate.
- Thanks.
- You’re welcome.
You’re an idiot.
MISSION DISTRICT COMMUNITY CENTER
RESPECT
I missed this.
Let’s do it more often.
Do you have to go back to San Francisco?
Not right away.
What if we stayed?
I’ll see if they can extend our stay.
One day.
One more day.
Ok.
That’s enough.
We’re leaving.
Why?
- No availability?
- No.
One of my dad’s partners is checking in.
Do you fear being seen with me?
That’s not it.
Can you pack? Please.
Please, pack.
Miss McCarthy, welcome.
May I have your attention, please?
First of all, welcome to the “Michael McCarthy” wing.
As you know, my father is a tireless defender of the arts
and has donated, from his private collection, the works we can admire here today,
so I invite you to join me in welcoming,
not only a great human being,
but a man who doesn’t seem to stop in his effort to make this
a better city. Michael McCarthy.
Thank you.
First, I want to thank you all for being here today.
It means a lot.
I also want to thank my son Jake,
not only for his kind and generous words,
which are sometimes a bit exaggerated about his father,
but because he too is a great advocate.
He has created programs that help the most needy in our community,
and I thank him.
And I want to thank my beautiful daughter Jennifer,
who, since she graduated from university, has always been by my side,
helping this foundation run as it should.
Hi, it’s me.
I wanted to tell you I stopped by the house.
I took my things and left the keys on the kitchen table.
I came here to be with you.
You know what you mean to me and what I risked to be here.
But I don’t want to keep hiding all the time.
So, please...
Leave me.
I’ll manage on my own.
Fernando?
Where are you? I’m worried.
What do you want?
Come back.
Where will you sleep?
Maybe I’ll go back to Mexico.
Don’t call me.
This one has a new entrance.
We’d have to modify the façade and request new permits.
Do you want me to show you the budgets?
I’ll review it later. We’ll talk then.
Of course.
MCCARTHY FOUNDATION
The person you’re trying to call is not available.
Your call was sent to voicemail. Leave your message...
- Six months!
Very good.
- Are we doing well?
- Happy anniversary!
Yes.
What are we toasting to?
Better you do it.
First me in English and then you in Spanish.
Alright.
- To another six months...
- Only six months?
Hello, Jake.
Hello. Hello, hello. How are you?
Fine, what’s up?
Tomorrow we’ll have a barbecue in the garden.
The kids want to see you and spend time...
Will Dad go?
Yes.
Sorry to miss it, I’m going to Mexico City.
You’re going to Mexico City? When?
I’m on the plane, I’ll visit the academy.
The... the academy?
Yes.
What do you mean you’ll visit it?
Well, they’re doing a great job...
So why go, if they’re already doing a good job?
Jake.
I’m joking, just joking. Take care, ok?
- I will. I’ll be back Tuesday.
- I worry about you.
- Ah, I… I’m fine.
- Call me when you’re back, alright?
- Ok. Love you all. Have fun.
- Ok. We love you.
- Bye.
- Good, thanks. Bye.
You're going to sit on the table...
and I'm going to suck your balls without touching your penis.
And no matter how hard you are...
we won't fuck.
Let's see how long you can last.
Do you think you know me well?
I know you're wet.
Your nipples are hard.
And all you want is for me to turn you over
and spank your ass.
That'll shut you up.
I'll take my penis and stick it in you...
while I kiss your neck.
Is that what you think I'm thinking?
And you want me to stick my finger up your ass at the same time.
You don't know me well.
But I know you get hard talking to me.
And you're dying for me to suck your balls.
And come in your face, just like yesterday.
Why don't we go to the couch?
I'm going to lick you while you suck my balls.
To the couch? Why so far away?
Suck them.
Even though you’re sweaty from exercise?
I think that’s how you like them.
Really?
Wait for me there.
Fernando called us and said he was safe in San Francisco.
Leave him alone.
I told Fernando not to leave Mexico and that what he did was very dangerous.
I told Fernando not to leave Mexico and that what he did is very dangerous.
Yes, but the one who humiliated him at the hotel was her.
Better just tell him to go.
And also tell him why not find someone his own age.
Beautiful.
Thank you.
Well, I ask you all to stand up too.
Please come closer.
Many of you already know our dear Jennifer McCarthy,
director of the foundation that supports us.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Thank you.
Thank you. I’m sorry I don’t speak Spanish to tell you how wonderful you are,
but maybe you could translate it.
Thank you. She’s very happy to be here.
And she’s seen a lot of progress since the last time she joined us.
Sorry I didn’t come earlier.
Thank you very much for coming.
Where is Fernando?
He hasn’t been here in weeks.
Thank you for receiving me.
Let me know if you hear anything about him.
Martha?
There are clothes for you in the closet. That, give it to your family.
- The rest, keep it.
- Thanks.
Ok? On the corner. When Fernando returns, will you call me?
One moment.
One moment...
When Fernando returns, call me immediately.
Ah. “When Fernando gets home, call me immediately.”
- Of course, ma’am.
- Ok. Yes?
- Yes.
- Ok, thank you.
Would you like something to eat?
No, no thank you.
- Thanks.
- Goodbye.
Bye.
This is how it looks.
I’ll be very clear.
It’s almost impossible to find an illegal because...
they’re not in the records.
I’ll send you the information... Do what you can.
- I don’t want to give you false hope.
- Money is not a problem.
Ok.
Could you tell me a little about your relationship?
He’s a dancer...
He works at my foundation in Mexico City.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
Hello.
Ready to go in?
Yes.
Incredible. What’s your name?
My name is Fernando.
- Where are you from?
- Thanks.
I’m from Mexico. Thanks.
Mexico. I’m trying to get a ticket for the ballet.
I’m going to the bathroom, won’t be long.
- Hurry up.
- Yes.
Hello.
Fernando.
- Hello, Mary.
- Hello.
- I came to see Mathew.
- Fine, I’ll let him know you’re here.
- Thanks.
- You’re welcome.
- What a pretty blouse.
- Thanks.
- Did you like last night’s performance?
- Oh my God! It was horrible.
Please tell me you hated it.
- Oh, I hated it. My father liked it.
- Of course he did.
I saw you outside. I wanted to greet you, but...
you were talking with a dancer in the street.
- I preferred not to interrupt.
- Oh, he’s so talented.
- He works in a motel or something.
- In a motel?
Yes, he’s from Mexico. You could help him.
Sure.
Why don’t you send me his information? I’ll see if the foundation can help.
That would be fantastic. How are you?
- Very well.
- How’s your project going?
Good.
I came to talk to you about a building
we’re remodeling in the Mission District.
How exciting!
- I’ll show you some photos.
- Ok.
Did your parents tell you I went to see them?
No.
How did you find me?
I saw when Matthew gave you his card.
You know him.
He’ll let me train with the company.
- Will you stay?
- Yes.
- How do you make money?
- Don’t you see?
We were happy in Mexico.
Do you think it’s okay to beg in the street?
They could deport you.
I wasn’t begging.
And I don’t think you care what happens to me.
I do care.
You know I do.
- Hello.
I came to see Matthew.
Sorry, but he already left.
I really need to talk to him. Could you give me his cell number?
Sorry, I can’t give you that information.
I understand.
Do you want to leave him a message?
- No, it’s fine. Thanks.
- You’re welcome.
Fernando, leave now.
Immigration is here asking for papers. They already took Pablo.
Why don’t you have papers?
I was deported from New York in 2013 for dancing in Union Square.
You were just dancing?
People started giving me money, but I didn’t ask for it.
What happened after you were deported?
I hired a lawyer. I fought for a long time.
My plan was to stay in New York but... it didn’t happen.
I think you have talent, and I hope we can work together.
Thanks, I hope so too.
Again, thanks for showing me everything today, and for letting me in.
It’s nothing. Good luck.
Can you pick that up?
Oh my God!
Very good.
Fernando...
I’d like to see a little more... of you today.
Do you know "Black Swan"?
Yes, I know it.
Great. Let’s do the ending of "Black Swan".
- From the back row forward?
- Yes, please.
Natasha, let’s take it from the ending of "Black Swan".
Good.
Very good.
Very good. Good work.
- Arlette.
- Yes?
I’d like to see you with Fernando, please.
Maybe from the beginning of "Black Swan".
- Do you both know it?
- Yes.
Excellent.
- Hey.
- Nice to meet you. Arlette.
Fernando.
How do you want us to start?
Let’s start from the beginning, both straight to sous-sus.
Alright, and then you do...
Yes, the usual...
Normal.
Ok. I’ll try.
To the pretty girls,
we sing it like this...
Happy birthday, my love!
Grandma?
No, my love.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you, darling.
Obviously I didn’t make it.
- I’m sure it’s delicious.
- Yes.
Come on, Fer, cheer up.
Stop thinking about it.
The person you called is not available.
Your call will be transferred to voicemail. Leave your message...
THE FEATHER AND THE STARS
Shall I serve you another?
Of course. Yes.
Excuse me. Thank you.
Hello.
Thanks for the ticket.
I loved the performance.
Me too.
What? You came?
Yes.
Where?
We’ll come together next time.
Hello.
It’s me.
Good morning!
There’s a mat and yoga bands in the living room.
Do you need money?
No, I’ll go to the motel for my wallet.
Here’s cash and the key.
I’ll leave soon.
No rush.
Have breakfast and call me if you need anything.
Very good.
Thank you all.
It has been a true pleasure to have
Fernando as a member of this company.
And I want to thank you for welcoming him.
And it really has been a very easy decision
to give Fernando the lead role.
Fernando... where did you learn to dance?
In Mexico.
Did you go to a school?
Of course, I danced since I was a child.
Did you also beg in the streets?
I don’t beg.
I thought that’s how you met Matthew.
I just wanted a ticket to the ballet, I wasn’t begging...
He saw you before the show, weren’t you asking for money?
- Joe!
- What?
So what if he danced outside the theater? You wouldn’t dare.
I don’t have to dance in the street for money.
- Shut up!
- It was clear he just wanted a ticket.
Since he’s undocumented, it took guts to do it.
Why don’t we just leave?
Damn gringo bastards, brother.
We cross the border, wipe their asses
and there’s no problem.
But just take someone’s job away and look...
they send you to hell.
So unfair.
Serve yourself another, Lety, please.
And pour one for yourself too.
Hi, Mom!
I’m fine, yes. I came to the bar.
No, go to sleep now.
Ok.
I love you too.
Bye.
I’ll introduce you.
Hello, girls. This is Fernando.
- He’s a dance teacher here.
- Hello, Fernando.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
They’re students. Very interested in learning ballet.
- They are Robert, Charlie, and Lily.
- Hi.
Hi. Why ballet?
We went to the ballet once and loved it so much.
It was unforgettable for all of us.
Yes.
What was the best part of the performance?
The lifts.
- The lifts?
- Yes, it was impressive.
You must work hard, you know that, right?
Yes, they told us we must come here every afternoon... so...
At least six days.
- Six days?
- Oh wow. Ok.
It’s very strict.
- Don’t be late or you’ll have problems.
- Yes.
- Never late.
- Nice to see you.
- Bye.
- A pleasure.
It was great. Cool. You know.
What happened to you?
Dance, that’s what happened.
Ice helps.
- Does it hurt?
- No.
Well, it hurts a little more than the massage.
- Did the massage hurt?
- No, not much.
- You should put more pressure.
- More pressure, huh?
- Yes, thanks.
- But I don’t want to...
- It’s fine.
- Oh, darling.
- Is that okay?
- Yes.
You introduced me as their teacher.
- Juanita doesn’t know we’re together.
- It’s obvious we’re together.
It’s obvious you’re always acting.
I’m not acting, you’re their teacher.
- Can I be both?
- Yes, of course.
Hello.
A pleasure.
- Do you remember?
- Of course.
Well, it doesn’t seem like it.
Good afternoon everyone, thank you very much for being here.
I’d love to introduce the man of the moment, my father,
Michael McCarthy.
We wouldn’t be here if not for his generosity.
Let’s give him a big round of applause, please.
Well, my daughter is very generous.
The truth is none of this would be possible
without the foundation that she and her brother Jake created.
So I’d like you to give them applause, please.
We couldn’t be more excited to be here
and learn about what you’re doing. So please,
continue with your activities and don’t let us interrupt you.
- Thanks.
- It’s nothing.
You were turning, right?
Look... you turn backwards and then...
Something like that. Hello. Fernando.
And then, yes... you raise your arm.
- Hello.
- Fernando.
- Delighted.
- Thank you very much.
Don’t thank me. Please.
Yes.
Yes, like that. From the top.
Don’t forget your position. Yes.
Ok, like this. Wait.
One...
Two, three.
And lift.
Hello.
It turned out perfect, you look very handsome.
- Thanks.
- Did you have a good day?
Yes, it was good, but long.
I had a three‑hour rehearsal,
- until...
- Thanks. Want a glass of wine?
- Yes.
- One more.
During rehearsal, one of the guys dropped a ballerina.
- No!
- Yes.
Then there was an argument about whose fault it was.
And he didn’t want to take responsibility.
It’s a general rule in ballet...
- Jennifer?
- Daphne.
- Hi.
- Good to see you.
- Long time.
- I know.
- Good to see you.
He’s Fernando, an exceptionally talented dancer.
- A pleasure, Fernando.
- The pleasure is mine.
Is he in your program?
No, he’s in the San Francisco Ballet company.
- Fantastic!
- Enjoy your meal.
Thanks.
You were saying?
Pointe flex.
I’m hungry.
Well, you’ve been working...
at least for an hour.
I try.
- I know.
- I added tofu, do you like it?
I like everything you make.
I’ve never had so much food at home.
We could have gone to a restaurant.
Don’t use your key, I’ll open.
Who is it?
It’s my brother, I didn’t know he’d come.
Do you think he’ll stay?
I don’t know.
Hey, hey! You’re coming out with me today.
I have an extra ticket for the game.
- Take your coat.
- Well...
It’s good to see you. I’ll have a glass of water.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
I know you. From the community center.
Yes.
You... yes...
- Remind me.
- I’m a ballet teacher.
The ballet teacher.
- From Mexico or...?
- Yes.
Great.
- Jake.
- I’m Fernando.
Fernando, of course. Good to see you.
Likewise.
I’d invite you...
but I only have one extra ticket.
Looks like I interrupted you.
I’ll leave you two alone and...
Goodbye.
- I’ll call you tomorrow.
- Yes, that’s fine.
Have fun.
You’re doing well, the rhythm is perfect.
Alright, let’s start, mark the step.
Good.
One, two, three, four.
One. Super!
One... Yes!
Keep going.
So, it’s about those places... and that.
I think...
Hello!
Hi, Dad.
Thanks for coming.
Of course.
- Shall we get a coffee?
- I already had one.
Let’s go out. I won’t take much of your time.
I’ll get straight to the point.
Jake said he saw the Mexican dancer at your house yesterday.
Does he live with you?
Dad... it’s nothing.
You know I want you to be happy and have a relationship.
And give me some grandchildren.
You know I tried but I can’t.
- I know, but I didn’t come to talk about that.
- Why are you here?
What do you want us to talk about?
Look, I’m glad you help immigrants.
You know I support you with that.
But there are limits, do you understand what I’m saying?
- Excuse me, may we order?
- Of course.
I’d like the sea bass.
- Good choice. Thank you.
- Thanks.
Sir?
May I recommend the bass?
What are “capers”?
Ah. Capers.
Alright. I’ll have that.
- You won’t regret it.
- Thanks.
- Where are you from?
- I’m from Mexico City, you?
Ah... I’m from Puebla.
But we’ve been here 20 years now.
- Well, a lifetime.
- Yes, it’s a long time.
Are you visiting?
I live here. I’m teaching ballet.
Oh, that’s great.
- I’m Fernando.
- I’m Joaquín. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, Joaquín.
- Likewise. Would you like something to drink?
I’ll start with the goat cheese salad.
- Ok.
- He means drinks.
Oh, sorry. No, I’m fine. I didn’t mean to interrupt your talk.
- It’s fine, Joaquín, thanks.
- Ok. I’ll be right back.
Excuse me.
Did you forget me?
- Why?
- Well, you can speak in English.
I think you should know a little Spanish, right?
After all the time you spent in Mexico,
having a Mexican boyfriend...
- A little, miss.
- Enough.
- Please!
- Enough!
I’m in a bad mood, sorry.
I had an argument with my dad.
Was it about me?
No.
Not at all, in fact it was Jake’s fault.
It was because he saw me at your house the other day.
- How are you, son?
- Very well.
- Really?
- I haven’t seen you at the meetings.
- That skateboard is very fast, eh.
- Tell me when and we’ll meet.
- No? I’ll greet your mom.
- We’ll go for breakfast.
Why aren’t you in school?
The teachers have a school meeting.
Hello.
The first Friday of every month.
Will you let your sister ride it? You must lend it to her.
Are you happy not to have gone to school?
Yes!
- We talked about you at the meeting.
- Ah, sure.
Well, we’re leaving.
- Goodbye, kids.
- Bye.
Up to there, stop.
From the side.
That’s better.
Stop for a moment, please.
Fernando, can you come?
IMMIGRATION
We already tried over there and it didn’t work.
She must have contacts, it’s her business.
She must have contacts in Tijuana, at all the borders.
Do you already have contacts there?
Not yet in Tijuana, but the coyote who passed us must have contacts.
- How much did they charge you?
- They charged us eight thousand.
Eight thousand.
Yes, it’s a lot, but...
I think yes, she’ll connect us, buddy.
- Are you all Mexicans?
- Yes!
Show me your INE, please.
- I don’t have INE.
- You don’t have INE.
- But I’m Mexican.
- Where are you from?
- From Honduras.
- From Honduras. This way.
- I come from El Salvador.
- This way, please.
Everyone else go with my colleagues and give some information.
Go ahead, please. Go ahead.
Look friend, we’re from Venezuela.
Identification, please.
You are... Tomás Alba?
- Go that way, please.
- Will it take long, miss?
- One or two hours at most.
- Thanks.
- Last name?
- Let’s see, gentlemen!
Go ahead, come in.
Officer, even if we’re not Mexicans, we have rights.
To go to the bathroom, to drink water, to see a doctor.
We’re only migrants, we’re not criminals.
Why do you treat us like this?
He always says the same thing.
- It comes in here.
- The passport too?
The passport and the case number also come here, sir.
Any questions you can call us.
My name is Arturo.
Passengers of flight 114, boarding is ready.
Please go to counter 112 for check‑in.
- Thank you.
We’ve arrived.
I’m fine.
When will you come?
Ok.
How long will you stay?
I have to return Monday, I have a meeting in New York.
What day is today?
It’s Monday.
I’ll be here all week.
I’ll return immediately.
We don’t need anything in San Francisco.
We can start our company here.
Yes, another location. Experienced dancers.
That would take time.
We have time.
I can come more often.
I could almost live here.
That would be nice.
No, he proposed in Las Vegas.
She said, “Let’s do it” and he said, “Let’s do it in Las Vegas.”
- He can’t go to Las Vegas, so...
- No.
- My joke was...
- Wait, wait, wait.
- The joke is good.
- There may be a chance
to try again.
I was married and divorced and it’s not... a big deal.
- Really?
- Wow, I didn’t know that.
Because you haven’t married him, it’s great.
Thanks.
- They’re the best.
- Super.
But what a good idea!
Cheers! Drink up.
Wedding next year.
- Why so long?
- Where?
No, the idea was obviously to have married already,
but he keeps putting it off.
And honestly I’m a little tired.
So... it would be good to cross again.
Don’t you think I should look for a career in San Francisco?
- Wouldn’t you like me to come back?
- No, no, I’d love for you to return.
- We’ve tried...
- Ok, I want to return.
- Let’s go back.
- Safely.
- In a way he doesn’t risk... you know.
- Cheers... cheers because you’re coming back.
No, no, no, no.
Did you eat anything?
- No.
- No. Have you drunk on an empty stomach?
- Yes.
- Ok. Eat this.
No, thanks.
I can’t go to New York if you don’t take care of yourself.
Don’t go.
Just stay.
Of course.
Where’s the mezcal?
There’s mezcal here for...
Why do you like San Francisco?
What will you do there that you can’t do here?
They’ll never make you an official member of the company.
We won’t be able to be together there.
I can’t cancel my trip to New York.
It’s not fair that you make me leave you like this.
Don’t cancel it.
Look... just go to New York.
I didn’t want to tell you until I had it all figured out
but I found someone who can help me cross through El Paso.
- I won’t give you money to kill yourself.
- I don’t need money.
I just need to get to Juárez on Tuesday.
When you finish in New York, I’ll be able to be in San Francisco.
We weren’t happy there!
But I was.
Don’t worry.
They told me this time we won’t go in a trailer.
So it’s safer and faster.
You know I’d do anything for you, right?
Of course.
I have something to tell you.
Then you decide if you want us to stay together.
Tell me if you want me to come back after...
my trip or if...
you don’t want to see me again.
What’s wrong?
I made you get deported.
You were never going to...
return to Mexico and we couldn’t be together in...
In San Francisco, there was too much pressure, you know?
I called Immigration Services, said you were an illegal immigrant
that you were dancing in the company and had been deported before,
in 2013.
You have to understand why I did it.
This time everything will be better.
I’ll be here more often.
We’ll have our company here.
Think about it while I’m gone.
And if you don’t...
If you don’t want me to come back, you can stay here,
I’ll pay the bills. I’ll never abandon you.
I did it for us because I love you.
- Do you want us to be together?
- Yes.
Very much.
Ok.
Fernando...
Can we talk?
Fernando.
I need to go to the bathroom.
You can go in the yard.
No!
Can I go now?
I thought the idea was to be together, right?
You’re right to be upset, I’m very sorry.
I’m not.
I’m happy we’re together.
- Me too.
- I’m going to shower.
Or maybe I won’t.
I forgot you liked me sweaty.
Stop, enough!
Stop!
No.
Have you forgiven me?
Did you file my residency application?
No!
Thank you very much.
Sorry, I forgot to tell you it wasn’t necessary for you to come today.
Go home.
She hasn’t been feeling well today.
You know? Go. Come another day.
Martha?
No, it’s not necessary. I’ll take care of Jennifer these days.
And when she feels better, I’ll call you.
- Are you sure, young man?
- Sure.
Sorry I didn’t call to cancel earlier.
I’ll wait for your call, young man.
My family is waiting for me in New York.
- I’m going out, do you need anything?
- Let me go.
What happened, Rafa?
Sir, sorry for coming without notice,
but I call the young lady and it goes to voicemail.
Just to check if the airport service for Monday is still on.
Not anymore.
She’s staying here. Good night, Rafa.
Ok, sir.
Let’s go.
- Tell them what you did to me.
- Shut your damn mouth.
Tell them to leave our house.
I’ll be back!
Everyone will know what you did to me.
I’ll tell everyone who you are!
A liar!
What do we do?
Hi, Dad.
Yes, I know.
Alright.
See you.
DEDICATED TO THE MEMORY OF MY DEAR FRIEND GRÉGOIRE LASSALLE