Eddie and Jean met
and fell in love.
Eddie and Jean got married
and bought a house.
Eddie and Jean
were gonna have a kid
but didn't.
So, every morning,
Eddie kisses Jean,
Eddie leaves the house,
and Jean's alone.
Fucking Eddie, come on.
Eddie, have you seen
the scissors? I...
You're wearing it.
Looks real good on you.
Who's that?
He's our baby.
There were still some tags.
Aren't you gonna say something?
This some kind of
sick joke, Eddie?
'Cause I'm not really
in the mood.
No.
It's a baby, Jean.
I can see that.
It's all worked out.
He's our baby.
Come here, look.
Here, you can...
Where did you...?
Uh, not now, Jean.
It's your baby.
What's his name?
That's up to you.
Yeah?
Something burning?
Yes.
Where's the other egg?
On the floor.
Mmm.
I'll get it.
Hey, I'm not
gonna be home tonight.
You'll be all right?
That's my little firecracker.
Eddie, I...
What?
Nothing.
Hey.
Don't worry about it so much.
Your eggs are terrible anyway.
Hey, Singh. Come on in.
Nice to see you.
Rowe, thanks for being here.
Oh.
Come on, come on.
- My boy.
- I'm so fucking enjoying it here.
Hey, hey, watch your mouth.
I got a kid.
All right, all right.
I know.
Hold on one second.
Jimmy.
You're okay?
Yeah. Why?
What are you doing?
No one's here?
What are you talking about?
Something happened tonight.
We have to go.
Now, Jean.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on. Let's go.
Jimmy, what are you doing here?
Go ahead, down the hall.
Why are you in Eddie's closet?
You don't have time to pack.
- You can get stuff on the way.
- You got to slow down.
I-I don't know what's happening.
You'll work out with Cal
where you're gonna go.
Who the hell is Cal?
Where is Eddie?
This is 200 grand.
Cal will manage how the money
is spent, but you hold onto it.
- Is Eddie okay?
- You give him ten grand right away,
and you can work it out from
there if he stays with you.
Who told you to tell me
all of this?
What...
Jimmy.
Jimmy, Jimmy, hey, hey.
Stop, stop, stop.
Jimmy, it's me. It's Jean.
Please tell me what's happening.
Just take the bag, sweetheart.
Go wake up the kid.
I'm Cal.
All Eddie said is
he wouldn't be home tonight,
but he says that all the time,
and then I wake up
in the middle of the night and
he's right there next to me.
I don't know what's going on
or who you are or why
any of this is happening.
He's never like this.
It's like he knows
something isn't right.
I mean, he cries when
he's hungry, but he just ate.
Don't they say that
about babies?
They can feel an energy, like...
like, even if
you're trying to hide it,
they know how you really feel.
You have your own?
No.
I get kicked out of my house
in the middle of the night,
and we're sent with you,
a complete stranger...
- You know what Eddie is, right?
- That he's a thief?
- That he steals for a living?
- Jean.
- Yes, I know what Eddie is.
- Then you know what's going on.
Look, I don't know who you are,
but I don't like the way
- you're talking...
- I'm how you and the baby stay safe.
Harry.
Sorry?
The baby.
You said "the baby."
I thought you might like
to know his name.
Is he okay?
I don't know.
You work with him?
I used to.
Jimmy said we'd figure out
where I'm going.
I have a sister
who I can call...
- No sisters, no people.
- How long are we gonna be away?
I don't know.
So, I'm supposed to live
you don't know where
for you don't know how long,
and also you don't know
if Eddie's okay.
Just let me call him.
Let him be the one
to explain it.
You can't.
You're talking about my husband.
No one knows where he is.
You can't call him, because
no one knows where he is.
Is anybody looking?
Everyone's looking.
And they're looking
for you, too.
A nice house.
Near a park.
I like to take walks
with a stroller.
Why isn't it lit?
I've been told
it isn't good for me.
So, what's the point?
It helps.
Oh, thank God.
He seemed like...
He's fine now.
Good thing he's drinking.
If it's easier to feed him,
you know, without...
I can step out.
What do you mean?
Uh...
Oh.
It's fine.
He's fine. See?
- Cal?
- What? What is it?
It's Harry.
Something's wrong.
He's burning up. Feel.
I think we need to go
to a hospital.
No.
No people.
People ask questions.
Hospitals need information.
What part of "everyone's looking
for you" don't you understand?
We can't, Jean.
The, um, uh, star's partner
of the team that wins, uh,
two out of three rounds
gets to stay on.
If you understand that,
you're better than I.
Now, they, uh,
what-what they really mean
is that you
and the star's partner,
and you, Patty,
you get to stay on
if you win the next round.
He stays, and you stay, too.
You like that arrangement,
I can tell.
Uh, see, but if you don't win,
you go, she stays.
Jean.
- Shh.
- Sir?
Ma'am?
Sir?
Excuse me. Sorry.
Don't look back.
Ma'am, are you all right?
What?
Feel.
It broke.
Excuse me?
The baby... he had a fever,
but he's feeling much cool...
- Get out of the car.
- What's the problem?
Get out of the car.
But, sir, the baby's sleeping.
Wait. Cal.
Cal.
I don't understand
what's happening.
Just do what he says.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yes.
This man isn't bothering you?
Ma'am, why are you
with this man?
He's my husband.
Is there a problem?
Why were you sleeping
in your car?
We're sorry, Officer.
We had just...
I'm asking her.
We're moving to a new house,
and we were so excited,
we wanted to drive all night
and sleep there.
But then, around...
I don't know, around...
What time was it again, dear?
Uh, a-around 1:00 or 2:00?
That's right.
Around 1:00 or 2:00,
he started to get tired,
and I was so worried with the
baby and everything, his fever,
so I made him pull over
right away.
I didn't even want him
driving to a motel.
It's my fault, Officer.
Do you have kids?
Well, then you know
how mothers can be.
It won't happen again,
I promise.
Make sure it doesn't.
I didn't know
that I could lie like that.
What?
I made a white baby.
Kitchen's stocked.
There's, uh, milk.
Eggs.
Bread.
Some bananas.
Crackers.
And pasta.
And a dining room.
And television.
Your room and the baby's room
are all set upstairs.
The formula you asked for,
diapers,
and some medicine
if he gets sick again.
There's a telephone
in the drawer
of your nightstand upstairs.
In an emergency,
you take it out, plug it in,
And call this number.
Okay?
And you're not to talk
to anyone.
No friends, no acquaintances.
And make sure
and keep the door locked.
Why are you telling me
everything like...
I'll be back when I can.
When you can?
When do we get to go home?
I need you to be patient,
all right?
- But Jimmy said you were gonna help us get set up.
- Jean.
And I've never been on my own.
I-I just need a minute to...
This is the way
things have to be.
But Eddie would want you
to stay with us.
I'm doing the best I can!
Let's both just do
the best we can.
Who did all this?
Eddie still has friends,
I guess.
What do you mean "still"?
Cal.
What about the park?
There is no park.
Hello?
It's your neighbor.
Hi.
- Is everything all right?
- Yes.
Of course.
Oh, no, I...
I didn't mean to frighten you.
M-My friends lived
in this house for years.
It's nice to see
someone new here.
I'm Evelyn.
Mary.
Nice to meet you, Mary.
Um, I live, uh, two doors down.
My husband passed
a few years ago.
Uh, but if you ever need
any help or anything...
Oh.
Thank you.
All right.
Goodbye.
Oh, what's your baby's name?
- Harry.
Oh.
Harry and Mary.
Candygram.
But when my daughter moved away,
it was hard again.
Hmm.
When the television's on,
I forget I'm alone.
This was delicious.
Oh, it's easy.
I'll give you the recipe.
I'm a terrible cook.
Do you mind me asking...
Is Harry sleeping
through the night?
I'm sorry.
D-Do you hear him crying?
I'm-I'm trying to keep him...
Oh, no, no, dear.
It's just...
You seem exhausted.
I'm so tired.
I'm so tired all the time.
I swear I hear him crying
when he's asleep.
What happened to your husband?
Uh...
I'm prying.
I just...
Where's your bathroom?
Upstairs at the end of the hall.
Didn't you say your friends
used to live here?
Pardon?
You said
your friends lived here.
- The bathroom.
- Gosh, no.
You're right.
I guess I'm getting old
faster than I thought.
Evelyn?
Evel...
Are you all right?
Good night.
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
Hello.
Hello?
Shit.
Evelyn?
- Evelyn, I know that this is...
- Jean.
Sit down.
Ah, tut-tut-tut-tut.
Where's Eddie?
We know you know.
I don't know anything.
Shut the kid up.
- What the fuck is wrong with it?
- I have to stand up.
- No, you stay the fuck down.
- I-I have to rock him.
- Please just let me stand up.
- No, absol...
It's okay.
Cover his ears.
Wait.
- You can't just kill someone.
- Someone who what, Jean?
I didn't, I didn't want
to do that.
- We could've explained...
- I didn't want to do any of that.
- We could have told her...
- She saw me kill those men!
- She was innocent.
- How do you know?
She was an innocent...
How do I know what?
God, she might have
worked for them.
- She might have tipped them off.
- It's not possible.
Are you really gonna tell me the
thought didn't cross your mind?
- But what if she was innocent?
- She-she was dead.
She was dead the moment
you invited her in.
I told you, no people.
- Try the finger.
- It won't work.
- It always works.
- Not if he's hungry.
- He's hungry?
- Yeah.
- Then fucking feed him!
- I can't!
What? Are-are you serious, Jean?
- It's nothing I haven't seen before.
- I can't.
I can't have children.
Eddie said he didn't care.
That wasn't why he wanted me.
He said he loved me
and we would figure it out.
But we couldn't adopt
'cause of his record.
Obviously.
And then, one day,
he walks in with a baby.
I said, "Who is that?"
Eddie smiles and says,
"He's our baby."
This girl was in trouble.
Eddie paid for everything.
Best doctors, all of it.
Her father was gonna disown her,
but Eddie put it right.
Eddie said everybody's life
got saved that day.
I think about his mother.
I think about her all the time.
Do you have anyone?
What?
You wouldn't tell me anyway.
Once I found out
I couldn't have a kid,
I stopped wanting it.
Thought maybe
it would be better.
I shouldn't bring a baby
into a life like this.
Eddie's a criminal.
I told myself
that's why I kept losing them.
That's why they wouldn't
stay with me.
But I really did want it.
More than anything.
I just had to keep living,
you know?
So I burned it all up.
I burned it up till there was
nothing left but the fire.
And then in walked Eddie
with a baby.
This is no place for a child.
D-Does he laugh?
What?
Do you make him laugh?
What the hell
are you talking about?
If you've heard him laugh.
You know.
Course I've heard him laugh.
Well, then you know.
He laughs.
Especially when I...
What?
When what?
I do this thing
when I'm singing.
I don't know... he likes it.
It happened and it worked,
so I kept doing it.
It's not even
a song about babies.
And now that
I'm talking about it,
I'm realizing
it's actually pretty weird.
Do it.
He's asleep.
I'll get the idea.
Absolutely not.
Fine.
If you're too chicken.
♪ Looking out ♪
♪ On the morning rain ♪
♪ A-whoo ♪
♪ I used to feel so uninspired ♪
♪ And when I knew ♪
♪ I had to face another day ♪
♪ A-whoo ♪
♪ Lord, it made me feel
so tired ♪
♪ Before the day I met you ♪
♪ Life was so unkind ♪
♪ You're the key
to my peace of mind ♪
♪ 'Cause you make me feel ♪
♪ You make me feel ♪
♪ You make me feel like ♪
♪ A natural woman ♪
♪ Woman. ♪
Okay?
There's a first time
for everything.
There's, uh, some more cans in
the pantry once this runs out.
Some old clothes
in the wardrobe.
There's a water pump out there,
enough wood out on
the side of the house for now.
There's no phone.
There's never been any trouble,
but just in case...
Move that chair.
Move that one back.
Grab the table,
move it that way.
It was my hiding place.
When I was a kid.
This was your family's.
I'll be back soon.
- You're not gonna leave me.
- Do you have a better idea?
What about the money
at the house?
That money's gone, Jean.
Don't you have money?
Like Eddie?
I worked for Eddie.
I'm not Eddie.
So, what am I, a chore?
Shh.
This isn't about you, Jean.
Eddie killed the boss.
Marvin.
The night we left.
Then Marvin's guys went over
to your place, killed Jimmy.
Now no one knows what's what.
It's just...
The city's chaos.
That's all I know.
Eddie would never kill anyone.
Eddie's a killer, Jean.
He has been for a long time.
Where is he now?
I don't know.
You swear?
I-I really don't know.
You do have someone.
The someone who told you
those weren't good for you.
And they told you that
because they love you.
He didn't have a name.
Harry.
I named him Harry.
No reason.
I-I just liked the name.
When I was pregnant the longest,
I named the baby Harry.
I never told anyone.
How long do you think
it's gonna be until...
Fire.
Hot.
Yeah.
Fire.
F... F...
Hot.
I did that.
I did it.
♪ A-whoo ♪
Mom!
She found my hiding place.
She sure did.
I'm Teri.
This is Paul.
And that's Art.
I'm sorry. Who...
Teri.
Cal's wife.
Why don't you get out of
that hole, help us unpack.
Hey. Come on, give me a hand.
And that's...?
Cal's dad.
You're Eddie's wife.
You know Eddie?
Yeah, I know Eddie.
Paul?
You run and go check
the wood, baby?
And...
Eddie used to work with Cal?
He wouldn't tell me much.
Cal's a smart man.
- Is Cal...
- He'll be here.
- Is he...
- Don't worry about Cal.
Almost out!
I just want
to get back to sleep.
Now I know where Cal gets it.
He's good with the baby?
Teri said her first husband
was no good.
Oh, I was gonna feed him.
No.
We don't eat
in the middle of the night.
It's best he learns that.
Everything all right?
Everything's fine.
Go back to sleep.
When Paul was little,
we had to live in this old hotel
in the city for a while.
The Saint Francis.
I remember that.
Why?
It was safe for us.
It's Black-owned,
Black-operated.
Place where people could go
to fix their lives.
I mean, it was
kind of a in-between place.
Not quite there yet,
but better than
where they'd been.
"Where there is despair,
I may bring hope."
You know
the Prayer of Saint Francis.
The one good thing I kept
from Catholic school.
Everything smelled old.
Sometimes the toilets
wouldn't flush.
But Paul loved it.
There was a phone in the hall.
He'd run to it
every time it rang.
A little answering service,
up on his tippy-toes.
You were hiding.
Paul, eat your peas.
What did you do to the peas?
Something wrong?
They're the ones from the can?
Yeah.
They're delicious.
Oh.
Salt, pepper, some butter.
Some love.
You just heat them up
out of the can?
I'm a terrible cook.
You feed your family, yeah?
Yeah, but...
Then you're
the world's greatest chef.
I got the place
when Cal was five.
Are you married?
I was.
My wife passed
about four years ago.
Cal wouldn't
talk about anything.
His family or anything.
Occupational hazard.
I'm about to take out a gun.
It's empty.
You ever use one?
All these men
and all their guns.
My husband wouldn't even
let me drive the car.
Listen, anyone can
learn to shoot.
But the hard part is what you
actually do when the time comes.
Now, when you practice,
you pull the trigger...
...and you think about pressure
and alignment.
But what you really need
to figure out is
what you'll do when it's real.
Here.
Get used to the weight.
Why did Art show me
how to use a gun?
Paul, can you go outside
and find Grandpa?
There were some guys
outside our apartment.
You live in the city?
Yeah.
First, I thought
Cal was just paranoid,
but after two more nights of it,
he packed up and sent us away.
Said he'd be right behind us.
I just thought you should be
prepared for what comes next.
What comes next?
I don't know yet.
But I've been
through this before.
Art said something
the other night.
What?
Eddie was your first husband.
Art told you that?
I put it together.
Eddie did the same thing to you?
Before Cal?
Except it's worse
'cause we have a kid.
Nothing's worse for you.
You don't know that.
Yeah, I do.
Eddie never told me
he had another wife.
He never told me
a lot of things.
That's what they do.
Teri.
Are you awake?
Something's not right.
We should go find Cal.
We need to find Cal and Eddie.
You need to stop
worrying about...
I am so sick of everyone
telling me what to do.
What?
I was gonna leave.
I was gonna leave when
I was sure you were all asleep.
Of course I know
Cal's in trouble.
Sorry.
Art was gonna tell you
in the morning.
I'm going with you.
And you can't stop me.
No one can give me
a straight answer
about what I'm supposed to do
or where I'm supposed to be,
and it's because
there is no answer.
No one knows anything.
So I'm doing this.
I'm coming.
Are you done?
- Yes.
- All right.
All right, I'm coming?
You already told me you were.
Okay.
Those two dark windows...
That's our apartment.
We usually leave a light on.
Put this in your pocket.
So you always know it's there.
We have to go somewhere.
And when we're there, I need you
to listen to me, okay?
You can't tell anyone
who you are.
It's not a safe place for us.
And we're gonna need
some different clothes.
Hello there, gorgeous.
Want?
No.
Thank you.
See that guy
over there? That's Mike.
Stay here, okay?
And keep to yourself.
If it isn't Old Firecracker.
Don't call me old, asshole.
Come here.
How are you?
Never thought I'd see her again.
How do you know her?
She used to be married
to a guy I know.
Eddie?
You know Eddie?
She just told me about him.
Man, that was some shit.
What?
Oh, you don't know?
Watch yourself with her.
She took everything from him.
And I mean everything.
But he started a whole new life
and a new family.
Kept it far away
from this shithole.
It's like I said, just never
thought I'd see her again.
Something's going down.
We need to leave.
Paul is Eddie's son.
Not now, Jean.
Why didn't you tell me?
Eddie would keep me in the dark.
Told me it was to protect me,
just like you, just like Cal,
but I don't believe it anymore.
Is any of this real, or are you
just like the rest of them?
Shit, it's locked.
Mike!
Come on. Come on.
What are you doing?
Stay here.
You all right?
It's okay.
You're okay.
Thank you.
Room 12.
I came back for you.
But you were gone.
Hi.
Eddie and I had Paul
the year we got married.
Soon after that, I found out
what he really did.
I wanted to leave,
but Eddie promised me that
his next job would be his last.
It wasn't. And it never was.
Cal was Eddie's guy.
But he didn't want it,
not the way Eddie did.
I think it even
scared him a little.
But he was always there.
Always... even.
We started
confiding in each other,
and eventually we fell in love.
It was Eddie
you were hiding from.
When you were here.
We came without a plan.
We got restless, and we left.
That's when Eddie found us.
He loved us too much to hurt us,
but he wasn't gonna let us go
without getting
something in return.
So we made a deal.
We would get to be together.
We could get out.
But one day Eddie would call,
and Cal wouldn't be able
to say no.
That was me.
That was you.
I work at the university,
and Cal's at a moving company.
Paul thinks he's his dad.
And a really good one.
As time went on, we thought
it might really be over.
That we might really have...
gotten out.
We put the past in a box,
and we put that box
in a secret drawer.
And we thought
that maybe it would just...
...disappear.
I'm so sorry.
That guy Mike at the club...
He's a real piece of shit,
always has been.
And I knew it would be
dangerous there.
Things have been like that
since Eddie killed Marvin.
But going there was
the best option we had.
What do you mean?
If I'm right, word will
get to Cal that I'm in the city,
and once Cal knows that,
he'll find us.
Mike works with Eddie?
They did some jobs together.
Then Eddie shot his ear off.
Mike called you "Firecracker."
Was that...?
Don't tell me...
So, what do we do now?
We wait.
Hello?
Thank you.
Teri, there's some men
out front.
We can go out the back.
Thank you.
I'll meet you there.
Jean, no matter what you hear,
keep walking.
Hey, Teri.
Came to talk to you, huh?
Teri, where you going?
Where's Teri?
She said she'll meet us here.
Paul and Harry?
With your dad at the cabin.
So, can I get you anything?
Coffee.
Two.
Are you okay?
Eddie's dead.
Here you go.
At least it stopped
raining, right?
Anything else?
No, thank you.
I'll get a job.
What?
An apartment, maybe.
Some place far away.
Harry can grow up there.
He won't remember any of this.
I know everything, Cal.
Do you need help?
I'm all right.
Where is she?
She'll be here.
Did Eddie do that?
He was dead before I got there.
Take the Wilson Street Bridge.
But it'll take longer.
Just stay off Central.
Why? We ditched the truck.
- Teri.
- We have to get back to the kids.
You're the one who said
Mike's guys were
outside the hotel.
I-I don't trust them.
Can't believe
that asshole's still alive.
But Eddie's dead.
I don't think he knows.
Someone's following us.
Whoa.
He's gone. He's gone.
Cal.
Teri.
No, no. No, no, no, no.
Teri! Cal!
No. No.
Teri!
Cal!
Is this her?
Shut the fuck up.
What's happening?
Shut the fuck up!
- This is Jean?
- Yes!
Eddie's wife?
Jesus Christ!
Did I not tell this asshole
to shut the fuck up?
It's nice to finally
meet you, Jean.
I'm sorry I didn't know
that was you in my club.
Where's Eddie?
Eddie's dead.
Jean, Jean, Jean.
Don't do that.
Don't lie to me.
Don't you know
this is the moment
this can all be over?
All's you have to...
Teri?
Teri.
Okay. Okay.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Okay.
Go.
I killed Mike.
Jean.
I don't think I can move.
Art.
It's all right now.
Your mom and dad are outside.
It's okay, baby.
Your mama's here.
Okay. Okay.
We're gonna play a game. Okay?
You have to close your eyes,
and you can't open them
till I say so.
Okay?
And when I tell you to
open them, you can't look back.
Got it?
All right, Paul.
Close your eyes.
There's a big one coming up.
Step. Step again.
Okay, Paul.
Keep them closed.
Okay, Paul, open your eyes.
Okay.
You're not
supposed to look back.