# Do-wat a-do-wat
a- do-wat a-do-wat do-wat #
# Shoobee doobee-wah
do-wat be-bobbee bobbee #
# Cry baby, cry baby,
cry baby #
# My cry baby, uh-oh #
# Is such a cry baby #
# Uh-oh #
# Cryin' all the time #
# Cry baby #
# My cry baby, uh-oh #
# Is such a cry baby #
# Uh-oh #
# Cryin' all the time #
# All the time #
# Oh, when the raindrops
start to fall #
# Tears fall from my eyes #
# Then my heart
starts to call #
# Don't you realize? #
# Oh, realize #
# My cry baby, uh-oh #
# Is such a cry baby #
# Uh-oh #
# Cryin' all the time #
# Oh, when a bad boy
looks at me #
# Everybody knows #
# Ooh, ouch,
my blood turns hot #
# Right down to my toes #
# A- to my toes #
# Do-wat a-do-wat
a- do-wat a-do-wat do-wat #
# Shoobee doobee-wah
do-wat be-bobbee bobbee #
# Cry baby, cry baby,
cry baby #
# My cry baby, uh-oh #
# Is such a cry baby #
# Uh-oh #
# Cryin' all the time #
# All the time #
# Oh, when they tell me
he's no good #
# Oh, what do they know? #
# What's bad to them
is good to me #
# He sure makes me glow #
# He makes me glow #
# My cry baby, uh-oh #
# Is such a cry baby #
# Uh-oh #
# Cryin' all the time #
# When the raindrops
start to fall #
# Tears fall from my eyes #
# Then my heart
starts to call #
# Don't you realize? #
# Oh, realize #
# My cry baby, uh-oh #
# Is such a cry baby #
# Uh-oh #
# Cryin' all the time #
# Time #
# You big old cry baby ##
[alarm ringing]
Hi, kids.
Remember, always look
both ways before crossing.
Mother!
We're having your favorite
supper tonight, Wanda.
Potatoes au gratin.
(all)
Mmm.
Now walk.
Look left, look right.
That's right, then walk.
Good teenagers.
Are you gonna work
this summer?
##[Music playing
on car stereo]
(Hector)
Wanda, honey.
You want a ride
home with Dad?
I got a lift. Thanks, anyway.
We could count
out-of-state license plates.
I saw one this morning
all the way up from Virginia.
Dad, would you
just leave me alone?
Bye, honey.
(woman)
# O look, daddy,
you're so cool #
# But I can't break
my momma's rules #
# She would have to see
what's in your family tree #
# Before she would let you
come home just for me #
(man)
# Oh, you thinking
about marriage #
# Now and then #
# Oh, you goin'
pretty steady #
# Now and then #
# Gee you look so pleasant #
# Well, I think I'm ready #
# This is what you need #
# Do you have plenty money? #
# Yes, I do #
# Tell me,
is it all in cash? #
# Just for you #
# Will you give me
all your lovin'? #
# If you're true #
# Then I will love you
long as well #
little Square.
# Yes, we and you #
Want to hang out
with us Drapes tonight?
[Groaning]
Allison Vernon-Williams,
get in this car.
What's the trouble,
honey?
These hoodlums
bothering you?
(Allison)
No, no,
we were just talking.
Grandmother, Baldwin,
this is Wade Walker.
They call me Cry-Baby.
This here is
my sister, Pepper.
Greetings, Granny-o.
Allison's my girl,
so hands off, Cry-Baby.
You could have
fooled me, Square.
Mrs. Vernon-Williams, I hear
you're having a talent show
at your charm school today.
I can barely imagine
what you would call music.
I can sing pretty good.
"Well," not "good."
Haven't you ever heard
of the English language?
Don't go flip out,
mama.
Yeah.
Sometimes shook-up old ladies
get cut.
(Baldwin)
Come on, honey.
They're just bums.
Mr. Puniverse
wants a fat lip.
I'd like to hear you sing.
(Grandmother)
I will say this once
and once only.
Stay away from
my granddaughter,
you common
juvenile delinquents.
It was nice
talking to you all.
# Just you and me #
# Go see our father #
# Tell our sisters
and our brothers #
# Just you and me #
Let's go.
[All cheering]
# That you're going to
marry me ##
The prettiest and most
talented girl in school
and yet she socializes
with Drapes.
We're Squares, Allison,
and Squares
got to stick together.
Yeah, but Drapes
are people, too.
They just look different.
Maybe Cry-Baby can sing.
Something cool,
something hep.
And where did you learn
those vulgar jazz words?
Your poor dead parents would
turn over in their graves.
It's those jukebox records
she listens to.
Honey, his kind of music
isn't even on the Hit Parade.
How can I think when
you're always touching me?
I have told you, Baldwin,
a young lady does not
like to be pawed.
[Laughing]
##[Women and Cadillacs
by The Nite Riders
playing on car stereo]
# The woman want a Cadillac
she don't want no man #
# I used to have a woman,
said she loved me so #
I think Cry-Baby's
got a girlfriend.
Cry-Baby and
Allison sitting in a tree
K-l-S-S-l-N-G.
Shut up, Milton.
[All laugh]
Hey, Hatchet-Face,
you think Cry-Baby's
got blue balls for the chick?
Allison's a Square, Wanda.
Cry-Baby don't dig Squares.
No, she's a "Scrape."
Part Square, part Drape.
I think she's pretty.
Cry-Baby,
want some hooch?
I don't drink
and drive.
[Tires screeching]
# Mess around with me #
# Turn back, baby #
You're too young to
know the shameful truth
about the Walker
boy's family.
But let me warn you,
evil is in his blood.
[Car horn honking]
##[Gee by The Crows playing]
# Love that girl #
# Oh, please #
# Listen to me #
Move up, now.
That's not funny.
# Why I love that girl #
# Love that girl #
# Hold me, baby, squeeze me #
# Never let me go #
# I'm not takin' chances #
You're a dead man, Walker.
# Oh, Gee, #
# Yes, I love her ##
[car horn honking]
(Baldwin)
Car! Car!
[Screaming]
[Tires screeching]
[Car horns blaring]
[All whooping]
##[music playing]
[People chattering]
[Girls chattering]
[Microphone squeaks]
Good afternoon,
ladies and gentlemen
and welcome to the annual
RSVP Talent Show.
(audience)
Good afternoon,
Mrs. Vernon-Williams.
First, I must apologize
for my frazzled nerves.
However, this afternoon
we were attacked
by a gang of
juvenile delinquents.
[Audience gasps]
It's all right.
No one was injured.
Juvenile delinquents
are everywhere.
Right here in this community.
Boys with long hair
and tattoos
who spit on the sidewalk.
Can't believe it.
(woman)
How disgusting.
Girls who wear tight slacks.
Hysterectomy pants,
I call them.
[All murmuring]
And if one of these creatures
ever approach you
on the street,
you are to silently
repeat to yourself
the four "B's"
you learned here at RSVP.
And what are they,
children, the four "B's"?
(all)
Beauty, brains,
breeding, bounty!
[Audience applauding]
Yes! Yes!
Teenagers everywhere,
repent!
Let Jesus Christ
be your gang leader!
Get out of Turkey Point
before it's too late.
Thank you very much for the picture, sweet heart
Oh yeah!
All right, who's up next here ?
Toe-Joe Jackson's
art photography right here!
Be a nudie-cutie,
make good money to bootie.
Hey, I'm paying $3 a shot.
what the hell, You got it
why not show it, right?
Hey, you.
Yeah, you, the looker
with the class-A
sealed-beam headlights.
You want to pose
for Toe-Joe?
Beat it, creep.
Here he comes now,
with that devil woman.
Hi, Mrs. Hackett.
Imagine our shame.
Our only child, and he carries
illegal weapons,
drives fast cars,
and wears clothes
obviously designed
by homosexuals.
But he knows better.
Jesus is still in his heart.
Jeez, Mom and Dad,
go home.
You're embarrassing me.
I'm a teenager.
I want to live.
##[Music playing]
Hey!
Looks like somebody
lost their laundry.
Hello, Cry-Baby.
You scorch me, man.
Later, Lenora.
But, Cry-Baby, I need a date
for tonight's
Jukebox Jamboree.
Well, I'm solo, sugar.
You wanna see these gunboats?
I give, Cry-Baby.
I give bare second
on the first date.
Use your mentality
and cool down.
Well, Lenora,
your bosoms ain't nothing.
Better watch it, bozo.
You might catch a cold.
My brother wouldn't
touch your titties
with a 10-foot pole.
He likes his women bad,
Lenora, not cheap.
##[Scatting]
# Oh, life could be a dream #
# If I could take you
up in paradise up above #
# If you would tell me
I'm the only one
that you love #
[girls chattering]
# Life could be a dream,
sweetheart #
# Hello hello again, sh-boom,
and hopin' we'll meet again #
# Oh, life could be a dream #
# If only all
my precious plans #
# Would come true #
# If you would let me spend
my whole life lovin' you #
# Life could be a dream #
# Sweetheart #
# Sh-boom sh-boom #
# Ya-da-da Da-da-da
Da-da-da Da #
# Sh-boom sh-boom #
# Ya-da-da Da-da-da
Da-da-da Da #
# Sh-boom sh-boom #
# Ya-da-da Da-da-da
Da-da-da Da, sh-boom #
[girls squealing]
# Now every time,
I look at you #
# Something is on my mind #
# If you do what
I want you to do #
# Baby, we'd be so fine #
# Oh, life could be a dream #
# If I could take you up
in paradise up above #
# If you would tell me
I'm the only one
that you love #
# Life could be a dream,
sweetheart #
# Hello hello again, sh-boom
and hopin' we'll meet again #
# Sh-boom sh-boom #
# Life could be a dream,
sweetheart ##
[audience applauding]
Uncle Belvedere!
Wow!
You caught me in
my birthday suit,
butt-naked.
Grandma, we're home!
How much?
(Ramona)
That muffler?
Dupree, for you
$15, take it or leave it.
Come on, Ramona.
$10. This thing's
hotter than a pistol.
You guys wanna do business
with Ramona Rickettes
or would you rather
shop at Sears?
Now, give me the bread
and keep your trap shut.
You're a hard woman.
I'm going to see
you in hell, Dupree.
[Laughing]
Go on, get out of here.
[Kids chattering]
Have you been bothering
your great-grandma all day?
She has customers.
Hell, no. They helped me
steal a car.
It's a '51 Olds.
It's really cool.
That's my little Snare-Drum.
And, Ma, I swiped
six hubcaps like a big girl.
Way to go, Susie-Q.
Make those monster faces,
Hatchet. Please.
[Howling]
[Children screaming]
Goddamn gopher's digging up
my front yard.
What are you
teenagers waiting for?
Turkey Point is
open for business!
Let's celebrate!
[All cheering]
Come on.
Come on, everybody.
Come on in.
Today's a special day for me
and your grandmother.
We've been together
10 whole years.
[All whooping]
I'm just so proud of
all my Drape children.
Oh, Wanda, you sure is pretty
in them tight clothes
all painted up like trash.
I wish you
and Belvedere were my parents.
Oh.
Now, Milton,
boy, you are
everything a man should be.
You're young,
stupid, and mean.
We're gonna play
some cool music
for you tonight, Ramona.
And, Hatchet-Face.
Oh, honey.
You're just like me.
Now, you put
the "T" in "tough."
So hard, you could've been
eating nails for breakfast.
But that's the way a woman's
got to be these days.
I'd kick a Square's ass
for you in a minute,
Mrs. Rickettes.
Oh, this is the best gang
my grandson could ever have.
Grandma,
I'm so happy all knocked up
I wish I was having triplets.
Well, we got a little surprise
for your young one
in your oven.
You show her, Bel.
Sure will.
(Cry-Baby)
Oh, Pep, ain't that cute?
It's beautiful, Grandma.
Cry-Baby.
When you was a boy,
you had to be
the man of this family.
But I taught you
how to dress, didn't I?
You sure did,
Uncle Belvedere.
Yeah, well,
you're the future now, boy.
You're the only future
for this godforsaken family.
And I want you to
go out there tonight
and sing, boy.
I want you to
sing your heart out.
You can show him now,
Belvedere.
This took a lot of hubcaps,
Cry-Baby.
[Gasping]
[All cheering]
Grandmother,
Uncle Belvedere,
you've made me
the happiest juvenile
delinquent in Baltimore.
And guess what?
[Motorcycle engine rumbling]
I met a girl!
# My friends all know it #
# How I adore him #
# I've whispered to angels #
# What I'd do for him #
# He is the answer #
# To a teenage prayer #
# He won't go steady #
# The crowd has told me #
# But I keep waiting #
# To have him hold me #
# Why won't you listen #
# To a teenage prayer #
# I wait by the window
at seven #
# and chill when my thrill
passes by #
# His kiss could
send me to heaven #
# Into his arms I would fly #
# My heart goes #
# Piddily patter, patter
piddily patter, patter #
Stay in your places.
[People chattering]
Get back to your room.
(boy #1)
Is he here? Is he here?
(boy #2)
I can't see anything.
That's him.
Cry-Baby Walker.
[Sighing]
I'm sorry about
this afternoon,
Mrs. Vernon-Williams.
Is Allison home?
'Cause, uh,
I'm gonna sing tonight
and I thought
she might like to hear me.
[Groans]
Mind your manners.
This is what we think
of your kind of music.
[Grunting]
How dare you hit him!
You don't own me, Baldwin.
I have the right
to hear Cry-Baby sing.
Don't get all
worked up, honey.
The punk got
what he deserved.
[All gasping]
Come on.
Allison.
Get up. Go! Go! Go!
Hop on, honey.
Just one minute,
young lady...
I'll take good care of her,
Mrs. Vernon-Williams.
I promise.
And it's okay about my face.
It don't hurt much.
Please.
It's not a school night,
and I have been a good girl.
Just one night of happiness,
that's all I ask.
But what if you
get your dress dirty?
[Sighs]
Thank you, Grandmother.
##[Pistol Packin' Mama
by Al Dexter playing]
# I have a girlfriend #
# She says I'm her only one #
# We want to get married #
# But we're so young #
# So young #
# Can't marry no one #
# But we know our #
# heart's direction #
# So young #
# Can't marry no one ##
You okay?
I didn't get no axle grease
on you, did I?
No. No. I'm fine.
Been to Turkey Point before?
My Grandmother
wouldn't let me.
She calls it
the Redneck Riviera.
It's where I live.
Beautiful, ain't it?
It's really wild.
But I'm... I'm afraid that
I'm not going to fit in here.
You know,
with your friends and stuff.
You're cool, Allison.
You just look Square.
Underneath it all,
I think you're really hep.
Well, what have we here?
First Square to ever
set foot in Turkey Point.
Hey, fine mama.
Welcome to
the Jukebox Jamboree.
These are the Cry-Baby girls.
That's Wanda.
Dig it, babe.
You need a new look.
(Hatchet-face)
Don't you got tits?
Stick them out,
for God's sake.
That's Hatchet-Face.
She don't mean no harm.
First thing
a Cry-Baby girl learns,
our bazooms are our weapons.
Now, Pepper's pregnant.
But she can fight like a man.
I wouldn't be
caught dead
in a full skirt.
Hey, girls.
What do you think?
Let's give Allison here
a bad-girl beauty makeover.
Are you game?
Sure.
Think I got
what it takes?
[All whooping]
You got it, Allison.
You got it raw.
Hey, hey, hey!
Dig it, all you
hep cats and cool chicks.
You know me.
Ramona Rickettes!
[Audience applauding]
Now let me introduce to you
the Cry-Baby combo,
Milton, Pepper,
Wanda, Hatchet-Face.
[Audience cheering]
(both)
Hi, Mom.
##[Band playing]
And now,
the baddest baby of them all,
the man you came here for,
the big boo-hoo,
the terrible teardrop,
ladies and gentlemen,
my grandson, Cry-Baby!
[Audience cheering]
# Well, one for all
and all for one #
# And all we want
is to have some fun #
# But Squares,
beware of our property #
# Yeah, if you're lookin' to
rumble, you're looking at me #
# 'Cause I'm the king #
# King cry-baby #
# Yeah, I'm the king #
# A king cry-baby
with a tear in my eye #
[audience cheering]
# Baby cry, baby cry #
# Oh baby cry, oh baby cry,
oh baby cry, wow #
# Well, I was born on
the wrong side of the tracks #
# In the backseat of
a stolen Cadillac #
# I had my first cigarette
before I could walk #
# And I was strummin' this
guitar before I could talk #
# 'Cause I'm the king #
# King cry-baby #
# Yeah, I'm the king #
# Oh, I'm the king #
# King cry-baby #
# A king cry-baby
with a tear in my eye #
[all cheering]
# If you mess with the king,
you're gonna cry,
oh baby cry #
# Oh baby cry, oh baby cry,
# Well, I'm a lonely king
who needs a queen #
# Yeah, you're the sweetest
lump of sugar
that I've ever seen #
# Ain't got a ring
or crown for you #
# Well, if I had your love #
# I'd lose
these cry-baby blues #
# She's the queen #
Go on up there, honey.
Go on.
# She's the queen #
# Well, let people talk,
I don't care #
# Let me prove to you daddy
that I ain't no Square #
# You'll be my queen
and I'll be your king #
# But if you leave my hive,
you're gonna feel my sting #
# 'Cause you're my queen #
# Queen cry-baby #
# You're the king #
# King cry-baby #
# I'll be the queen #
# Cry-cry baby #
# A king cry-baby
with a queen by my side #
# And if you mess with us,
man you're gonna cry,
oh baby cry #
# Baby cry, baby cry,
# Cry, baby cry, baby cry,
baby cry #
[audience applauding]
[Audience cheering]
##[Cherry
by The Jive Bombers playing]
# Cherry #
Kiss me. Kiss me hard.
[Thunder clapping]
I've never given
a French kiss before.
Watch. It's easy.
You just open your mouth,
and I open mine,
and we wiggle
our tongues together.
And it feels real sexy.
I won't get mononucleosis,
will I?
No, Allison. Just try it.
If you don't like it,
I promise I'll stop.
# I'll get you yet #
# Someday, Cherry #
# You'll be my pet #
# Right now #
# Cherry #
# The day is set ##
(boy)
Break the window.
[Laughing]
I'm sorry, Allison.
It's just that
you are so beautiful.
I want to let you,
but I can't.
For my parents' sake.
Cry-Baby, they're both dead.
I'm an orphan.
I'm sorry, Allison.
No wonder we're together,
honey.
I'm an orphan, too.
You are?
Yes.
And orphans
have special needs.
Just on the outside
of the shirt, okay?
Is it okay with you?
Yes. Oh, yes!
My parents were,
they good people
and they... they loved me.
I want you. I need you.
I love you, too, Allison.
They had to go on
a business trip together.
It was their
first airplane ride.
Oh, Cry-Baby,
your fingers feel so good.
I've been saving it up
for a girl like you, honey.
Mommy and Daddy
took separate planes
for safety.
In case one plane crashed,
I would still have
a living parent.
But, Cry-Baby,
both planes crashed
and I never saw
my parents alive again.
[Thunder cracking]
Goddamn! Lightning!
What's the matter,
Cry-Baby?
Everything is the matter.
It's just a thunderstorm.
Heat lightning.
It's sexy.
It's not sexy.
Electricity makes me insane.
Why, Cry-Baby? Why?
Here's why.
Electricity killed my parents.
They died in
the electric chair?
That's right, Allison.
My father was
the Alphabet Bomber.
He may have been crazy,
but he was my pop.
The only one I ever had.
God. I read about
the Alphabet Bomber.
Bombs exploding
in the... the airport,
the barbershop.
That's right,
all in alphabetical order.
Carwash, drugstore.
I used to lay in my cradle
and hear him scream
in his sleep.
# A, B, C, D,
E, F, G ##
[mimics explosions]
But your mom?
My mother
tried to stop him.
She couldn't even spell,
for Christ's sake,
but they fried her, too.
But I'll pay them
all back, Allison.
That's why, every day,
I gotta do
something rotten
for my parents' sake
and I cry for
what I have to do.
But not much, though.
One single, salty tear
is all that they will ever
suck out of this Cry-Baby.
[Thunder clapping]
[Yelling]
Cry-Baby.
[Grunting]
[People screaming]
[All yelling]
[Laughing]
[Police car siren wailing]
I'm going to have his baby.
(Baldwin)
Allison!
[Wind whooshing]
Oh, my God.
What have they done to you?
Allison, come home.
They beat me and kicked me.
All because I love you.
[Screaming]
[Thunder clapping]
[Engine revving]
Get on.
Don't do it, Allison.
No!
(all)
Too smart to work,
too cool to care.
Come to Turkey Point,
man, if you dare.
Too smart to work,
too cool to care.
Come to Turkey Point,
man, if you dare.
L-Let her go.
She's with me.
Her name is Allison
and she is a nice girl.
Allison, I'm sorry
to get you locked up.
But tonight, well,
you were the coolest date
I ever had.
But, Cry-Baby,
who is that girl?
Why didn't you tell me
you already had
a lady friend?
Lenora ain't nothing to me,
I swear on my daddy's grave.
I'm burning inside
to touch you, baby.
(reporter #1)
How do you feel about
your granddaughter
becoming a Drapette?
(reporter #2)
Mrs. Vernon-Williams,
a picture, please.
Please, no pictures.
[People chattering]
(judge)
Order.
Order in this courtroom.
What a sad vision
of today's youth.
The juvenile authorities have
had it with Drape gangs.
Milton Hackett.
Wanda Woodward.
Mona Malnorowski,
also known as Hatchet-Face.
You are blights
on this community.
Are the parents here?
Yes, Your Honor.
We have been praying
all night for our son.
And praying so hard
that we got headaches.
Hi, Wanda honey.
You were on the radio.
Would you just get me
the fuck out of here?
What does
"fuck" mean, Hector?
Oh, Maggie, it's just
a teen nonsense word
Wanda uses
to make herself
feel all grown-up.
Your Honor,
could we take Wanda
the fuck home?
[All laughing]
[Gavel pounding]
Good God!
Order.
Order in this courtroom.
You hear that, Your Honor?
It's a sign.
[Speaking indistinctly]
She is speaking
in tongues.
God is in her gullet.
And he is in yours, too.
Let him out.
Let the words of
the Savior be heard.
Order! Order!
No wonder
your children are in trouble.
And you, Miss Malnorowski...
By the way, that's a shame
about your face.
There's nothing
the matter with my face.
I got character.
I see that your parents
haven't taken the trouble
to come to get you.
(Mr. Malnorowski)
Oh, yes, we did.
You happy now, Mona?
You finally did it.
You put your own mother
in an iron lung.
Mrs. Malnorowski,
there is no smoking
in this courtroom.
Why not?
I pay taxes on cigarettes,
don't I?
And what do I get
for those taxes?
Happiness? Hell, no.
I get tuberculosis.
[Explodes]
Oh, Christ!
Now I got a flat tire.
I'm going to
release these delinquents
to their parents' custody.
And if they were mine,
I'd give them
a bare-assed whipping.
Ramona and
Belvedere Rickettes,
I find you guilty of
disturbing the peace
and I fine
the both of you $1,000.
That's all we have.
How are we supposed to live?
Damn you.
Handcuff those brats.
Don't touch my children.
(judge)
And you, Pepper Walker,
I'm going to have
your two children
put in the custody
of the Chatterbox Orphanage,
until they're adopted
by God-fearing parents
who at least will give
them Christian names.
(Pepper)
Not my children.
They're my flesh and blood.
They're all I have!
Mrs. Tadlock.
Get away from them.
[All clamoring]
Don't you touch them!
Come on.
(Pepper)
I love you, children.
(judge)
Wade Walker,
better known as "Cry-Baby"
what a sad and silly name
for a young man.
You were the ringleader
in tonight's gang war.
Grandmother, help him.
We were just
singing together.
[People murmuring]
Judge, let Allison go
and I'll take the full blame.
I didn't mean no harm,
Mrs. Vernon-Williams.
I may be a Drape,
but I love your granddaughter.
And if that's a crime,
I'll stand convicted, ma'am.
I am going to release
Allison this one time,
because you are a fine
and beautiful woman,
Mrs. Vernon-Williams.
[People murmuring]
But not you, Cry-Baby Walker.
The only place you're
going to sing is in jail.
No!
I find you guilty
of rampant
juvenile delinquency
and I hereby sentence you
to the Maryland
Training School for Boys
until your 21st birthday.
Ha!
[Banging gavel]
Court dismissed.
[People exclaiming]
Lock him up!
You can't lock up his music!
[Crowd clamoring]
I'll get out, sugar dumpling,
if it's the last thing I do!
I swear.
Cry-Baby!
##[In The Jailhouse
by Webb Pierce playing]
# He's in the jailhouse now
He's in the jailhouse now #
# He's in the jailhouse now ##
Boy, do I have a story
for you.
How does it feel to be
a juvenile delinquent?
It feels good. I've never
been so happy
in my whole life.
(man)
I hear you were...
Lenora, you filthy hag.
I wouldn't let you
shine my boots!
Allison's my girl.
A-L-L-I-S-O-N, fellows.
(male reporter)
When did he propose?
[Reporters clamoring]
Oh, just last night.
You see, I'm pregnant
with his child.
Well, you know
that Cry-Baby is an orphan.
He wants his baby
to have a real family
for the family
that he himself never had.
[Inmates clamoring]
(guard)
Break it up!
[All applauding]
Shut up!
Delinquents, hit the sack!
(man)
Oh, I swear.
Strip down, asshole.
It's beddy-bye time.
[Grunting]
Now, don't forget
to say your prayers.
God bless
my probation officer.
(all)
God bless
my probation officer.
God bless the draft board.
(all)
God bless
the juvenile authorities.
(all)
God bless
the juvenile authorities.
We're going to give you
a haircut tomorrow,
pretty boy.
You ever hear
of a Whiffle?
[Gagging]
Well, that's what
you're going to get,
you big old cry-baby, you.
[Laughing]
God bless
Dwight Eisenhower.
(all)
God bless Dwight Eisenhower.
God bless Roy Cohn.
(all)
God bless Richard Nixon.
[Sighing]
Nighty-night, boys.
[Inmates murmuring]
[Sniffing]
Cry-Baby.
# Teardrops are falling #
(all)
# Cry, go on, cry #
# Teardrops are falling #
# Out of my eyes #
# I wonder why #
# Teardrops are falling #
# For you make me cry #
# Yes, teardrops are falling #
# Falling from my eyes #
# Yes, yes, yes,
you made me cry #
# When you went away #
# You stayed away so long #
# Come back, my dear #
# My heart is aching #
# Almost breaking #
# If you hear me #
# Come back to me #
# Teardrops are falling #
# And you make #
# Me cry #
(all)
# Cry don't cry #
# Oooh ##
[gulping]
[Panting]
##[Band playing]
[People chattering]
Oh.
(male announcer)
Call these Drapettes bold,
call them brazen,
but don't call them Square.
Yes, mothers,
you should be worried.
Following
last night's disturbance
at Turkey Point
Cry-Baby Walker had the nerve
to announce his engagement
to fellow gang member and
known hussy, Lenora Frigid,
mother-to-be of his child.
Cry-Baby is an orphan.
He wants his baby
to have a real family
for the family
that he himself
never had.
Wade Walker, defiantly
entering the Maryland
Training School for Boys
had this to say:
It feels good, man.
I've never been so happy
in my whole life.
##[Band playing]
[People chattering]
Hurry, Allison, hide.
The newspapers have blown this
completely out of proportion.
He lied to me,
Grandmother.
And the whole world knows
that I'm just a Drape fool.
Oh, heavy hangs the head
that last night
wore the crown.
##[Band approaching]
Allison.
[People clamoring]
##[Scatting]
Allison Vernon-Williams, you
don't have to decide today.
Give your heart
some time to think.
Allison, would you
sing with me today?
##[Jailbird
by Sonny Knight playing]
# Jailbird, Jailbird
Go around stealing cars #
[clanging]
# Jailbird, Jailbird #
# You'll end up
behind iron bars #
# Jailbird, Jailbird #
# Your face was
on the early news #
# Jailbird, Jailbird ##
Hey, man, your old lady's
on the radio.
There's trouble, Cry-Baby,
big trouble.
Allison!
There's a new place
that's opening.
It's sort of wild,
kind of cool.
It's called a theme park
and it's the first one
in the state of Maryland.
I'd be proud to, Baldwin.
Cry-Baby Walker, I hope
you're happy with Lenora.
I only have one thing
to say to you.
I think you're a liar
and a cad,
and I spit on your tears.
I can sing better than
Cry-Baby Walker
any day of the week.
[Switching stations]
[Growling]
[Screaming]
# Well, I'm in here
'cause I drive too fast #
# And I'm too young
to have a criminal past #
# Some good behavior
would be all right #
# But I don't seem
to qualify #
# I'm just out
for a little fun #
# But I'm guilty till I'm 21 #
# I guess I'm doing time
for being young #
# So cut these
shackles off of me #
(all)
# Let me go, let me go #
# This kind of suit
don't set me free #
# Set me free, set me free #
# Well, I can't live
if I can't ride #
# Let me ride, let me ride #
# And I want my baby
by my side #
# I want my baby by my side #
# I'm just out
for a little fun #
# But I'm guilty till I'm 21 #
# I guess I'm doing time
for being young #
# Now, I can't
let the right thing #
# Stand in my way #
# Someday, baby,
I'll know better #
# But right now
I'm making my pay #
[all hollering]
# What do I do,
who do I thank? #
# What can I do?
What can I do? #
# To get me out of
this stinking tank #
# Stinking tank
Stinking tank #
# It's heartbreaking
to be this age #
# Stuck in a cage
Stuck in a cage #
# Locked in the prison
of teenage rage #
# Stuck in a cage
with a teenage rage #
[all clamoring]
# Well, I was out
for a little fun #
# I guess I'm guilty
till I'm 21 #
# I must be doing time
for being young #
# Stuck in a cage
with a teenage rage #
# I don't want
to be doing time
for being young ##
[clicking]
[People chattering]
##[I'm a Bad Bad Girl
by Little Esther playing]
# I'm a bad girl ##
Who the hell is this?
This is Inga.
She's from Sweden.
She's an exchange student.
And she's going to be
staying with us for a while.
Inga, this is our daughter,
Wanda. Say hello.
Ya?
[Scoffs]
I'm blowing this joint.
Well, Inga doesn't understand
English very well.
Inga, say hello to Wanda.
Ya?
Say hello to our daughter.
Uh, h-honey,
why don't you come over
and sit down?
Get to know one another.
Look at all
the wonderful presents
she's brought us
from her native land.
Let's all put on a folk hat
and learn something
about a foreign culture.
Do we have a surprise
for you. Don't we, Meg?
We sure do.
All this silly trouble
you've been having lately...
Wanda, honey,
you're going to Sweden,
this afternoon at 3:00.
You mean you swapped me?
For a milkmaid?
Oh, honey, Inga's mater
and pater will treat you
just like one of the family.
Ya, Inga?
Ya. Ya, Ya.
##[Nosey Joe
by Bullmoose Jackson playing]
# There's a man in town
all the women know #
# He goes by the name
of Nosey Joe #
# He don't care
if they're married #
# He takes his pick #
# Long as they're women,
he's ready to stick #
# His big nose
in their business #
Hey, you goin' my way?
Oh, it's you.
You ever hear of something
called a theme park?
Yeah, there's a big opening
over there today.
Well, that's where
I'm going, stallion.
Well, hop on in.
[Laughing]
# I'm tellin' you women,
this ain't no jive #
# If you get too close
this man will drive ##
[tires screeching]
[People shouting]
Hold on, homeboy.
Almost done.
I know it hurts,
but being this cool's
always a pain.
Ah, the pain ain't nothing,
Dupree.
I've been hurt all my life,
but real tears wash away.
Ow.
This one's for Allison
and I want it to last forever.
Oh.
There you go. It's a beauty.
[Door clanking]
You never have to
cry again.
[Squeaking]
I heard talkin' in here.
W-what's that on your face,
blubber-boy?
A booger?
Are you blind?
It's a lonely teardrop.
[Chuckling]
Oh, ain't that cute?
It ought to go real good
with your new haircut.
[Laughs]
I ain't gettin'
no haircut.
You wanna bet?
You're next, sniffle-snot.
[Laughing]
[Continues laughing]
[Door squeaking]
[Whispering]
Cry-Baby, look!
It's your only chance, man.
Nobody's going to
turn me Square, Dupree.
I want my girl,
I want my family,
and I want my gang.
Thanks for the tattoo.
Ah. Oh, man.
[Bell dings]
[Mooing]
Come on, gorgeous.
[Cloth ripping]
[Helicopter approaching]
##[Rubber Biscuit
by The Chips playing]
Look. Is that the prison?
# Chick'n hon-a-chick-a-chick
hole-a-hubba #
# He'll ride a chuck-a-lucka
wanna jubba #
Move over, Milton.
Let me try.
# Hi-low 'n-ay
wanna dubba hubba #
# Day down sum
wanna jigga-wah #
# They'll ride a
wanna lubba hubba #
(Hatchet-Face)
Geronimo!
[Laughs]
# We all ride a
wanna dib-a-doo #
[people shouting]
What do
we have here?
Who is that?
This is a jailbreak!
# She'll ride
wanna dib-a-doo #
# Downtown wanna dib-a-doo #
[people clamoring]
[Gunfire continues]
Milton! Hatchet!
(Hatchet-Face)
Cry-Baby, where are you?
Cry-Baby!
(man #1)
He's in the library!
(man #2)
No, no, he's in the cafeteria!
(man #3)
No, he's in the hole.
(man #4)
No, he's in the movies.
That way!
[All clamoring]
(Hatchet-Face)
Cry-Baby!
(woman)
Hurry, David.
(man)
I've almost got it.
[Screaming]
[All yelling]
[All clamoring]
# She'll ride a hole-a-hubba #
# He'll drive a wanna jubba #
Hurry up!
# I'll ride sum
wanna jigga-wah #
# Bring me down a
one lubba hubba #
# We'll ride a hubbin
in the lubba hubba #
# Hmm, what you want
for nothin'? #
[Hatchet-Face yelling]
[Glass breaking]
# Dow wow ooo ##
[panting]
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
[Rats squeaking]
[Yelling]
[Squeaking]
What's down here?
What, this way?
[Squeaking]
Ohhh.
Thanks, pal.
[Grunting]
[All laughing]
[Squeaking]
Just come
right this way.
Now, uh, this is,
uh, Sheila.
She's Caucasian,
but that's about all
I can recommend.
Bad table manners.
Uh, we were thinking
of two children, actually.
About
6 or 7 years old.
With some spunk.
Well, now,
what about him?
Little Joey,
mother's little helper.
He not only vacuums,
he does windows.
Irons. Yes.
Here, these are the ones
we want.
A double-header!
(both)
Yay!
Oh, they're adorable.
We'll take them.
Uh-uh. Now, that's
a thing with 2 heads,
absolutely not.
Siamese twins
are a financial burden.
Sewing all those
old school clothes together.
You're not
psychologically equipped.
Mrs. Tadlock,
these are my children
and I'm taking them with me.
That's right, sister.
[Children cheering]
You!
[Children clamoring]
Let me outta here. Help.
[Tires squealing]
Come on, we got to get
to the Enchanted Forest.
Turn left.
No, turn right.
[Tires squealing]
##[Scatting]
# Mr. Sandman #
# Yes? #
[people laughing]
# Bring me a dream #
# I am the cutest
that she's ever seen #
# Give her the word
that I'm not a rover #
Oh.
# Then tell her that her
lonesome nights are over #
What?
Shh.
(Allison)
# Sandman, I'm so alone #
# Don't have nobody
to call my own #
# Please turn on
your magic beam #
# Why, Mr. Sandman,
bring her a dream #
##[scatting]
# Mister Sandman,
bring us a dream #
# Us a dream #
# Give him a pair of eyes
with a come hither gleam #
# Give him a lonely heart
like Pagliacci #
# And lots of wavy hair
like Liberace #
# Mr. Sandman
someone to hold #
# Would be so peachy
before we're too old #
# So please turn on
your magic beam #
# Mr. Sandman bring us #
# Please, please
please, Mr. Sandman #
# Bring us a dream ##
[audience applauding]
[Audience cheering]
[People screaming]
[Cheering]
(all)
Drapes!
Allison Vernon-Williams,
the decision is yours.
You sang with the Squares.
Now sing with the Drapes.
[Audience cheering]
Yay!
(Hatchet-Face)
Cry-Baby needs you.
We'll get married
and live in suburbia.
I love you, Allison.
I don't wanna hurt you,
Baldwin.
I had my baby. Isn't he cute?
I'm a Square now.
Wave to Allison.
You maybe a Square, Lenora,
but you're still a tramp.
(all)
Oh.
Allison, pick the man
who loves you the most.
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# won't you let my man
go free? #
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# won't you let my man
go free? #
# He don't belong in prison #
# though he's guilty
as can be #
# But the only crime
he's guilty of #
# is simply loving me #
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# won't you let my man
go free? #
(all)
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
(Allison)
# Won't you let my man
go free? #
# Yeah, yeah, yeah #
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# won't you
let this jailbird free? #
# Whoa, whoa, whoa #
# Just look into his eyes #
# Open up that door #
# Just listen to his guitar,
you'll know the score #
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# let an honest man go free #
# Yeah, yeah, yeah #
(all)
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# don't you make no lifer
out of me #
# I'm innocent, I swear it #
# Let my woman testify #
# She'll tell you
where I was that night #
# Yeah, I'm his alibi #
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# Won't you let my man
go free? #
# Well, I'm tired
of pressing license plates #
# down in this rotten hole #
# I gotta reach the outside
before I lose control #
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# don't you make no lifer
out of me #
[inmates clamoring]
(Allison)
# Yeah, yeah, yeah #
(man)
Walker, Wade Walker,
you have a visitor.
[Whirring]
(all)
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# let me out
of this penitentiary #
# Let me out #
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# don't you make no lifer
out of me #
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# won't you let my baby
go free? #
# Ah, oh, whoa, whoa, whoa #
# Let my man go free #
# Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa #
# Don't make no lifer
out of me #
(all)
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# Can't you see how much love
she's got for me? #
[snarling]
# Well, let him go,
let him go #
# Let him go #
# Let my man go free #
# Ah, whoa, oh #
(all)
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# Well, let me out #
(all)
# Please, Mr. Jailer #
# Don't make me shout #
# Well, let me out ##
[people clamoring]
[All clamoring]
[Audience applauding]
Criminal!
Cry-Baby Walker, society has
given you a second chance.
[People cheering]
You're rehabilitated now.
Here is $3.50.
And a pair
of clean underwear.
[People booing]
You think you're
a big man, Cry-Baby.
But you're lower
than your dead father.
Guess who pulled the switch
on that jerk?
[People laughing]
My grandpappy, that's who.
And every Christmas since,
my whole family
gathers together,
and he re-tells the story
of the day
he electrocuted
your daddy
and we just laugh.
[People laughing]
Let me punch his ugly face.
[People agreeing]
It's okay, Hatchet.
You're beautiful, baby.
[People applauding]
But I'll take care
of this maggot.
Do you know how to play
the automobile game
called "chicken"?
Huh, sure,
my car and your jalopy.
[People laughing]
We head toward one another
at full speed.
First one to turn the wheel
before we smash is a chicken.
[People clucking]
Is that legal?
Stop this insanity.
I got some new rules,
sucker.
How about you and me
on top of the car?
[People agreeing]
I'm man enough,
you big cry-baby.
[People booing]
That's Mr. Baby to you.
[People laughing]
Fellows of the press,
this chicken race
tonight is for my daddy.
And I'd like to sing something
in his memory,
something hillbilly.
[Audience agreeing]
Something colored.
[Groaning]
[People booing]
Something my daddy
would've loved.
[Audience cheering]
##[Guitar playing]
# You call us hoods #
# and say we've gone mad #
# Cause we feel so good
when we're being bad #
# We're high school hellcats #
(all)
# On our own #
# High school hellcats #
# Almost grown #
# Come on and pick a fight
I wish you would #
# We love being bad #
# 'Cause sure feels good #
# Oh! #
Baldwin, please.
Be a gentleman
and call off this race,
it's too dangerous.
Mrs. Vernon-Williams,
you were born a Square
and you're gonna die
a Square.
You're coming with me.
Come on, lady!
Get in the car!
No!
# Yeah, stand back, look out
We're renegade teens #
# Friends of the devil
But twice as mean #
# We're looking for kicks
We want them now #
# We're gonna get them #
(all)
# And we don't care how #
# We're high school hellcats #
# Almost grown #
# High school hellcats #
(all)
# Almost grown #
# Come on, pick a fight
We wish you would #
# We love being bad #
(all)
# 'Cause it sure feels good #
[people whooping]
[Audience clamoring]
[Tires squealing]
(Cry-Baby)
Come on!
Come on, Come on!
[Whooping]
# Well, you lock us up
in your schools #
# We weren't born
to live by rules #
Get down from there
this minute.
Sit down, you traitor.
# When you say stop,
I say go, yeah, go! #
# We're high school hellcats #
(all)
# On our own #
Cry-Baby!
What are you doing?
# Wish you would #
# We love being bad #
(Pepper)
# 'Cause it feels so good #
[people yelling]
Uh-huh. Yes.
# USA, the land of the free #
# We should be
what we want to be #
# But everyone says we
should be like them #
(all)
# But we're
high school hellcats #
# And we never fit in #
# We're
high school hellcats #
Allison, help! Help me!
# Come on and pick a fight,
we wish you would #
# We love being bad
'cause it sure feels good #
# We're high school hellcats #
[cloth ripping]
# Come on and pick a fight,
we wish you would #
# We love being bad
'cause it sure feels good #
[yelling]
# We love being bad
'cause it sure feels good #
Turn the wheel!
# 'Cause it sure feels good ##
Chicken!
[Tires squealing]
Yay!
[Whooping]
[All cheering]
[Allison screaming]
[Audience cheering]
##[Bad Boy
by The Jive Bombers playing]
[Audience applauding]
# I'm just a bad boy #
# All dressed up
in fancy clothes #
# I'm takin' the trouble #
# To blow my bubbles away #
# The hot, blazin' sun #
# Won't hurt my head #
# 'Cause you'll always
find me #
# Right there in the shade #
# I can see all the folks #
# They're laughin' at me #
# 'Cause I'm just #
# Naturally lazy, crazy #
# Bad boy #
# All dressed up
in fancy clothes #
# I'm takin' the trouble #
# To blow my bubbles away ##
##[King Cry Baby
by James Intveld playing]
# Well, one for all
and all for one #
# And all we want
is to have some fun #
# But Squares beware
of our property #
# Yeah, if you're lookin'
to rumble #
# You're lookin' at me
'cause I'm the king #
# King cry-baby #
# 'Cause I'm the king #
# Yeah, I'm the king #
# King cry-baby #
# A king cry-baby
with a tear in my eye #
# If you mess with the king,
you're gonna cry, baby cry #
# Oh baby cry, oh baby cry,
oh baby cry, wow! #
# Well, I was born on
the wrong side of the tracks #
# In the backseat
of a stolen Cadillac #
# I had my first cigarette
before I could walk #
# And I was
strummin' this guitar #
# Before I could talk
'cause I'm the king #
# King cry-baby #
# Yeah, I'm the king #
# 'Cause I'm the king #
# King cry-baby #
# A king cry-baby
with a tear in my eye #
# If you mess with the king,
you're gonna cry,
oh baby cry #
# Oh baby cry, oh baby cry,
# Well, I'm a lonely king
who needs a queen #
# Yeah, you're
the sweetest lump of sugar #
# That I've ever seen #
# Ain't got a ring
or crown for you #
# Well, if I had your love #
# I'd lose
these cry-baby blues #
[whooping]
# She's the queen #
(woman)
# Well, let people talk
I don't care #
# Let me prove to you daddy
that I ain't no Square #
# You'll be my queen
and I'll be your king #
# Yeah, but if you
leave my hive #
# You're gonna feel my sting #
# 'Cause you're my queen #
# Queen cry-baby #
# You're the king #
# King cry-baby #
# I'll be the queen #
# Cry, cry-baby #
# A king cry-baby
with my queen by my side #
# And if you mess with us, man
you're gonna cry,
oh baby cry #
# Oh baby cry, oh baby cry,
# Oh, cry, baby cry,
baby cry, baby cry #
# Cry, baby cry, baby cry,
baby cry #
# A king cry-baby
with my queen by my side #
# And if you mess with us, man
you're gonna cry #
# Oh, baby cry, baby cry,
baby cry, baby cry #
# Oh baby cry, oh baby cry,
oh baby cry #
# Oh, cry baby cry, baby cry,
baby cry #
# Oh, cry, baby cry, baby cry,
baby cry ##