Amira's brought down outside the area.
The keeper catches it comfortably.
It now looks like there will be
a substitution for the blues.
Gentry replaces Penny.
Take your time.
You what?
Big head on that, mate. Thank you.
No problem.
Two weeks of straight drinking.
What a great time.
I had a great time.
I felt better when I got home.
Easy.
What about...
-No, we're too old for Ibiza.
What are you on about?
You're never too old for the island.
That's what people who are too old
for Ibiza say. Where are the crisps?
I said, "Can I have crisps for that guy?"
I pointed to you.
He said you're not allowed
to have crisps anymore.
-He said you're only allowed salad.
-Fucking dickhead.
That's what he said, Dom. Sorry.
-That's harsh, man.
Why don't we go to... boom! Amsterdam?
No, it's too touristy now, isn't it?
-Alright, TripAdvisor.
-I'm not getting off my head again.
-Yeah, good wines.
No.
Berlin, then?
-Nein.
Belgium?
Belgium? Mate, no one's ever
been to Belgium by choice.
What's in Belgium?
-Beers that are, like, 42% or something.
What about hiking?
Yeah... hiking.
-That's a good shout.
-Come on, man. Let's do something good.
What's it called again?
The King's Trail.
It kind of runs between Sweden and Norway.
-You can go there in the summer.
Yeah, apart from,
there's more history than hillbillies.
I wanna do something different.
I don't wanna go to Amsterdam.
We wanna... mix it up.
Yeah, it's not like we're 21 anymore.
Oh, look, there's that...
Look, I'm gonna get a bottle.
Who's on it?
No way. School night, mate.
I wanna crack on.
Does no one wanna...
Anyone wanna come with me?
-Nope.
Come on, Robert.
-Go on, then.
Oh, man!
Bad idea.
You're not getting involved,
are you?
-I'm getting an Uber.
-Yeah, good.
Don't you think, when we meet up,
it getting harder to have a good time?
Did you know that Phil
actually suggested making this brunch?
Fucking brunch.
I'm not...
I'm not gonna plan a lads' holiday
over a fucking avocado on toast, mate.
I'm not doing it.
Avocado's alright.
Do you really wanna go hiking?
Hiking for fun?
-Yeah.
In fucking Sweden?
Yeah, I do.
I don't know, I just wanna
test myself a little, have a challenge.
Do you know what would be a challenge?
Getting Dom on the side of a mountain.
Where's the vodka?
It's just a shame, you know. It's a shame.
It's a shame what he's become.
Yeah. Yeah, big shame.
Yeah, big successful businessman
with a beautiful wife and children.
Yeah, no. It's a...
What else have you got?
Don't fucking argue, you cunt.
There's more. Where the fuck is it, huh?
Stop fucking crying.
Don't fucking move.
Give me your wallet.
Give it to him.
OK.
Look, it's OK.
Don't stand there. Do it.
Give me your fucking wallet.
What else you got?
Take his watch.
Give me the watch.
Here.
Do it.
OK.
And the ring.
No.
-That's my wedding ring.
We don't give a fuck.
Just give me the fucking ring.
Just take it off him.
No, look, you've done enough. It...
-Just leave.
Take it the fuck off him!
Come on.
Listen, you take that ring off,
or I will fuck you up.
Look, I'm not gonna...
Oh, fuck.
Mate, what are you doing?
I told you.
Fucking hell, mate!
What are you doing?
It's alright. I've got it.
For fuck's sake, leave it!
Right, let's go! Let's go!
Morning.
Fuck me, it's cold.
I'll get the coffees on.
Morning, bud.
Morning.
Like I just walked up
a big fucking mountain, man.
One night down, two to go, mate.
It makes you feel insignificant.
Speak for yourself.
Come on, man. Where's your soul?
These mountains were smashed out
by Nordic gods with big bastard hammers.
You know what they have
on walking trails in England?
Pubs.  Yeah, whatever.
Don't tell me you aren't impressed.
Give me a pint of ale
and some pork scratchings.
Yeah, yeah, these are new boots.
They were reduced to 200 quid.
-Memory foam as well.
But you need to break them in.
Yeah, definitely.
It's basic common sense, Phil.
OK, I think I've found a spot...
just up the top of that hill.
Fuck me.
It's beautiful.
Jesus...
Christ.
Oh, fuck every hill in the world!
Shall we do this?
Bo will be up there waiting for him.
Man, I hated that dog.
He was a good man.
The best of us.
It should never have happened.
It should never have happened,
but it did.
And all we can do is remember him.
Robert, we miss you mate.
We haven't seen her.
I can't remember the last time I saw her.
Yeah, I mean, she mentioned Gayle.
Yeah, well, they get on.
Get together or something...
Rob would have loved this place.
Except we wouldn't be here, would we?
We would be on some...
terrible lads' holiday
he would have hated.
I've said it before,
I don't care what anyone says.
It wasn't your fault, mate.
-I think it is, yeah, just over there.
-I know.
I thought we were further out.
When we get back,
I was thinking I might stop on a few days.
Maybe get out there,
do a little bit more hiking.
What do you think, man?
I don't know, mate.
We came all this way.
We have to make the most of it.
I think... I think this is enough for me.
Here. Give it here.
Fuck.
It's the wrong way round.
Give it here.
-Unclip the pole.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, this is awful
in almost every conceivable way.
There are some, Phil,
who consider this character-building.
Quite frankly, right now,
Sweden can lick my bridge.
-My bridge.
Jesus Christ, the bridge.
-Oh, you mean the perineum.
-Yeah, the gooch.
-The bridge.
-Yeah, yeah.
Fuck!
Come on. Let's get you up.
-Oh, fuck! Shit!
Alright, come on. Easy, easy.
-Come on, you're alright.
Up, up.
Yeah, alright. Easy.
Fuck.
-Walk about a bit on it.
Give it a walk around.
That's it.
You're OK.
Oh, it's twisted.
It hurts like a son of a bitch.
You can probably walk it off.
No, it's my meniscus.
I've done it before. It's fucked.
Alright, we'll get him
something to lean on.
Phil, can you get the rods, please?
What are we thinking, Dom?
Because the trail goes right round
those mountains. It's probably, what...?
Six hours till we camp?
Another eight round to the lodge?
What are we thinking?
Fuck me.
I'm not doing 14 hours on this. OK, man?
Let's get the map.
Do you wanna try
your phone as well?
-No, no need.
There's no reception anyway.
Cheers, man. Luke, my office.
What do you think?
I think we could be carrying him out there
like a fucking Egyptian princess
if we're not careful.
-It's probably not as bad as he says.
-Almost certainly not as bad as he says.
But it's not gonna stop him moaning
all the way back, is it?
-There is another way out of this, man.
Well, you saw it last night... the lodge.
It's not that far as the crow flies. Look.
If we go south-west, through here,
we cut the journey in half.
A little off-trail hiking.
Could be exciting,
might even do us some good.
We could be kicking back by the evening.
I think we need this.
Look, why don't me and you
leave them here with the food?
Then we can go back, get some help.
No fucking way you're leaving us
on this fucking mountain.
I can walk, alright?
If you know a quicker route, let's do it.
How's the knee, Dom
Killing me.
Are there bears in this forest?
Of course there's fucking bears.
Big bastards as well.
We should have gone to Vegas.
You'd find something
to fall over in Vegas.
Yeah, a massive pile of tits.
Shit...
Everything in this bastard country
is a relic.
Strange place to park, isn't it?
My next door neighbor
has one of those.
My eldest is absolutely obsessed by it.
I got a hand job in one of those once,
at a festival.
Thanks, Phil. What a beautiful story.
Are you scared of the woods?
Now, is it me
or is it really quiet in here?
Alright, don't shit your pants.
The trees soak up the sound.
That's what trees do.
Hiking was easier yesterday.
Well, we weren't in the forest.
No, we bloody weren't.
Come on.
The sooner we get to town, the sooner
we get to the bar and get drunk.
The Swedes were big into logging,
until the 1950s.
-Then they decided to pack it in.
That's interesting.
Which is why Sweden
is an untouched land of natural beauty,
and Britain is a car park.
If you love Sweden so much,
why don't you marry it?
Right, time out.
Dom, what did Gayle say when you told her
you were going on a hiking holiday?
She said, "Who are you
and what have you done with my husband?"
Oh, here we go. Photo op.
-Here we go.
Scott of the Antarctic.
Work it, baby.
-Fucking Amelia Earhart over there.
Wallop. Yes, that's it.
-Look at that.
-Let's get a selfie while we're here.
Selfie
You too, Luke. Come on.
Let's preserve this magic moment.
There you go.
It's a beautiful thing.
Here we go. Everyone get in.
One, two three... and Brexit. Boom.
-Yes.
-Yeah, yeah. Four twats in a forest.
Yeah.
My stomach is beginning to eat itself.
Yeah, I could do a steak.
Big fat, juicy steak.
I want peppercorn sauce,
I want hand-cooked chips,
side salad.
A nice tumbler of scotch...
and a big fat cigar at the end.
Oh, man.
I could go for some sushi right now.
Yeah, some red wine instead of white.
Lashings of wasabi.
Big Mac, plastic tray, by myself,
and no one to talk to.
Can I have a kebab, please, mate?
Donner?
-No, chicken shish, please.
Rob liked a Donner, remember that?
Yeah.
Every Saturday night at uni.
There he was,
pissed, covered in grease.
What the fuck is that?
Why is it ripped open?
It's been gutted.
Yeah, why hang it like that?
I mean, would someone do that?
It didn't fucking put itself there,
that's for sure.
Could be hunters out here.
What, bait?
Possibly.
Or it's the bit they don't show you
in nature documentaries.
-A bear.
Do bears do that?
I don't know, Dominic.
I'm not a fucking bear expert.
It's still bleeding.
So?
So, it means that whatever did that...
We should go.
It's a fresh kill.
Yeah, we should go.
Fucking Jesus Christ!
Fuck.
Where the hell are we, Hutch?
Let me check.
This is ridiculous, man.
We should pitch the tents.
We should pitch the tents!
So we're giving up making it
back to town tonight, then?
Well, I don't see
we have much choice, Philip.
Guys.
What is it?
Look at this.
Huh?
Look.
Well, how about that!
What is that?
Is that a house?
Come on.
Thank Christ.
-Hey, Hutch. Wait a minute!
Come on!
Can you see anything?
It looks empty.
We should leave it alone, then.
Let's kick it in.
No fucking way.
We need to get under cover, mate.
Phil, give us a hand.
Alright, come on, then.
Wait, wait, wait!
We can't just break in.
We can't stay out here all night.
On three, yeah?
One, two, three.
Luke, you're getting soaked!
Did you hear that?
No, I didn't hear anything.
Come on!
This is clearly the house
we'll get murdered in.
It's not as bad
as our uni accommodation.
That's the shape on the tree, I think.
Guys, this place
is definitely abandoned, yeah?
Abandoned
Whoever it was, they were packing.
Look at that.
I don't like this place.
-Not too keen on it myself, mate.
But it's a lesser of two evils
kind of situation.
Hutch,
I definitely just heard something outside.
Maybe you did, Lukey.
We're not the only animals in the woods.
Alright, let's see
if we can get this stove working.
We'll need stuff to burn.
Like what?
Anything made of wood will do.
We're gonna smash the place up,
are we?
Fuck them.
Whoever lives here has more to worry about
than their table being on fire.
Might be some stuff to burn up there.
Go on, Phil. You're nearest.
What?
Go on!
Do you want me to come with you?
No.
Hey! That's it, lad!
Dickheads.
Guys, get the fuck up here, now!
What now?
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck is that?
That's witchcraft.
Huh?
That's what that is: witchcraft.
Is that meant to be a person?
What, with no head
and antlers for hands?
-If I hear anything come down the stairs--
-Don't! Fucking hell!
I'm going downstairs
to get that fire started.
You guys can stay up here if you want.
Yeah, good idea.
Come on.
It looked like that thing
in the tree.
Could be idolizing a spirit
or a deity.
Some kind of pagan or Nordic shit,
like an offering.
Yeah, well, I almost offered up
a massive shit when I saw it.
-Well, that is Nordic.
Who knows what they're into out here?
Living here in the middle of nowhere...
Sun goes down,
doesn't come up for six months... You're bound to go fucking mental
in the winter.
We should burn
this place down when we leave.
I'm fucking well up for burning it down.
Listen, though, I think that...
when we wake up tomorrow, we should think
about just going back out the way we came.
We don't need to willfully add
another day to the trip, do we?
Let's just stick to the shortcut--
My old scoutmaster used to say,
"If a shortcut was a shortcut,
it would be called a route."
Why do you pretend you were in the Scouts?
You were never in the Scouts.
Where did I get the quote from?
Guys, right, we have a map,
we have a compass,
we have supplies.
So as long as we don't panic,
as long as we don't fuck ourselves,
we're gonna be absolutely OK.
No one's fucking anyone.
It could be a long night.
No one's fucking anybody.
We're in sleeping bags,
for crying out loud.
It could get messy.
I'd give anyone a grand to go upstairs
and sleep with that thing.
Absolutely, no way.
-My wife would never forgive me.
No, she wouldn't.
Goodnight.
Yeah, alright. OK, a couple of hours.
As soon as it's light, we'll get out.
Hutch?
Mate. Wake up, mate.
It's OK. It's OK.
Where the fuck am I?
We're in that house.
We're in that fucking house.
Get up, OK? Get up! Where's the... where's my fucking...
Jesus Christ.
I've pissed myself.
Gayle!
Dom.
Dom?
Dom!
Gayle!
-Dom, wake up. Mate, mate, it's OK.
It's OK. Get up, mate.
You, two...
Wake up!
Where's Phil?
Where the fuck's...
Phil?
Fuck!
Phil!
Phil, what are you doing?
It's OK.
Mate, get up. OK?
What is this I don't know, mate.
Get up, OK?
Just grab everything. Just shove it in the bags. Let's go.
Can we fucking hurry up, yeah?
I want to get out of here now!
Oh, for fuck's sake.
We shouldn't be here.
It's a warning.
We don't know that.
We do not know that.
-It's a warning.
Fuck!
Listen.
Hutch, we just go out
the way we came in, OK?
We go back north-east.
It's a knee-jerk plan.
It's a bad plan...
Mate.
Hey! Hey!
Is that a path?
No, Dom. South-west is this way, mate.
South-west can go fuck itself.
You said we would
get out of this forest yesterday.
The storm slowed us down.
What do you want me to do?
So did the dead thing hanging in the trees
and the spooky fucking house!
-We don't even know where that goes.
We could end up in Norway for all we know.
Great!
I'm sick of this off
A path means civilization.
Dom.
Marvelous.
Are we gonna talk about it or not?
-Because I'd really like to talk about it.
-I'd rather not, mate.
You'd rather not.
I woke up stark bollock-naked
in front of that thing, praying to it.
-I'd love if someone could explain that.
-It was a nightmare, Phil.
-You had what's known as a nightmare.
Well, what happened to you?
We all did. We all had nightmares.
We got spooked
and we had bad dreams, alright?
Yeah.
-Leave it out, mate.
-No, hang on, mate.
You were screaming and shouting
at the top of your voice.
You were shouting, "Gayle."
I said, leave it out, Luke.
Something made me do that.
-Press on.
-Bad dreams or not, I'd never do that.
-Something was there--
For fuck's sake!
Listen to yourself, mate.
I'm a bit fucking humiliated
about being found in my kegs
covered in piss, alright?
I don't really wanna psychoanalyze it.
I don't wanna play fucking make-believe.
Because right now,
we have some real fucking problems,
like finding out which way
this fucking path ends up.
Enough of the bullshit ghost stories, OK?
You're starting to sound
like my daughters.
Outside, I'd never have done that, mate.
Something's not right here.
-Yes.
-That ridge up there.
What, towards the light?
Yeah.
We're just tracking along it.
Five more minutes on this path
and I'm pulling rank.
You see these things?
Manmade.
We're getting somewhere.
Should we have a look Absolutely not.
Let's keep going.
Yeah.
We can still get out of here today.
Dom...
Dom,
maybe we should think about this.
Dom?
Dom.
Guys,
I just need a minute.
My knee is killing me.
These are the wrong fucking shoes.
Dom,
you might have to push
through the pain barrier a bit, mate.
We can't keep going at this pace.
Screw you.
I'm through the pain barrier.
I'm in bloody agony.
No, I think you're uncomfortable.
There's a difference.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize
you were a doctor.
Why don't you give yourself
a fucking prostate exam
and leave me in peace, yeah?
Dom, come on. Get up.
No.
Dom, I want out of these woods now.
Please get up.
This is fucking ridiculous.
I'm gonna go to the top of that ridge
and see if I can see anything.
Yeah. Good idea, man.
-To the ridge, straight back.
Got it.
-Don't go too far.
Got it!
Fuck!
Guys!
-There's something there.
What?
-There's something up there in the woods.
Like what?
-Something fucking big.
What, like an animal?
Can we all agree to not
start losing our fucking shit here?
I'm telling you,
there is something up there.
I'm not trying to fucking freak you out,
but I woke up last night...
and there was some fucking...
Look at this.
What?
What the fuck is that?
Nothing has done that to you.
You...
You were on your own.
You've done it to yourself.
-You were outside. You walked into a tree.
Why do you have to fucking deny
everything I say?
Because I do not
value your judgement, Luke.
-And I want to get the fuck out of here.
-We wouldn't be here if it wasn't for you.
No, we wouldn't be here
if it wasn't for you.
Dom, shut up!
Come on. What do you mean by that?
Track it back.
You know what I'm talking about.
No, I don't. I don't, no.
Why don't you just...
fucking come out and say it?
Oh, come on, guys. This is bullshit!
-Come on, mate.
-Now, there it is.
Now he's got some
fucking fight in him, yeah?
Where was that with Rob?
You'll fight your friends.
-You can't stand up for them.
-You're not my friend anymore.
-You're not my fucking friend.
No, I'm not.
-No, you're fucking not.
For fuck's sake.
No, you are fucking not. OK?
Do you know what?
I am fucking done with you.
Not a drop of blood on you.
Fucking coward.
-Dom, you shut the fuck up.
No, hang on, Hutch, mate.
No, hang on, hang on. What?
Fucking what?
He has his skull cracked in half...
and you come out of there
without a drop of blood on you.
What the fuck are you doing?
What was that?
You alright, mate?
-He's broken my nose.
Shut up!
You've not broken your nose, alright?
Don't start your shit now.
You keep quiet if you want,
but somebody's got to say something.
This is exactly the kind of situation
where people fall out,
and we need to be...
Where are you going?
We need to be working together, man.
Luke. Fucking hell. Luke!
Luke.
Is that what you think?
That it was my fault?
That I should have stood up?
I don't know.
Looks like someone was here.
Are we stopping?
What the fuck is that?
Yeah, what is that, man?
Some sort of fabric, I think.
I think it's a tent or something.
It's a credit card.
Anna Eriksen, expires 1984.
That's a bad sign, isn't it?
Just leaving your tent behind,
and your shoes.
Guys.
Guys, seriously, come on.
We're not gonna
be these people, right, OK?
Because we registered at the lodge,
and in five hours' time,
they are gonna report us missing.
We're on a path in the woods.
It is near a hiking trail.
This is where people get found, right?
It's getting dark again.
Oh... thanks. Thank you.
How are you doing?
Well, I'm looking forward
to the rescue party.
Dom's knee is getting worse, not better.
Phil's not looking great.
You're the strongest.
You should try and get out, get help.
I'll stay with these two.
You think so?
Definitely.
I'll get you fixed up in the morning.
-Take the compass, head south-west.
-OK.
-Keep south-west.
-Good man, mate.
Yeah.
How are we doing here, mate?
Let's have a look at this.
Oh, looks nasty, man.
It's not good.
Have you put anything on it?
No, I haven't got anything.
Maybe Dom's got something
in his backpack.
Fucking shoes.
That looks grim.
Coward.
Phil!
-Phil, Phil, Phil!
It was here.
-I don't know.
Where's Hutch?
-All I saw was shadows.
What?
-I don't know!
-It just took him.
Hutch!
Get up! Hutch is gone.
Hutch is gone!
Oh, fuck.
What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
Hutch!
-Hutch!
Luke!
Hutch!
-We're getting turned around out here.
Maybe we should, like,
try and retrace our steps?
All we have is in the tents, Luke.
-He's fucking screaming.
I know, but if we run around in circles,
we're gonna get fucking lost. OK?
We need to get back to the camp.
We need to get our bearings. Yeah?
Fuck.
Fuck!
We'll find the tents
and come back for him.
Is that...
Is that Hutch?
Oh, my God!
Fuck.
No.
I don't know.
What about his kids?
Listen, OK?
Just calm down.
We need to get out of here, now.
We need to move.
We can't leave him here.
When we get out,
we'll send people back to get him.
Fucking hell, we don't know where we are.
It put him there, didn't it?
What?
It knew we were gonna come this way.
We were supposed to find him.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
You don't fucking do this.
-You keep your shit together!
Shush.
He's right.
I'm not leaving him like this.
-We should say something.
We need to go.
It's gonna come back.
Dom, come on.
Come on.
It was at that house.
We had those nightmares
and it followed us, didn't it?
Yeah.
It followed us from that house
and it did that to Hutch.
Did you actually see it yesterday?
No, I don't know what I saw.
Well,
I did see it...
while I was up on that ridge
and the trees were the same as this.
Jesus Christ.
It was big, OK.
It had to be to put
that fucking elk in the tree.
It was hunters. Pagan fucking hillbillies
from those houses.
-No one's lived in those houses for years.
Fucking hell.
-Keep your voice down.
There are houses here.
There are people
and they killed our fucking friend.
Shut the fuck up. Shut up.
Keep your fucking voice down.
There are three of us,
and there is one of it.
And I've got a fucking knife.
So, we're gonna keep going
in the direction that Hutch said
until we get out of this fucking forest,
do you hear me?
Oh, my God.
You see?
There are people.
Are we following these?
Of course not.
We shouldn't go that way.
OK.
South-west is up.
I'm tired, man.
It's OK.
Come on, mate. Get up.
It got inside my head, man.
It made me pray
to that thing in the house.
I can't get it out my fucking head.
Come on, mate. Get up.
We're far away from that now.
Come on, you can do it.
Phil, look. Look.
Phil.
Where are you going?
We're close.
Guys, I can see the end!
I can see the end.
Hutch was... Hutch was right.
Guys?
Guys, you've got to see this.
Dom?
Phil?
What are you doing?
We heard something.
Phil.
You can't run.
Dom?
Phil?
Shh...
What the...?
Fuck, fuck.
You're alive, you're alive.
Where's Phil?
I just heard something coming and it...
And it just took him.
What did it look like?
I don't know.
It was fast.
It's fucking hunting us.
Jesus Christ.
I thought I'd die.
I don't wanna die.
-I don't wanna die alone.
-Look at me.
Look at me.
I am not going to leave you. OK?
OK?
-Yes.
Yeah.
But I think I might have found a way out.
Do you think you can move your leg?
Yeah, a little.
OK. OK.
Piggy back?
-I'm afraid we're gonna have to run.
-Yeah.
OK?
-I know.
Are you ready?
In a minute. In a minute.
Let's go on "three".
OK?
One.
Two.
Three.
His eyes... His eyes...
There's a path.
Oh, fuck.
We've got to go.
Phil!
No, we've got to go!
Dom! Come on.
We've got to go!
Hello?
Please!
Come on. Get up, get up!
Luke.
Wake up.
What the fuck?
What is that?
I don't know, mate. I don't fucking know.
What can you see?
I see people.
-Two, three... four.
What are they doing?
It looks like they're...
It looks like they're building,
putting something together.
What do they want?
Those fuckers!
I've got to get out of here.
Can you reach the table?
Why?
Break the glass, cut the ropes.
Go on. Go on, Luke.
Yes.
Go on, Luke.
Fuck.
Is that water?
Water?
What are you doing?
What?
Come on. No, give him some.
No, give... Give him some.
Oh, no! No!
Luke! Help!
Dom!
Dom! Dom!
No!
Oh, my God!
-Dom!
Oh, God, no!
They prepare for sacrifice...
Over soon.
Are you OK?
Dom?
Are you OK, mate?
I never told you
about my nightmare.
I saw these people...
offering me to that thing.
Its dead hands...
gripping me.
And I saw...
Gayle.
I saw my wife.
I'm gonna die here, Luke.
No.
No, you're not.
I couldn't lose all of you.
They're gonna kill me. Do you understand?
They are not...
They're not gonna kill you because
I'm not gonna let them kill you, OK?
Listen to me.
You're gonna get out of here.
And you're gonna...
burn this fucking place to the ground
behind you.
Do you understand?
You don't stop.
You keep going.
You live.
And you tell my wife...
I tried to get back to her.
I'm not gonna do that
because I don't need to do that. OK?
Luke.
I don't need to do that.
OK?
Come on.
Come on!
What the hell is this?
You fucking stupid pricks.
Why don't we do this, yeah?
What are you waiting for?
Come on.
Fucking come on.
Gayle?
Gayle!
Dom?
Come on.
Gayle!
Gayle.
Dom.
Gayle?
Did you take him down from the tree?
We don't move the bodies.
What is it?
A god. Ancient.
One of the Jötunn.
A bastard offspring of Loki.
We do not say its name.
Because you're afraid of it?
We worship it.
It keeps us here...
lets us live beyond natural life.
No more pain. No more death.
Your ritual begins tonight.
It is a privilege to worship.
You will kneel before the god.
If not,
it will hang you from the trees.
Why me?
Your pain is great.
Yeah, I'm not like you
and I will not live like this.
You will kneel before it,
like the rest of us.
Fuck off.
Shit.
Fuck.
Drop the axe.
Stay there.
No, no.