So, hey guys!
Um, found out the units
are shipping me off
to St. Adeline again.
Didn't matter what I said.
They didn't hear me.
Um, I'm sure
some of you know
what that's like,
not to be heard,
to feel like you're alone
in the world
and no one cares.
Um, that's why
I wrote this song,
for you guys,
and I hope you like it.
* Up in the air
* You're always there
* And I'm alone
trying not to show
how much I care *
* And do you see
me trying to be *
* Everything I think
that you would want
or ever need *
* All the static in my mind
* I'm having trouble
trying to find *
Ugh, Sara Croft.
I can't believe
they're making me
room with her again
this year.
Doesn't sound so bad to me.
I'm expecting you to be
on your best behavior
this fall.
Best behavior, got it.
I thought we decided
you'd leave that at home.
You decided that, not me.
I don't want you goofing off
with that thing.
Absolutely.
Hey, after what you did
this summer,
you mess up again,
if I get one call
from the Sisters, that's it.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
Zoe, Jason, welcome back.
-Hi, Sister Rebecca.
-Hi.
-Sister.
-Hi, Sister.
I trust you all had
a wonderful summer?
It was great.
Mmhmm.
Jason.
Don't worry.
We'll look after him.
Thank you.
Sister Sophia?
Yes.
It's lovely
to finally meet you.
So nice to meet you, too.
Please, have a seat.
Sorry things have been
so hectic around here.
It always takes
a couple of days
for the kids to settle in
after the summer.
It's understandable.
So, I see you spent
the last three years
teaching at a school
in Missoula, Montana.
How was that?
It was definitely colder.
Well, the school had nothing
but glowing things
to say about you.
And I loved everything
about teaching
those young angels
the word of our Lord.
Of course,
although I don't know
what the protocol
was at St. Val's,
but here we prefer
our teachers
wear no make-up,
of any kind.
Over there is
the instructional building.
Your classroom will be
on the second floor.
The building across campus
is the boys' dorm
and the girls' dorm
is right there.
Better to keep them
as far apart as possible.
-Absolutely.
-Ah, here's one
of your students now.
Jason Brady,
this is Sister Sophia,
your new homeroom teacher.
Hi.
It's so nice to meet you.
Jason is
our resident musician.
And a bit of a celebrity
from what I hear.
Really?
You must be quite good.
Uh, I'm okay.
I'll, uh, I'll see you in class.
Oh, don't take offense
if Jason seems
a bit distant.
He's been having
a hard time.
-Why is that?
-Well, his grades
have been falling
and he got into a bit
of trouble this summer.
Really?
DUI.
Wrecked
his father's car.
Thank God
no one was hurt.
Come.
This is your room.
It's not fancy
but we've never had
any complaints.
It's perfect.
Good.
Well, I'll leave you
to get settled in.
Sister, we're very happy
you're here.
Thank you, Sister.
Hm.
Forgive me for not praying
as much as I should have
this summer.
I'm working really hard
to get into Whittendale.
And that's all
I'm really praying for.
That and my brother.
He's getting into
a lot of trouble.
He could really
use some guidance.
Thank you.
This is it, man,
my last year
to bag Sara Croft.
Pete, give it up already, man.
Come on, she's practically
bagged everyone else.
My chances have to be good.
So, Jay, how many
fans you got now?
I'm up to like 10,000.
Dude, that is
such a babe score.
You know that, right?
Hey, did I ever tell you
you sing like a girl?
That's not what
your sister thinks.
Hey, let's hit
the PS4.
You coming?
Maybe later, man.
* Up in the air
* You're always there
* And I'm alone
trying not to show
how much I care *
* And do you see
* Sky without the clouds
* You're the voice
that laughs too loud *
* You're the one face
in the crowd
I always want around *
* But I'm stuck
on the ground *
That was beautiful.
That was far better
than just okay.
You're really talented,
Jason.
Your parents
must be very proud.
Yeah.
Yeah, right.
May I?
Do you play?
Um.
Not really.
You know, your lyrics,
they...
...really speak
to you, don't they?
Yeah, yeah, I guess
you could say that.
You know, I get it, Jason.
I know what it's like
to be misunderstood.
If you ever need
to talk, I'm around.
Okay.
I'll see you in class.
Hey, rock star.
You still in hot water
with your dad?
Yeah, something like that.
Well, we got the whole year
to get you into
even more trouble.
Looks like Sara
found someone else
she hasn't bagged.
Shut up.
Good morning, class.
Good morning.
I'm your new teacher,
Sister Sophia.
Good morning, Sister Sophia.
Can't get more grounded
than I am.
Yeah, you're always grounded,
I feel like.
One day I'll get
visiting rights.
Can't wait.
Toxic Tramp.
Hmm.
Now I understand
why you seem to have
difficulty focusing Miss--
Croft, Sara Croft.
Well, Sara, how about
I help you focus?
I trust that you'll
check your behavior.
After all, you don't want
to go to Hell, do you?
Whatever.
Now.
Where were we?
Oh, how about
we take a look
at your fancy
new textbooks?
Uh, chapter one looks like
a great place to start.
Uh, yes, Miss--
Brady, Zoe Brady.
Oh...
Yes.
Shouldn't we start
with the Morning Prayer?
Of course.
Zoe, why don't you lead us?
Give me, O Lord...
I pray Thee firm faith,
unwavering hope,
perfect charity.
Pour into my heart the spirit
of wisdom and understanding,
the spirit of counsel
and spiritual strength,
the spirit of knowledge--
Hey.
Nice job getting in trouble
on your first day.
I didn't get
in trouble.
Do you know what's weird?
Our new teacher, she didn't
say the Morning Prayer.
So?
So, that's like
sacrilege around here.
The last thing you need
is a distraction
like Sara Croft.
God, Zoe, are you gonna
get on me like Dad now, too?
Dad's not getting on you,
he's trying to help you.
Well, then everybody
can stop trying to help.
Jason?
-About this morning...
-Hey, look, I'm sorry, okay,
I didn't mean
to interrupt your--
No, it's okay,
you don't have to apologize.
I just wanted to make sure
that we got off
on the right foot,
because I want this
to be a good year for you...
and for me.
Okay.
So...
This Sara...
Is she your girlfriend?
No.
I don't have a girlfriend.
Oh.
I'm surprised.
I'd think you were
quite a catch.
Have a good night, Jason.
* Trying not to show
how much I care *
* And do you see
* Me trying to be
* I think that
you would want
or ever need *
Hey!
Hey.
So, what do you think
about the new teacher?
She's okay,
I guess.
Well, I think
she's a bitch.
You know,
I bet one day,
you're going to be
even bigger than Bieber.
Yeah, we'll see.
Well, just in case,
I think I should
take my chance now.
Miss Croft!
I see you did not
heed my warning.
Jason, get to class.
Go.
You're new here so I doubt
you know who my dad is.
I mean, he like practically
pays for this school.
I don't care
who your daddy is.
Do not let me catch you
with that boy ever again.
Now go to class.
Jason?
A minute please.
You didn't think you were
gonna get off the hook
that easy, did you?
Besides, I thought you said
that Sara wasn't
your girlfriend.
Come to my chambers
after your last class
and we'll have a word.
I thought students
weren't allowed
in the teacher's quarters.
Well, they are
if they're invited.
Sister Sophia?
Whoa.
You're a bad boy, Jason.
You didn't come to see me.
No, I'm sorry.
I--I totally forgot.
I'll let it slide.
This time.
Hi, you two.
How was your
first week back?
Good.
-Hi.
Hey, rock star.
Got big plans this weekend?
Hardly.
Well, if you
get out on parole,
you have my number.
Okay, I got it,
but let's see what happens.
You know,
Sister Sophia,
I know it's been
a change coming here.
And we may not do things
the same way as at St. Val's.
But if you ever
need anything--
Bye.
My door is always open.
Actually, Sister Rebecca,
there is something.
My Aunt Francis is ill
and in hospice
at Mount Cedar.
I'd like to go
visit her.
Of course.
Take as much time
as you need.
I'll be sure to pray
the rosary for her.
Just remember the kids
are back for mass on Sunday.
It's so weird,
our new teacher didn't give us
any homework,
and we should be studying
for the SAT, which I'm
gonna have to do anyway
if I want to get
into Whittendale.
* I'm an overachiever,
baby, baby, baby *
Well, that sounds
like a solid idea, Zoe.
Hi, honey.
Hey, babe.
And what about you,
Jason, any plans?
Well, I doubt I'm gonna get
into Whittendale.
We don't expect that, honey,
just that you, you know,
apply somewhere.
Actually I've been
thinking about that.
I want to take a year off,
work on my music.
Is it just me?
Now that doesn't sound
like such a good idea.
-I'll pay rent.
-So now you're talking
about getting a job...
you know, Jason,
once you quit school,
it makes it that much harder
to go back, at least
if you're in school,
you're working
towards something.
I know what I want
to work towards
it's just not what you want.
That's not what
I'm expecting.
Okay, then maybe
taking a year off
isn't such a bad idea
and if he's paying rent,
I think that's
very responsible.
-Yes, yes.
-Yes.
I just want him
to strive to be
something more than
just a starving artist.
What, so you don't think
I'll make it?
-I'm not saying that.
-That's what it sounds like.
And I'm gonna go be
a starving artist
out back, okay?
I'm gonna skip dinner.
Jason.
David.
* All I am
and all I'll be *
* Take me home
* Even lovers forget
what beats in their chest *
* I am
* Home
Hello?
Hey, Sara.
Tonight?
Yeah, I don't think I can,
I'm kind of still grounded.
Yeah, I'm really on thin ice.
So, I'm just gonna have
to see you at school, okay?
Cool.
Oh, okay.
Sister Sophia.
What are you doing up here?
I thought I might
have heard some rustling.
Well, the kids
have been known
to try and sneak out before.
I trust you didn't
find anything.
No, nothing at all.
Everyone's sleeping.
Good, just make sure
you report any inappropriate
behavior back to me.
We have a reputation
to uphold.
Of course.
Prude.
Give me, O Lord,
I pray thee firm faith,
unwavering hope,
perfect charity.
Pour into my heart the spirit
of wisdom and understanding,
the spirit of counsel
and spiritual strength,
the spirit of knowledge
and true godliness.
Amen.
All right, everyone,
let's review the homework
that I gave you.
Open your textbooks
to page 34.
Sara Croft, what is that?
I can't believe this.
Marijuana.
That's not mine.
Really, then what is it
doing in your textbook?
I don't know,
it's probably a joke,
I mean, is it even real?
Oh, it's real.
And you, Miss Croft,
are in very big trouble.
Well she's denied
any wrongdoing
and insists she has no idea
how she came to have it.
But still, we have
a very strict policy
on illegal drugs.
I've notified her parents
and she will be
indefinitely suspended.
Well, I'm concerned
that there may be
more than one person
involved in this mess.
These acts of wickedness
rarely happen in a vacuum.
It may be prudent to proceed
with a full inspection
of the school.
After all, Sister,
you want to ensure
that your school
is clean, right?
All right, in light
of the circumstances,
I don't think we have
any other choice.
Well, there goes
your only chance
at getting laid this year.
Boys, if you don't mind
stepping into the hall.
-What's the problem?
-We're conducting
an inspection, this will
only take a minute.
Let's go.
-Move.
-I don't have any--
I know.
Move.
Mr. Brady.
Would you like
to explain this, please?
-I've never seen that before.
-Then why was it found
under your mattress?
I don't know.
Dude, don't look at me,
you're the alcy.
Shut the hell up, man!
Boys, that's enough!
Mr. Robertson, could you
step into the room, please?
Now.
This is such crap,
I don't know whose that is.
Listen, son,
all of us are tempted,
we understand that.
But the best thing to do here
is to tell the truth
and get it
off your conscience.
My conscience is clear.
The evidence suggests otherwise
and we can't just look
the other way, Jason.
So you're gonna ruin my life
over something I didn't do?
You don't believe me.
Look, if my dad
hears about this,
he'll kill me.
Father, in light of this,
maybe we should give
Jason a second chance.
After all, it's alcohol,
it's not an illicit drug.
Sister, the young man
has struggled
with this before.
We have to tell his parents.
May I speak from the heart?
Of course.
We have all
struggled with sin.
And we've all
been shown mercy.
Perhaps if Jason
was to stay the weekend,
and work around the school,
and help the sisters
tend to the grounds,
we could overlook
this little indiscretion,
and just keep it
to ourselves.
Jason, this sounds
like a proper penance.
What do you think, son?
Okay.
Sure.
Thank you, Sister.
Good.
You know, Sister Sophia,
it was a wonderful act
of mercy you showed
that young man.
Well, I am truly blessed
and I wanted to share
my happiness with everyone.
I must say,
I find it so refreshing
to see a young woman
like yourself
taking the cloth.
It's no secret that our
numbers are dwindling.
So tell me, Sister, when did
you hear your calling?
Well, it all started
with a song.
-A song?
-That's right.
I heard it one day
and it was if the songwriter
was singing just for me.
* Everything I think
that you would want
or ever need *
* All this started
Mm.
St. Adeline hires
Montana nun.
Sister Sophia?
Yes?
(Laura)
Hi, Sister Sophia.
My name is Candace,
Candace Fullman.
I'm a member
of your congregation.
I'm just a stone's throw.
Oh, hello,
I haven't met you yet.
I heard that
you've been transferred
to a St. Adeline's School
in California?
I'm afraid so, yes.
I'm driving there right now.
Today, all by yourself?
Yes, I know it's crazy,
but God has His way
of moving us
around as He needs.
I'm sorry to see you go.
Oh, dear God.
And that was it.
I knew what my calling was.
What's the name
of the song?
Ah, perhaps
we should have
the choir sing it
this Sunday.
Oh, well,
to be honest,
it's more like
a pop song.
It's one of my little
guilty pleasures.
Oh well,
if that's all,
I shouldn't feel
too guilty about that.
So what am I gonna
tell Mom and Dad?
Just tell them I volunteered
to stay the weekend
to work, you know,
to show my school
love and spirit.
Oh, yeah, 'cause they're
gonna believe that.
They will
if you say it.
I don't know,
if they have questions,
just have them call
Sister Sophia.
Why?
She fixed it.
Why did she do that?
She thinks I'm cool.
Actually I'm gonna stay
the weekend.
Why?
To keep an eye on you.
Zoe.
Zoe, come on.
Here, let me help you.
Thanks.
These flowers are so pretty
when they start to bloom.
Yeah.
So, tell me about your dad.
He thinks I'm throwing
away my future
because I want
to be a musician.
But it's the one thing
I'm good at, you know?
I'm never gonna be
a straight-A student
like my sister.
I'm just not.
Trust me, I know
what it's like
being something you're not.
And it really sucks.
It does really suck.
Wow, it is so hot out here.
Whoo.
Sister Sophia?
Shh.
Sister Sophia.
No, please.
It's Sophia.
Just Sophia.
Remember how I said,
"It's hard being someone
that you're not."
I can't do it anymore.
Not tonight...
...because I didn't
choose this.
And I get you, Jason.
Just like I know
that you get me.
No, no, no, no, no,
I can't, I can't, I can't.
I can't, I can't.
Jason.
This is wrong, this is wrong.
I can't, I can't.
It's okay.
Come here.
Please.
Mm, oh God.
Jason.
Hey.
Don't look so nervous.
It's okay.
No morning-after
regrets, all right?
It's not that easy,
you're a nun
and my teacher.
I told you last night.
I'm different.
I don't belong here.
Just like you.
We're both misunderstood,
which is why we can't say
anything to anyone,
especially your sister,
because if she finds out,
she'll go running to Daddy.
Am I right?
And then, well--
Yeah.
I should, um,
get to breakfast
before it's over.
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
Uh, looking for my brother.
Well, he's not here.
And you shouldn't be either.
Or did you forget
about the rules
about coming into
the boys dormitory?
No, I was just
worried about him.
Well, you should
go worry somewhere else.
Why are you in his room?
I'm conducting my rounds.
Now, scoot,
before I call the Father.
Hey!
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah, why?
I didn't see you
at breakfast.
Oh, I wasn't hungry.
I went to your room.
Sister Sophia was there.
-What?
-Yeah, she was,
like, going through
your stuff or something.
What's going on?
I don't know.
I--I don't know.
Jay.
Nothing's
going on, okay?
All right, everyone,
that's it for today.
Uh, Zoe, a moment please.
Zoe, I know how important
getting into college
is to you, which is why
I was disappointed
in your test result.
Are you sure?
I mean, I thought
I knew everything.
Trust me, I'm sure.
But don't worry.
I want to give you
another chance.
Come by after your last class
and you can take it again.
Really?
Really.
Thank you.
So is it just me
or does anyone else think
-Sister Sophia's kind of hot?
-Hey, I'm already going to hell
-for what I'm thinking of her.
-That ship has long
-sailed, buddy.
-What the hell's
-that supposed to mean?
-It means you can't
have everything,
what do you want, Sara Croft,
do you want Sister Sophia?
What else do you want?
Sister Sophia?
What are you doing?
Zoe.
I would have never pegged
you as a cheater.
No, I'm not, I mean--
I think we need to go
see Sister Rebecca.
Let's go.
I caught her looking
at the test answers.
Even after I was gonna
give her a second chance.
Zoe, is this true?
Honestly, I didn't mean to.
It was just there and--
And the temptation
was too great.
Remember, lead us not
into temptation,
but deliver us
from the evil one.
Thank you, Sister Sophia.
That'll be all.
Well, I hope that this prompts
immediate suspension,
because quite frankly--
I said, that'll be all.
I am so sorry, Sister Rebecca.
I admit, I did look at the test,
but it was just there.
I couldn't help but see it.
Please, don't let
this affect my record.
Zoe, I know how focused
and driven you are
on your schooling,
but you must stop and think
before you act,
because Sister Sophia is right.
Temptation is everywhere,
and we need the resolve
to overcome it.
Now, Sister Sophia
may seem strict,
but she is very devout
in her ways.
Not really.
Excuse me?
There's just something
different about her.
She's not like
any of the teachers
I've had at this school.
Well, we're all different, Zoe.
And Sister Sophia is
a very well-respected teacher.
She doesn't say
the Morning Prayer.
I don't understand.
She asks someone in the class
to say it, and she doesn't.
Well, whether we mouth
the words or not,
God can still hear us as long
as it's spoken in our hearts.
I want you to pray every night
for the next three nights,
and ask for forgiveness.
I will.
Okay.
Thank you, Sister.
Of course.
Forgive me, Father,
for I have sinned.
It's been, like,
a year since my last confession.
I engaged in fornication...
lust, whatever
you wanna call it.
The problem is,
I know what I did was wrong,
but I can't stop
thinking about it.
It's like a part of me knows
I'm probably going
to Hell for it,
and the other part
doesn't really care.
Is that bad?
Father?
Well, well, well.
Bishop O'Reilly,
always a pleasure.
It looks so beautiful, Sister.
We've been waiting for you.
So how did Sister Sophia fit
into your illustrious staff?
Well, I think--
You know I met her while
I was on a tour of the north.
Really?
It was about 30 below,
and the school
that she was teaching at
had lost the power
to its heating.
Sister Sophia had the children
huddled in a circle
pretending to be penguins
to keep warm.
Really? Hm.
You seem surprised.
It's just, she seems
stricter here,
more aloof.
Well, the Sister Sophia I met
was truly a ray of sunshine.
Huh.
Bishop, why don't you
make yourself
comfortable in the lounge,
and I'll ask her to join us.
Thank you, Sister.
All right.
Sister Sophia?
Sister Sophia!
Where you off to
in such a hurry?
I'm so sorry.
I just got a phone call
that my aunt
has taken a turn for the worse.
I'm on my way to hospice.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Is there anything we can do?
No, it's in God's hands.
Of course--I'm just sorry
you'll miss the chance
to visit with Bishop O'Reilly.
Yes, the Bishop, please,
send him my regards.
Oh, I will.
And we'll both say
a prayer for your aunt.
Thank you, Sister.
* We could fall
* Come crashing down
Here you go, sweetheart.
Don't forget the tomatoes.
You nut.
So, there's a party
at Sara Croft's later.
I was wondering if I could go.
It's probably a better idea if
you stay in, do some studying.
Maybe even look
at some colleges.
Pass the salt, please.
I already told you,
I want to take a year off.
Oh, then maybe
you can explain to me
exactly why we've
invested all this money
the past 17 years sending you
to the finest schools.
I didn't ask you to.
You could have sent me
to public school.
You did it so you could
show off to your friends.
"My kids got into Whittendale."
I got in trouble.
Honey.
Sister Sophia caught me
looking at test answers.
Yes, but Sister Rebecca
understood.
She didn't mean
any harm by it, David.
That's because she's part
of the good flock.
If I did it,
I would have been expelled.
That's not true.
No, Jason's right.
It is absolutely
all about track record.
And people will most assuredly
lose faith in you
if you continue
to make mistakes.
Pass the salad dressing, please.
Thank you.
No one gave you permission
to be excused.
You can chalk it up
on my bad track record.
David.
* I'm stuck on the ground
Wait, Jason.
I'll talk to Dad.
What's the point, Zoe?
He's right--why should
he have any faith in me?
I'm just a screw-up.
Jason, no, don't!
Hey.
You bring your guitar?
Naw.
That's too bad.
I was hoping
you could serenade me.
I'll be back
at St. Adeline's, you know.
My dad's working on it
right now.
So that bitch Sister Sophia
can kiss my ass.
Come on.
Oh, God.
I can't.
What?
Sorry, I got to go.
Jason!
Wait, Jason!
Hey, you!
You got some ID for that?
I'll take that as a no.
Keep your hands
where I can see 'em,
step forward, please.
Stop.
Got anything in your pockets?
I am so, so sorry, Officer.
This is all my fault.
I was left in charge
of watching him.
He has a medical condition.
He's making such great strides.
God willing, and with the good
faith of people like yourself,
we'll get him back
on the right path.
He just needs a chance, please.
All right, Sister.
You just make sure
you get him home safe.
And you, hey, that beer,
it stays here.
God bless you, Officer.
Good luck.
Hey, I can't go
home like this.
I promised my dad
I wouldn't drink
after the accident.
Then let's get you sober.
I've been thinking.
Would it be such a bad thing
if Jason took a year off?
Gosh, he's struggling.
Which is why a structured
environment like college
would be good for him.
Yeah, for some,
like you.
Maybe not for him.
David, he's so lost.
I mean, the boy we raised
wouldn't get in a car
and drive drunk.
So what's happened?
Where did we go wrong?
I'm gonna go look for him.
So, what happened tonight?
Nothing, just my dad.
It was a good thing
I was looking out for you.
Can you get this, please?
I get your frustration, Jason.
My father never really
understood me either.
Thought I was a blight
on the family name.
But that's okay.
We don't need them anymore,
because we have each other.
You were following me.
I had a premonition
that you might need my help.
-Listen, Sister Sophia--
-It's Sophia.
Sophia, what we're doing
is wrong.
No, it's not.
I have money.
I have lots of money.
And I can give you
everything that you need.
I'll take you away.
I'll take you to Paris.
I can be your muse.
You can write beautiful
love songs about me.
And then no one
can keep us apart anymore.
No, I can't do this.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
This is sick.
Jason, don't say that.
I want to be left alone.
This was a big mistake,
and it's over, okay?
Is it her?
Is it that tramp that you went
to go see tonight?
Jason, you've been drinking!
I don't care!
Jason, please don't leave me!
Please, Jason!
Where are you?
Hey, I'm on Riverside.
Look, do you think
you can come pick me up?
Just don't say anything
to Mom and Dad, please.
I can't, Dad took the car.
He's out looking for you.
Hey.
What the heck
are ya doing out here?
Was out with
a couple of the guys
and just wanted
to be alone
to think, you know.
Okay, well,
I can appreciate that.
I've been doing
some thinking myself.
And I've decided...
...you're right,
I've been pushing you
in a direction
probably better suited
for me than for you.
And I'm sorry.
What do you say
we figure out a plan,
one that you're happy with
and one that I can live with
knowing that
you're gonna be okay.
Okay.
Good.
Just for the record,
I haven't lost
faith in you...
and I never will.
Thanks, Dad.
Well, why don't you
head on up to bed
and get some rest.
Come on, pick it up, sweetie.
We are late.
Come on, you can do it.
Come on, Zoe.
I don't want to be late
getting you back to school.
Let's go.
Resist the Devil,
and he will flee from you.
Draw near to God,
and God will draw near to you.
Cleanse your hands,
purify your hearts,
you of two minds.
Begin to lament,
to mourn, to weep.
Let your laughter
be turned into mourning,
your joy into dejection.
Humble yourself
before the Lord,
and He will exalt you
to the highest mountain.
It is only when we stop
listening that we go astray.
Sister Sophia, hey, hey,
Sister Sophia, what did you--?
What did you--?
Hey, hey, wake up.
Wake up, wake up.
Hey, come on.
Oh, my God.
Hey, hey, come here.
Come, come here.
Come here.
Okay, okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I knew you would try to save me.
You do love me.
You were faking that?
After all the horrible
things you said,
I almost thought about
really killing myself.
But I know that
you didn't mean it.
Okay, I'm gonna report you
to Father Macey.
Do it.
Oh, the scandal, Jason.
You would forever be remembered
as the boy
who slept with the nun.
Somehow I doubt
that would go over well
with your father's friends
and colleagues.
See you in class.
Be a good boy.
What?
It was Sister Sophia's car.
The car I saw
this morning, remember?
The car that was parked
down the street.
No, it wasn't,
just leave it alone.
I just checked
the license plate.
Are you trying
to protect her or something?
No, I'm not trying
to protect--
Just stop asking
stupid questions.
It wasn't her car, okay?
No, I'm not gonna stop.
I know when you're
hiding something.
Zoe, okay, okay, look,
you just gotta trust me.
It's not what you think.
I'm dealing with a situation,
and I just need
to figure it out.
Just don't tell
anybody about this,
especially not
Mom and Dad, okay?
Zoe, if you love me, you will
keep your mouth shut, okay?
Okay.
Good.
I'll see you later.
Good morning, class.
Good morning.
Who would like to start
the Morning Prayer?
Jason, why don't you lead us?
Give me, O Lord, I pray Thee...
Firm faith, unwavering hope,
perfect charity.
Pour into my heart the spirit
of wisdom and understanding,
the spirit of counsel
and spiritual strength,
the spirit of knowledge
and true godliness.
Beautifully recited
this morning.
Sister Rebecca.
What do we owe the visit?
Sara will be
rejoining the class.
Sister, how could
she be allowed back?
The decision of expulsion
is up to the board.
And in this case they felt
she had never been
in any serious trouble before.
That is ridiculous.
I thought you taught
values here.
We do,
but Sara's parents
happen to be generous donors
to the school.
The board will not
ignore that fact.
And Sister Sophia,
if we expect our students
to recite prayer,
then we should, too.
So, where'd you run off
to Saturday night?
We were just starting
to have some fun.
Jason, please stay.
Later.
It is impossible
to run away from this,
from us.
I don't want you talking
to that girl.
You can't tell me what to do.
Sara's my friend.
Your friend?
What kind of friend?
None of your business.
It is my business.
You are my business.
I'm not anymore.
Bye.
Hey.
Hey, I'm sorry
about the other night.
I was just nervous.
Can we maybe try again sometime?
Sure.
We'll just have to find a way
to get you to relax.
I know, why don't you play
your guitar for me later?
Okay.
I'll meet you
in the common room.
-I know.
-Told you!
* Traveled miles,
followed heart *
* Lost my way,
found my start *
* Given up,
knowing now *
* My whole family
doesn't get me now *
* All I am is a fire
* I am here to inspire
* What is faith?
* Ohhh
What the hell?
Soap can be so slippery.
Oh, my God!
Help, help, someone help!
Sister Rebecca said
she just slipped
and hit her head
on the tile.
I mean, I've showered
hundreds of times in there.
I just--I can't believe it.
Neither can I.
Jason, have you said
your prayers for Sara?
Please tell me that you
had nothing to do with this.
The police said
it was an accident.
And before you go around
making horrible accusations,
I suggest you take
a hard look in the mirror.
You're the one
who's been committing
all the mortal sins around here.
Me?
What about you?
Let me show you something.
Looks like you're
enjoying yourself.
Whoa, whoa, you recorded us?
I like watching you,
what can I say--here, listen.
No, no, no,
you have to erase that.
Maybe I'll put it online,
or maybe I won't,
if you act nice.
It would ruin you, too.
I'm already ruined,
and I don't care.
Jason, I don't want to quarrel.
I just want to get out of here,
and I want you to come with me.
Please.
I can't wait much longer.
It's just crazy, I mean,
I was talking to her,
like, an hour before, and then
I just find her in the shower.
Come on, come on.
You've been through a lot.
Let's get you guys home.
This has been a week
of great sorrow.
Yes, it has.
Even more so for me.
What do you mean?
My Aunt Francis
passed away this morning.
Lord, have mercy.
I am so sorry.
I'd like to go
to her funeral,
if that's okay with you.
Of course.
You have my blessing.
Thank you, Sister.
So this is nice, huh?
Mr. Brady,
what a pleasure to have you
and your family
dining with us this evening.
Let me bring you out
something special
to get you started with.
Thank you, Morgan.
So, how are you two holding up?
Okay, I guess.
I can't imagine how
that poor girl's family
is doing right now.
Evening--may I help you?
Table for one.
Certainly.
Right this way.
How about you, son,
you all right?
Hello, Jason?
Yeah?
Yeah, I'm okay, I guess.
I do not believe this.
What, sweetheart?
I don't wanna bother you all,
but I'm Sister Sophia.
I'm Zoe and Jason's
homeroom teacher.
Oh, of course.
What a pleasure to meet you.
It's a pleasure
to meet you as well.
Oh, Mr. Brady,
you have quite the reputation
as a chiropractor.
You've done your homework.
You must be quite pleased with
your new position at the school.
I am pleased.
Although this week has proven
to be quite challenging.
Oh, of course.
It's just horrible
what happened.
Indeed.
Well, I should get
back to my table.
It was good seeing you.
I hope that you two find
some comfort this weekend.
Pardon me, are you dining alone
this evening?
Well, yes.
I just came
from my aunt's funeral.
She passed away
earlier this week.
Oh, Sister,
we're so sorry to hear that.
Well, we can't
let you dine alone.
Please, you should join us.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Jason.
No, it's, it's a family dinner.
You understand.
Its, it's a family thing.
Son, don't be rude.
I don't wanna intrude
on family dinner.
Please, we will not
take no for an answer.
In that case, thank you.
Morgan, can we get another
setting here, please?
Oh, of course.
There you are.
That's very kind of you.
Of course.
In case someone calls me.
So where did you teach
before St. Adeline?
I was at a school in Missoula.
Montana?
Is that where you're from?
Born and raised.
I thought you were born
in Billings.
Well, yes, technically.
But Billings is
right next to Missoula, so--
So how do you like Los Angeles?
It's different.
Warmer.
That's for sure.
But I especially
like the people.
They're warmer, too.
Well, I suppose that depends
on where you go.
Missoula is not
next to Billings.
It's over 300 miles away.
In a state as big as Montana,
300 miles away
is right next door.
Can we talk
about something else?
Here we are.
-Oh, look at this.
-Enjoy.
Oh, wow, that looks fantastic.
Thank you, Morgan.
My pleasure.
But, you must have had
a lady there
by the name of Francis.
Please check again.
I just want
the funeral information
so I can send flowers.
I'm sorry, we don't have
anyone here by that name.
But her niece, Sister Sophia,
has been visiting every weekend.
Surely you must know her.
There hasn't been any visitor
by that name either.
Okay, thank you.
Oh my God, Jason.
What's going on?
You have to swear
that you will not say this
to anybody.
I swear.
She, um...
she was flirting with me, right?
And oh, God, I was an idiot.
I let it happen.
You let what happen?
I slept with her, Zoe.
I didn't plan it.
It just happened.
And now it's gotten
way out of hand.
She won't leave me alone.
She wants me to, like,
run away with her
to Paris or something.
God, Jason, you have
to tell someone about this.
No, do you know
what this would do to Mom?
I slept with a nun.
And Dad, are you kidding me?
He'd never forgive me.
Plus, um,
she's got a video of us.
She's threatening to post it
online if I say anything.
You can't let her
get away with this.
You're the victim here.
What do I do?
I don't even think
she's a real nun.
I mean, what kind of nun
acts like this?
I don't even think
she's Sister Sophia.
What do you mean?
She doesn't know
where she was born,
she doesn't know how far
Billings is from Missoula.
Those are things that
the real Sophia would know.
So who is she?
I don't know.
Maybe we just...
take it to the police.
With what? A hunch?
She's a freak
who can't read maps?
Come on.
We're gonna need
more proof than that.
There's a laptop in her room.
Maybe if we could get into it,
we can find the proof we need.
And then what?
Turn the tables on her.
Sister.
You startled me.
A word, in my office.
Why are you lying?
What on Earth do you mean?
Since the day you arrived
there was something about you
I couldn't put my finger on.
And even one of my best students
voiced her concerns.
Of course I dismissed them.
Then, I found out
you were lying about your aunt.
I called the hospital.
There is no Aunt Francis.
My Aunt Francis
went by her first name, Mary.
That's why they don't
have a record of it.
Then why didn't they have
any record of you?
I mean, surely they would have
remembered a nun
coming there
every weekend to visit.
So, now you've lied to me again.
I wonder, Sister Sophia,
what else are you lying about?
It's really weird,
there are no pictures
of Sister Sophia on here,
but there are tons of photos
of this other nun.
Check this out.
She's has another laptop.
I'm not sure where you're
getting your information from,
but I'm not lying.
What are you doing?
Calling St. Val's.
I'm sure they can clear this
all up.
This is ridiculous.
What is St. Val's gonna tell you
that I can't?
Oh, I'm sure
quite a bit.
In fact, I'm sure the dean would
love to have a chat with you.
What's this?
Oh, my God.
She has hundreds
of pictures of you.
Give me the phone.
Give me that phone!
I am going to get the Father.
Sister Rebecca,
I'll tell you the truth.
Laura Patterson?
Is that her real name?
She's not a nun.
You were right, she's been
pretending the whole time.
We gotta show this
to Sister Rebecca now.
Sister Rebecca?
Sister Rebecca.
Hey, it's Sunday.
Let's check the chapel.
Hello?
Sister Rebecca?
What are you doing?
Where's Sister Rebecca?
I don't know.
But she did say that you've been
telling lies about me, Zoe.
I'm lying?
That's hilarious
coming from someone
who isn't even
who she says she is.
You recognize this?
I believe your name is Laura?
Laura Patterson.
You're not even
a real nun, are you?
I knew it.
Come on.
No, it was you, Jason.
You led me here.
You wrote those songs for me.
I didn't write
those songs for you.
I don't even know you.
You know me better than anyone.
Come on, it's time for us to go.
I'm not going
anywhere with you, ever.
You're really sick,
you know that?
Just leave my brother alone.
Don't listen to her.
She's trying to keep us apart.
There is no us,
Sophia, Laura,
whoever the hell you are.
You're just--you're just
some crazy stalker
who deserves to be locked up.
No.
Zoe!
Now we can be together.
I am sick and tired of people
trying to keep us apart.
First that slut Sara,
and now your sister.
Well, I'm done.
This is for us, Jason.
Get out of here!
Jason?
Zoe.
Well, Sister,
if there ever was a year
to test our faith,
this was it.
It most definitely was.
I just thank God
He was looking out
for all of us.
Why don't we all
take a little road trip
out to Whittendale this weekend?
Really?
Yeah, check out your residence,
Zoe, see what you might need.
Yeah, that sounds great.
Why don't you drive,
seeing as your mom's car
is now yours.
For real?
Happy graduation,
honey.
Just be careful.
Got something
for you, too, Jason.
No way.
Well, if you're
gonna be the best,
you got to play
on the best.
Thanks, Dad.
I'm proud of you--
always will be.
Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Well, how does it sound?