[unsettling string music playing]
[distorted bubbling]
[thudding echoes faintly]
-[gasps softly]
-[phone vibrating]
[scoffs]
[vibrating stops]
Laura Blacklock. Coming or going?
[Laura] Good question.
Run it by fact-checking
and let me know, would you?
Great piece on the NGOs. Welcome back.
-[woman 1] Hi, Lo. Love the article.
-Thanks.
-[man] Nice piece. Great work.
-[woman 2] Just read it. It's great.
Thanks.
[under breath] Oh man.
[keyboard clacking]
[intriguing string music playing]
[phone ringing nearby]
[sighs]
Lo, got a minute before editorial?
Yeah, just a sec.
How was your trip back?
Well, the second of my four-hour flights
on an eight-seater turboprop plane
was only one day delayed,
so, you know, I loved every minute of it.
Do I detect the brittle sarcasm
of the severely jet-lagged
or is the malaise something deeper?
[Laura sighs]
They drowned that woman.
Yeah. I know.
[Laura] They killed her.
Just because she agreed to speak to me.
People are capable of appalling things.
You know what? Just sometimes I would like
them not to do appalling things.
I would like to be surprised.
Are we talking about stealing NGO funds
from starving children now
or your checkered romantic history?
Oh. Yes, be serious. Thank you.
[woman] I thought I was.
-Ha!
-[phone vibrating]
God.
Oh, speak of the devil!
-[woman] Which devil is that?
-Go away.
-Two disasters ago.
-[woman] Ooh!
-Ben Morgan?
-Ben Morgan!
-[woman] What does he want?
-No idea.
Probably wants to collect
some of his rare Japanese vinyl
he's got cluttering up my apartment.
-[sighs]
-[Laura] What?
Lo, you didn't have to come
straight back in today.
-[sighs]
-Take some time off.
I'm… I'm not very good at taking time off.
You should ask Ben.
[sighs]
In that case, what's next?
We have an in on that FIFA corruption
story if you're still interested.
Do you know what?
Something has just come in,
which I think might, um…
restore my faith in humanity.
It's Anne Lyngstad, you know?
She's the Norwegian shipping heiress.
She's got stage four leukemia.
And her husband is, uh, setting up
a foundation in her name.
Sounds uplifting.
But here's the fun part.
He wants to take the board members
on his fuck-off big yacht
to, uh, a fundraising gala in Norway.
Wants me to come along,
cover it, raise awareness.
Let me get this straight.
This poor woman gets sick,
and now some billionaires
in her circle have decided
cancer's awful
and they should do something about it.
But only if you go
and tell everyone how great they are.
Yes, pretty much.
But obviously with my journalistic flair.
This is a story how?
Oh, come on.
It's human interest for inhumane times.
[woman] Mm.
You just told me I needed a break.
So long as it is a break.
Not a leave of absence.
I am pretty sure hard-hitting journalism
can survive without me for the week.
[rousing string music playing]
[seagulls calling]
Thank you. Thanks.
[woman 1] Welcome aboard
the Aurora Borealis.
[Laura] What a beautiful boat.
Uh, so, so… your shoes, Miss Blacklock.
-My--?
-Shoes, yep.
Sorry, what have I done?
We keep all of the shoes
in that basket over there.
We can offer you some slippers
or socks or shoes for the gym.
We have your sizes.
So just let us know, okay?
[Laura] Okay. Thanks.
-We all get it wrong first time.
-Yeah.
First time at the rodeo?
I'm not quite up
with the yacht etiquette yet.
I call it yachtiquette, actually.
By the way, I'm Laura. Hello.
-Adam Sutherland.
-[Laura] Nice to meet you.
-[woman 2] Champagne, madam?
-Thank you.
[sighs] Way too early for me.
[giggles] Hello, there. Hi.
Hi, I'm Karla. I'm the chief steward.
You will be in cabin 8
on the starboard side. Fantastic sunrises.
Dr. Mehta, you're in cabin 2,
closest to Miss Lyngstad.
-Thank you.
-[Karla] You're welcome.
-Are you Miss Lyngstad's doctor?
-Well…
I'm an old friend of Richard's, really.
Ever since Anne became ill,
I've, uh, sadly become
a somewhat constant presence
in their lives.
She's fought as hard as anyone could.
-All full of contraband?
-Every one of them.
Excuse me.
-Thomas. Heidi.
-[Thomas] Ah!
-[Heidi] Oh, Robert. You old bastard.
-[Robert chuckling]
Wasn't a complete wash.
[intriguing string music playing]
[Thomas] Looking well.
Lost a bit of weight?
[Robert] It's the stress.
[camera shutter clicking]
Of all the superyachts
on all the cruises in all the world.
[Laura] Ben Morgan.
-Oh, I don't believe it. Jesus.
-[Ben] I did try calling you.
Why am I not surprised to see you here?
-Of course! Benjamin. Sh… Uh, this is, um…
-[Ben] Lo and I already know each other.
Oh! Journo circles.
You guys worked together before?
[chuckling] No.
No, you've done something else
together before, haven't you?
Let me know if you need me
to engage a deckhand
to prevent a repeat performance.
[Laura] Won't be necessary. Thank you.
-It ended a while ago.
-Okay.
-Okay, well, I hope it ended amicably.
-Something like that.
That's a no. That's a no. I've…
I've touched a nerve. I do feel awkward.
I might… If you guys--
-I'm gonna…
-Yeah, okay, probably better.
Why is she in jeans?
I feel like there was a dress code, no?
[uneasy string music playing]
That's the first time I've heard you refer
to our shared history as amicable.
It's the first time I've thought about
our shared history at all to be honest.
Ouch.
One-nil?
Two-nil.
Okay, I'll take that. I'll take that.
Mr. Tyler, Mr. Jensen.
[uneasy string music continues]
And the Heatherleys, and Miss Blacklock.
Ladies and gentlemen, our lovely stewards
will now lead you to your rooms.
Mr. Bullmer will join you
for welcome drinks later.
Laura, have you met Dame Heatherley?
Runs a gallery for the rich and famous.
She used to be in Mayfair.
Now she's decided to migrate east
in search of… [inhales sharply]
…some sort of, um… zeitier-geist, I guess.
-Why did you do that?
-So, so desperately funny, Adam.
Laura is going to be spying on us
dans ze voyage.
Oh, right. So you're Bullmer's journo, eh?
Yeah, Laura. Lo.
Nice to meet you, Dame Heatherley.
Oh, stop it.
Please, would you just call me Heidi?
Uh, my colleague actually
went to see your exhibition.
-She said it was magnificent.
-Oh, it is.
The artist films herself
succumbing to Rohypnol,
then getting dressed and undressed.
Then being put
in various different postures
out in public
over eight hours by her assistants.
Jaw-dropping.
-It sounds…
-Horrendous.
-Even for me. I mean, that is…
-[Heidi] Tommo, you big lug.
Come and meet Richie's hackette.
-A journo!
-Mm.
Any good? You know, I've been thinking
about writing my memoirs.
-Ooh, the world awaits with bated breath.
-[Thomas chuckles]
[woman] Oh, I'm sorry, Miss Blacklock.
The rest of your luggage
should've been brought down.
Oh, no. That's it.
Oh, uh, would you like me
to unpack for you?
God, no, no.
Um… I wouldn't subject you to the chaos.
[rousing string music playing]
[deep clanking]
All right, boys.
Let's fire it up. Let's go.
[ship horn honks]
[woman coughing]
[glass clinking]
[Richard] Friends…
-[woman] That's him.
-Romans.
Board members.
[Heidi] Oh, there we go!
I welcome you to the Aurora Borealis.
[guests] Aurora Borealis!
When we commissioned her,
Anne and I imagined a different future
than the one that has come about.
-Yes.
-[Richard] There's no sugarcoating it.
-Yeah.
-[Richard] That fight has taken its toll.
[inhales deeply]
Anyway, we've…
We've rethought the purpose
of this humble barge,
and, uh… [chuckles]
…and you're here
to inaugurate our project.
We are.
Now, I know this is
an unusual approach to charity,
three days on a luxury yacht,
but the money all of you have donated,
which is a considerable amount,
will go to those in society
who cannot afford private doctors
or experimental treatments.
So here's to you.
-To you.
-Hear, hear.
-[man] To you.
[Richard] Now, I know
most of you are here to meet Anne,
but I'm sorry to say after a long day
of travelling, she's… she's resting.
-So I propose…
-Yes.
…a light supper, an early night,
and a big day of celebration
with Anne tomorrow.
-[Thomas] Oh yes.
-[Heidi] Perfect.
-What do you think?
-[woman] Wonderful.
Mm.
But first,
a nice surprise.
-Come and meet Danny.
-[Heidi] No, it's not…
[rock music blaring from boat]
Danny Tyler.
I didn't think he was still alive.
-Just about.
-Not for want of trying.
Danny!
That's amazing.
-Laura Blacklock.
-Hi.
I'm Richard.
-So pleased to have you with us.
-Thank you very much.
If you're in luck, Tommy,
he'll have brought his Viagra.
[Thomas] Oh, I never use it.
There you go. Thank you.
-Bullmer, you old scoundrel.
-[Richard chuckles]
How are you, brother?
-All the better for seeing you.
-How's Anne doing?
She's all right.
-Welcome aboard.
-[Danny] Thank you.
Wow.
Who are you?
Uh, Laura's an award-winning journalist.
She's doing a piece on the foundation.
Shame.
Last thing I need's a fly on the wall.
Thank you.
My mother's a big fan, by the way.
-[Danny] Ouch.
-[Thomas laughs]
I like you.
-Now, the big question is, Richard…
-Mm-hmm.
…are we currently in international waters?
'Cause I've got a bag full of drugs
I'd like to share
with these beautiful people.
Not sure I can pay
for another round of rehab--
No, I'm joking, man.
I've been clean and serene since 1917.
[Heidi cackles]
[sighs] Still so hot.
Are you, like, uh,
you know, deep undercover?
Bugger off.
Come on, surely after all
your pontificating about me selling out,
it cannot be that Laura Blacklock is
just here for the money.
There he is.
There's the Ben I remember.
[Laura] I figured out why Ben was calling.
And? How did it go?
-Good surprise or bad?
-[Laura chuckles]
No comment.
Tell me you're not enjoying it a bit.
The champagne is quite good.
[woman] Come on.
You said this was a break. Enjoy yourself.
[Ben] …only together
for nine months, less even.
That's weird.
She doesn't seem like your type.
Come on. That is flattering as hell.
Look at her.
[woman] She's pretty but… a bit boring.
[water trickling]
[Laura exhales heavily]
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
[uneasy music playing]
Mm… [chuckles nervously]
Sorry!
-[indistinct chatter]
-[enchanting string music playing]
[Adam] Oh yeah? You'd better introduce me.
Oh wow.
[Thomas chuckles]
[woman 1] What a beautiful dress.
Is there an alfresco opera later?
Sorry. I thought you…
-Bit overdressed. Sorry.
-[Adam] No.
Not at all, love.
You are rockin' that glitter ball.
-[Adam] Do I detect a little jealousy?
-[Richard] You look lovely.
You look great.
-I thought you dressed for dinner and…
-[Ben] It's fine.
Shiny.
[strings grow frenetic]
[indistinct lively chatter]
[guests chuckling]
[woman 2] Miss Blacklock,
if after dinner
you could meet Mrs. Lyngstad,
she'd very much appreciate it.
-Oh yeah. Yeah, sure.
-Thank you.
[strings fade out]
I'm Sigrid.
I'm Mr. Bullmer's head of security.
How long have you worked for the family?
[Sigrid] This is my first year.
-Right here.
-Thanks.
If you just… wait here,
Miss Lyngstad will join you shortly.
[sighs] The library.
[chuckles] The one thing on the boat
I insisted on designing myself.
-Miss Lyngstad, thank you for inviting me.
-Call me Anne, please.
I'm so glad you agreed to come.
I follow your work.
Your Guardian exposé on those brave
Kurdish women really stuck with me.
I'm the one who asked for you.
It's important work you do,
giving a voice to the voiceless.
-Thank you.
-[Anne coughs]
Shall I get the doctor?
I… [catches breath]
[exhales deeply]
I… I've stopped all my medication.
My pills, the transfusions.
All of it.
One day I just… couldn't anymore.
[grunts weakly]
It becomes too consuming being a patient.
Without all the drugs
you can really feel it.
Time escaping you.
I'm sorry.
I… I was wondering if I could get
your opinion on something.
Of course.
[Anne] My speech for the gala.
I'd be grateful if you could go over it.
My mind is not what it once was.
[Laura] Yeah.
[delicate string music playing]
You're giving all your money away?
That's very generous. Um…
What brought that on, may I ask?
It's about settling up.
Putting back in what you've taken out.
And over the years we've taken so much.
The foundation will be handed over
to people far smarter
and far kinder
than Richard or I ever were.
[chuckles softly]
Well, it's… it's charity without the ego.
Hard to be egotistical
when you're worm food.
[Anne exhales deeply]
I'd like to continue this tomorrow.
Here perhaps?
I'm happy to help in any way I can.
[Anne] And Laura?
Thank you.
[Laura] Mm.
[door clicks open]
Hey, shining lady.
You working the late shift?
I could bail if you have
something more fun in mind.
[Laura groans]
I try not to make the same mistake twice.
-Ouch.
-[chuckles softly]
You were a very good mistake though.
-Yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
-Very good?
-Mm.
For me and God knows how many others.
[chuckles]
Oh.
[Ben sighs]
It's okay.
-I'm sorry I was a dick in the end.
-You were a dick in the end.
-I know.
-Mm.
Apology accepted.
[water sloshing]
[ominous strings intensify]
[music fades]
[gurgling scream]
[deep rumbling]
-[muffled screaming]
-[thudding]
[audio distorts, intensifies]
-[grunting]
-[glass shattering]
[Laura gasps]
[tense, muffled voices]
[unsettling string music playing]
-[woman whimpers]
-[man grunts]
-[woman yelps]
-[thudding]
[man shouting]
[thudding continues]
[grunting grows louder]
[waves sloshing]
[heavy splash]
[Laura panting]
[music darkens]
[gasps]
[vibrating]
[woman] Just stay right there.
It's cabin 8.
She says there's someone in the water.
What? Code Oscar. Code Oscar.
Someone's gone overboard.
[alarm blaring]
Possible M.O.B., starboard side, cabin 10.
10? Reduce speed, switch to manual.
Man overboard. Man overboard.
All crew to muster.
Mayday, this is the Aurora Borealis,
requesting urgent assistance.
-[Karla] I haven't woken the passengers.
-[Captain] She's in 8, right?
-[Karla] She is.
-All right.
-I'll leave you to it.
-Thank you.
I heard a splash, went out to the balcony,
and saw somebody in the water.
-We're coming about. We'll find them.
-Who did you see?
Um, I… I don't know.
It was only for a second.
I assume it's the woman next door,
from the cabin there.
-From cabin 10?
-[Laura] Yeah.
What's going on?
We've received a report
of a guest falling overboard.
What? Who?
I… I don't know.
I think it was a woman, but I don't know.
[Danny] Enter.
Man overboard?
What's happening?
Where's Lars?
Uh, he's in cabin 6.
-Do you know where he is?
-Missing guest from cabin 6.
Lars Jensen. All--
Ooh, ooh, Miss Blacklock.
I have got this under control.
If you could--
Somebody's missing. We have to find them.
What, they're missing?
Sweetheart, have you heard that…
She's not here. I was asleep.
I didn't hear her come back to bed.
You don't think…?
[snoring]
Oh my God.
[man on radio] We've located Mr. Jensen.
[man] Mr. Jensen?
Yes?
So who called the M.O.B.?
Laura Blacklock, the journalist.
-And she said it was from cabin 10?
-Yes, sir. That's what's so unusual.
[Richard] Don't worry.
Try to sleep. I'll take care of it.
There was a woman.
She was… [sighs] She was about my height.
She had blonde hair. She had a hoodie on.
She's coming out of the shower.
I was… She…
I came in accidentally.
I was in the corridor, backing in--
There was never a guest staying in here,
Miss Blacklock.
This… This cabin was always empty.
The guest who was supposed
to be in it cancelled two days ago.
-Sh…
-Yes. That's right.
There was blood on the glass.
There was blood out here. There…
[unsettling music intensifies]
There was… There was somebody
on this balcony. There wa…
Wait. No, there was somebody
on the balcony. I can prove it.
The… The boat was moving,
and she was smoking outside,
so I picked up the cigarette…
-What? They're not here.
-The cabins are serviced twice a day, so…
Uh… Look, listen, I am…
-[trash can thuds]
-I'm not imagining this.
[man on radio] Headcount complete.
Uh, thank you. Call the coast guard.
Cancel the mayday.
The coast guard.
You called the coast guard?
-[Captain] Of course.
-They'll continue searching?
We've conducted our search, ma'am.
Everyone's accounted for.
There… Someone is out there.
They could still be alive.
I think it's time for everyone
to go back to sleep. It's… rather late.
[Captain] Night, Miss Blacklock.
-Uh… You ca… You…
-I'm very sorry, Miss Blacklock.
No. Listen. Listen. This is just…
[Captain] Reminder to all crew
that cabin 10 is out of bounds
until we reach port in Norway.
[man on radio] Copy that.
Um, Miss Blacklock, sorry.
Are you sure you're going to be all right?
Can I get you some tea or…?
No? Okay. Just… sleep well.
[scoffs]
[panting]
[music darkens]
[music fades out]
[knocking]
-Hello?
-[door opens]
-[woman] You buzzed?
-Uh…
Yeah, I can't get any internet connection.
Oh, I'm so sorry, Miss Blacklock.
But the system's on the fritz.
The techs are looking into it.
-I can get you some reading materials.
-[sighs] No. It's fine, thank you.
-[woman] Okay.
-[door closes]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[laughing]
-Mr. Bullmer?
-Oh, please. Call me Richard.
Um, the woman
I saw last night in cabin 10.
Mm.
Nothing to be embarrassed about.
You were convinced what you saw was real.
-It was real.
-Oh.
Um, I would like to see the crew.
If one of them is the woman--
Think one of my staff were having
a cheeky shower in cabin 10
when guests were arriving?
The guests are accounted for.
Who else could it have been?
You're right. Let's meet the crew.
[deep thrum of waves]
[Richard]
So, excepting our CTO and captain,
who are naturally at their stations
while we're under sail, this is our crew.
-I'm sorry for the inconvenience--
-See anyone you recognize?
[uneasy string music playing]
I understand the journalistic instinct.
-The CTO?
-[Richard] He's a man.
You're looking for a woman, right?
[music fades out]
-[Laura] I hope they didn't wake you.
-No. I was able to get back to sleep.
Um, is now a good time to, uh…
continue our conversation from yesterday?
Oh, I'm…
I'm feeling a bit too weak,
to be honest. It's…
all this medication.
It really takes it out of me.
I think I need to rest for tonight.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I hope you feel better.
[sighs]
[Laura] Oh my God.
They all think I'm crazy.
No, come on. No one likes being woken up
in the night. They'll get over it.
-I know what I saw.
-It was dark.
No, it wasn't. It wasn't dark
when I saw her in cabin 10. I saw her.
She came out of the shower.
We looked straight at each other.
We even spoke. She spoke.
And now what? She's just disappeared.
What were you doing
in someone else's cabin?
-[Laura] I was avoiding you.
-Huh?
You were showing Grace your photographs
in the hallway, and I just…
[Ben chuckles]
-[keyboard clacking]
-Wait.
-You've been taking photos. Give me that.
-Yeah.
Hey, excuse me.
-When we arrived?
-[Ben] Yeah.
If there is a picture of her arriving,
then nobody can deny she exists.
I have to take photos of everyone.
It is what it is.
Huh.
-[Ben] Those are not from the boat--
-Wait. Wow.
You really… You spend
a lot of time with these people.
[intriguing string music playing]
[gasps] Oh my God. That's her.
That's her. That's the woman I saw.
-That is her.
-[Ben] Lo…
[exhales loudly]
Lo, this is a photograph of a stranger,
taken at a party months ago.
-Lo, wait. Hey!
-[camera clicks]
[Ben] Whoa, hey. Slow down.
Let's just discuss the approach.
[Laura] I've found her.
The woman in cabin 10.
That's her.
-What photo is this?
-[Ben] Uh, it's from May, I think.
-The thing Adam threw at the Groucho.
-Oh yeah. That was a fun one.
I'm sorry. This is a picture of…
a woman who looks like the woman
you say you saw in cabin 10?
No, that is the woman I saw
at a party thrown by one of your guests.
Right.
Who is she?
Adam, do you know?
I don't know. What?
[Adam groans]
No. Never seen her before.
You're in a photograph with her.
Okay. Well…
I don't know.
Dozens of women look like that.
Most women… all women. She's just a woman.
Adam does seem to surround himself
with a certain type.
-[Richard chuckles]
-[Adam] Thank you, Tommo.
Nobody asked your opinion.
You know what?
Uh… [smacks lips]
[tauntingly] Lo.
Laura.
I have no idea who this person is.
-All right?
-[laptop snaps closed]
Laura, I'm sure what you experienced
yesterday was very traumatic for you.
But am I right in thinking
that it was only a couple of months ago
you witnessed a murder?
-[Laura yells] Elena!
-[indistinct shouting]
[loud, distorted rumbling]
Um… Sorry, um…
How'd you know about that?
[uneasy string music playing]
Rowan told me what happened
to that woman you interviewed.
-Why would you tell them?
-I was worried about you, Lo.
It's not uncommon for images to resurface,
especially in those minutes
between sleep and wake.
-[Grace] Poor thing.
-[Danny] You just gotta go with it, girl.
I've always got little people dancing
on the edge of my vision.
It's kind of beautiful.
God, I don't believe this.
[Grace] Don't be embarrassed, babe.
It's fine.
[Heidi] Adam. Tell the truth.
Did you bring a stowaway on board?
-[Adam] Yeah, I was going to but then…
-[audio distorts]
[exhales heavily]
Laura, if it's any help,
I can have Sigrid try and track down
this woman in the photograph.
But I must ask you to be mindful
of what this journey is.
For me, for my wife,
and my guests.
Look, I… I think it's important
that you can feel relaxed here.
Sig!
Can we book Miss Blacklock in at the spa?
Just something soothing.
-I think that might be…
-[Sigrid] Sure.
…might be helpful. Yeah?
[woman] This is a mixture of volcanic ash,
subarctic peat, and natural oils.
When you shower,
they'll be activated by the heat.
It soothes the muscles,
relieves tension.
-[gurgling scream]
-[Laura gasps]
[catches breath]
[grunting softly]
[haunting music playing]
[footsteps treading]
[gasps]
[music intensifies]
-[woman] Is everything okay?
-Who was in this room?
-When?
-What? Just now.
Just w-w-when I was in the shower.
Was it you?
I had to send towels to the laundry.
Did something happen?
-Did you write something?
-Oh, hey.
Mm. Muddy. [chuckles]
Were you in my room?
-Excuse me, in your room?
-The treatment room.
[scoffs]
Uh, no, I just got out the sauna,
and I was planning on going for a massage.
If that's okay.
You're obsessed with me,
aren't you? [sucks teeth]
[menacing music playing]
-I need to look at the CCTV.
-What would you like to see?
The spa. Um, anyone who came in or out
in the last 20 minutes.
Sorry, but we turn off CCTV everywhere
when guests are on board.
-Sorry? The cameras are off?
-[Captain] Yeah.
Who ordered that?
It's quite normal on a boat
with so many high-profile guests.
-They find it easier to relax if--
-They know they aren't being watched.
[water trickling]
[breathing heavily]
[gasps]
-[indistinct voices]
-Shit.
[sighs]
[menacing music intensifies]
Oh shit.
[whimpers]
[panting] Oh my God.
[exhales deeply]
They said nobody has been
in that cabin, right?
This is the maiden voyage.
If no one was in that cabin,
whose hair is this?
[inhales deeply, sighs]
Whoever's hair this is,
they went overboard.
I get it. You may not like these people--
Listen, I am… I am not having
a some sort of post-traumatic episode.
-I am… I am not imagining things.
-No, I'm not trying to say you are, Lo.
I'm saying
you don't need to be the one who fixes it.
[sighs sharply] Look.
For the next, what, 36 hours,
we're stuck on board.
If Nilssen doesn't find the girl
and you still feel like this when we dock,
I'll go with you to the police to report
a missing woman with that hair you have.
But pushing this further now
is not helping your situation.
[Ben] These people run the world.
Or the very least have lunch dates
with the ones who do.
If you piss them off…
[ominous music playing]
[Grace] You've had quite a day.
How are you doing?
Come here. Help me with this.
[Laura] So how did, uh, you and Lars meet?
His board were getting concerned that
the whole incel Caesar vibe was passé.
They thought a weekend away with me,
glimpsed on my socials,
might convince shareholders
they're being led
by the right type of red-blooded alpha.
-Wait, so you're not actually to--
-[Grace] Absolutely not. Purely optics.
To be honest,
I don't think he likes women.
It's kind of creepy.
Do you want a selfie? No charge.
Come on. Boost your socials.
-Ready?
-[camera clicks]
Cute.
You know, I really admire what you do.
I think I could've been a journalist,
if I hadn't been so…
[clicks tongue] …you know.
[unsettling string music playing]
[Richard] The thing is
the sum is the problem.
[guests chatter indistinctly]
[Heidi] So you're allowed to drink
on the job, are you?
Well, good for you.
You know, back in the 90s, I worked
for this fabulous gallery in Mayfair.
Lunch was an absolute
duel to the death by martini.
Do you often sleep in the bathtub?
-Only when we've had a brawl.
-[Laura] Huh.
What are the brawls about?
Honestly, neither of us
can ever remember in the morning.
-And there's rarely any bruises, so…
-[Thomas] And if there are…
they're mine.
[both chuckle]
Oh, can I fix your collar, babe?
[hushed] I really wouldn't pry too much.
You don't want to get
on the bad side of them. Especially her.
[unsettling string music intensifies]
[guests laughing]
-[Lars] You okay?
-[music halts]
[Laura] Yeah, I'm fine.
How do you know Richard and Anne?
I'm also rich.
Yeah, I, um…
I built this tech company.
Richard was, uh,
correctly impressed and invested.
AI and facial recognition.
-[clears throat]
-[glass clinking]
[Richard] I'm sure most of you know
the story behind all this, that, uh…
I wanted to give Anne
a reason to keep fighting.
To make something so beautiful and…
that she would feel the same way I do.
That it… That it would've been a sin to…
to leave this world without…
without setting foot on a…
[sighs]
I'm so proud of you, my darling.
And I'm just… [breathing shakily]
I'm just so thankful that…
Sorry. [clearing throat, sniffling]
[Anne] Thank you all for being here.
I don't… really know what to say. I just…
I just…
-Oh, my darling.
-[Grace] So sad.
[Richard] That's okay.
You all right?
[Anne] Sorry.
-Please enjoy your dinner. Cheers.
-[awkward chuckling]
-[Heidi] To you, my darling.
-[Adam] Cheers.
♪ To the stars, my love ♪
♪ To the sea ♪
-♪ Till the wheels, my love ♪
-[whooping]
♪ Till they roll over me ♪
[cheering]
-[Thomas] Love it.
-Thank you.
Darling Anne,
you know, your beautiful soul
is gonna burn brightly forever, my love.
Do you remember that duet we did
in Amalfi all those years ago?
-Yes.
-[Danny] Right?
I… I feel really tired.
Of course.
-I think I… I have to go to bed.
-[Grace] Oh no.
-I'll help you.
-It's okay.
-[guitar plays]
-[Heidi] Sleep well, my love.
[Danny] I will serenade you to sleep,
my dear.
[sighs happily]
That's the one. I remember now.
-[Richard] Yeah, beautiful.
-Thank you, Danny.
♪ How'd you like the sound
Of those four-letter words ♪
♪ They make you look so clever ♪
♪ As I fall to the Earth ♪
♪ I wanna walk through the mud
And I've not seen the night ♪
♪ I wanna hold onto you, darling
And make you feel all right ♪
-[unsettling string music builds]
-♪ If I could just draw… ♪
[Richard] A pod of whales
not far from here.
[Grace] Doctor,
sure you don't want to join?
I'm gonna stay with my patient.
[Grace] Aw.
Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye!
[engine rumbles]
[cheering]
[unsettling string music continues]
[voices shouting in distance]
-[clattering]
-[sizzling]
Miss Blacklock.
Is everything okay? Did you get lost?
Um, actually, I was, um…
I was hoping to talk to some of the crew.
Okay. [chuckles nervously]
Um… Look.
Have any of you guys seen
this woman on board?
No.
Okay. Any chance you could take a photo
and show it to the rest of the crew?
Um, and one more question.
-[chuckles nervously]
-[camera clicks]
How easy would it be to smuggle someone
on board without the crew seeing?
Um…
I don't think the owners would be happy
for us to be talking to you about that.
Whale watching wasn't for you?
I'm not very good with the cold.
That's the… crew staircase, isn't it?
Yeah, um, I… [chuckles]
…uh, just wanted to see
the rest of the yacht.
[Laura chuckles nervously]
Must be getting back to Anne.
Enjoy the peace and quiet while it lasts.
[Laura] No, no, no.
[whooping]
[deep thrum of waves]
[Grace giggling]
You're not a real photographer.
[Ben] I'm distracted.
This is the effect you're having on me.
-[camera clicking]
-I'm just a guy trying to do his job.
Maybe we can take some later.
-I have another outfit.
-[Ben] I'll bring both my cameras.
-Want another drink?
-Sure. I'll come with you.
[chatter continues faintly]
[unsettling string music playing]
[Grace] They have people
that do that for us.
-[thud]
-[Laura yells]
-[button clicks]
-[music intensifies]
Think about
all the things of God's bounty.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[Heidi] Take him out for dinner first.
[muffled screaming]
I remember you…
-Oh my God!
-What?
-What's the matter?
-Help her!
Help her! She's bleeding.
Help her!
[high-pitched ringing]
[muffled] Hey. Look at me.
-Miss Blacklock.
-[Ben] Lo, it's okay.
We're just… [distinctly] …trying
to understand what happened.
I already told you what happened.
Somebody pushed me in.
You must have seen--
I went back to the bridge
just after I saw you.
But you were alone, Miss Blacklock.
Somebody on board is trying to kill me.
-[Richard] Laura.
-To silence me.
[Richard] I can imagine
what you've been through.
But I'm sure you were
the only person on that deck.
[Laura] I didn't fall in. I didn't.
Listen,
the cover didn't just close by itself.
My dear. Why would you be targeted?
[ominous string music playing]
You've lost a button.
Were you in my room?
[chuckling] No, I wasn't.
-My God, you were in my room.
-Lo, slow down.
My God, uh…
-Where's my stuff?
-[Richard] What stuff?
Where's my stuff? My… you know, my stuff.
The clothes I was wearing, my coat.
Your clothes were taken
to the laundry room.
[churning, rattling]
[man] Uh… What are you doing?
-Ma'am?
-It's okay. Just leave her be.
-Okay.
-Miss, we've put your belongings here.
We tried to dry the phone out but…
There was a… There was a ziplock bag.
It was in the coat pocket.
This is all we found.
[sighs]
Of course it is.
-[Ben] There you are.
-[Laura] No. You stay away from me.
-Lo, come on. Look, come here.
-No, don't…
What the hell is wrong with you?
Whoever did this to me
went through my jacket.
The hair was in my jacket.
What? You think I had
something to do with this?
Only you knew about the hair. Only you.
I'm sorry.
Okay? I… I told the others about it.
That you… you had some evidence.
They think you're nuts, Lo.
I was defending you, okay?
Stop helping.
Danny, seriously, come on.
What… What about the gala?
The girl tried to drown herself, yeah?
What's she gonna do next?
I'm asking her to disembark.
You could've had a body
on this boat, yeah? A body!
-I cannot afford any more scandal.
-Please--
-You know that.
-Just reconsider.
Something just don't feel right.
I've gotta go. I'm sorry. Okay?
[Richard] Anne's a fan. Apparently,
she used to be a good journalist.
-[Thomas] The woman's a damn nuisance.
-She's an absolute nut job.
Do we know any other rock stars
with spare time on their hands?
[Heidi] Oh! Well done. Fruit loop.
No, really, well done.
What? Wait.
You don't think that's suspicious?
I get pushed in the pool
and he just leaves?
He was scared of what you'd do next.
-[laughing] Okay.
-[Heidi] Like the rest of us, frankly.
[Thomas] Did you seriously think
Danny could've pushed someone?
-[Heidi scoffs]
-Maybe.
-And who else? Think I could've done it?
-Yeah, could I?
Neither of you can account for when
the other one came back into the cabin.
Oh! This is genuine… No, you are
genuinely next-level stark raving mad.
[Adam squirms angrily]
There was no body in the water, Lo.
There wasn't a body there.
You were asleep.
You were walking around, dreaming,
and your addled, attention-starved brain
just made the whole thing up.
So drop it.
Please, God.
You are a bit of a downer, Lo.
It's kind of toxic.
[unsettling string music playing]
-[deep thud]
-[gasps]
[wind howling eerily]
[breathing deeply]
[knocking]
-[knocking]
-[gasps]
[breathing shakily]
[tense music swells]
Wait! Oh my God.
-[loud clattering thud]
-[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[deep rumble]
[machinery buzzing]
[Laura] No, wait!
[doors slamming]
[tense music builds]
-[music stops]
-[Laura breathing shakily]
[door creaking]
[unsettling music playing]
Who are you?
-I saw you drown.
-[woman] No, you didn't.
Look, you've seen me now.
I'm alive. Now just drop this.
-I warned you.
-You wrote the message in the mirror?
-Why did you push me in the pool?
-That wasn't me.
-Who took the hair out of my jacket?
-[woman] Stop!
-He'll kill you. You need to stop!
-Who are you talking about?
-What is going on? Who went overboard?
-Stop! He will kill you.
-[Laura] Oh my G…
-[breathing heavily]
Anne?
[yells] Why?
[heavy thud]
[Anne gasps softly]
[grunting]
[lock clanks]
[wind whistling eerily]
[dark string music playing]
[Laura gasps, whimpers]
[grunting, panting]
[yells] Help!
[dark string music continues]
[Anne] Without all the drugs
you can… you can really feel it.
All this medication.
It really takes it out of me.
That's the one. I remember now.
I'd like to continue this tomorrow.
[breath trembling]
-[deep scraping]
-[thud]
[footsteps treading]
Who are you?
I know that you're not Anne.
You didn't know that Anne had stopped
taking her medication.
You forgot we had
an appointment to talk the next day.
It was Anne who went overboard, wasn't it?
And you've been pretending
to be her ever since.
It was never part of the plan.
Whose voice was it
that I heard in the room that night?
[breathes deeply]
It was…
Oh my God. I've been so stupid.
It was Bullmer, wasn't it? It was…
He knew that, uh, that…
that Anne was disinheriting him.
I didn't think he was going to kill her.
[eerie piano music swells]
[woman] I was only meant to pretend
to be Anne for one day.
To meet with some lawyers. Sign a will.
He just said it would be like acting.
-Have a play and tell me what you think.
-Yeah.
[woman] There's this software.
Some kind of facial recognition.
He approached me over Facebook.
[beeping]
[woman] He invited me to this party
in London. Paid for everything.
I've never been offered so much money.
[Richard] You need to be comfortable
with me in order for this to work.
[door clicks open]
Richard?
What? What is this?
[dramatic music intensifies]
-[Richard] Uh…
-Who are you?
-Why does she…? You're crazy.
-Anne, calm down.
-[Anne] Completely crazy.
-Calm down.
Shut up. Listen, just…
[faintly] Fucking shut up. Shut up!
A pathetic annuity?
That's all you were gonna leave me?
-[fleshy thud]
-[woman yelps]
What?
[panting]
[woman whimpering]
You…
Everything's okay.
Anne.
[woman] I would never have agreed to it.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Not that.
[woman gasps]
[heavy splash]
[woman] I should have stopped him.
[breathing sharply]
[alarm blaring]
[sighing]
[sobbing] I just… I never imagined
it would end like this.
You don't know where I come from.
What it's like to have nothing.
Nothing to give the ones
who depend on you.
My daughter is everything to me.
What's your name?
Carrie.
[Laura] Okay, Carrie. Listen to me.
Will you listen to me, Carrie?
He is using you.
You think he's going to let you walk away
after you sign those contracts?
You have seen him kill someone.
He's not going to leave
a loose end lying around.
They've already tried to kill me.
We have to work together.
I need to go back upstairs.
[door opens, slams]
[inhales deeply]
[faint chatter, laughter]
-Oh. Anne.
-[camera shutter clicking]
Anne.
Where have you been, my darling?
[mutters]
You almost missed the whole show.
I'm sorry.
[Richard breathes deeply]
Anne and I would like to say
thank you once again for…
being here with us in this special time.
I love you, darling.
It's been the greatest privilege for me,
spending my life with you.
Well, if we can't take the Aurora
to the Northern Lights,
we'll bring them here to us.
-[firework squeals]
-[cheering, clapping]
[wistful string music playing]
-That's more like it!
-That's amazing!
-[fireworks popping faintly]
-[gasps]
-Impressed. I am impressed.
-Come, come, come.
[exhaling deeply]
I love you so much.
[Robert] Oh. Hello there.
Just checking on the patient.
I'd let her sleep.
She's had an emotional couple of days.
Right.
Hey, Lo?
Uh… [clicks tongue]
I'm here if you need me.
[dark string music playing]
[Richard] She can't bloody disappear.
We're at sea. There's nowhere to go.
The captain and I will keep looking.
[Richard] When you find her,
get rid of her.
Yeah?
I'm done.
I can't. This is not what we discussed.
[Richard] Nothing has happened the way
we discussed. That's the whole point.
Anne was one thing.
I mean, giving an overdose
to a woman that's already dying,
but this is cold-blooded murder.
Do I need to remind you
where we were three years ago?
With you bawling your eyes out,
begging for my help.
Don't think I'm stupid enough to believe
that was the only woman you did that to?
Richard, please.
How many others would've come out
of the woodwork had I not buried it?
You wouldn't have just been struck off.
You would've spent
your fucking life in prison.
Look, I appreciate
everything that you have done.
I know, but we're not forgetting
our arrangement, are we?
No.
[inhales deeply]
I'll take care of her.
Thanks, Robert.
[breathing heavily]
[Richard exhales slowly]
You have to go to the police. You have
to tell them everything that you told me.
I can't. They'll arrest me too.
I'm an accomplice.
Someone got killed.
They'll take my daughter away from me.
I just need to sign what he wants me
to sign and turn up at that gala.
You really think
that he's going to let you go alive?
Carrie, he'll get rid of you.
You know that.
Do they know that I'm down here?
They don't know where you are,
but they're looking.
How long before we dock?
About two hours. I'll leave the door open.
-It gives you a chance.
-Look, Carrie.
Nothing's going to happen
until you've signed that will.
Bullmer needs you alive.
But after you've done what he wants,
you're in danger.
[inhales sharply]
I'm going to get to you.
I promise.
[exhales deeply]
[tense music playing]
[Captain] All crew, all crew,
30 minute warning.
We are dropping anchor in 30 minutes.
[deep clanking]
-[Adam] Hey, Lars, Lars.
-Oh yeah.
Did you…
By the way, did you download my album?
I feel like saying, "Three times,
Karla, is probably too many."
[door thuds]
-[Robert] This is the last room.
-[man] It is, sir.
Oh, Mr… Mr. Morgan, Dr. Mehta has asked
that we allow her to rest.
Apparently she was in a state last night.
He's given her sedatives.
-Just let her know I stopped by, okay?
-Of course.
Thank you.
[Karla] Mm.
[tense string music continues]
-[Richard] Ah, Ben.
-Hey.
Thank you so much
for your presence these past few days.
Yeah.
Can't wait to see
what you snap at the gala.
[Ben] Sure. I, uh…
I'm worried about Lo.
[Richard] Yeah, yeah, me too.
Well, she couldn't be
in better hands though.
Money couldn't buy
a better doctor, trust me.
He's agreed to stay with her
until she's well enough to join us later.
Uh… Stopped a little short, no?
Well, shallow water means
we can't stop any closer.
The only downside to having
such a large boat.
[Captain] All passengers, all passengers.
-Transport is leaving in five minutes.
-[thud]
[Captain] Please make your way
to the swim deck.
It has been our absolute pleasure
hosting you all these past few days.
-I look forward to seeing you soon.
-[Adam] Thank you.
-[Karla] Goodbye.
-I'm sorry.
-Ben?
-[Karla] Goodbye, sir.
It's just Lo. Doesn't feel right
leaving her here. I'll follow later.
[Adam] Can we, um…
Can we maybe go, please?
-I am freezing.
-[Grace] Shut up, Adam.
[Heidi] Seriously, come on.
-We can't wait for everybody.
-[engine starts]
[music swells, halts]
[radios beeping]
[panting]
-Come on. What do I do?
-[radio buzzes]
Hello? Hello?
-[Robert] Laura.
-Hello?
[Robert] Thank God we found you.
Everyone's been so worried.
You stay away from me.
I… I just want to make sure you're okay.
I mean, you…
-I'm fine.
-You've been missing for over a day.
[Laura] I'm fine.
I just want to make sure
you haven't hurt yourself.
[menacing music playing]
-[gasps]
-It's okay, Laura. We can fix this.
[Laura yells]
[Laura grunting]
[screaming]
What the hell?
What was in it?
What was it?
-[panting]
-[Ben] What the hell was in it?
Ben, Ben, Ben.
[straining] Lo. Run!
-Get the truth out! [choking]
-Fuck.
[Robert grunts]
[choking]
-[Ben grunts]
-[thud]
[Robert choking]
[gags]
Oh God. Ben.
[Captain] Stay where you are.
[screams]
[gasping]
[ominous string music playing]
[panting]
[pensive string music playing]
-[Richard] What's the matter?
-Ben's dead.
-[Richard] What are you talking about?
-[Robert] He tried to attack me.
He was protecting Lo and…
it was unavoidable.
-You stow the bodies?
-It's just him. Lo jumped into the water.
With these temperatures,
she wouldn't have made it.
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
I'm not gonna let this fall apart.
You understand?
She's about to sign the will.
And then after the gala,
you get rid of her.
[strings fade out]
[man speaking Norwegian]
[in English] I was, uh, just commenting
on the… sudden change of heart
after all the work on the foundation.
-Sure.
-Well…
My husband's been by my side
all these difficult years, so…
On reflection, I decided on
a more reasonable solution.
[uneasy string music playing]
[clicks tongue]
Shall we sign?
Yeah.
[Richard] You feeling weak?
Do you need Dr. Mehta
to give you something?
No.
I feel fine.
[Richard clears throat]
Take your pick.
I'll do the talking tonight.
All you have to do is smile and wave.
I'm gonna get changed. I'll get you later.
[uneasy string music continues]
[man and woman speaking Norwegian]
-[clattering]
-[voices speaking Norwegian]
[in English] Security on two.
Please. Anne is dead.
I just saw Anne with her lawyers.
[Laura] Did she change her will?
Did she sign all her money
over to Bullmer?
Anne told me
that she was disinheriting him.
The night you took me to her,
that's the night that Anne went overboard.
Bullmer killed her.
That woman has been impersonating
her ever since.
Bullmer paid her to do it.
Look. Look.
Read it. It's the speech
Anne intended to give tonight.
[scoffs] This is insane.
What if I can prove it?
[dark string music playing]
[Richard] It gives me great pleasure
to see you gathered here to pay tribute
to the woman at whose side
I have worshiped for so many years now.
Whose vision and…
and ambition
have not only helped maintain
her family's legacy,
but also enriched
the lives of so many of us here.
[all] Hear, hear.
A woman who needs no introduction.
Anne Lyngstad.
[cheering]
[Richard] My darling Anne would like
today to be a day of joy,
not sadness.
To see it as a beginning.
Anne's grandfather started
a small shipping enterprise 70 years ago.
And to think where we are now,
setting up the Lyngstad Foundation,
with the intention of giving back.
If he were here,
I'm sure Alfred would be very proud
of… of all Anne's achievements.
And I will certainly pr…
I… I'm sorry. What are you…?
[Laura] Sorry for the interruption,
but Anne Lyngstad has asked me
to make sure her story is told properly.
-Just a second, everybody. We'll, uh…
-Um, will you let me speak?
-What's going on?
-Ridiculous. This woman is delusional.
-She spent the last four days--
-Let her speak.
[hushed chatter]
[Thomas] What's going on, Richard?
That's enough.
Please take her up to the house.
I said, let her speak.
Darling, it's very kind of you
to take pity on her--
I want her to speak.
I don't want her to ruin this celebration.
-[Carrie] Take your hands off my guest.
-[Richard] Take her. Do as I say.
[Heidi] Yeah, Richard.
Anne wants her to speak.
-Would you let the woman go?
-Yes, it's her party after all.
You heard Miss Lyngstad. Let her go.
Thank you.
This is the document
that Anne Lyngstad gave me four days ago.
-The speech she planned to give.
-This woman is unhinged.
Anne, will you let me read it
for you, please?
Yes, please.
-I'm warning you. Do not do this.
-[Heidi] Would you just let her speak?
"On my death, my remaining business
interests and capital will be liquefied."
"Everything to be put
into the Lyngstad Foundation."
-"Control shall then be transferred to--"
-Cut the mic. Cut her mic!
-"…to an ind… to an independent party."
-[mic screeches]
"My husband, Richard Bullmer,
will henceforth no longer be involved
with the foundation."
-[Richard] This is a lie.
-Richard.
[Richard] She's written that herself.
She's trying to create a scandal.
-Are these your words, Anne?
-Yes, they are.
Who do you think you are?
You think you can do this to me?
Do what? We're just telling the truth,
aren't we, Anne?
Yes, Laura.
Now you've heard your wife's wishes,
haven't you?
What you're doing is not smart.
-It is not smart.
-[Heidi] What the hell is going on?
[Richard chuckling]
You know what? You know what?
Uh, ladies and gentlemen,
I think perhaps we call it a day.
We'll find another opportunity
to… to finish. Anne's feeling--
I'm feeling a lot better, actually.
You're not even Anne.
-[guests gasp]
-This woman's not even Anne.
Hey, hey, hey!
If she's not Anne, who is she then?
And where's the real Anne?
Is there something else
you want to tell your guests?
Who is she?
-[guests gasp]
-[Heidi] Richard, Richard!
-[Richard] Stay back!
-Richard, calm down.
[Richard] Stay back!
Listen, you take it back.
Or I'll kill you.
-[Richard] Stay back!
-[Heidi] Calm down!
Put the knife down, Richard.
Come on, Bullmer. It's over. It's over.
Move! Move!
-[Heidi] Hey!
-[Thomas] Richard!
[Richard] Stay back!
-[Heidi] Richard, please stop it.
-Move. Get out of my way.
-Stop it!
-Get out of the way!
Get out of the way!
You stay where you are or I'll kill her.
Listen. I will stab you right here
if you don't stop fighting me.
-Laura, what the hell is going on?
-[Laura] It's not Anne.
-What?
-He threw Anne off the boat four days ago.
[Heidi] Shit.
[speaking Norwegian]
[tense string music continues]
[shutters rattling]
[Richard in English]
Keep moving. This way.
Down here.
Hurry up. Untie this.
In there.
Bullmer, drop the knife!
Or what?
-I think you should drop the knife.
-Fuck you!
[gun cocks]
What are you do--
[grunting]
Don't you dare.
Fucking…
[Carrie choking]
I can't get a clear shot.
How dare you.
Fucking dare you.
[heavy thud]
[both panting]
-[Carrie sobbing]
-[Laura] It's okay.
[tender string music playing]
-[Carrie gasps]
-[Laura] It's okay. It's over.
-[whimpering]
-It's over. It's okay. You're okay.
It's okay. It's okay. It's over.
It's over. It's okay. You're okay.
[whimpering slows]
[Carrie] Thank you for telling the truth.
[sirens wailing in distance]
[officer speaking Norwegian]
[string music brightens]
-[lively office chatter]
-[keyboard clacking]
[music fades out]
-Thanks.
-I loved your piece.
You're the reason I wanted to intern here.
When you're done sucking up,
mine's a tea, milk, two sugars.
[woman] Anyone else would've made it
all about him,
but you managed to find the good in it.
It really surprised me.
Me too.
[pensive string music playing]
A human story for inhuman times.
Just what we need.
-Editorial in five.
-[Laura] I'm on my way.
-[notification dings]
-[sighs]
-[girl giggling]
-[Carrie] Hey! She's good. And I'm good.
You should come visit us.
[breathes deeply]
[energetic indie music playing]
♪ Oh, what's wrong ♪
♪ Lately ♪
♪ What is wrong? ♪
♪ Thought we got ♪
♪ Washed away ♪
♪ Can before ♪
♪ Come to stay ♪
♪ Everything happens all the time ♪
♪ All around, all the time ♪
♪ All around me now ♪
♪ And I just wanna make it feel good ♪
♪ Oh, what's wrong ♪
♪ What is wrong? ♪
♪ Know that face ♪
♪ Off by heart ♪
♪ We were just here ♪
♪ What is wrong? ♪
[music fades out]
[mysterious string music playing]
[dark string music playing]
[music fades out]
[wistful piano and string music playing]