You didn't wake me.
You were sleeping.
You can't bear
to have breakfast with me.
I've boiled you an egg. See?
I'd hardly have
boiled you an egg...
if I didn't want to see you.
Um, tea or coffee?
Does any woman
ever stay long enough...
to find out what the hell
goes on in your head?
What are you doing tonight?
I'm seeing my daughter.
Your daughter?
You've kept very
quiet about her.
Have I?
Well, she's been
abroad for a year.
Did you say tea?
I'm going.
Have fun with your daughter.
Tickets, please.
Tickets.
Excuse me.
Tickets, please.
Oh.
Hey. Hey, you.
Your feet. Your feet.
Hey, kid.
Up.
It's all right.
There. Where do you live?
It's just up here.
I'll be fine now. Thank you.
Goodbye.
Look after yourself.
I'm worried about him.
He looks terrible.
The boy's saying
he doesn't need a doctor.
- He does.
- I don't need a doctor.
- Good, then.
- Peter.
We're not going to
argue about this.
Remind me.
How old are you, now?
Michael's 15.
It's scarlet fever.
He'll be in bed
for several months, at least.
Complete isolation.
Emily, keep away.
He's contagious.
Emily.
How are you feeling?
Better.
I meant to tell you...
...the day I got ill,
a woman helped me.
She helped you?
Yes. She brought me home.
Do you have her address?
- Hello?
- Yes?
I brought you these flowers
to say thank you.
Put them over
there in the sink.
I would have come earlier,
I've been in bed three months.
- You are better now?
- Yes. Thank you.
- Have you always been weak?
Oh, no. I've never
been sick before.
It's incredibly boring.
There's nothing to do.
I couldn't even be
bothered to read.
Well, thank you again.
Wait.
I'll walk with you.
I have to go to work.
Wait in the hall
while I change.
There are two more
buckets downstairs.
You can fill them
and bring them up.
You look ridiculous.
Look at you, kid.
You can't go home like that.
Take off your clothes.
I'll run you a bath.
Do you always take
a bath in your trousers?
It's all right. I won't look.
I'll get you a towel.
So that's why you came back.
You're so beautiful.
What are you talking about?
Look at me, kid.
Mm. Mm.
Slowly.
Slowly...
Shh.
You've inconvenienced
your mother.
How many more times?
I've said I'm sorry.
- You scared her.
- I got lost, that's all.
That's why I was late.
Can I have some more?
How can anyone get lost
in their own hometown?
I meant to head
for the castle.
I ended up at the field.
- Opposite directions.
- None of your business.
- He's lying.
- He's not lying.
Michael never lies.
I've decided I want
to go back to school tomorrow.
- The doctor says
you need three weeks.
Well, I'm going.
Peter?
- Hey.
- Ooh.
Like this?
That's right.
No, not so fast.
Ah.
It's all right.
Do it again.
Mm...
Oh.
What's your name?
- What?
- Your name.
- Why do you want to know?
- I've been here three times.
I want to know your name.
What's wrong with that?
Nothing, kid.
There's nothing
wrong with that.
- It's Hanna.
- You look so suspicious.
- What's yours, kid?
- Michael.
Michael. Hmm.
So I'm with a Michael.
Hanna.
The notion of secrecy...
is central to
Western literature.
You may say the whole
idea of character...
is defined by people...
holding specific information,
which, for various reasons,
sometimes perverse,
sometimes noble,
they are determined
not to disclose.
You never tell me
what you've been studying.
Studying?
At school.
- Do you learn languages?
- Yes.
- What languages?
- Latin.
Say something in Latin.
It's Horace.
It's wonderful.
Do you want some Greek?
It's beautiful.
How can you tell?
How do you know,
when you've no idea
what it means?
What are you
studying in German?
I'm studying a play.
By a writer called Gotthold
Ephraim Lessing.
You heard of him?
The play's called
Emilia Galotti.
You can read it.
I'd rather listen to you.
All right.
'Act One. Scene One.
The setting:
one of the prince's chambers.
The Prince...'
I'm not very good.
Go on.
'Complaints, nothing
but complaints.
For goodness sake,
is there anything
left but work?
Just imagine that
people actually envy us.'
You're good at it, aren't you?
Good at what?
Reading.
What's funny?
I didn't think I was
good at anything.
Whoo.
What are you doing?
What is this?
Why did you behave
as if you didn't know me?
You didn't want to
know me. You could...
see I was in the
first carriage.
- So why did you
sit in the second?
What did you
think I was doing?
- Why did you
think I was there?
How should I know?
Now, I've been working.
I need a bath.
And I'd like to be by myself.
Would you please leave?.
I... I didn't mean
to upset you.
You don't have the
power to upset me.
You don't matter
enough to upset me.
I don't know what to say.
I've never been with
a woman before.
We've been together
four weeks,
and I can't live without you.
I can't.
Even the thought
of it kills me.
I sat in the second carriage...
because I thought
you might kiss me.
Kid, you thought
we could make love in a tram?
Is it true what you said?
That I don't matter to you?
Do you forgive me?
Do you love me?
- Do you have a book?
- Yes, I have.
I took one with
me this morning.
- What is it?
- The Odyssey, by Homer.
It's my homework.
We're changing the
order we do things.
Read to me first, kid.
Then we make love.
- The Odyssey, by Homer.
- What's an odyssey?
A journey.
He sets out on a journey.
Good.
'Sing to me of the man, Muse
The man of twists and turns
Driven time and
again off course
Once he had plundered...
- The hallowed
heights of Troy'
Come here.
'He pressed
her hand to his lips.
She was dead.
Past all help, or need of it.'
'I poked into the place a...
ways, encountered a
little open patch...
as big as a bedroom,
all hung around with vines,
and found a man
lying there asleep.
And, by jings, it
was my old Jim.
'When you landed,
I reckoned I could
catch up with you...
on the land without
having to shout...
at you. But when
I see that house.
I begin to go slow.''
'Lady Chatterley...
felt his naked
flesh against her...
as he came into her.
For a moment,
he was still inside her...'
This is disgusting.
Where did you get this?
- I borrowed it from
someone at school.
Oh...
You should be ashamed.
Go on.
'Billions of bilious
blue blistering...
barnacles in a
thundering typhoon.
It is water.' 'But
what on earth...
did you expect it to be?'
- Whiskey.
'Whiskey, by
thunder, whiskey.'
'Whiskey? Come now, captain,
you can't be serious.''
That's enough for today, kid.
I was wondering, do you think
you could get some time off?
Maybe we could go on a trip.
- What sort of trip?
- A cycling holiday.
Just two days.
I've got a guide book.
I've worked out the route.
Look. What do you think?
I think you like
planning, don't you?
'I'm not frightened.
I'm not frightened
of anything.
The more I suffer,
the more I love.
Danger will only
increase my love.
It will sharpen it.
It will give it spice.
I'll be the only
angel you need.
You will leave life
even more beautiful...
than you entered it.
Heaven will take you back
and look at you and say,
'Only one thing
can make a soul...
complete, and that
thing is love.'
- Hello.
- Excuse me.
Do you know what you'd like?
- Um...
- What are you having?
- You order. I'll
have what you have.
OK.
Um...
Two frankfurters,
two potato salads...
and two beers, please.
- Thank you.
- I hope your
mother was happy.
Thank you.
She enjoyed her
meal very much.
Come on.
Here, let me show you
where we're going.
It's OK, kid.
I don't want to know.
- What are you doing?
I'm writing a poem. About you.
- Can I hear it?
- It's not ready.
I'll read it to you one day.
- Morning, Hendrick.
- Good morning, Mr. Berg.
- You're in court 306.
- Thank you.
- You all right, Michael?
- I'm fine.
- Hurry. You know
what she's like.
See you later.
Good luck.
Please stand.
Please sit down.
The defendant, please.
They're coming.
- Hello.
- What did she say?
- Good morning, ladies.
Welcome your new
fellow-students.
Treat them with courtesy.
- Sit down.
- Hello.
- My name's Sophie.
- I'm Michael.
The Odyssey.
Take our your books.
Everyone believes
Homer's subject is homecoming.
In fact, The Odyssey
is a book about a journey.
Home is a place you dream of.
Berg, I don't mean to
distract you, but...
we're meant to study
Homer, not Sophie.
- It's wonderful, isn't it?
- Wonderful.
It's gonna be a great summer.
- Why do you leave early?
- He always leaves early.
- Do you have somewhere to go?
- See you tomorrow.
Sorry I'm late.
I got held up at school.
I have a new book.
The Lady with a Little Dog.
By Anton Chekhov.
'The talk was that a new face
had appeared on the promenade,
a lady with a little dog.'
Schmitz, one moment, please.
I read the reports on you.
Every single one.
Excellent work.
You'll be working
in the office.
You got promoted.
Congratulations.
- Yee-haw.
- Ah.
Let's get out of here.
Come on. Michael,
we're leaving.
Let's go.
Come on, Michael.
It's meant to be a surprise
for your birthday.
- Come on.
- What's the matter?
- I'm sorry. Really.
- We thought you'd like it.
We've got beer.
We're gonna dance.
I promised someone.
Michael, please.
'Here and there the reflection
of the stars and the lights,
on the bank quivered
and trembled.'
- Oh, kid, kid.
- What?
- Stop.
- What's wrong now?
Nothing's wrong.
It's nothing.
You know, you never ask.
You never bother
to ask how I am.
You never say.
It just happens to
be my birthday.
It's my birthday, that's all.
You've never
even asked when it is.
- If you want a fight, kid...
- I don't want a fight.
- What's wrong with you?.
What business is it of yours?.
It's always on your terms.
Everything.
We do what you want.
It's always what you want.
- My friends were
giving me a party.
Why are you here?
Go back to your party.
Is that what you want?
Mm. Mm.
It's always me
that has to apologize.
You don't have to apologize.
No one has to apologize.
War and Peace, kid.
Now, you must go
back to your friends.
Are you all right?
It's him.
Good.
Get the boy something to eat.
I think we all knew you'd
come back to us eventually.
Mr. Berg? It is 8:00.
Your daughter.
Thank you.
Julia.
- I've not kept you waiting?
- I was early.
Welcome back.
So how will you decide?
I don't know.
I'm happy back in
Berlin, I suppose.
- You've seen your mother?
- Mm-hmm.
I wanted to get
away. That's all.
It was Paris,
but it could have
been anywhere.
Away from your parents?
I'm aware I was difficult.
I wasn't always open with you.
I'm not open with anyone.
I knew you were distant.
You know...
I always assumed
it was my fault.
Julia.
How wrong can you be?
- I'll see you very soon.
- See you soon.
- Good night, Dad.
- Good night.
Those of you
for the special seminar group,
please stay on in this room.
Professor Rohl will
be here in a moment.
Well, we seem
to be quite a small group.
A small group
and a select one.
Clearly, this is going
to be a unique seminar.
We are going to start...
with a reading
list, gentlemen.
Karl Jaspers...
- And ladies.
...The Question
of German Guilt.
So this is where you are.
Yes.
Come in.
- You take work seriously.
- I don't know.
You're rather a serious boy.
It's how I was brought up.
What about you?
Are you serious?
You're sure you want
to work tonight?
Yeah.
But I won't work every night.
See you tomorrow.
- Yes. Exactly
- That's right.
You need a hand.
- Why all the police?
They're worried
about demonstrators.
- For or against?
- Both.
Wow. It's a circus.
All rise.
All photographers
are now asked to leave.
This court is now in session.
Please sit down.
First thing I'm going to do
is hear motions...
from each of the
defendants' lawyers.
They're arguing that there's...
no reason to keep the
defendants in jail...
until the outcome
of the forthcoming trial.
- I'll take these
cases one by one.
Want a pen?
- I got a pen.
- Hanna Schmitz.
- Your name is Hanna Schmitz?
- Yes.
Can you speak louder please?
- My name is Hanna Schmitz.
- Thank you.
- You were born on
October 21 st, 1922?
Yes.
At Hermannstadt.
- And you're now 43 years old?
- Yes.
- You joined the SS in 1943?
What was your
reason for joining?
You were working...
at the Siemens
factory at the time?
Yes.
You'd recently
been offered a promotion.
Why did you prefer
to join the SS?
- Objection.
- I'll re-phrase my question.
I'm trying to ascertain...
if she joined the
SS freely, hmm?
Of her own free will.
- I heard there were jobs.
- Go on.
I was working at Siemens...
when I heard the
SS was recruiting.
Did you know the kind of work
you'd be expected to do?
They were looking for guards.
- I applied for a job.
You worked first at Auschwitz?
- Yes.
- Until 1944.
Then you were moved to
a smaller camp near Kraków?
- Yes.
- Are you OK?
- You helped move prisoners...
- I'm fine.
...west in the winter of 1944...
in the so-called
death marches?
- So, what did you think?
- I don't know.
It wasn't quite what
I was expecting.
Wasn't it? In what way?
What were you expecting?
I thought it was exciting.
Exciting? Why?
Why did you think
it was exciting?
Because it's justice.
Societies think they operate
by something called morality,
but they don't.
They operate by
something called law.
You're not guilty of anything...
merely by working
at Auschwitz.
Eight thousand people
worked at Auschwitz.
Precisely 19 have
been convicted,
and only six for murder.
To prove murder,
you have to prove intent.
That's the law.
The question is
never was it wrong,
but was it legal.
And not by our laws, no.
- By the laws at the time.
- But isn't that...
- What?
...narrow?
Oh, yes. The law is narrow.
On the other hand.
I suspect people who
kill other people...
tend to be aware
that it's wrong.
Miss Schmitz,
you're familiar
with this book?
- Yes.
- Parts of it...
have already been
read out in court.
It's by a survivor,
a prisoner who survived.
Ilana Mather.
She was in the camp...
when she was a
child, wasn't she?
- She was with her mother.
- Yes.
In the book,
she describes a
selection process.
At the end of the
month's labor,
every month,
sixty inmates were selected.
Picked out to be sent from...
the satellite camp
back to Auschwitz.
That's right, isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
And, so far,
each of your fellow
defendants...
has specifically denied
being part of that process.
Now, I'm going to ask you.
Were you part of it?
Yes.
So you helped make
the selection?
- Yes.
- You admit that?
Then tell me,
how did that selection happen?
There were six guards,
so we decided we'd
choose ten people each.
That's how we did
it every month.
We'd all choose ten.
Your fellow defendants
took part in the process?
We all did.
Even though they've denied it?
Saying 'we,' 'we all'...
is easier than saying
'I,' 'I alone,'
isn't it, Miss Schmitz?
Did you not realize...
that you were sending
these women to their deaths?
But they were new arrivals,
new women were
arriving all the time.
So... the old ones
had to make room...
for the new ones.
- I'm not sure
you understand...
We couldn't keep everyone.
- There wasn't room.
- No.
But what I'm saying...
Let me rephrase.
To make room, you were
picking women out and saying,
'You, you and you have
to be sent back to be killed.'
Well, what would
you have done?
Should I never
have signed up at Siemens?
Ms. Mather,
they're ready for you now.
Go, go. Go, go, go.
- Where's Michael?
- I don't know.
In your book, you describe
the process of selection.
Yes.
You were made to
work and then,
when you were no longer
any use to them,
then they sent you back
to Auschwitz to be killed.
Are there people here
who made that selection?
Yes.
I need you to identify them.
Can you please point them out?
Her.
And her.
Thank you. Please continue.
Each of the guards
would choose...
a certain number of women.
Hanna Schmitz
chose differently.
In what way differently?
She had favorites.
Girls, mostly young.
We all remarked on it.
She gave them food
and places to sleep.
In the evening,
she... she asked
them to join her.
And we all thought...
Well, you can imagine
what we thought.
And then we found
out she was making...
these women read aloud to her.
They were reading to her.
At first, we
thought this guard,
this guard is...
...more sensitive,
she's more human,
she's kinder.
Often, she chose
the weak, the sick.
She picked them out.
She seemed to be
protecting them almost.
But then she dispatched them.
Is that kinder?
I want to
move on now to the march.
As I understand
it, you and your...
daughter were marched
for many months.
In the winter of 1944,
our camp was closed down.
We were told we
had to move on.
But the plan kept
changing every day.
Women were dying
all around us in the snow.
Half of us died on the march.
My daughter says in the book,
'Less a death march,
more a death gallop.'
Please tell us about
the night in the church.
That night, we thought
we were lucky...
because we had a
roof over our heads.
Go on.
We'd arrived in a village.
As always, the guards
took the best...
quarters. They took
the priest's house.
But they let us
sleep in a church.
There was a bombing raid
in the middle of the night.
The church was hit.
At first, we could
only hear the fire.
It was in the steeple.
Then we could see
burning beams...
...and they began to
crash to the floor.
Everyone rushed...
...rushed to the doors.
But the doors had been
locked on the outside.
The church burned down?
Nobody came to open the doors?
Is that right?
Nobody.
Even though you
were all burning to death?
How many people were killed?
Everyone was killed.
But you survived?
Thank you.
I want to thank you
for coming to this country...
today to testify.
I don't know. I don't know
what we're doing here anymore.
Don't you?
You tell us to
think like lawyers,
but there's something...
disgusting about this.
- How so?
This didn't happen
to the Germans.
It happened to the Jews.
- What are we trying to do?
- We're trying to understand.
Six women locked 300
Jews in a church...
and let them burn.
What is there to understand?
Tell me. I'm asking.
I started out believing
in this trial.
I thought it was great.
Now, I think it's...
it's just a diversion.
Yes? Diversion from what?
You choose six women,
you put them on trial,
you say, 'They were
the evil ones,
they were the guilty ones.'
One of the victims
happened to write a book.
That's why they're on trial
and nobody else.
Do you know how many camps
there were in Europe?
People go on about
how much did everyone know?
Who knew? What did they know?
Everyone knew.
Our parents, our teachers.
That isn't the question.
The question is,
'How'd you let this happen?'
Better, 'Why didn't you...
kill yourself when
you found out?'
Thousands. That's how many.
There were thousands of camps.
Everyone knew.
Look at that woman.
- Which woman?
The woman you're
always staring at.
I'm sorry, but you are.
I don't know which
woman you mean.
You know what I'd do?
Put the gun in my hand,
I'd shoot her myself.
Shoot them all.
Why did you
not unlock the doors?
Why did you not
unlock the doors?
I've asked all of you,
and I'm getting no answer.
Two of the victims
are in this court.
They deserve an answer.
This is the SS report.
You all have copies.
The report which was written,
approved and signed
by all of you...
immediately after the event.
In the written report,
you all claim you
didn't even know...
about the fire until
after it happened.
But that isn't true, is it?
Well?
It's not true.
- I don't know what
you're asking.
The first thing I'm asking...
- is why didn't you
unlock the doors?
Obviously.
For the obvious reason.
- We couldn't.
- Why couldn't you?
We were guards.
Our job was to
guard the prisoners.
We couldn't just
let them escape.
I see. And if they escaped,
then you'd be blamed,
you'd be charged,
you might even be executed?
- No.
- Well, then?
If we'd opened the doors,
there would have been chaos.
How could we have
restored order?
It happened so fast.
It was snowing. The bombs.
The flames... There
were flames...
all over the village.
Then the screaming began,
and got worse and worse.
If they'd all
come rushing out,
we couldn't just
let them escape.
We couldn't.
We were responsible for them.
So you did know
what was happening?
You did know? You
made a choice.
You let them die,
rather than risk
letting them escape.
The other defendants have made
an allegation against you.
Have you heard
this allegation?
They say you were in charge.
It isn't true.
I was... I was just
one of the guards.
- She was in charge.
- She was.
- Of course she was.
- Did you write the report?
No. No. We all
discussed what to say.
We all wrote it together.
She wrote the report.
She was in charge.
- Is that true?
- No.
- Yes, you did.
- Does it matter?
- She wrote it.
- I need a sample...
- of your handwriting.
- My...
- My handwriting?
- Yes. I need to establish...
- who wrote the report.
I don't see how
that's appropriate.
- 20 years have gone by.
Take her paper.
Approach the bench.
- Compare handwriting
of 20 years?
Approach the bench.
I will not be overruled
in my own court.
I'm sorry...
I'd rather listen to you.
There's no need.
I wrote the report.
Silence, please.
Order.
You've been skipping seminars.
I have a piece of information.
Concerning one of
the defendants.
- Something they're
not admitting.
What information?
You don't need me to tell you.
It's perfectly clear.
You have a moral...
obligation to disclose
it to the court.
It happens this information
is favorable to the defendant.
It can help her case.
It may even affect
the outcome,
certainly the sentencing.
- So?
- There's a problem.
The defendant herself
is determined...
to keep this
information secret.
- A moment, please.
- Sorry.
What are her reasons?
Because she's ashamed.
Ashamed of what?
- Have you spoken to her?
- Of course not.
Why 'of course not?'
I can't.
I can't do that.
I can't talk to her.
What we feel isn't important.
It's utterly unimportant.
The only question
is what we do.
If people like you don't learn...
from what happened
to people like me,
then what the hell
is the point of anything?
Schmitz?
You have a visitor.
Quiet, please.
Gertrud Ballow.
Andreas Michael Springer.
Michael Berg.
Walter Sherman.
Time's up.
Are you coming in?
You took your time.
What is it?
Where are you going?
I'm sorry.
I need to sleep by myself.
I'll just be a minute.
- Nazi.
- Nazi whore.
Nazi.
Silence in the court.
All rise.
The court
finds guilty the defendants
Rita Beckhart,
Caroline Steinhoff.
Regina Kroit, Angela Zeva...
and Andrea Lumen...
of jointly aiding and
abetting murder...
in 300 cases.
The court finds
guilty the defendant
Hanna Schmitz of
murder in 300 cases.
The court sentences
the accused as follows:
Rita Beckhart,
Caroline Steinhoff.
Regina Kroit, Angela Zeva
and Andrea Lumen...
to each serve a total
sentence in prison...
of four years
and three months.
Hanna Schmitz,
in view of your own admissions
and your special role,
you're in a
different category.
The court sentences
the accused.
Schmitz, to
imprisonment for life.
Where are we going?
I said I'll tell you
when we get there.
- You told me you
liked surprises.
I like surprises.
She's grown, hasn't she?
I don't know. It's
so long since
I saw her, Michael.
How can I tell?
It's my fault.
We shouldn't have
come unannounced.
Daddy's going to live
in his own house.
Mother, I'm afraid
I have some bad news.
Julia knows.
We've already told her.
Gertrud and I,
we are getting a divorce.
You don't come for
your father's...
funeral, but you
come for this?
It's not easy
for me to visit this town.
- Were you really so unhappy?
- That's not what I'm saying.
- It's not what I meant.
- Well, then?
You mustn't worry
about Gertrud.
I'm going to look after her.
She's already a
state prosecutor,
so she earns far
more than I do.
Michael...
...I'm not worried
about Gertrud.
I'm worried about you.
'Sing to me of the Man, Muse
The man of twists and turns
Driven time and
again off course
Once he had plundered
the hallowed heights of Troy'
215, mail.
217, mail.
220, mail.
1219.66215.
Number?
Open it.
Testing, testing.
One, two, three.
The Odyssey by Homer.
'Sing to me of the Man, Muse
The man of twists and turns
Driven time and
again off course
Once he had plundered...
the hallowed
heights of Troy...'
'...to the house of death.
But they held fast in place,
hoping that others
might still come.
Shades of famous heroes,
men who died in
the old days...
and ghosts of an
even older age.
I long to see.'
'Come, sheathe your sword,
let's go to bed together.
Mount my bed and mix
in the magic work of love.
We'll breed deep
trust between us.'
'Not for all the
world, not until...
you consent to swear, goddess,
a blinding oath you'll never...
plot some new
intrigue to harm me.'
'Straightaway, she began...
to swear the oath
that I required.
Never, she would
never do me harm.
And when she'd finished
then, at last.
I mounted Circes'
gorgeous bed.'
'When young Dawn, with her...
rose-red fingers
shone once more,
they yoked their pair again,
and out through the gates
and echoing colonnade,
they whipped the team
to a run and on they flew,
holding nothing back,
and the princes...
reached the wheatlands...'
'...those purebred
stallions...
...as the sun sank...'
'...is my beginning.'
'Truly, and I have to confess,
I am jealous.
It's true, till now...'
'Perfectly astonishing.
I've always said
it was all tricks,
but he went to
sleep under my very eyes.'
'He lifted a large newspaper
from the table...
and began stamping his feet...
and flourishing
the newspaper...
to drive Gregor back
into his room.'...
'Zhivago... even a cake,
rather like a Baba au Rhum
known as a Zhivago bun.
At one time you
only had to say...
to your sleigh
driver in Moscow,
'Zhivago's.' And,
rather as if you had said...'
'The Lady with the Little Dog
by Anton Chekhov.'
'The talk was that a new face
had appeared on the promenade,
a lady with a little dog.
Dmitri Dmitritch Gurov...
had already spent
two weeks in Yalta,
so he was bored with it...
and always looking
for fresh faces.'
Sitting in the
pavilion at Vernet,
he saw a young woman
walking on the seafront.
A fair-haired young lady...
of medium height,
wearing a beret...'
I want to take out a book.
Which book?
Do you have
The Lady with the Little Dog?
What's your name?
Hanna Schmitz.
The Lady with the Little Dog.
...Dog.
One, two, three,
four, five, six.
The Lady with the Little Dog.
The...
The.
The. The. The.
- No letter?
- No letter. Sign.
- You're Michael Berg?
- Yes.
Thank you for calling me.
You got my letter?
I have it here.
As I say, Hanna Schmitz...
is coming up for
release very soon.
Hanna has been in prison
for over 20 years.
She has no family.
She has no friends.
You're her only contact.
And I'm told you
don't visit her.
No, I don't.
When she gets out,
she's going to need a job.
She's going to need
somewhere to live.
You can't imagine
how frightening...
the modern world
will seem to her.
Mm-hmm.
I have no one else to ask.
If you don't take
responsibility for her,
then Hanna has no
future at all.
It's kind of you.
Thank you for letting me know.
- You're Michael Berg?
- Yes.
I'm Louisa Brenner.
Good morning.
- How do you do?
We were expecting you earlier.
I should warn you,
for a long time
Hanna held herself together.
She was very
purposeful. In the...
last few years,
she's different.
She's let herself go.
I'm taking you straight
to the canteen.
They've just finished
their lunch.
Table four.
You've grown up, kid.
I've got a friend
who's a tailor.
He'll give you a job.
And I've found you
somewhere to live.
It's a nice place.
Quite small, but it's nice.
- You'll like it.
- Thank you.
There are various
social programs,
cultural stuff I
can sign you up for.
And the public
library is very close.
You read a lot?
I prefer being read to.
That's over now, isn't it?
Did you get married?
I did. Yes, I did.
We have a daughter.
I'm not seeing as much of her
as I'd like.
I'd like to see
a great deal more of her.
The marriage didn't last.
Have you spent time
thinking about the past?
- You mean with you?
- No.
No, I didn't mean with me.
Before the trial,
I never thought
about the past.
I never had to.
Now?
What do you feel now?
It doesn't matter what I feel.
It doesn't matter
what I think.
The dead are still dead.
I wasn't sure what
you'd learned.
Well, I have learned, kid.
I've learned to read.
I'll pick you up
next week, OK?
That sounds a good plan.
We can do it quietly,
or we can make a fuss.
Quietly.
OK. Quietly.
- Take care, kid.
- You, too. See you next week.
I've come to collect
Hanna Schmitz.
Please. Please, take a seat.
She didn't pack.
She never intended to leave.
'The talk was that
a new face...
had appeared on the promenade,
a lady with a little dog.'
She left me a message.
A sort of will.
I'll read the bit
that concerns you.
'There is money in
the old tea tin.
Give it to Michael Berg.
He should send it,
alongside the 7,000
Marks in the bank,
to the daughter who
survived the fire.
It's for her.
She should decide
what to do with it.
And tell Michael
I said hello.'
- Ms. Mather?
- Yes.
- You're Michael Berg.
I was expecting you.
- Please.
- Thank you.
So you must tell
me, exactly what...
brings you to the
United States?
I was here already.
I was at a conference
in Boston.
- You're a lawyer?
- Yes.
I was intrigued
by your letter,
but I can't say I
wholly understood it.
- You attended the trial?
- Yes. Almost 20 years ago.
I was a law student.
I remember you.
I remember your
mother very clearly.
My mother died in Israel
a good many years ago.
I... I'm sorry.
Go on, please.
Perhaps you heard.
Hanna Schmitz recently died.
She killed herself.
She was a friend of yours?
A kind of friend.
It's as simple as this.
Hanna was illiterate...
for the greater
part of her life.
Is that an explanation
of her behavior?
- No.
- Or an excuse?
No. No.
She taught herself to read
when she was in prison.
I sent her tapes.
She had always liked...
being read to.
Why don't you start
by being honest with me?
At least start that way.
What was the nature
of your friendship?
When I was young,
I had an affair with Hanna.
I'm not sure I can
help you, Mr. Berg.
And...
...even if I could,
I'm not willing to.
I was almost 16
when I took up with her.
The affair only
lasted a summer.
But...
But what?
I see.
And did Hanna Schmitz
acknowledge...
the effect she'd
had on your life?
She'd done much worse
to other people.
I've never told anyone.
People ask all the time
what I learned in the camps.
But the camps weren't therapy.
What do you think
these places were,
universities?
We didn't go there to learn.
One becomes very clear
about these things.
What are you asking for?
Forgiveness for her?
Or do you just want
to feel better yourself?
My advice? Go to the theater
if you want catharsis. Please.
Go to literature.
Don't go to the camps.
Nothing comes
out of the camps.
Nothing.
What she wanted...
What she wanted was
to leave you her money.
- I have it with me.
- To do what?
As you think fit.
Here.
When I was a little girl,
I had a tea tin
for my treasures.
Not quite like this.
It had Cyrillic lettering.
I took it with me to the camp,
but it got stolen.
- What was in it?
- Sentimental things.
A piece of hair from our dog.
Some tickets to the operas...
my father had taken me to.
It wasn't stolen
for its contents.
It was the tin itself...
that was valuable,
what you could do with it.
There's nothing
I can do with this money.
I give it to anything
associated...
with extermination of Jews,
then to me it seems...
...like absolution, and that's...
something I'm
neither willing...
- nor in a position to grant.
- I was thinking maybe...
an organization to
encourage literacy.
Good. Good.
Do you know if there
is a Jewish organization?
I'd be surprised
if there isn't.
There's a Jewish organization
for everything.
Not that illiteracy
is a very Jewish problem.
Why don't you find out?
Send them the money.
Shall I do it in Hanna's name?
As you think fit.
I'll keep the tin.
Thank you.
- Where are we going?
I thought you liked surprises.
I do. I do like surprises.
Hanna Schmitz.
Who was she?
That's what I
wanted to tell you.
That's why we're here.
So tell me.
I was 15.
I was coming home from school.
I was feeling ill.
And a woman helped me.
Subtitles by 'ElDorado80'