(AIRCRAFT PASSING BY)
(GRUNTING)
(TIRES SQUEAK)
(DRIVER SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Your wife will be wearing
a purple dress.
Look for the hummingbird.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(CONVERSING INDISTINCTLY)
(CHATTERING)
(LAUGHS EXCITEDLY)
(BOTH SIGH)
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Friends, colleagues...
...and those who thought he was
a figment of my imagination...
...may I introduce,
all the way from Paris...
and completely out of the blue...
my wonderful, wonderful husband!
(PEOPLE CLAPPING)
Bonsoir.
I thought he was stuck in
France forever!
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
So it is true.
You do exist!
- Oui.
- (FRIENDS LAUGH)
Oh Maurice, how long do we have?
The company gave me six weeks leave.
Six weeks? That is a lifetime!
(WOMAN CHUCKLES)
You know, Christine never stops
talking about you.
All good things I hope.
All amazing.
Oh hell, now I have to be amazing.
(FRIENDS CHUCKLE)
Ladies and gentlemen...
I haven't seen my wife in many months.
I know you will forgive me
if I take her home...
...we must renew our acquaintance.
(LAUGHS)
I must give you some money.
No. Go, go.
We will settle the bill.
You go settle your overdue account
with your husband.
Maurice.
You have a wonderful wife.
When you're settled,
we must all meet.
You can tell us all about
phosphate mining.
I look forward to it.
À bientôt.
- Bonsoir.
- Bonsoir. Bonsoir.
Merci.
Not bad.
You weren't so bad yourself.
Max Vatan.
Marian ne Beauséjour.
I've heard a lot about you
around the circuit.
I've heard a lot about you.
Keep going straight.
I'll tell you when to turn.
You were in Dieppe for a while?
A husband would offer his wife
a cigarette
before lighting his own.
Turn right here.
Thank you.
What went wrong in Paris?
Your entire circuit was taken out.
I never discuss non-relevant operational
information with anyone.
I'll try to stay relevant then.
That would be appreciated.
Do they trust you?
Two months ago, I got promoted
to the Embassy Liaison Department.
I deal with the German legation
every day.
But do they trust you?
How did it look?
They seemed to like you.
And I like them.
I keep the emotions real.
That's why it works.
- (HORN HONKS)
- Don't slow down.
This is how you drive in Casablanca.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Now that you're here I can show you off.
We won't be in the apartment much.
I have to go out there and sell you.
We'll have to be careful.
I've told everyone
my husband is from Paris.
And?
And...
Your French is good,
but your Parisian accent is terrible.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
I've been working
on it for months.
Let's hear it.
That was it.
Oh. So then we're in trouble.
That was pure Quebec.
With French Moroccans
you might be okay,
but we'll have to be careful
in front of real Parisians until the party.
The party's in 10 days.
Is my invitation gonna be a problem?
Now that you're here,
I'm going to set up
a meeting with Herr Hobar.
And then it's up to you.
Can you stand 10 days
in this tiny little place,
Le Québécois?
It's not so bad.
Water's hot, sometimes.
I'll take the couch.
Actually, you'll sleep on the roof.
It's cooler.
And in Casablanca,
the roof is where husbands go
after they've made love to their wives.
(MUEZZIN VOCALIZING
IN THE DISTANCE)
The neighbors will find it curious
if I don't come to visit you
on your first night.
I've told Madame Torgenot
and Madame Petit all about you.
They'll be very excited.
They'll guess that
the sex is already over.
And it was great, by the way.
(CHUCKLES)
Then,
you went to the roof.
I missed you
because I've been sleeping alone
so many months.
So I came up to tell you I love you.
You're very thorough.
That's why I'm still alive.
Now we should talk.
And laugh.
Mmm. We're married.
Why would we laugh?
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHING)
Kiss me.
Now talk.
Tell me what you'll do after the war.
I don't know what I'll do after the war.
(WHISPERING) Look.
The lovely Madame Petit
in apartment seven.
She's married
to a German tank captain.
And she's watching us.
So we should talk. And laugh.
Okay.
After the war, I'm buying a ranch.
With horses.
A ranch!
You mean, like in the movies?
Cowboys? Bang, bang?
Yeah.
Are you just saying this to
say something, or is it real?
Mmm, it's real.
It's a ranch on a prairie
outside a place called Medicine Hat.
Now I know you're joking.
You think you'll ever get there?
Well,
I guess that's not the point
of Medicine Hat, huh?
No.
Okay. That wasn't so hard, was it?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Now this is the part
where I tell you I love you
and leave you to count the stars,
or whatever it is men do
on their rooftops.
Je t'aime.
Je t'aime aussi.
Now kiss me again.
Bon nuit.
(BOTH SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
You can come in now.
Voilà.
(MUTTERS IN FRENCH)
You are somewhat formal and reserved.
But you like expensive clothes.
And your shoes are always polished.
I told everyone
you're quite a serious Catholic.
At least you can smell like a Parisian.
I'll leave you to choose.
Before I left London,
Guy Sangster asked me
to say thank you.
We flew Lizzies together.
You remember Guy?
You got him out of Dieppe in '41.
Okay. What did he say about me?
He said you were beautiful.
And good.
Being good at this kind of work
is not very beautiful.
You look okay.
Let's go.
- MARIANNE: Bonjour.
- (MAX ORDERING IN FRENCH)
(ALL GREETING IN FRENCH)
(CLAUDE SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
It was a lovely mass...
...good sermon as well.
Did you get him an invitation
to the Ambassador's party yet?
We're working on it.
We're meeting some Government
people for dinner next week.
You should come.
(CHUCKLES)
Look at his face.
That fake smile.
Maurice isn't very sociable.
We'll do it for the women, yes?
Oui.
Good. Until next week.
- Au revoir.
Merci.
Bonjour.
You seem to have all Vichy
under your spell, Madame Berne.
Turn around and smile, Québécois.
WOMAN: Bonjour.
Ça va?
The German officer at ten o'clock.
I think I recognize him.
He was attached to the Abwehr.
In Marseille.
He interrogated me once.
He hasn't seen you.
He's reading his paper.
MARIANNE: Merci.
(LAUGHS)
You're sure that it's him?
Oui.
Really sure?
60% sure.
(LINE RINGING)
- (OPERATOR GREETING IN FRENCH)
- (SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Put me through to the Vichy
Commissariat of Police.
Quickly.
(OPERATOR SPEAKING)
Yes... I'll hold.
(STRAINING)
(GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
(OPERATOR SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
(DIAL TONE HUMMING)
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Sounds like somebody's choking
back there.
Okay, chérie.
(MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Mademoiselle.
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
- (ALL LAUGHING)
- (CLAUDE SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Maurice, meet my friend Vincent...
...he's also from Paris.
(MARIANNE SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
My love!
I'm bored.
Dance with me.
You're utterly crazy, Madame Berne.
Yes.
You could do with being
a little crazy yourself.
(SLOW JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
Well played.
Watch out for him.
A lot of jealous guys giving me
the evil eye.
It's because they know
I'm in love with you.
It's very obvious.
Mmm.
What went wrong in Paris?
V Section left us hanging out to dry.
How'd you get away?
I ran.
And ran, and kept on running.
(WHISPERS) Madam Petit.
Lurking in the window.
Bonsoir.
(GUNSHOTS)
This Herr Hobar
we're meeting tomorrow,
what can you tell me about him?
He's the Ambassador's liaison.
A high-ranking Party member
from Cologne.
He likes golf and gambling.
He's our final hurdle.
You have two seconds.
Go.
The guns will be taped
under the champagne table.
The Ambassador arrives
at precisely 8:30.
If he's late?
He's German. He'll be on time.
How come you don't know Stens?
I do know Stens.
I didn't see you set the travel safety.
You'll be okay to use
a Sten on the night, though?
I would be okay if I had to use cutlery.
The diversion attack will happen
five minutes later at 8:35.
And then everything will be
in God's hands.
Good.
Hopefully, he'll know
how to work the safety.
(EXHALING)
It's hot.
What are you doing?
Testing you
the way you tested me.
I know you are armed
with a weapon, Mr. Vatan.
I'm just checking
your safety catch is engaged.
(CHUCKLES)
There.
We had our first fight.
Now we're okay again, yes?
Marianne,
we both know people
who've fucked each other.
Then they fucked up,
and now they're fucking dead.
Wow, that's a lot of fucks.
Fasten your goddamn buttons.
Actually, Max,
the mistake people make
in these situations isn't fucking.
It's feeling.
(SOLDIERS CHATTERING IN GERMAN)
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Have you been waiting long?
Non.
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Herr Hobarwill see you now.
MARIANNE: Oh, merci.
MAX: Non.
My husband's trying to cut down.
He says the war makes everyone
smoke too much.
I've only heard good things
about him around town.
Good things.
Sit down, please.
Your husband doesn't speak English?
Only a little.
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Your wife has asked if she could bring
you to the Ambassador's Ball tomorrow.
Yes, but...
...if it's a problem, I understand.
He doesn't seem to want to come.
Oh.
There is a stupid poker game
in the Rue Valence.
(LAUGHING) I see.
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
What are you saying about me?
Don't embarrass me.
You're coming and that's that.
So, your husband plays poker?
MARIANNE: Oh, he's obsessed.
As am I. As am I.
And now we cut. High card wins.
Wins what?
If his card is higher than mine,
he can go to his poker game.
If it's lower, he must come to the party.
(LAUGHS) This is too absurd.
- (CHUCKLING)
- (SPEAKING FRENCH)
Shuffle, Mr. Berne.
High card wins.
(MAX SHUFFLING)
Mining?
Yes.
(MAX CONTINUES SHUFFLING)
He works with phosphate, right?
That's right.
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Now cut, Mr. Berne.
For your freedom.
Too bad.
No pokerforyou.
(CHUCKLES)
Merci.
- Merci.
- Au revoir.
Ah. Uh... (EXHALES)
One more thing. Boring. Procedure.
For new names on the list.
- (CLEARS THROAT)
- (SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Mr. Berne...
...write down the chemical formula
for phosphate, please.
See you both tomorrow.
So, it's in the cards.
We get our chance to make history.
I couldn't sleep.
Mmm.
I won't let you down, Le Québécois.
I know.
Let's get out of here.
Let's go watch the sunrise.
What are our odds?
Of surviving?
60-40.
Against.
Both of us, I don't know.
So, tell me about Medicine Hat.
Pretty green. Rolling hills. Clear water.
Just a place I go when things get dark.
You?
You have a place?
When the war is over,
it won't matter where I am.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
We should be going.
(ENGINE STARTS)
If we're dead tomorrow,
no one would know.
(ENGINE STOPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(SPEAKING SOFTLY IN FRENCH)
(KIDS LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
You look beautiful.
The guns?
Gone.
Bien.
Merci, Le Québécois.
I'm from Ontario.
(SOFT CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Merci.
(MARIANNE SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
It's 8:32.
Three minutes until
the diversion.
(MAX SIGHS)
In this kind of situation, I find it
useful to think about something funny.
Smile or something.
You look beautiful.
You already told me that.
Quoi?
Can you even see me?
Not really.
Ah. You two.
- Ah. You two.
- Good evening.
Good evening. How are you?
Very well, thank you. And you?
Not bad.
So...?
So... It's lovely.
HOBAR: Mmm.
Heil Hitler.
(MAX SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
He's late.
(GLASS CLINKING)
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
(AMBASSADOR
SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
(EXPLOSION)
(PANICKED CHATTER)
(PANICKED SHOUTING)
(MAN SHOUTING IN GERMAN)
(ALARM SOUNDING)
(WHIMPERS)
Move!
(GUARD SHOUTING)
(MEN SHOUTING IN THE DISTANCE)
(TIRES SCREECH)
No one's following us.
We're alive, Max. We're both alive.
Come with me to London.
Come with me to London
and be my wife.
(BELL TOLLING)
George?
Salute me, Frenchman.
- Go to hell.
- This is hell, it's an office.
I heard an unspeakable rumor
about you being in love.
Oh.
Gotta go, George. Buy me a drink later.
Max, you appear to be walking on air.
It's revolting!
- Good morning, sir.
- Morning.
They said Frank wanted to see me?
Yes, straight away.
Max, please remember
you're in the land of "Yes, sir, no, sir."
Don't throw anything or hit anyone.
Got it.
He's ready to see you.
Frank.
They said you had news.
Yes, yes, I have news,
Wing Commander,
regarding Marianne Beauséjour.
It's been three fucking weeks.
"Sir."
"It's been three fucking weeks, sir."
It's been three fucking weeks, sir.
After a thorough vetting procedure
carried out by V Section in Gibraltar,
Marianne Beauséjour
has been approved
for passage to England.
That'll be all, Wing Commander.
Max.
You're a bloody fool.
Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
Marriages made in the field never work.
You're absolutely right, sir.
You're invited to the wedding,
by the way.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
WEDDING GUEST: Bravo!
GEORGE: Careful, careful, Max!
Hold on.
Here we go. Come on.
That's it.
Come on in, darlings.
GEORGE: Don't ask me why that's true.
What the hell have we here?
Here's a fun fact.
Only thing in London not rationed,
champagne!
Champagne and sex.
Oh, my God, Max,
your sister is obsessed!
Yes. Isn't it wonderful?
To my formerly permafrosted brother,
thawed at last by love.
That's rather poetic.
(SIREN WAILING)
Oh, for goodness sake!
BRIDGET: Honestly, I'll miss the Blitz.
I will. No one cares
who does what to who.
So we should be drinking to war.
And freedom.
MARGARET: To war!
GEORGE: To freedom.
Marianne, I would offer you
my congratulations,
but I've known Max a long time.
I'll just wish you good luck.
BRIDGET: Mmm, no, no, no.
Now my brother is just
an ordinary man flying a desk
in some boring office.
Oh, oh,
a talented boy like Max
won't be behind a desk
with Frank for long.
Our spooky friends from V Section,
they will come calling
just when you least expect it.
(RUMBLING IN THE DISTANCE)
You entirely okay, Madame Vatan?
Entirely.
(MISSILE WHISTLING)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
MIDWIFE: Breathe, breathe, breathe.
MAX: Get up! Get outside!
Hang on! Get her out. Quickly.
Quickly.
- (RUMBLING)
- (CRYING)
I need that trolley. Help me.
- Get this up now. Come on.
- (CRYING)
Get her on it. Away from the wall.
Come on. Come on.
Help me, someone! Come and help me!
That's it. I need some help!
Get me some light over here now!
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
Very close.
Good girl. Good girl.
(GROANING)
Pant for me. Good girl.
(PANTING)
(STRAINING)
C'est moi.
This is really me, as I am before God.
(CRIES)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(BABY WAILING)
MIDWIFE: It's a girl.
(CRYING)
(OBSERVERS APPLAUDING)
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Anna...
Anna... it's you.
(CHUCKLES)
Mmm.
There. A celebration.
For what?
Your first weekend off in 57 days.
I counted.
- Are the eggs from the hens?
- From our hens.
Ah, so they were
a good investment, hmm?
Weren't they?
Max,
let's go to the heath
and pick mushrooms.
Tomorrow I want to serve stroganoff
at the party.
What party?
Oh, darling, I've got lots of new friends
who are dying to meet you.
You'll like them.
They're refugees.
Intellectuals. Bohemians.
Hampstead is full of interesting people.
MAX: Hello.
Hello.
Poor Max.
In Casablanca,
we pretended you hated parties,
and voilà, it's true!
(CHUCKLES)
MAX: What's the new
nanny's name again?
- MARIANNE: Miss Sinclair.
- Miss Sinclair.
MAX: Hello, Miss Sinclair.
MARIANNE: Hello.
Max has three days off. Isn't that great?
She just woke up.
We won't be long.
We're just gonna
pick some mushrooms.
Oh, take your time.
It's always my pleasure.
- Bye.
- MAX: Bye-bye.
MARIANNE: (CHUCKLES)
I have to go and get Anna.
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
Just once you can ignore it. Just once.
Hampstead 235.
Sure. 1500. I'll be there.
When will you be back?
You know I don't know.
What the hell is it that's so important?
Liberating your country.
Then you must go.
(OFFICE WORKERS
TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Good morning, Margaret.
- Good afternoon, sir.
- Afternoon.
George is in your office.
I thought you said
to meet you in the mess.
Uh, I lied.
(STUTTERS) It isn't me
you're here to see.
- Oh, do you...
- No.
No, V Section want to speak to you.
Well, why didn't they call me?
Because V Section, they never say
what they mean
and they never mean what they say.
And they never say anything
on the phone.
I told you they'd come for you eventually,
didn't I, Max?
Such a clever boy.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I suppose I ought to
congratulate you on your promotion.
Since you seem to know so much,
what is the position?
Oh, it goes way, way above my level
of security, old man.
I'm just the messenger boy.
(CLICKING)
- Wing Commander.
- Frank.
Have a seat.
We haven't been introduced.
Okay, Frank, whatever the job is,
I don't want it.
I'm perfectly happy to stay with you.
Max,
I'm afraid this really
isn't what you think it is.
And, well,
there's no easy way to say
what we're about to say.
We believe your wife is a German spy.
(LAUGHS)
Okay, wait. Wait.
Seriously, Frank, who is this?
I'm a rat catcher.
I also outrank you,
so you can call me "sir."
You have to listen to him, Max.
He outranks both of us.
Over the past seven days,
V Section has intercepted
coded messages
being sent from London to Berlin
on a WT transceiver.
We haven't traced the signal
to an address yet,
but it's coming from the Highgate region
of North London,
and the information
concerns the activities
of SOE circuits in France.
In one transcript,
the agent refers to his source as,
"Fräulein." So it's a woman.
Okay, okay, Frank, can we speak alone
for a moment?
Wing Commander Vatan,
do you ever speak to your wife
about your work?
Okay.
Uh, sir, before this
thing gets out of hand,
may I speak? Hmm?
May I speak?
- FRANK: Yes.
- Yes?
My wife is Marianne Beauséjour.
Marianne Beauséjour ran the most
effective resistance circuit in Paris
until V Section fucked it up
for her in '41.
We met in Casablanca,
where together we assassinated
the German Ambassador.
She's the mother of my child.
She gave birth to my child,
for Chrissake.
This is a translated transcript
of an interrogation
of a German Abwehr officer
captured in Tobruk.
Amongst many other things,
he claims that Marianne Beauséjour
was arrested and executed in May 1941
when the rest of her circuit
was captured in Paris.
Marianne Beauséjour's identity
was then given to a German agent
of similar build and coloring.
She was flown to Casablanca,
where no one knew the real Marianne.
And it was subsequently discovered
that the German Ambassador
who you assassinated in Casablanca
was a dissident.
Hitler wanted him killed.
This is insane.
All the information
in the intercepted communications
had crossed your desk.
Yes, everything crosses
my fucking desk.
Max, this is now an operational mission.
If Marianne is indeed a German spy...
- My wife is not a spy!
- FRANK: If she is,
we need to keep her in place
for 72 hours
so that we can identify her handler
and clean out the rest of her circuit.
(CHAIR CLATTERING)
No.
Now we've got that out of the way,
perhaps we could discuss
the operational details
of the next 72 hours?
So, this is gonna be a standard
"blue-dye" procedure, blue dye being...
I know what a "blue-dye" is.
Tonight,
you will receive a telephone call
at exactly 2307.
Repeat the time, Wing Commander.
2307, sir.
You will take the call
and you will write down a message
somewhere your wife can read it.
It'll be false information,
only you will have it.
But it'll appear to be of a high grade,
so she will have to pass it on quickly.
By midday on Monday,
our agents will have decoded
enemy traffic from the weekend.
So if the false information
is among the batches sent from London,
we shall know for sure.
If you are right, Max,
the information won't appear
on the transcripts,
and all this will be forgotten.
But if it is proven that
your wife is a spy,
routine procedures in cases
of intimate betrayal
will apply.
You will execute her
with your own hand,
and if we discover
that you are an accomplice in any way,
you will be hanged for high treason.
Wing Commander Vatan,
do you understand?
He needs to confirm
that he understands
routine procedures in...
He understands the procedure, damn it.
Good.
FRANK: Max, it is vital
you do nothing differently.
You are not to investigate
or take matters into your own hands,
do you understand?
(SIGHS)
Sir, I, uh...
I apologize for behaving
unprofessionally just then.
But I know for a fact
you'll be proven wrong.
Now, Wing Commander,
you will go home
and carry on as if nothing's happened.
You're dismissed.
You were ages.
You know how it is.
Once you get in, you can't get out.
A young pilot needed a pep talk.
Then I got dragged into a briefing.
Hey.
What happened to my kiss?
How's the princess?
Sleeping.
Well, the big news is
I definitely have the weekend off.
Until the phone rings.
Nope.
Definitely free the whole weekend.
So...
The party is on.
Yeah, the party's on.
We'll need to get some drinks
for tomorrow night.
Mmm-hmm.
I'll pick some up in the morning.
(PHONE RINGING)
It's like they're watching us.
Honey... Honey, give me my arm.
Honey, give me my arm.
Give me my arm.
Hampstead 235.
Wing Commander Vatan.
- Honey, do you have a pen?
- No.
Mmm-hmm. Go ahead.
- Mmm-hmm.
- (MARIANNE CHUCKLES)
Yeah.
(EXHALES)
Mmm-hmm.
(SIGHING)
Yeah, I got it.
I'll dispatch it in the morning.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Don't think I'm going
to let you sleep, Mr. Vatan.
MARIANNE:
I keep the emotions real.
That's why it works.
MARIANNE: Come back to bed.
It'll be okay.
It'll be okay, because it's not true.
(MAN TALKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER RADIO)
Honey,
you're in uniform.
Yeah, I'm gonna pop by the base
and pick up some whiskey.
There's 50 cases of the good stuff
stashed in the diplomatic hangar.
They won't miss a few.
Why not just go to the shop?
Nothing but the best
for your intellectuals.
I'll meet you at the pub after
and we'll pick up the beer.
Of course.
- (MARIANNE LAUGHING)
- (ANNA COOING)
(CELLO PLAYING)
(DOORBELL RINGING)
- Hi.
- Max.
What the hell brings you here?
I just dropped by to invite you both
to a party tonight.
Why didn't you just phone?
Max, you look like you did
the day that you burned the barn down.
Marianne's cooking.
Why don't you come by?
Actually, Max,
tonight might not be possible.
Max!
Max, I heard that you were in V Section.
If they're offering you
some kind of suicide mission,
you can say no to them, you know that.
You hardly have anything on.
What's happened? Max.
They're running a blue-dye on Marianne.
Oh, my God.
But it isn't true.
And I will prove it.
I'd like you there tonight.
Excuse me. Where can I find
Group Captain Guy Sangster?
He's in the chapel, sir.
Hello, Guy.
GUY: Wing Commander Vatan.
(GUY SCOFFS)
What do you want from me, Max?
I'm finished.
You people just threw me away.
I need your help.
- I have a question.
- Yeah?
Tough.
(SIGHS)
I'm trusting you to tell no one about this.
Fuck you!
I've been left here to fucking rot, Max!
You told me you were smuggled
out of France by Marianne Beauséjour.
Dieppe, 1941.
Is this her?
Why are you asking me about your wife?
Guy, please, is this her?
Oh, they didn't tell you.
Max.
My right eye has been shot out
and my left retina is detached.
All I can see is
a white shape.
Fuck.
Well, you know, Max,
if you hadn't sent me into a strip
covered in fucking German AAA!
My own son screamed when he saw me.
I'm sorry, Guy.
Max?
Delamare.
Delamare is still operational in Dieppe.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hampstead 235.
Hi, honey, I'm at the strip.
They're asking people
to give blood after the raid,
so I'm gonna be another hour.
So meet you at the pub after?
MARIANNE: Yes, I'll ask Mrs. Sinclair
to look after Anna.
Okay, I love you. I'll see you there.
Love you.
Corporal.
Put two cases of scotch
from the officers' crate in my car.
- Keep a bottle for yourself.
- Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
- Who's flying Dieppe tonight?
- FLETCHER: Hunter, sir.
- Where can I find him?
- Try the shithouse, sir.
(ADAM RETCHING)
(TOILET FLUSHING)
At ease.
Sorry, sir.
Something I've eaten.
These'll settle your stomach.
I'm going to save
the amphetamines until takeoff.
Then barbiturates when I get back.
If I get back.
MAX: There's an operative in Dieppe.
His name is Paul Delamare.
Do you know him?
No. This is my first time.
First time to Dieppe?
First time behind enemy lines ever, sir.
Paul Delamare runs the landing sites.
You can't miss him,
he only has one arm.
He's usually had a few, but he's okay.
I want you to give him this.
Give it only to him,
only to the man with one arm.
Is this Marianne Beauséjour?
Tell him you need an answer.
A simple oui or non. Only that.
Yes, sir.
Wait for my call in the telegraph office.
I'll call you at midnight.
This is classified.
No one must know, you understand?
Yes, sir.
It's very important.
You can count on me, sir.
The fields in Dieppe
are lined with poplar trees.
They're invisible if there's no moon,
- so climb quickly.
- I know. I've been briefed.
Good.
Who are you thinking about?
My mother.
Don't.
Think about your father.
He's proud of you.
Yes, sir.
- Oh.
- Sorry. Go ahead.
Thank you.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO)
Hi, Billy. Two brandies.
Sorry.
I've ordered three crates of bitter.
Hazel, filthy pipe smoke.
Thank you.
Did you get the whiskey?
I did. Churchill's own.
A husband would offer his wife
a cigarette before lighting his own.
You did give blood!
Good.
I thought perhaps
you were out with your mistress.
It would explain why
you were different with me last night.
Different?
In bed.
It felt different.
Good.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(INHALING)
Excuse me!
Me and my mates would really love
to see you two ladies kiss each other.
(SOLDIERS EXCLAIMING)
SOLDIER:
I don't believe it!
(LAUGHTER)
SOLDIER: That was crazy!
Max, this is splendid.
Marianne!
Wonderful party! Brilliant!
Getting enough to drink?
Very funny, old man.
(WOMAN GIGGLING)
Hey, excuse me.
We have a garden for that.
Take it outside, please.
(THUDDING)
Okay. You two, outside. Outside.
WOMAN: Come here.
(GIGGLING)
MARIANNE: My people
are behaving so badly.
I thought they would eat something,
not just drink and have sex.
Half of them I don't even know.
I think word spread around Hampstead.
C'est Londres.
C'est la guerre.
(LOUD THUMPING)
Would you go check no one is
actually fucking in Anna's room?
Sure.
(CONVERSING INDISTINCTLY)
- Max! Max, Max.
- (SHUSHING)
Ooh. Ooh.
(WHISPERS) Sorry.
Listen.
(STAMMERS)
I've been briefed that you're operational,
but I haven't been told
why you're operational.
Now, look, I thought as a friend
I ought to just give you
a word of warning.
If the job V Section are offering you
is the one everyone's talking about...
Max, if they want you to run
the resistance in France on D-Day,
you should know they wouldn't
just call you in for a job interview.
They would test you somehow.
Test?
How?
Way, way above
my security clearance, old man.
But if I were you,
I'd tell them to stick their job.
(JAZZ MUSIC CONTINUES)
MAX: Careful, Margaret.
(INAUDIBLE)
Max.
I was able to make it after all.
Frank! I didn't expect you.
Please introduce a little sobriety
to the affair.
I wasn't planning on doing
anything of the sort.
A large whiskey and soda, if you please.
Would you get it, honey?
Frank still has his work face on.
You keep chickens, don't you?
Frank, you know too much.
Show me your chickens, Max.
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
(GUESTS CLAMORING EXCITEDLY)
You willfully and blatantly
disobeyed orders.
First you visit Guy Sangster
and burst
half his bloody stitches, then...
Frank, if it was your wife,
would you trust V Section?
Adam Hunter's Lysander
was shot to pieces three hours ago.
On the ground. With him in it!
He's dead!
Because he stayed too long
waiting for an answer
to a question from a drunk.
Frank, tell me.
- Is this a game?
- A game?
A game.
A test.
I was just saying to Max
that he's taken to office life
like a duck to water.
I wouldn't know.
I hardly see him.
Come on, honey, let's dance.
Frank brought you bad news?
Another boy dead.
Something more than that, I think.
I asked Bridget
if there was something wrong with you,
and she said you were fine.
But she's not trained to lie
like you and me.
We've had a setback.
I can't talk about it.
WOMAN: I think something's
burning in the oven!
It could be the stroganoff.
Stand down, Flight Lieutenant.
- Margaret?
- Sir.
Is the Dieppe drop still on tomorrow?
I believe it is, sir.
- Forecast?
- Clear skies, sir.
Hey.
The man with the pipe. Who is he?
His name is Lombard.
He has a jewelry shop
on the high street.
He was trying to sell me
a diamond broach.
But I told him we're broke.
Hey, where are you going?
- Max!
- JEFFREY: Marianne.
I really need to speak to you.
Oh. Jeffrey, you're too drunk.
Hey.
Your wife changed her mind.
You mean about the earrings.
No, no, no,
I was trying to sell her a broach.
I do have some beautiful earrings.
I can offer you a very good price.
MARIANNE: Max.
It's okay, Mr. Lombard.
We really are broke.
Good night.
(EXPLOSION)
(GUNFIRE)
I'll have to get Anna.
OFFICER: I didn't hear a siren.
Where were the sirens?
(SIREN WAILING)
GEORGE: Now they sound the alarm.
Bloody ARP, always two steps behind.
FRANK: Get these bloody lights off!
(EXPLOSIONS CONTINUE)
They're targeting the East End again.
(SIREN CONTINUES)
We should be all right here.
Max, no more.
Please?
By Monday morning, we'll...
We'll know for sure.
Try and get some rest.
- Frank?
- It's not a game.
Even if it is,
V Section wouldn't tell you.
Would they?
They wouldn't tell you, Frank.
SOLDIER: Look!
We got one! Yes!
(EXPLOSIONS AND GUNFIRE)
SOLDIER: It's heading right towards us!
Everyone take cover!
MAX: Get down!
Max!
Will you get rid of everyone?
Yeah.
Max.
Tomorrow we have
a whole day with Anna.
Let's forget the war.
Let's make the best day ever.
Yeah.
I'd like that.
(PEOPLE CLAPPING)
Who's gonna jump first?
(ANNA BABBLING)
I've lit a fire. Come sit with us.
This one?
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
Flight Lieutenant!
I have good news.
You have the night off.
Yes, sir.
(SINGING IN FRENCH)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(AIRCRAFT APPROACHING)
(ENGINE STOPS)
(MONET SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
What the hell are you doing?
Why have you switched off the engine?
Where is Paul Delamare?
Paul Delamare???
He's in jail.
What?
Delamare is in jail.
What? Gestapo?
No, local police.
Drunk as usual.
Take me to the jail.
(DOGS BARKING)
(MONET WHISPERING IN FRENCH )
(WHISPERING IN FRENCH )
How many inside?
This time of night, only one.
(SNORING)
(GASPS)
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
I don't want any trouble!
Where is Paul Delamare?
Cell number three.
(BOTH SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
I don't want any trouble.
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
(SNORING)
Open it.
(GASPS LOUDLY)
(EXCLAIMING IN FRENCH)
(REPEATING IN FRENCH)
I'm sorry, Mr. Delamare.
I'm in a hurry.
What I'm going to say is top secret.
Do you speak English?
No. Why?
- (SHOUTING IN FRENCH)
- (SHUSHING)
Look. Look closely.
Is the woman in this photograph
Marianne Beauséjour?
Who?
Marianne Beauséjour!
(RETCHING)
(GROANING)
Look! Is it her?
Give me the bottle!
Yes or no, and then you get a drink.
Marianne Beauséjour?
Marianne Beauséjour.
Marianne Beauséjour...
Look!
Yes. It's her.
- Yes?
- Now let me have a drink.
Look again. Are you sure?
Fuck you!
Look. Look!
- She look the same. Yeah.
- Yes?
She laughs a lot. Brown hair.
- And she has brown eyes, yes?
- Right. Brown eyes.
She's got blue eyes!
God damn it, blue eyes!
Right! I mean blue.
Don't you fuck with me, Delamare.
I made a mistake.
- Look!
- She has blue eyes.
I know her. Sure.
She is the life of the party.
Go on.
And she paints.
Paints, yes. She paints what?
Wonderful watercolors.
That's right.
- Give me the bottle.
- That's right.
(MONET SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
The Krauts!
And she plays the piano like a goddess.
Piano?
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Don't move.
(SOLDIER SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Who wants some American cigarettes?
(WOMEN SQUEALING)
(WHISPERS) Hey!
- Quoi?
- (SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Sometimes the Krauts...
...they come to get American cigarettes.
American cigarettes?
We confiscate them from the Resistance.
I remember Marianne.
I remember when I met her.
It was in a café. In Dordogne.
The place was full of German soldiers.
(BOTH SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
We gotta go!
- We gotta go!
- Wait!
There was a piano.
She went to it
and played La Marseillaise
in front of all those Germans!
(LAUGHS)
(SINGING LA MARSEILLAISE)
- (SHUSHING)
- (MUFFLED SINGING)
(LOUD BANGING ON DOOR)
(BANGING CONTINUES)
SOLDIER: Hey, Pierre!
Lucky Strike?
(SOLDIER SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Do you have the cigarettes?
Give them to him.
(MONET WHISPERING IN FRENCH)
- (CONTINUES BANGING)
- Allo, Pierre?
Pierre, c'est moi!
(YELLING IN FRENCH)
(SHOUTING IN FRENCH)
(GENDARME SHOUTING IN FRENCH)
(SOLDIERS SCREAMING)
(SHOUTING IN FRENCH)
Behind the jail!
The Resistance are running
behind the jail!
The Krauts are in the square!
A grenade.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SOLDIERS SCREAMING)
Marianne,
I need you to come with me.
Drop off Anna
and come with me now, please.
What the hell are you doing?
Marianne...
I want you to play the piano for me.
You want what?
Why on earth would you want me
to play the piano?
I want you to play the piano
because I love you.
What are you talking about?
You haven't slept. Let's go home.
I want you to play La Marseillaise.
Now, you have asked me
some strange things...
Play.
Marianne Beauséjour
played La Marseillaise
in a café full of Germans in '41.
I want you to play it for me.
I know the story.
She was a very brave woman.
I thought they wouldn't find me here.
But they did.
And they threatened Anna.
And I'm... And I'm so sorry.
I am so sorry.
Did you send it?
The message! Did you send it?
Yes.
(SOBBING)
I'm sorry.
(MARIANNE WEEPING)
I need to know,
is this real?
Do you love me?
I love you. I love you.
I've loved you since Casablanca.
(SOBBING)
Okay, listen to me. This is how it will be.
There is a Medicine Hat
in Switzerland or Peru
or wherever the hell.
We won't make it.
If we stay one more hour,
V Section's gonna order me to kill you.
And when I refuse,
they're gonna shoot us both.
You understand?
We go now.
We have to get Anna.
(DOORBELL RINGING)
Where is Marianne?
You used my child as collateral.
You've done far worse,
Wing Commander Vatan.
Who else is watching us?
Ich bin einen
agent des Reiches.
I will only give you my...
(CRYING)
MAX: Come here, sweetheart.
It's okay, honey. It's okay. It's okay.
(ANNA CONTINUES CRYING)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (GASPS)
Very good, sir. You're free to pass.
Wait here.
(ENGINE TURNING OVER)
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
(ENGINE CLANGING)
- (ENGINE TURNING OVER)
- (ANNA COOING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(ENGINE STOPS)
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
(SPUTTERING CONTINUES)
(ENGINE STARTING)
It's over, Max!
The blue-dye came back positive.
But you already know that, don't you?
Frank, wait!
Wait! Let me explain.
- The circuit's been cleaned.
- Max Vatan,
in the name of
His Majesty King George VI...
MAX: They had her boxed in, Frank!
FRANK: I charge you with high treason...
MAX: No! Please!
FRANK:...for aiding
and abetting the German spy
known as Marianne Beauséjour.
MAX: Frank, she had no choice.
They threatened Anna.
They would have killed us all!
FRANK: Max, have you lost your mind?
She's a German spy!
MAX: I won't let you do this, Frank.
I've done my duty.
We've cleaned up the circuit.
FRANK: They had valuable
information, damn you!
MAX: She had no choice!
They threatened Anna!
If you want to walk away from this,
then do what needs to be done.
She had no choice.
They had her boxed in.
They would've killed us all.
FRANK: The Section won't care.
They threatened Anna!
For your child's sake,
don't throw your life away!
MAX: We did our duty.
Just walk away.
Walk away, Frank.
Max.
Je t'aime, mon Québécois.
I love you.
Take good care of her.
(GUN COCKS)
(GUNSHOT)
Stand down.
Wing Commander Vatan executed
the enemy agent with his own hand.
That is how you will report it.
That is an order.
MARIANNE: My dearest, darling Anna.
I'm writing this
on a Sunday night in London.
If you're reading this,
then you barely knew me
and may have no memory of who I am.
I am your mother.
You were born in an air raid
in the middle of a war
to two people who loved each other.
Our year together
in the house in Hampstead
has been the happiest time of my life.
Today you took your first steps.
I am so grateful that I saw you walk
for the first time
with your father by my side.
Max, my love,
you are my world.
I hope you will be able to forgive me.
And I hope you make it to Medicine Hat.
I have a picture of it in my mind,
and I pray Anna's eyes will see it.
My beautiful daughter,
I love you with all my heart.
I hope you will live your life in peace.
I rest knowing your father
will take good care of you.
I remain your loving mother,
Marianne Vatan.