Welcome to Blackwood
Pharmaceuticals.
Thank you for your interest in
our Phase One clinical trials.
Blackwood are committed
to innovation,
pioneering research into hundreds
of new medicines each year.
In Phase One, we use
healthy volunteers like you,
to help us better understand
how a drug affects the body
before giving it to those
with a medical condition.
Without your help, none
of this would be possible.
Our facilities
are fully equipped
and state of the art.
We hope you enjoy your stay.
Hey!
You must be Claire. I'm Alison.
Looks like we're roommates!
Cool. Yeah, nice to meet you.
Hey... I'm Alison.
Us three are the only
girls, it seems like.
Wow... you sure brought
a lot for five days.
I've never done anything
like this before, have you?
I'm a little nervous.
It's silly I know,
we'll be fine.
This is probably the
worst part, the waiting...
Alison, sorry. I've had a pretty
rough night and I'm exhausted.
I just wanted to have
a nap before we start.
- Yeah, sorry, go ahead. I'll shut up.
- Thanks.
Good morning.
All participants please
convene in the Exam Room.
No Wi-Fi. No reception.
It's bullshit!
What do ya expect,
we're in a basement.
Nah, they're doing
it on purpose.
So we can't tweet about the trial
while it's happening or whatever.
This is why I keep
saying we need a union.
Every trial they try
pulling more shit.
Hello everyone. I'm Dr. Burke, and
I'll be supervising this trial.
I'm sure you've heard all of this
before, but just to reiterate.
This is a phase one safety
study for Abexetine BRN14.
Five days total.
Dosage begins at 25mg,
and rises to 85mg by the end.
This is a double blind trial.
You'll be closely monitored for
any irregularities or side effects,
but it's a fairly minimal dose,
so we expect it to
be smooth sailing.
If you do have any
questions, however,
please speak to any of
the nurses... yes, Ray?
Are we going to get
to go outside at all?
Afraid not. Participants are confined
to this floor for the duration.
Ah, you're joking, right?
I'm sorry, but I don't
make the rules here.
What's with all the trees?
Dunno.
Food's better than
on Belmont at least.
Yeah, fried dog shit would be
better than the food on Belmont.
Money's good too,
for what it is.
Did you hear about the off-the-books
trial they ran last year?
50 grand to stop your heart.
- That's a myth.
- It's not, man!
A friend of mine was on it.
- Well, a friend of a friend.
- Yeah, right.
Haven't seen you before.
- First time?
- Yeah.
Let me guess.
You heard about it from a friend,
and thought 'easy money', right?
Dunno about 'easy'.
But I needed the money and don't
have a lot of other options, so...
Young, broke and desperate.
The drug trial magic combo.
That's Vanessa. We see
her a lot on these things.
A bit of an oddball.
One of those home-schooled
kids, you know?
Her parents were big
religious nutjobs.
Fire and brimstone and all that.
It's the quiet ones
you've got to watch.
Now take a deep
breath and hold it.
- Sorry...
- Fuck!
- Any dizziness?
- No.
- Nausea?
- Headache?
- No.
- Numbness, tingling?
- Abdominal pain? - No.
- Dry mouth. - No.
I'm tapped out, I
can't pee this much.
- Shortness of breath?
- No.
I'll be back in 10 minutes.
Claire...
Claire, are you sleeping?
- Claire...
- What!
Wanna see a photo of my cat?
Yeah, that's a cat alright.
- Do you have any tattoos?
- No.
What about that
one on your ankle?
Why did you ask if you
know the answer already?
Cos I like it.
What does it mean?
It's Chinese for
'please be quiet'.
I should get a tattoo.
Although I don't
know what I'd get!
I feel like whatever I'd get,
I'll think it's totally
stupid in 5 years' time.
Like when I was 15 I wanted to
get a Deathly Hallows tattoo.
So embarrassing to
even contemplate...
Alison, will you shut...!
Long day, huh?
Yeah.
Still, it's all for
a worthy cause right?
Is it? What's this drug
supposed to do again?
Oh they're looking
at all kinds of uses.
Weight loss, allergies,
treating motion sickness.
Yeah, we're really
doing the Lord's work.
You're a med student too?
- What?! No.
- Oh.
I thought there'd
be a few others.
Seems like I'm the only one.
I applied for the summer
internship with Blackwood.
Still waiting to hear, but they
approached me about this trial,
saying they were having
trouble making up the numbers.
So I thought it would be
a good chance to show them
I'm a team player, you know?
Now I'm kind of wondering
what I've gotten myself into.
I couldn't sleep.
Yeah, we know.
None of us could.
I thought this was meant
to be smooth sailing?
Yeah, they always say that.
Truth is, on half these
first-in-man trials
they have no idea
what's going to happen.
It's not like speed
anyway, it's...
It's way more than that.
It's... I can't
even describe it.
It's just a bit of insomnia,
it's not the end of the world.
You run enough of these tests,
nothing surprises you anymore.
You're probably a bit short-handed
with no night staff, right?
If you need any help running
tests, or anything...
I mean... that would be
completely unethical,
so you would
never... I know that.
I know that. I was...
uhm... I was joking.
Obviously.
We'll just see
how long it lasts.
30 hours now since I last slept.
It's a weird feeling.
Imagine it lasted though?
Like, forever.
Think what we could do
with all that extra time.
The days are long
enough as it is.
- Checkmate.
- What?
- No...
- Yeah.
Okay, we need a rematch.
One game you said.
I agreed to one.
I know, but I thought it
would take longer than that.
Come on, one more. There's
nothing else to do.
Okay, fine.
These all yours?
They're really good.
- Lots here of Paul, I see.
- No, there's not.
I'm doing everybody.
You gonna go talk to him?
No, I couldn't.
I get like super shy talking to
guys, can't think of what to say...
- Hey, Paul!
- Claire, don't...
- Do you want to come pose for a portrait?
- What?
- Do you want to post for a portrait?
- What do you mean?
Nothing.
It's not funny.
So clearly no one
is on a placebo.
Whatever this is,
it's going straight for
the central nervous system
and it's causing serious
brain inflammation.
Are you sure these
pills are only 25mg?
This is a double blind trial.
You know I can't give
you that information.
Yeah. Okay...
Have you seen the
scans that I sent?
I'm looking at them right now.
For Subject 7, how many days
later was the second scan taken?
No, you don't understand.
Both of those images were
taken during the same scan.
All that growth occurred
during one scan.
Hello?
Hi, this is George Bannon,
Senior VP for Research.
Can you repeat that?
Claire, look. There's
mice in there!
Look more like rats to me.
No, they're cute little mice.
It's so sad seeing
them in those cages.
Why?
What can they do anywhere else
that they can't do in there?
Lots of things.
You don't know what a
mouse is capable of, okay?
They could meet other mice,
they could have adventures...
They could fall in love!
Or get eaten or stepped on.
At least here they've got
a roof over their heads.
Do you have a roof
over your head?
I'm between places.
Yeah, but you have someone
you can stay with after this,
like, family or something?
Honestly, if I were a
mouse, I'd rather be
safe in a cage where I
get fed and looked after
than outside fending for myself.
No... No, that's not true.
You'd be in there planning a
little mice jailbreak or something.
Oh, look at that guy.
He's dying to get out.
Don't free the mice Alison,
you'd be in deep shit.
They're probably worth
more than we are.
So the parameters of
the trial have shifted.
What we're really
interested in now,
is how long you can stay awake.
So don't try to sleep,
and if you do start to feel
tired, please inform myself
or another member of
staff, immediately.
Doctor Burke...
Sorry, Doctor Burke.
I just wanted to...
Amir, go back with the others.
Claire, you alright in there?
Claire?
Yeah, I'm just...
[breathes heavily[
I'm not great with
enclosed spaces.
Just relax. It won't take long.
Claire, I can't deal with you
right now. Just stay in there.
Stop it, gimme a break.
Stay in there, be quiet.
You can cry all you want,
I'm not letting you out.
Please...
You're almost done.
Please, get me out!
Please, let me out!
It was bad, huh?
I've a trick.
I used to see this youth counsellor
for a bit, when I was younger.
And one time he told me about how
playing Tetris could help with PTSD,
because it stops your brain from
making visual memories or something.
So now whenever I feel
overwhelmed by negative thoughts,
I play a game of
Tetris in my head.
Try it, it works. Honestly!
I do the music too.
Alison...?
You gotta really picture the
blocks as they come down.
Alison, stop...
- Alison, that's really annoying.
- Good! That means it's working.
Alison, oh my God! You are the most
annoying person I have ever met!
This can't be good for us.
We sleep for a reason, right?
We're meant to sleep.
You're upping the dose again?
I'm taking half of this.
I'm taking half of this and that's
probably still more than I agreed to.
I thought it was
meant to be 85mg, max.
Yeah, I'm not taking these.
I understand there's some concern at
the new direction this trial is taking,
and I appreciate that.
Of course you are welcome
to leave at any point.
But I have just been informed that
there is now a bonus payment on offer
for any participants who
do stay until the end.
30 thousand euro.
Each.
- You wha'? - No fuck in...
- 30 grand!
30 grand! - Each!
30 G's baby!
Right, okay, this is the closest
thing they've got to champagne.
Give us a go of
that Paul, will ya?
We're rich, boys.
We're gonna be rich!
Come on, join the party.
You've clearly never
danced before in your life.
What are you talking
about? Look at these moves!
Go on... why aren't you happy?
Do you not think it's weird, they're
just giving us all this money?
Only you would be looking
at the downside of 30 grand.
Yeah, because there's
always a catch.
Not always.
It's not like a universal law.
- Well...
- Maybe we just got lucky.
Come on...
- Come on, come on...
- Fine!
Woah!
Welcome to the party, pal!
This is weird. I don't think
I've ever danced with someone
who wasn't trying to fuck me.
Hey, the night is young...!
Are you feeling tired?
No...
No, just uhm...
A bit, yeah. It just
came on all of a sudden.
I better go tell Dr. Burke.
'No, no. We need
to stop the trial!'
Their whole immune
systems have gone haywire.
We can't stop now.
Keep upping the dose.
Let's see what happens.
I can finally afford to
move somewhere decent,
get out of the kip I'm in now.
Imagine having a flat you're not
sharing with four other people.
My own living room just for me,
that'd be insane.
I can really
disappear for a while.
There's parts of India where
30 grand can last you years.
No need to work,
just be by myself,
living free.
I'll be first in my
family to go to college.
I've been saving up for years,
but this will pay for everything.
Youse are all thinking
way too small.
You gotta invest.
Put it into crypto.
Get in at the right moment,
you can make your fortune.
What about you?
30 grand, you must
have some plans.
Uhm...
Find somewhere to live, I guess.
Beyond that, I'd say I'll
blow through it pretty fast.
Easy come, easy go, you know.
We could find
somewhere together.
Because I'll need to find somewhere
for Uni, so we could be roommates.
No offence Alison, but I can't really see
us hanging out after all this is finished.
Do you not have
any real friends?
Eh... I didn't
mean it like that.
No, it's fine.
Honestly, it's fine.
Uhm...
I'm going to go and
stretch my legs.
What?
'You're making a big mistake.
'From here on out, whatever
happens to these people,
I won't be held responsible.'
Ah, here.
It's not there,
it's the top one.
The top one? I already
tried the top one.
Alison look, I...
I didn't mean what I said.
Wakey, wakey.
Alison...
Alison, wake up! Guys...
- What?
- Guys, help! Alison...
HELP!
Alison...
- Christ...
- Alison!
Alison!
Fuck!
Security breach. Initiating
lockdown protocol.
30 seconds to lockdown.
Claire...
Claire, come on! We've gotta go.
20 seconds to lockdown.
10 seconds to lockdown.
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two.
Ahhhh...
Get the door.
I'm sorry...
Lockdown complete.
We... we were trying
to get out, and then...
The door.
Alison, she's...
No, no, no!
Stay awake.
Everyone, stay awake.
Whatever you do, don't go to
sleep. Don't even close your eyes.
Listen to me...
If you fall asleep, you'll die.
What?
I'm telling you... I
saw our scans. They...
- You saw our scans?
- I snuck into Dr. Burke's office.
I... I knew something
wasn't right.
For the last four days, our brains
have been pushed into overdrive,
- and now they're shutting down.
- What do you mean, shutting down?
- How does a brain go into overdrive?
- What do you mean?
When you're asleep your
brain is still active,
what you're feeling now, is your brain
trying to shut itself down. The drug is...
- Are you telling us we're gonna die?
- No.
No. Not if we stay awake.
We just need to stay awake
until we can get out of here
and get help.
It looks like you're
in a lockdown.
At Blackwood, safety is
our number one priority.
It's an automated security
protocol at the newer facilities.
For containing threats,
whether it's infection,
security leaks,
bio terrorism, a million things.
For 24 hours the
facility is sealed
and all lines of
communication are cut off.
How did it happen?
I don't know...
Doctor Burke must have triggered
it by accident somehow.
There has to be some
way to override it.
It can't be overridden,
it can't be disabled,
that's the whole point.
The head of the company could
be in here, it wouldn't matter.
That door won't open
until the clock runs down.
I found some smelling salts. Should
be enough for five per person.
Hey, go easy. Ray!
- Ugh...
- They've got to last us all night.
Only use one if it's
an emergency, okay?
We've all got five, yeah?
What about these, some amphetamines,
give us a proper boost.
No, no... hey.
Whatever you do, do not
take any stimulants.
I wouldn't even drink coffee.
It's like...
Okay, imagine your brain is
a computer. And it's on fire.
Okay, no, no...
that's a bad metaphor.
Uh...
Okay, okay... I've got it.
Imagine your brain is a
car, and it's on fire.
But you can still steer and your
momentum will keep you moving.
That's why so long as we
stay awake, we're alright.
But taking uppers, anything like that,
you're just throwing petrol on the flames.
So that's the bad news.
But the good news is,
it's completely treatable.
Once we're out of here,
all they need to do,
is put us on immunosuppressants,
keep us monitored
and maybe, worst case scenario,
a medically induced coma.
What?
It sounds worse than it is.
Come on! We're
gonna be alright.
All we need to do is
last one more day.
Once those doors
open, we're saved.
We've now been awake
for over 100 hours.
As you can see, not
looking so sexy,
but... enduring.
You're gonna wear yourself out.
Exercise is good, man.
Keeps the blood flowing.
Still 20 hours to go.
Six survivors.
Battered but not
broken. The mood is...
Hey Attenborough, stop
narrating everything.
You're doing my head in.
Someone needs to make a record
of what's happening here.
When this is all over people
need to be held accountable.
Actually yeah, you're right.
Malpractice.
Gross negligence.
These are just words.
We're human beings,
and no six-figure
settlement could ever undo
the wrong that has
been done to us here.
Can you put a price
on our suffering?
5 million? 10 million?
Will 15 million
make me whole again?
Nice.
Subtle.
I'm just tracking our progress.
Keeping an eye on things.
It'd be way too risky to try any
treatment with what we have in here.
There's still so much I don't know
about the drug and how it works.
So, for the moment,
our best bet is to hang tight.
And wait for help.
I've still got her blood
under my fingernails.
Can't seem to get it out.
I know it's hard, but we
need to stay positive.
We're still here, and
we're going to be okay.
- Are we?
- Of course we are.
This is the worst part. Now
that we're off the drug,
the inflammation will be
starting to subside and...
Okay, that's all I
need for the moment.
Thanks for your help.
My name is Claire Brady.
And if you're watching
this, it's because I'm dead.
This is a message for
my Mum, Helen Brady.
She's a patient in
St. James Hospital.
Palliative care ward.
So this is a twist, eh?
Turns out I had even
less time left than you.
Took you 20 years
to ruin your liver.
I only needed four
days to fry my brain.
I guess it was cold of me
not to return your calls.
Cold and hard, that's me.
Where'd I learn that I wonder?
I know you just wanted to
tell me you're sorry, but
sorry won't fix this.
It's already too late.
Ta-daa...
You're free.
What will you do now?
So many possibilities.
Yep, that's what I figured.
- How many salts you got?
- None of your business.
C'mon man, don't
hold out on me now.
- Jesus, get over it, Ray.
- Just give us one, will ya?
Vanessa...
- Can you spare a salt?
- No.
What is it the
Bible always says?
Blessed art thou who shares.
Ah! That's not very God-like.
Marcus! You have
salts, I know you do.
- Hey, just give me one, will you?
- No, I'm sorry.
Just give me a salt, I'm
just asking for one salt.
Leave him alone, Ray! We all
got the same amount of salts.
It's not our fault
you're a goddamn hoover.
You were one of those
kids, weren't you?
Who always saved his
Easter eggs every year,
so you'd have one left in May
and could lord them over everyone
else. Act like Mister Bigshot...
- Hey! I don't believe in God.
- What?
I said... I don't
believe in God.
I told you this before.
I left home to get
away from all that.
Look, do you have any
idea what it's like,
growing up being told
everything you'd done was a sin.
I hated him!
Jesus! Sorry... yeah.
You're all cracking up.
Okay...
You can handle this, Amir.
It's a test. You've never
failed a test in your life.
You just need to keep working.
Stay focused.
Keep working. Stay focused.
Mild hallucinations.
To be expected
after so long awake.
Just keep working. Stay focused.
Keep working, stay focused.
Keep working, stay focused...
Claire...
You okay?
Come on.
How are you dealing
with this so well?
I dunno.
I mean, it's tough. But...
I'm not scared, I guess.
I know I'm gonna be alright.
I wish I had your confidence.
See this? I was on a
hike in the Sierras.
Fell. Shattered my ankle.
The pain was excruciating.
Thought for sure I
wouldn't be able to walk.
I was alone,
a cold night was coming and I
didn't want to freeze to death.
So... I walked.
You'd be amazed what you
can do when you have to.
Okay...
Great plan. Barely
passed biology in school.
I'm sure I'll have this
cracked in no time.
Oh...
I'm trying to work up the courage
to put my hand down on it.
I haven't had an easy life.
Me neither.
But I'm still not ready
for it to be over.
Me neither.
Okay, look. Nothing's changed.
There's only 15
more hours to go.
But we've made it this far.
Oh!
Ah!
Hey!
This is it, you realise that?
We've lost two already. Any
one of us could be next.
Do you think Blackwood expect
us to walk out of here?
They have already written
us off, and they're right.
Because if we carry on
like this, we're dead.
So we've got two options.
We can sit around
waiting to be rescued
by the same fuckers who did
this to us in the first place.
Or, we work together
and we find a way out.
I don't know about you,
but I'm tired of waiting.
Right. So this is the facility.
Did an 8 year old draw this?
This is where they've
sealed us off.
This is the exit
and this is us here.
All we need to do, is
break through that wall
and we're out.
- It won't work.
- How do you know?
I just know. Trust me,
they build these places
so when they lock them down,
there's no getting out.
Great. So that's one
vote for don't try.
What do the rest of you think?
I thought you looked cold.
What?
Hey...
- I think this is it. I'm almost through.
- What?
Yeah, yeah... pull it.
Yeah... yeah.
Now...
No, no, no, no!
What?
No, no...
No... FUCK!
No!
It's a bomb shelter job.
It's the same as the door.
There's no getting through that.
Okay look, that's not good.
But look, it's one wall.
We can try another one. We can tear
the whole place down if we have to.
Why would the next
wall be any different?
We're just wasting energy.
Alright, let's think.
- We've gotta take those uppers.
- No!
It's the only way
we'll get through this.
- No, Amir said they'll only make us worse.
- Fuck Amir, man!
Why are we even
listening to him?
Because he's the closest
thing we've got to a doctor.
Well, I don't see him out here. I
don't see him coming up with new ideas.
Do you see him coming
up with new ideas?
Alright, I'll go talk to him.
How did he know?
How did... how did
you know, Amir?
How did he know?
How did he know we'd never
get through that wall?
I mean, he was right. So?
Yeah, but how did he know?
I've been on way more
trials than anyone,
and I've never seen
any shit like this.
But somehow Amir knows everything
before it's about to happen.
He knows Blackwood, I guess.
Knows how they work.
He's only here because he was
trying to get a job with them.
Maybe he already has one.
Think about it. What are the
chances, this one guy on the trial
who knows everything about the drug,
everything about the facility...
One person who can run tests,
take samples, keep
everyone in line.
He's not your typical lab rat.
No, it never made sense he was
on this in the first place.
This snotty med student
in with all the lab rats.
Us fucking rejects, man.
Okay...
But how would Amir not
have fallen asleep already?
No one who is not on the drug
could have stayed awake this long.
Let's find out.
Amir...
We really need you in here.
You were right about the wall,
we're now just trying to
figure out what to do next.
Look, whatever work
you're doing can wait.
Amir!
I'm sorry.
I haven't been honest with you.
This is for you.
And the others.
It explains everything.
It's all my fault.
I caused the lockdown.
I broke their security and tried
to make copies of our MRI scans.
I was so stupid!
I should have known
what would happen.
Amir, no!
Amir, get up!
Did you not hear me? It's
my fault we're trapped here.
So? All the more reason
to help us find a way out.
- I told you, there's no way out.
- There's no way out...
So everyone keeps saying!
Well then, can you
fix us yourself?
- No.
- Why not? You're smart.
You're nearly a doctor. You've got
a whole lab full of stuff here.
Our brain is a car, right?
So if we're over-heating, can we
open the hood? No,
that sounds painful.
Can we... jump-start it,
or get out and push?
Wait, for real? I
just gave you an idea?
We could use our momentum.
Methyl iodide poisoning basically mimics
the effects of an ischemic stroke.
A strong enough dose would stop blood
flow to our brain almost completely,
which would normally
cause brain death,
but with these side effects
there may be a grace period.
We take a shot of tPA
right after the dose
and there'd be just
enough time for the enzyme
to catalyse the clot to breakdown
before the effects are irreversible.
- But is that a plan or just gibberish?
- I don't know, you tell me!
I'm so tired, it's hard to tell
if this makes sense or not.
Yes, yes! It sounds like a
winner. Let's catalyse the enzyme.
I'm on board. Let's
catalyse that shit.
- I'll go tell the others.
- Okay.
- Claire...
- There you are.
Listen, I was talking to
Amir and... What's wrong?
- I don't think we can trust Amir.
- What... why?
No, I don't... I don't buy it.
That sounds like one of Ray's
guinea pig campfire tales.
I know, I thought so too.
I wasn't sure.
So I went through Amir's
things and found these.
It's the uppers he
told us not to take.
Did I just die?
Paul!
You're not dead!
The power went out.
Something must have tripped. I
think I saw the fuses before,
down by the MRI room.
It's okay.
Come on.
Ah, shit! I'm almost
out of battery.
Oh... yes! Yes...
I'm not finding it.
Fuck, my phone's dead.
Shit, I think I'm hallucinating.
Okay, keep calm.
Focus on my voice.
Close your eyes.
- What did you say?
- I said, focus on my voice.
Close your eyes.
It's okay. Mummy's here.
Just lie down.
Close your eyes...
I'm not finding any fuses.
Paul! Oops! You lost him.
Why won't you go
to sleep! Paul!
I'm so excited!
He's dead. They're all
dead. You're all alone.
Go to sleep! Give up!
Bitch. Cunt. Die.
Claire...
Paul!
That was close.
Amir... where were ya?
I was looking for the fuses.
Vanessa... Thank
God you're alright.
Guys, what...
- What's going on?
- Have you been taking the uppers?
- What?
- We found the empty pill bottles.
That was... no, I
didn't take them!
I poured them out.
As a precaution!
Why are you backing away?
We're only asking questions.
No, please! Get
your hands off me!
Ray... stop!
Paul, grab his other arm!
Paul... don't!
Ahhh!
- Have you all lost your minds?
- Shut up!
Shut up.
You cut the power. I told
you this would happen.
I told you. He knew we were onto
him, so he tried to finish us off.
I didn't touch the fuses. I
didn't even know where they were.
- Yeah, who did it then?
- I don't know! They just blew. It happens.
You're working for
Blackwood. Admit it.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Guys... guys, listen to me.
You're tired. You're scared.
You're not thinking clearly.
Please just untie me,
and I'll explain everything.
You're acting crazy! You
don't know what you're doing.
Please, Claire...
He's up to something.
I know he knows something and we're
going to fucking figure it out, okay?
Figure it out.
- Do you think it's just him?
- Could be.
Could be others. They could
be watching us right now.
There could be secret
rooms all over this place.
Secret rooms! Will you
listen to yourselves?
We've gotta get the
truth out of him.
And how are you
going to do that?
Take a guess.
This is life and death. Do you want to
play it nice and end up like Marcus?
Ray's right.
If Amir's hiding something we
need to find out what it is.
And I think he's
hiding something.
Listen to what you're saying.
What you're talking about
doing to a human being.
I'm already going to hell.
We can't do this.
We can't... Paul!
Paul, say something!
We can't do this.
No... no, she's right.
We can't.
Fuck it, I'm doing it.
Ray... no!
No!
Here's what's gonna happen,
right? I'm gonna take this knife,
and every time you lie to me, you're
gonna get a little bit smaller.
- Please... please stop. Please don't.
- Ray... no, no!
- Are you working for Blackwood?
- Ray, you can't do this. He's...
Are you working for Blackwood.
He's got a cure!
I'm working on something.
It's not a cure. It's
more of a stop-gap.
I think I can help us.
Buy us some time, at least.
Bullshit! No...
Nah, it's just another lie. He'll
say anything to get out of this.
- No, you don't know that.
- Amir...
What's the idea?
It's a methyl iodide solution.
It's simple to make, I
can talk you through it.
No. I'm not taking anything he cooks
up. It'll probably kill us on the spot.
I'll try it.
We'll make it, I'll test it.
What have we got to lose?
Okay, so it's at 75
degrees now, what's next?
Amir?
Amir...
Start adding the iodine.
Slowly. Don't let it overheat.
We've only got one shot at this.
That was a very
stupid thing you did.
- You tripped the fuse.
- I didn't trip the fuse.
I saw you do it.
I needed Amir to fall asleep.
None of you believed me, I had
to prove he wasn't on the drug.
Are you going to
tell the others?
It's a sedative. Fast acting.
I'm waiting for Claire
to be distracted.
If you cover me, then
I can get to Amir.
Then we'll find out
if he's lying or not.
Damn, that's a lot
better than my plan.
I'm too fucking tired.
Okay... you're almost there.
Now add the last of the sulphate
and keep it at 70 degrees
until it's all distilled.
- Does that not hurt?
- No.
I mean, yeah. But...
It's good. It keeps me sharp.
So walk me through again
what's about to happen.
You take the formula,
it makes you stroke out.
Shot of tPA treats the
stroke, brings you back.
You should know though, if it doesn't
work, it'll kill you instantly.
Yeah, I figured.
You know, I've been thinking.
Considering what we've been
through, if we had to do this again.
I probably wouldn't
sign up for this trial.
You know Blackwood get hundreds of
applicants for their internship.
So when they asked me
to come on this trial,
I thought they saw
someone focused,
determined,
willing to put everything
into their career.
But maybe what they saw
was someone with no family,
no friends, no
connections to anyone.
Someone nobody would miss.
I feel like I've lived
my whole life wrong.
We get out of here, we
get a second chance.
I don't know what I'd
do with a second chance.
I don't even know
what I want anymore.
I just want to
see the sun again.
We've been in this basement so long,
it's become like a distant memory.
That's not much of a goal.
It's a start.
Okay..
I think...
I think it's ready.
After the shot, wait 30 seconds
before you give her the TPA.
Vanessa!
- Vanessa!
- Vanessa...
Get her up. Vanessa!
Vanessa... Vanessa!
Vanessa...
Get the shot!
Amir, stop.
Amir, stop!
Go on...
Do it...
What do you want to know?
I'm the one with
all the info, right?
Want me to tell you that
we're all gonna die here?
That our lives are just data
points on a spreadsheet?
That's it!
That's the big secret.
Claire... you alright?
- Claire...
- I'm fine.
I'm just gonna go and see
how much time we've got left.
My name is Claire Brady.
This is a message for my Mum.
What was that song you used
to sing to me as a kid?
I always wondered
if you made it up.
Anyway, it's been stuck
in my head all night.
It's funny the things
that come back to you.
You were a real demon
when you'd been drinking.
But the rest of the
time, you were my Mum.
And I get it now.
How hard it must have been, why
you couldn't stop.
Because
even though every part of
me is fighting against it,
I just...
I just really want
to go to sleep.
Goddamn secret rooms...
Guys, you've gotta
come and see this.
We're on to something.
Claire...
Just hold on,
okay? I'll be back.
Listen to me. You are not
just a stat in a spreadsheet.
They think we're nobodies, wait
till we're on every news channel
telling our story.
We'll bring the whole
fucking company down.
It's an autopsy room.
Paul!
I'm not listening to you.
You're only in my head.
But you're the smartest
one here, Amir.
Who else should you listen
to, if not your own head?
Claire?
You're relying on that
girl to come and save you?
She's left you here, hasn't she?
Tied up,
all by yourself.
Even if they did find a way out,
do you think they'd
let you come with them?
The only way you're walking
out of here is alone.
Hey! Time is not
on your side here.
You need to take control
of the situation.
So that's it then, is it?
You're just giving up.
Frankly, I am disappointed.
You had so much promise.
This was a test
Amir, and you failed.
You can't control the group.
You can't handle the
sleep deprivation.
Didn't even notice the knife.
Thanks for being on my side.
I'm sorry I...
Sorry I couldn't...
They must use it to send up
the bodies after autopsy.
It's a way out.
It's a fucking way out!
- I'll go get the others...
- No, wait.
We can just go.
Right now...
You and me.
Read your note.
HELP!
Ray and Amir are
both liabilities.
You know they are. We're
safer without them.
We have to start thinking about ourselves.
It's the only way we'll survive.
Claire...
This is it.
I'm going, I can feel it.
But you're going first.
I'm gonna make it hurt.
What was I doing?
Oh yeah.
I'll start with the eyes.
Unghh!
Ahhh!
Amir...
Amir, it's me. Put
down the knife.
Come on, now.
Just two more to go.
Amir...
Come on...
Come on!
No! Paul!
Ahhh!
This is Paul Murray,
making my final recording.
I am the last survivor of
Blackwood Labs trial BRN14.
If I don't... if
I don't survive,
on this phone, is the only...
On this phone is the
only true record...
The only true record
of what happened here.
Ahhhh!
Thank you for your patience.
The lockdown has now ended.
Is this real?
Clear.
Facility is clear.
All team, regroup by the door.
Okay, let's go.
Christ, watch out...
Ah!
After a four month
investigation,
Blackwood Pharmaceuticals
were today cleared
of any wrongdoing, in the
incident at a Research Facility,
which left six dead,
and one in a coma
with little chance of recovery.
The investigation concluded
that Doctor Ellen Burke had
been running a rogue trial,
and Blackwood had no
knowledge of her actions.
Blackwood released the
following statement.
We feel vindicated,
but still mourn the
great loss of life
in this senseless tragedy.
Hopefully, this puts an end
to any conspiracy
theories circulating,
which are an insult
to both the victims
and their families.
Blackwood remain
committed to our vision
of a brighter future,
through better medicine.
Nothing will stand in our way.