*** Subtitles by dylux ***
(RAPID TICKING)
(TICKING CONTINUES)
(TICKING FADES)
(DISTANT BARKING)
(DISTANT BARKING CONTINUES)
(BEEP)
(MURMURS)
(SLOW BEEPING CONTINUES)
(GROANS)
(BEEPS)
(PHONE BUZZES)
It's really late, Alice.
You shouldn't have taken off
like that.
Dad's gonna want his car back.
Alice, I don't know what to say.
Where is she? Is she coming home?
- Ali...
- (BEEPING)
Oh, shit.
(SIGHS)
It's gone 2 a.m.
- She went back to the flat?
- I don't know.
What... What... Well, where is
she, then? Mads, where's my car?
I don't know, Frank.
Just take my car tomorrow.
It's not about the car,
is it, Mads?
(FRANK SIGHS)
You're not on shift again?
No.
I thought the station was too understaffed
for any more leave.
- They are.
- Right.
(FRANK SIGHS)
(PHONE CHIMES)
This is just a lapse, Mads.
Look, why don't I call her?
Make sure she got back okay?
(RINGING)
Dad just wants to know
if you're back in the flat.
Look, if you don't wanna talk to us,
you can send us a text or whatever.
- Just...
- (ALICE, INDISTINCT)
- When? When did this happen? Just now?
- What's going on?
- Alice, are you hurt?
- What? What?
What about the other person,
are they hurt?
Maddie, Maddie, what's happened?
Alice? What about them?
- Can you see if they're hurt?
- Well, did someone hit her?
Frank, let me listen!
Okay, where are they now?
And what about you?
You're still in the car?
Okay. Is there anyone around
who can help?
Is there a house?
Is there a car?
- Anybody around who can help?
- Mads, put her on speakerphone.
- Why not? Where are you?
- I need to hear her! Mads.
What? Why are you not in
the city? Have you called 999?
No, no!
Let me talk to her first.
Is an ambulance on the way?
No, Alice, this is really
important. You have to call 999.
You have to tell them
exactly where you are
and exactly what happened, okay?
An operator will help you, all right?
I've already called them.
Okay, so an ambulance
is on the way.
Okay. Then why are you not
on the phone with the operator?
- You should be talking to them!
- I hung up!
Oh. You shouldn't have done that.
Done what? Can you fucking
tell me what's going on?
Shush! They'll be trying
to call you back.
- No, you need to call them back, Alice.
- Let me talk to her, Mads!
An operator can walk you through
exactly where the ambulance is...
Okay? They can tell you exactly what
you need to do, and I can't do that.
What? Of course, you can do that!
No, call 999, Alice.
Call them back. Frank! Oh!
- Alice? Sorry, what's going on?
- (INDISTINCT)
MADS: Oh, God.
Oh, fuck. Okay.
Okay, okay, listen, um...
I'm gonna come to you. Mom and I
are gonna drive over to you, all right?
So just stay on the phone.
She needs to be on the
phone with the operator.
No, with you! To you, Mads,
not some other paramedic.
Stay on the phone
until the ambulance arrives.
Alice, how long is the ambulance
gonna be? How long did they say?
- Thir-- Twenty minutes!
- Oh, God.
- Are you coming to get me?
- Where are you?
I'm in Ashfolk Forest,
on the Hallow Road.
Okay, coming.
- (CAR FAILS TO START)
- Alice, I'll be here on the phone.
I'll run you through exactly
what you need to do.
But you have to go to the person
on the road.
We need to know what condition
they're in first, Alice.
Okay? Are you out of the car?
Why is it still doing
this? Didn't you take it in?
No, you just have to push it in a bit
and jiggle it. It'll work eventually.
Alice, I can't help anyone if you
don't answer me or do as I say.
- Christ, Mads, sort your car out.
- Alice, talk to me!
- Where am I going?
- Hallow Road. Ashfolk Forest.
Ashfolk?
Sweetheart, if we're gonna
do this, we have to do it now.
(ALICE SOBS)
Alice, they might die if you
leave them out there on the road.
You don't want that to happen.
Then get out of the car.
Will you put her
on speakerphone right now?
Alice, how are they doing?
(ALICE SOBS)
It's a girl.
God, she's around my age. Mom...
What do I do? Mom?
- Is she breathing?
- She's not moving.
Okay, go to her.
Is she responsive?
I can't. Her eyes are open.
- Oh, Christ.
- Go and kneel next to her and...
- No, Alice...
- She's bleeding.
Yeah, Alice, we can't wait any longer.
Okay? You need to do this now.
- I'm here with you.
- You're not here. Nobody is here.
Darling, I'm driving as fast as I can.
I'll get there as fast as I can.
Right now you have to listen
to Mom, all right?
She knows how to save people.
This is her job.
She just ran out from nowhere...
I know. And no one's blaming you.
I don't think she's breathing.
Okay, Alice. First we have to
check her airway, okay?
I want you to place one hand
very gently on her forehead
and use the other to lift the tip
of her chin up to open up her airway.
- You got that?
- I have to put my phone down.
Yep. Put us on speakerphone
so you know we're here.
Okay. Her... Her airway is clear.
Okay, now I want you
to check her breathing.
Place one hand palm down
on her chest
and see if it's rising and falling,
and at the same time put your ear
right next her mouth and nose,
very close.
I want you to listen
and feel for her breath, okay?
(SHAKILY) Mom, I don't think she's...
Okay. Do you remember
the CPR training I gave you?
- Do you remember how it works?
- I can't...
Yes, you can, yes, you can.
Remember the chest compressions.
We're gonna do a cycle
of 30 at a time
followed by two rescue breaths
in between.
Don't forget to pinch
her nose shut, okay?
Alice, I don't want you
to have to do this, sweetheart,
but it's gonna be so much harder for you
later if you don't even try.
(ALICE SOBS)
Alice, start the compressions.
- Okay, okay.
- Okay, good girl.
- Do you remember the tempo?
- I think so.
- Okay, don't wait.
- Okay! I'm gonna count, I'm gonna count.
Okay, I'm here with you.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
six, seven, eight...
- Keep your arms straight.
- Nine, ten.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
- Thirty.
- Yeah, and two rescue breaths.
And two rescue breaths.
(ALICE EXHALES DEEPLY)
That's good, very good, Alice.
Now repeat the cycle.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
- One, two, three, four...
- Interlink your fingers.
- Use the heel of your hand.
- five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
One, two, three, four, five,
- six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
- Keep your arms straight.
(ALICE EXHALES DEEPLY)
And again.
You're doing great, Alice.
- What?
- She can't do this.
- She has to.
- Mads, what if the girl's dead?
- She hit someone, Frank.
- Yes, I know that.
Why are you asking?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
(ALICE EXHALES DEEPLY)
Okay, and again, Alice.
(ALICE PANTING)
Mom, there's nothing happening.
Okay, Alice. You just have to get
her heart pumping before the ambulance arrives.
- Keep repeating the cycles.
- What if they don't arrive in time?
Now, look, sweetheart,
I know this isn't easy,
but her life is in our hands.
In mine now, as well as yours,
Okay? So keep going.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
One, two, three, four, five, six...
No, don't slow down, sweetheart.
Don't slow down.
Do you remember the song?
♪ Nellie the elephant packed her trunk ♪
♪ And said goodbye to the circus ♪
♪ Off she went with
a trumpety-trump, trump... ♪
- Good. Yeah.
- ♪ The head of the herd was calling ♪
♪ Far, far away ♪
Interlink your fingers.
Keep the pressure.
- She... She's not breathing...
- Okay, two rescue breaths.
(ALICE EXHALES DEEPLY)
- Okay, do you feel a pulse?
- No. No, nothing is happening!
- It's not working!
- Okay, a pulse can be tricky to find.
Just go another cycle. Just until
the paramedic can come and take over.
- Mom, I can't...
- Don't let her die, Alice.
- Fucking hell, Maddie!
- Please, restart the compressions!
- This isn't working!
- We don't know that.
Darling, you can stop. It's okay to stop.
This isn't your fault.
She can't just stop! Alice?
You have no idea what sort
of condition that girl is in.
Alice might be doing this for nothing.
You are fucking traumatizing her.
This is my job, Frank. You've put me
in this position, in control.
- If she stops, then I can't help her.
- Mom?
- Okay. I can do a few more.
- Yes, my girl. I know you can.
♪ Nellie the elephant packed her trunk
and said goodbye to the circus ♪
♪ Off she went with a trumpety-trump,
trump, trump, trump ♪
♪ The head of the herd
was calling far, far away ♪
♪ They met one night in the silver light
on the road to Mandalay ♪
(ALICE EXHALES DEEPLY)
- And again, Alice.
- She has to stop.
No, and again, Alice.
♪ Nellie the elephant packed her trunk
and said goodbye to the circus ♪
♪ Off she went
with a trumpety-trump ♪
- (CRUNCH)
- What was... What was that?
- What is it? What's happened?
- Mom, her chest!
Sweetheart, it's all right. It can
happen, okay? You can still keep going.
Fucking hell, Mads.
What's she done?
Probably fractured a rib
or cracked her sternum.
It happens, okay?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Alice, go back to the car.
No, it doesn't mean
she's gone, Frank.
(WHIMPERS) Her chest, Mom,
it's caved.
Okay, okay.
Alice, get inside the car.
No, Frank, she can't. She can't.
For fuck's sake, stop! It's
over! Alice, leave the girl.
- Wait for the ambulance in the car.
- (ALICE WHIMPERS)
Yes, yes.
Frank, you have no idea
what this will do to her.
(WHIMPERING CONTINUES)
She was already gone, Mads.
There's nothing you can do
to reverse that. The girl's dead.
I'm sorry.
- (BEEPING)
- FRANK: Alice? Alice? Shit!
- Come on.
- (RINGING TONE)
(SIGHS) Come on, come on.
(IN CHEERY VOICE)
You've reached Alice Finch.
I'm too busy for you right now.
Leave a message if it's important.
Bye!
- (BEEPS)
- Alice, please, pick up.
Mom and I need to know
that the ambulance has arrived.
And that you're okay, all right?
We're not far now, so call us back.
FRANK: You think she's alone?
The ambulance is probably
there by now, right?
The response time for a Category 1 call
is under 15 minutes.
Is that a yes?
I'm sorry, hearing her go through that,
I had to tell her to stop.
We both know that girl was...
Mads, I only had
Alice's wellbeing on my mind.
I thought you would too.
It was a lost cause.
What are you doing?
- Maddie?
- It's my car, Frank.
(FRANK SCOFFS)
- When did you start up again?
- I haven't.
Look, I know I can't understand
what it must be like to lose a... a patient.
The girl was clearly dead.
I had to put Alice...
I had to put our daughter first.
- They were one and the same.
- No, they're not.
- You talked me into it.
- What's that supposed to mean?
She should have been on the phone
with a controlled responder, not me.
Can you put that out?
(RINGING TONE)
Come on, come on, come on.
(MINTS RATTLE)
You've reached Alice Finch.
I'm too busy for you right now.
Leave a message
if it's important. Bye!
- (BEEPS)
- Alice, please, please, pick up.
I need to know what's going on.
All right? This wasn't your fault.
The police'll understand that.
It'll be okay, Al.
A girl is dead, Frank.
She ran out into a dark road
in the middle of nowhere.
The police will take everything
into consideration.
And... And why was the girl
fucking around Ashfolk this late anyway?
- Really?
- It's almost 3 a.m.
We don't even know
why Alice was out there.
Mads, you know she had plenty
of reasons why.
- Ashfolk is on the way back.
- God. She was running from us, Frank.
She wasn't running. Why...
Why do you talk like that?
This was...
It was an argument, Mads.
This is just a lapse in judgement.
She's a good kid. You probably don't know
how well she's doing at uni.
Her... Her tutors have put her forward
for a year studying abroad. Australia.
We've raised her right, Mads.
- Frank.
- What?
I feel sorry for her parents.
The girl's.
What was she doing running
through the woods this late?
I don't know.
Maybe there's a campsite.
It's closed. Don't you remember
we used to take Alice there?
Last week of every September
at the end of the season?
Maybe there was a party.
(RINGING TONE)
- (ALICE BREATHING)
- Alice!
Alice, you cannot hang up
like that again.
- Has the ambulance arrived?
- (ALICE BREATHING)
- Alice, talk to us!
- Is anybody there with you?
- I'm back in the car.
- Okay, okay. Good. Okay, good.
- Just stay put. We're not far.
- It's stuck in a ditch.
I tried, but I couldn't get it free.
Don't worry about that, not now.
She shouldn't be driving anyway.
Alice, you know you can't leave the scene.
Mads, she's staying put, all right?
- What about the ambulance?
- They're not here.
Has anybody called you?
Has a responder called you?
- Have you been on the phone with them?
- No.
I don't understand. Somebody
should have been there by now.
They're probably delayed.
They're understaffed, like you said.
Why are you in Ashfolk Forest?
Mads, we can go through this
when we get there.
Don't you wanna hear it first
before the police get there?
- Alice, tell us what happened.
- (ALICE SIGHS)
(WHIMPERS)
I was driving. She ran out from the woods
straight into the car.
How fast were you driving?
- I couldn't get out of the way.
- How fast?
- I don't know. I skidded off-road.
- Why drive through Ashfolk?
I was heading for the flat,
but then I thought it would be faster.
- Faster than the motorway?
- I couldn't stay on a main road.
- What? Why not?
- Mads, take it easy.
Alice, the police are gonna
ask you all of these questions.
I couldn't breathe, or... or
focus. My hands were shaking.
I kept thinking
about everything you said.
I couldn't go back to the flat
because he'd be there!
I couldn't come home
because you'd be there.
I just needed to be alone!
So I drove into Ashfolk.
My friends and I used to come here
at night when there's no one.
This is where I first met Jakub.
If I'd seen Jakub at the flat,
then I would have had to tell him,
but I didn't know what to say.
Alice. Alice, don't worry
about him, not now.
If I'd told him first instead of you,
then I wouldn't be here!
(ALICE SOBS)
Alice, what time
did you arrive there?
I'm not sure. Maybe around ten.
Ten? That was over four hours ago.
- I was tired. I fell asleep.
- Christ, Alice! You can't do that!
I had nowhere to go!
And I was so tired.
I woke up and I couldn't find
the main road again.
I got lost. This place is a maze.
- I don't believe you.
- What?
I don't believe you drove there
to take a nap.
The police won't either.
- Alice, are you high?
- What? Don't be so ridiculous!
- Alice, tell me.
- Of course she isn't!
Frank, last September
Alice called me very upset
because she'd taken some MDMA
with some friends,
and she thought
she was having an overdose.
She was too frightened to go to
the hospital, so she called me.
It turns out she was just having
a panic attack. Isn't that right, Alice?
I... I waited until
it felt safe to drive again.
- Oh, God.
- I didn't feel anything.
- Alice, what have you taken?
- It wasn't a lot...
- I don't understand.
- Everyone at uni did it. I...
- I just needed to feel better.
- Alice. You realize what this means?
It means you were
under the influence.
It wasn't like that.
She just ran out into the road.
Alice, you don't even know
how fast you were going.
The police will... Why hasn't
the ambulance arrived?
Tell me you called them. Please!
- I thought you could save her.
- Alice.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Alice, why didn't you call 9-9-9?
- I don't know.
Yes, you do. You called us
because you always call us.
Because we give you
the easy way out.
I needed you to tell me what to do.
Alice, if an ambulance
was never coming,
then the CPR was all for nothing!
How could you not know that?
- I couldn't save her!
- I'm sorry!
The ambulance, they might
have saved her life!
Everything is happening so fast!
(ALICE SOBS)
Oh, God, we need to call someone.
I know a few police officers.
What about Sophia Grant?
- She would handle this gently.
- No, Mom, you're calling the police?
- We have to, Alice.
- Will they arrest me?
I don't know, Alice!
I don't know what to say!
- I don't know how to fix this!
- Am I going to jail?
- I can't fix it.
- (ALICE SOBS)
I can speak to Sophia and she'll know
how to handle the situation.
But... But she just jumped out.
I... I couldn't swerve. I promise.
Dad...
(ALICE WHIMPERS)
Please, I promise. I couldn't.
Alice, there is nothing more
for us to do!
You shouldn't have called me!
I don't wanna go to jail!
I'll take the blame.
I'll... I'll...
take the blame for her.
- You can't do that.
- Yes, I can. I'm her dad.
It's my car.
Just say I was driving.
- Frank, no.
- Just have to get to her first.
The police will find out.
I can talk to Sophia.
- She will handle this.
- And then Alice'll be arrested.
(ALICE WHIMPERS)
We get to Hallow Road first,
you can drive her home.
I'll stay behind with the car.
And... And the body.
I'll call the police and I'll tell them
exactly what Alice told us,
that she ran out on the road,
into the car,
and there was...
there was nothing I could do.
I'm sober, Mads.
There's no alcohol.
No drugs.
I mean, maybe I was speeding
a little bit.
But the police'll understand that.
It's 3 a.m.
Dark road, no street lights,
and she ran out of the woods.
- They will understand that.
- Frank.
There was nothing I could do
to prevent this.
So if we take Alice
out of the equation,
she was...
she was never even there.
Isn't that right, Alice?
(ALICE WHIMPERS)
I'm not here.
Good. That's settled, then.
Alice, I need to speak to your dad for a second.
I'm gonna put the phone on mute.
- No, I don't want to be alone.
- It'll only be for a second, okay?
- You can't cover this up for her.
- I'm not.
The police will find out.
The police will believe
what I tell them
because they'll have
no reason not to.
Look, someone has been killed, Frank.
What else is there to say, Mads?
Jesus fucking Christ!
What else can we do? Nothing!
If they say it's death by dangerous driving,
you will go to jail.
You could lose everything.
If Alice goes to jail,
I'll lose everything.
We can't punish her
for some stupid mistake.
This was an accident.
We can't ruin her future.
(ALICE SOBS)
You're giving her exactly what
she thinks she wants. An easy way out.
But she won't ever
forget her face, Frank.
It will influence every little decision
she makes for the rest of her life.
I know that.
And whatever we do, and however
much she tries to ignore it,
the guilt will eat away at her.
That's it, then?
It's all hopeless?
I can't accept that, and...
and I won't.
But if you are so keen to...
to give up, then, yes,
by all means,
call your police friend
and then you can explain to
our daughter why you won't help.
You can explain
why everything is lost.
Are you still there?
You can do that. Because
I won't. And... And I can't.
You make the call.
Mom.
- Dad?
- I'm here.
Oh! What's happening?
We're not far now.
We'll be there with you soon.
- It'll be okay, Al.
- Thank you.
I know. Just...
Just stay on the line.
(ALICE WHIMPERS)
(INDICATOR CLICKS)
What will happen to her?
Alice, we don't need
to talk about that now.
Mom? I want to know.
A coroner will come
and take her away.
- Not her family?
- No, they see her later.
- I've left her out on the road.
- Just stay in the car, Al.
(SIGHS) How can you
stand this, Mom?
- What do you mean?
- When you're at work.
You must see people like me
who've done this.
How can you stand
to look at them?
Alice, you haven't done
anything wrong.
- Accidents happen every day, Alice.
- This wasn't an accident.
Alice, I said we don't need
to talk about this now, all right?
Let's just think...
Let's... think about university.
You've probably got exams
coming up soon, right?
- I can't...
- And... And your placement.
The year...
The year studying down under.
I would have...
I'd have given anything
for a chance like that at your age.
Alice, we're just looking
straight ahead now, all right?
Just... Just straight ahead. We're not
looking behind, just straight ahead.
And you'll be far away from this
before you even know it.
(ALICE SIGHS)
- I can't finish uni.
- Yes, you can. And you will.
Because you're not gonna let
tonight dismantle your life.
- But what about Jakub?
- Alice, no.
- He deserves to know!
- No, Alice!
Whatever decisions about that,
we can discuss later.
You're not in the right
headspace, all right?
And I know what's best.
Mom and I both know
what's right for you.
- If Jakub wants to keep...
- Fuck Jakub! All right?
I know what he's like.
I know his type! He'll...
Alice, he'll want
nothing to do with you!
- But I have to tell him.
- Fucking hell, Alice!
I'm the one taking control here,
all right?
I'm the one solving this
problem. This fucking shitshow!
So I think I'm entitled to make
the decisions from now on in,
and giving up university
to start a family
with some fucking Pole at 18
is not an option!
Jakub is Czech.
(SIGHS)
Okay. Look, Alice. Alice, look.
You stole our car
to run away from an argument,
you drove into a forest
to get high,
having just found out
that you're pregnant,
instead of confronting
your boyfriend at the flat.
It...
Dad and I had you young, it's true,
and clearly we would
do anything for you.
But I stand by what I said.
You're not ready for
this responsibility, sweetheart.
(ALICE BREATHES HEAVILY)
When you told us,
I'm sorry if my reaction
was not the one
you were hoping for.
But I said it then
and I'll say it now,
you don't wanna be a parent, Alice.
Did you?
- What?
- Want to be a parent?
Oh, Al, don't be silly.
Of course we did.
All we wanna do is protect you
from everything that's happened.
And these accidents,
like the drugs and Jakub,
they can all be rectified,
and I will do whatever it takes
to get you back on track, and...
Alice, I will always be there
to guide you.
And these things will always
work out for the best...
(GPS BEEPS)
(BEEPS)
- Shit.
- Did we miss a turn?
Well, it's saying there was
a left. I didn't see a left.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure there wasn't a left.
The GPS is playing up like everything else
in this fucking car.
- Do we need to turn back?
- No, I know this is the way.
(GPS BEEPS)
- I fucking booked you a service, Mads.
- I think we need to turn back.
I think you should
have taken your car in.
Frank.
- I know where I'm going!
- It's telling us to go back!
This way brings you onto the backside
of the peaks right by Ashfolk Forest.
Not that you remember, or you even seem
to fucking care these days.
We used to come here every year
as a family.
- What? What's that supposed to mean?
- You know what it means.
- Do I?
- Yes!
(GPS BEEPS)
These last six, seven months,
you're not here.
- You're not.
- Dad, I think...
You certainly don't tell me
what's going on.
You wouldn't have believed me
if I'd told you Alice was taking drugs.
- It's not that.
- (GPS BEEPS)
You're absent.
You don't even go to work any...
You say things these days
that make it sound like you don't...
you just don't care, or ever cared.
(GPS BEEPS)
And I wish you'd fixed
your fucking car.
(GPS BEEPS)
- It's telling us to go back, Frank.
- There's nowhere left to turn.
- Dad, I can see you.
- What was that?
I see you. I can see your
headlights through the trees.
(ALICE BREATHES RAPIDLY)
(GPS BEEPS)
What... What do you mean?
Keep driving. It's a long road.
It winds round the forest.
- (GPS BEEPS)
- But you're not far.
I'll turn on the headlights
so you can see me.
- No, no, no! Turn them off!
- What?
Turn your lights off!
That's not us!
That's somebody else's car!
- Did they see you?
- They're still driving this way.
- They're gonna see me. Her!
- No, they're not. All right, listen.
Dad, what do I do? What...
They're... They're not gonna see her
and they won't know she's there,
because you're gonna get her
off the road, all right, Alice?
You're gonna go right now, and you're
gonna get her body off the road
and hide it in the woods
somewhere out of sight.
- No, Frank, she can't do that.
- Get her body off the road, Alice.
- No, Frank, no. Frank.
- Just fucking do it!
- No, Dad, I don't want to.
- You have to or it's over!
- Frank, listen to me.
- For Christ's sake!
- Before they're there!
- This will only make things worse.
We have this under control.
All right, Alice,
get her fucking body off the road.
(WHIMPERING) Okay.
- Frank.
- Don't. Don't, Maddie, don't.
- Don't dwell on it, Alice.
- (SOBBING) I can't do this.
Yes, you can. Grab her by the clothes.
Get her off the road!
- Please, quickly!
- (ALICE GRUNTS)
(DRAGGING)
(ALICE SOBBING)
(DRAGGING CONTINUES)
(ALICE GRUNTS)
Is she hidden? She safe?
I left her shoe in the road.
Well, go back and get it!
Quickly!
- (CRUNCHING FOOTSTEPS)
- Okay.
- (CRACKING)
- (ALICE SCREAMS)
Her face is changing!
- Wh... What do you mean?
- She's becoming someone else!
- Alice, you're not making any sense!
- No, I can't! No, I can't!
- Alice, are you still high?
- (ALICE BREATHES RAPIDLY)
- (RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
- (CAR ENGINE IDLES)
No, Alice, don't run.
Don't run! Don't run!
WOMAN: Hello there.
Are you all right? Darling,
turn off the headlights.
You're blinding the little thing.
We didn't mean to scare you.
Do you need some help
with your car?
- Are you out here alone?
- Alice, talk to her, make her leave.
WOMAN: My husband and I can help
if there's been an accident...
ALICE: I'm on the phone.
I mean, I'm okay. I'm not hurt.
- WOMAN: But what happened here?
- I... I just had to stop.
WOMAN: In a ditch? Do you mind
if I step out of my car?
- No, Alice. Make her leave.
- ALICE: No, please, honestly. I'm fine.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
WOMAN: Oh, there's no need
to look alarmed.
I needed to get
the blood flowing to my legs.
It's quite the drive
to get out here.
Oh, it's wonderfully scenic
in the day.
People say it's enchanted.
Has so much to hide,
especially in the pitch-black dark.
ALICE: Yeah.
- WOMAN: You're awfully tense.
- What?
WOMAN: You're awfully tense.
Like a ghost.
ALICE: No, an animal, a deer,
maybe, ran out in front of...
I... And I skidded
into the ditch and...
WOMAN: Darling, do we get deer
out here?
- MAN: No.
- WOMAN: Perhaps it was a runaway dog.
- What is wrong with them?
- I don't know.
WOMAN: We saw you flash your
lights at the top of the road.
We thought somebody might have
been in trouble.
ALICE: No. I'm sorry.
I'm not. I'm okay.
WOMAN: Mm-hm.
Alice, explain that you're talking
to your parents, that we're on our way.
ALICE: My parents, they're on the phone.
They're coming to get the car free.
WOMAN: Oh! Well, we can help with that.
ALICE: No, it's okay. I'm okay.
WOMAN: Nonsense. Darling,
fetch the ropes from the boot!
- We can tow her free.
- (CRUNCHING FOOTSTEPS)
Why don't you hand me your car keys?
Perhaps I can reverse you out.
ALICE: No. I'd rather you just leave.
WOMAN: Whoo! It's chilly.
Not many people come into
Ashfolk when it's this cold.
Especially not at night.
Where we are is almost as deep as you can
get into the forest by car.
Do you know why
it's called Hallow Road?
Because these are sacred grounds,
full of myth and lore.
In the ancient times, pagans used to honor
the fairies in these woods.
Now all the lores are reduced
to campfire stories
for young people who come
out here to get wasted.
So how did you end up here?
- Are you really all alone?
- ALICE: What?
WOMAN: You say "pardon", not "what".
And I asked
if somebody brought you here.
ALICE: You don't understand.
WOMAN: I can see in your eyes
that you're intoxicated.
So if you thought that you
could just drive into Ashfolk,
with your friends,
as you pleased,
and set up camp
where no one could find you,
and get drunk, or high,
or whatever,
then I should remind you
that you are breaking the law
and I'm within my rights
to call the authorities.
- ALICE: No, no.
- Do you understand?
ALICE: No, I'm not.
There's no one here.
I just got lost.
Please, I didn't...
WOMAN: Didn't what?
- ALICE: Just...
- Are you too soused to drive?
- Is that why you crashed?
- ALICE: Just leave me alone.
WOMAN: Do I need
to call the authorities?
ALICE: I'm really sorry.
WOMAN: Sorry for what? Miss?
- What is it that you want to tell me?
- ALICE: I didn't mean to...
Alice, Alice.
Put me on the phone with them.
Let me explain to them
what's going on, okay?
- ALICE: My Mom, she can talk to you.
- What are you gonna say?
- WOMAN: Okay, hand me your phone.
- No, keep it. Keep it.
Use the speakerphone.
- ALICE: It's my Mom speaking.
- Hello?
Hi. Hello. Can you hear me?
- WOMAN: You're this girl's mother?
- Yes, I'm Alice's mother.
I'm here with my husband.
And we've been listening
and we understand your concern.
Alice has just had a rough night.
She was... She was driving
back to university
and she got lost taking a shortcut
and ended up coming off the road.
And my husband and I,
we're driving into Ashfolk now.
We really appreciate you stopping
to check on Alice as you did.
But we're not far away now.
We're just a... just a...
just a few minutes away.
As in we can take care of Alice
from here on.
It's... It's okay for you to go.
WOMAN: You want us
to leave your daughter alone?
In the forest? In the dark?
Well, as I said,
we're only a few minutes away.
WOMAN: What were you doing
in the woods?
- ALICE: What?
- In the woods?
You came bounding out of there
all flustered.
- What were you doing?
- Excuse me. Excuse me, please!
Look, I'm sorry, but I can hear
that you're making Alice
really uncomfortable.
I mean no disrespect, but
the fact that you're strangers
driving around a forest late at night
makes me uncomfortable, okay?
It's very disconcerting, okay?
So my... my husband and I
would really appreciate it
if you and your husband
just got on your way
and got back in your car
and left our daughter alone.
WOMAN: Am I making you uncomfortable?
ALICE: Yes.
WOMAN: Okay, then.
(SLOW CRUNCHING FOOTSTEPS)
(ALICE BREATHES HEAVILY)
WOMAN: Make sure to clean your wound.
- You have blood on your shirt.
- ALICE: It's from in the car.
- WOMAN: After your accident?
- Yes, I cut my hand.
WOMAN: Mm-hm.
Have a pleasant night.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES,
ENGINE STARTS)
(ALICE EXHALES)
- ALICE: They're leaving.
- Okay. Alice, get back in the car.
- And lock the door.
- Thank you for not saying anything.
- She's been seen, Frank.
- I know, I know, but we're still okay.
- No, this lie will only get bigger.
- Let's just get there and see.
- I'm back inside.
- Okay, good. Lock the door, Al.
- How far away are you?
- We're...
(ALICE GASPS)
- Alice? Alice, what is it?
- No, no, no, no, no.
- What are they doing?
- No, they've stopped. By the woods.
- They're looking for her. Oh, my God.
- Okay, okay.
- Frank.
- What do I... What do I do? What do...
- They might not find her.
- Frank, we have to call the police.
- Before this can escalate further.
- No, no.
- Frank, we can't stop what's coming.
- Mom, what are you saying?
Alice. Alice.
I want you to stay in the car.
Don't get out. Tell them
that the police are coming.
And I'm gonna call now. Like I should
have done a long time ago.
- No!
- Alice, please, I'm sorry.
But I promise you,
this is now the only way.
- No!
- (ENGINE STARTS)
Alice, what are you doing?
(ENGINE REVS, TIRES SPIN)
Alice, stop, please.
Alice, you can't run.
Frank, tell her to stop!
Alice, please! Please!
I promise you, the police
will get you through this.
You can't run from this.
Alice, Alice, you can't.
There's nowhere left to go!
- (THUDDING)
- WOMAN: Miss? Stop! Get out of the car.
Hey. Hey! You're stuck. You're just
going deeper into the trench.
- ALICE: Go away!
- We found the girl. We know now.
- (TIRES SPIN)
- We know it was an accident, but you have to stop.
Before you hurt somebody else!
Miss, turn the engine off.
- ALICE: Please, please, leave me alone!
- We can't do that.
Alice, listen to me. Listen to me.
Dad and I are here for you.
We'll face this together.
But you have to stop.
WOMAN: The window, darling.
- (WINDOW SMASHES)
- (ALICE SCREAMS) No!
No, don't touch me! No!
You fucking leave her alone!
You leave her the fuck alone!
- Don't you touch my daughter!
- No!
(BEEPING)
- Oh, God.
- Maddie, what just happened?
What just happened?
(RINGING TONE)
(RINGING TONE STOPS)
Oh, God.
Frank, slow down.
(ENGINE REVS)
Maybe they were just trying
to stop her driving away.
They know, Mads.
They know, they know.
- We have to call the police.
- No, no, call Alice again.
- No.
- Call Alice again.
We need to know she's okay.
Then call the police!
No, Frank.
- Mads, we're almost fucking there!
- No!
- This is so hypocritical!
- What?
You told Alice she didn't want
the responsibility of being a parent.
All you seem to want to do
is fucking give it up yourself!
- What are you talking about?
- We have to be the ones who fix this!
(PHONE BUZZES)
Alice, Alice? Alice?
WOMAN: I take it you
knew about the girl.
- Where's Alice?
- You must be the father.
- She's in the car, calming down.
We had to break in to take her keys away.
She could have hurt herself.
Put her on the phone.
She's in shock and didn't
want to answer your calls.
Guilt has a funny way
of shutting down the body.
It was an accident.
- I'm not sure I see it that way.
- What does that mean?
The collision must have
happened on the road.
Yet the girl had been dragged
out of sight into the woods.
And the authorities
are nowhere to be found.
No ambulance, no police.
Just two parents on the phone.
And that's no accident, now, is it?
That's the dilemma in a dilemma.
Do we act logically or emotionally?
I can see that
the choices made here
were built out of emotion
for your daughter rather than logic
for that poor child
left out in the cold.
That's very easy for you to say.
I'm a paramedic.
That's why Alice called us.
I stupidly thought I could
save the girl over the phone,
and by the time I realized
I couldn't, it was too late.
Too late? Why was it too late?
Would you please just fucking
put Alice on the phone?
- No. You left her for dead.
- No, we didn't. We... We tried CPR.
Alice did. We... But the girl
could not be resuscitated.
The girl seemed very much alive
when my husband took her away.
- What did you... What did you say?
- The girl is alive.
Oh, my God.
- I don't understand.
- Oh, thank Christ.
I wouldn't sound too elated.
- Wh... But... But she's alive?
- I just said so.
- Did you call the police?
- No.
- Why not?
- (CRUNCHING FOOTSTEPS)
- (ALICE WHIMPERS)
- Alice? Is that... Is that Alice?
- WOMAN: Quiet now.
- Please, please put her on the phone!
- Shush. Stay in the car. Stay in the car.
- Don't hurt her!
You do let your imagination
run away with you.
- But I suppose we all create stories.
- There isn't a story.
The girl ran... ran
in front of the car in the dark.
This wasn't Alice's fault.
She did everything she could to save her.
That... That's...
That's the truth.
That doesn't explain
why she's here.
Driving while intoxicated.
- What do you want?
- A better story.
Are you... Are you a parent?
Mm-hm.
Then you understand
how far you'd go to...
to protect your own child.
You... You understand that?
All Alice did, all she did
was... was drive into the woods
to escape a stressful situation.
It was me... I was the one
who... who told her to hide the body
because I didn't want anyone
to find out until we got there.
My... My wife was then to drive her home
and I was to stay and take the blame.
But I... I promise you we were...
we weren't going to run.
I'm... I'm the one responsible,
not Alice.
I'm... I'm the one... I'm the one to blame.
And that's the story.
Pl... Please...
No parent wants to be
their child's monster.
Nobody wants to tell them no.
And then they grow up
and it's too late.
My husband and I
learned that the hard way.
Similar to how you are now.
And we've been atoning, paying
back the piper ever since.
That's decided, then. You
should talk to your daughter.
(CRUNCHING FOOTSTEPS)
Thank you.
- (CAR DOOR OPENS)
- It's Alice, yes? Here.
You're dehydrated and faint.
Have some water. Drink.
Good. Now, talk to your parents.
ALICE: Hello.
Are you okay?
ALICE: I don't understand.
How can she still be alive?
Alice, you were so terrified
that you'd killed her,
you convinced yourself it was true.
But the most important thing is she's...
she's... she's gonna be okay.
Mom?
I don't know. Maybe...
Maybe we missed her heartbeat.
But I felt her chest collapse.
- Alice, you saved her life.
- If I'd called an ambulance...
She's gonna be okay.
And... And you're gonna be okay.
And the woman will still let us
go along with the plan
to say that I was
the one driving, all right?
Nothing will change. Okay?
It has to be your decision, Alice.
- No, the decision's been made.
- No. Frank, we can't make it for her.
Why can't...
Why can't you let this work?
Cos I know what happens if you
don't face what you've done.
It breaks you down.
Every part of you.
I had to quit being a paramedic.
What do you mean?
I'd been ignoring
the warning signs for a while.
You know, the alarm bells telling me
that I couldn't do it any more.
Then I was called out to a woman
my age, in a shopping centre.
And when we arrived at the scene,
I could see that she was having a panic attack.
And she presented exactly
as I would have expected.
Difficulty breathing, cramping fingers,
wide, staring eyes.
We get these cases all the time.
I'm good at them.
I can always talk someone
through a panic attack.
And my colleague said, "I think
we should take her to hospital."
And I said, "No, she'll be fine
in a minute."
And then she wasn't, and I couldn't
get her to regulate her breathing,
so we had to move, and in the ambulance
she went into cardiac arrest.
And I did CPR,
but I couldn't bring her back.
And when we got to the hospital,
the A&E doctor in charge
told me that she'd had
a massive pulmonary embolism.
She'd had multiple clots
on her lungs.
And I'd missed it. I'd asked
all the wrong questions.
And I... I was so sure
about what I was looking at,
I was so sure it was a panic
attack that I'd missed it.
And... And nobody blamed me.
It was considered
an understandable mistake.
So I handed in my resignation.
So, Alice, it has to be
your decision, sweetheart.
It can't... Dad and I can't
make it for you, all right?
ALICE: I left her there.
The girl, just like me.
I saw my face on her body.
Yeah...
If she lives,
then I want to say sorry.
I want to do the right thing.
Okay.
I'm gonna tell the woman
before it's too late.
- How far away are you?
- We're close. A couple of minutes.
Okay. Then I'll see you in a bit.
(BEEPING)
I'd forgotten how deep this goes.
Why would anyone
come here at night, alone?
Here we go.
Something's not right.
Alice? Alice? Al?
What the fuck? Where are they?
Would the police just pick them up and go?
- No, no, no, they wouldn't do that.
- Mads, there's no one here!
Alice? Al?
Frank. Frank.
It's the girl!
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
Mads, they lied!
(DIALS NUMBER)
WOMAN: Emergency services.
- Which service do you require?
- I need the police.
- Connecting you now.
- MAN: Go ahead, caller.
You're through to the police.
What's the address of your location?
It's Ashfolk Forest...
Hallow Road, Ashfolk Forest, National Park.
- Yes, may I take your name, please?
- It's Madeline Finch.
- And the nature of the emergency?
- It's about a car accident.
My daughter was driving out here and she hit
and she killed someone with her car.
Okay, okay. An ambulance and police
have been dispatched to the area.
Did you witness the accident?
No, no, my husband and I
have only just arrived on the scene.
So you are present with your
daughter and the victim now?
No, the victim only.
- And your daughter?
- She... Well... She...
Hello?
(WHISPERS) Maddie, it's Alice.
- Mrs. Finch...
- Mads, it's Alice. It's Alice.
- (CRYING) Mads, it's Alice.
- Mrs. Finch?
It's Alice.
Mrs. Finch, hello?
Are you still there?
(MADDIE WAILS)
Hello? Mrs. Finch, talk to me.
I need you to say something, please.
(MADDIE WAILS)
Mrs. Finch, hello? Are you still there?
Mrs. Finch, are you okay?
Hello?
No, it can't be her.
It can't be her, Frank.
It's not her. Do you remember?
She said something and we heard her.
Do you remember? It can't
be her, Frank. It's not her.
- Mrs. Finch?
- It's not Alice. It's not her.
- Can you hear me?
- FRANK: Mads, it's her.
- I need to understand what's going on.
- Frank, she...
- Hello?
- It's not, Frank. It's not Alice.
Stop. Stop.
- It's not Alice.
- That's Alice.
- Don't you... Don't you remember?
- Hello?
She... She said to us
that the face was changing
and we heard something.
- We heard it.
- What are you talking about?
- Can you hear me?
- That's Alice.
- Hello? Mrs. Finch, talk to me. Hello?
- No, Frank. No, because she...
- Mads, what are you talking about?
- What are you talking about?
- No, Frank.
- Because we heard something...
- Mads.
And she told us
that the face was changing.
- What are you talking about?
- And we heard the horrible sound.
- And she's...
- That's Alice.
- Just shut up, Frank! Shut up!
Mrs. Finch, I need you to say some...
(RINGING TONE)
- Alice?
- (RUSTLING)
- Listen.
- (WHISPERS) Listen to this.
- (WHISPERS) What is that?
- Alice?
- (RUSTLING)
- ALICE: Mom?
- Alice, I'm here. I'm here.
(ALICE WHIMPERS)
- I feel sick.
- WOMAN: I'm sure.
We're here to help.
- Alice, where are you?
- ALICE: Mom, we're still in the forest.
(ALICE WHIMPERS)
They can't be far.
ALICE: Why are we still here?
Are we going to the hospital?
To the police? Is the girl okay?
WOMAN: No. She's dead, Alice.
You killed her.
You left her to freeze
in the woods on Hallow Road.
- ALICE: I don't... I don't understand.
- Yes, you do.
You knew she was dead
when you ran her down.
And you knew that was the end
of your own life,
your promising future, that nothing
would ever be the same again.
- You knew what you'd done.
- ALICE: No. (SOBS)
- I want my parents. Where are they?
- WOMAN: We're here, Alice.
ALICE: No! You're not my parents!
- Oh, but we are now.
- (ALICE SOBS)
Who you call your parents
are no longer in control.
Oh, my God!
They don't have what it takes
to liberate you
from this awful,
evil thing you've done.
- ALICE: What is this?
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
WOMAN: No parent wants to be
their child's monster, Alice.
They can't face what needs to
be done. But we can, Alice.
And we're here for you now.
As we were here
for the child before you.
And the child before her.
ALICE: Please, let me go!
(ALICE BREATHES HEAVILY)
Which way? Which way? Which way?
ALICE: Please, I don't want to be here!
WOMAN: No, but you deserve to be
here. You all asked for this.
ALICE: Mom!
WOMAN: A parent's base instinct
is to believe
that they can spare their child
from life's consequences.
That they can save you,
no matter the cost.
- So they make up stories.
- Is that them?
That's why you're on this path.
ALICE: I don't want to be here!
What is this? Where am I, please?
WOMAN: How far do you think
they'll go for you, Alice?
How long do you think
they'll keep driving?
ALICE: No, no, no. Please,
please, what are you doing?
WOMAN: Don't they know that
their story has no resolution?
ALICE: Please.
Where are you taking me?
WOMAN: With one endless road
after another...
- ALICE: Please.
- That just goes on and on.
No, no, no, no!
You've gotta move!
You've gotta move! Move!
You've got to move!
- Our daughter's there!
- ALICE: No! Where are you taking me?
- No, no, no! No!
- Please, give me my phone!
No, I need to fix this. Please,
let me have another chance!
- Please!
- WOMAN: It's too late.
Please. Please, please.
Give me another chance!
Maddie, they won't move!
They won't move!
ALICE: You don't understand.
I'm pregnant!
(ALICE SOBS)
WOMAN: Then we'll rectify
your child too.
- (ROARING)
- (ALICE SCREAMS) No!
(BEEPING)
(RINGING TONE)
(RINGING TONE CONTINUES)
You've reached Alice Finch.
I'm too busy for you right now.
Leave a message
if it's important. Bye!
(RINGING TONE)
(RINGING TONE CONTINUES)
(RAINDROPS PATTER)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
You've reached Alice Finch.
I'm too busy for you right now.
Leave a message
if it's important. Bye!
(RINGING TONE)
(DISTANT BIRDS SQUAWKING)
(INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
Initial impressions, the girl was wasted.
Crashed the car in a ditch.
Stepped in the middle of the road,
all disorientated,
someone ran her over in the dark.
Driver panicked, hid the body,
fled the scene.
That's not what
the parents are saying.
They identified the body.
They're convinced it's not
the body of their real daughter.
They said they were on the phone
to their daughter when it all happened.
DETECTIVE: It must be the trauma.
Probably struggling to come
to terms with everything.
OFFICER: Can you blame them?