( Birds chirping,
wind blowing softly )
( Woman laughing in distance )
( Squeals )
( laughing continues )
I love it here.
I know you do.
I can feel my life, you know?
Sportscaster on radio:
Pitch to Hatteberg.
Strike ball over the
outside corner, at the knees.
Appeared a little upset
with the call
by the home-plate umpire,
didn't appear to say anything.
( Continues indistinctly )
( Sportscast stops )
- Hey.
- Woman: Hey.
Morning, Dr. Fowler.
Morning, Natalie.
How you doing, boys?
Great!
Hey, Duncan,
sure you don't want to go?
- Want to get in here?
- No, he wants to stay here.
Scootch up.
Get in the middle there.
Come on. Bye, Dr. Fowler.
- Bye.
- Bye!
( laughing ) You don't
want to wave good-bye?
You don't want to wave good-bye?
( laughs ) Sweetie, what do
you want for breakfast?
Cereal.
Sportscaster: The WEEI
Red Sox radio network.
Announcer: You've been listening
to "Red Sox Replay."
WQSS Camden's repeat broadcast
of Boston Red Sox baseball
has been brought to you
by George C. Hall & Sons
of Rockland in business
in mid-coast since 19...
( foghorn blowing )
( Back-up signal beeping )
There you go.
( Engine slowing )
Oh, boy.
You see what happened
to this poor fella?
What?
Well, look. He lost an arm.
See, the trap has nylon nets,
called heads,
two side side heads
to let the lobster crawl in
and inside, what they call
a bedroom head
to hold the bait
and keeps him from escaping.
Now you know the old saying
"two's company,
three's a crowd"?
Well, it's like that.
You, uh, get more than
two of these in a bedroom
and chances are something
like that's going to happen.
That's why Frank can't
leave these traps
for more than a day.
Dad, show him this one.
Now
the older females,
like this old gal
they're the most dangerous,
especially when they're
growing berries.
Berries?
Yeah, eggs. You see?
She could take out
two males, no problem.
That's when you get a lobster
you can't sell.
But this fine lady,
she, uh, she has it easy
'cause the state says
we have to let her go.
( Water splashes )
Okay, now, you think
you can handle this?
- Mm-hmm.
- Are you sure?
- Okay, go ahead.
Put her in the tank.
( Chuckles ) Good.
- Higher. Higher!
- Higher!
I'll swing you higher.
Like that?
- That high enough?
- ( sportscaster talking indistinctly )
Duncan: Yep.
Aah, Ruth hates these.
What?
I got the wrong kind of buns.
Maybe we can borrow hers.
Two.
You've had a lot, huh?
Here, sweetie.
Ah, what I would give
to have back my youth.
Yeah, well, Willis, you never
had that in your youth.
You can go play.
Hey, father, you made it.
If I don't get to see
you fellas here,
I don't get to see you at all.
Hey.
You want a beer?
No, I'm going to go see
if your mom needs
any help, okay?
- All right, good luck.
- Yeah.
( Knife chopping )
Excuse me.
Can I help you with
anything here?
Oh, yes, you can
hand me that bowl, dear.
Great.
- Uh, this one here?
- ( water running in sink )
Yes. Thank you.
I'm looking forward
to that concert on Labor Day.
The music's so unusual.
It's haunting, really.
It is, isn't it?
Mmm.
How did you learn about
that, uh, style?
- At Brown.
- Ah.
I did my thesis
on Eastern European folk music.
Oh, I thought about
becoming a teacher.
Oh, why didn't you?
Mommy!
Yeah? What are you eating?
Nothing.
Is it good?
Yeah.
Swing me. Swing me.
Okay, I'll swing you, Dunc.
I'll be right back.
So, Mr. Strout mentioned
you again.
I'll bet he did.
He still talks about you.
Says you're the best can-packer
he ever had.
Yeah?
Says you looked real cute in
that hair net.
Excuse me, boys. An offering.
Here, father.
Thank you.
So that's what
Charles Sr.'s doing
and, uh, Becky went
to the hairdressing academy
after high school.
Of course, after she got married
she decided she wanted to stay
home with the boys, you know.
She still loves doing hair,
though.
Where do you go, father?
I just go to Super cuts.
Wha?
You can't request
the same girl at Super cuts.
Man: I tell you, those boys
are having a great time.
It was good of you
to do this for them.
Well, she hasn't
brought them before
because she's embarrassed.
She shouldn't be embarrassed.
I wish you hadn't put up
that monstrosity.
We're just going to have to
take it apart when they leave.
- What, the swing?
- The swing.
Oh, Ruth, he's a kid.
What do you expect?
"Happy birthday. Here's a box.
Drag it around for a while."
He's a kid.
He's like me, he wants it now.
( Gasps ) Oh, the cake.
Oh, great.
Man on radio: Find solutions
to fit your unique goals
and 3,500 New England
team members to help you...
Hey, there, birthday boy,
come here!
- Daddy, daddy!
- Yeah, Duncan!
( laughs )
♪ Happy birthday to you
Hey.
♪ Happy birthday, dear Duncan
♪ Happy birthday to you
Mom, I don't want to go.
♪ Happy birthday to you,
Happy birthday to you ♪
Mom, I don't want to go.
Shit. What is he doing here?
♪ Dear Duncan
( growls playfully )
♪ Happy birthday to you
( grunts ) Hey, there, Jase.
Come on over here, buddy.
Daddy's taking us to the arcade.
I told you he'd come, butt face.
( laughs )
Hey, Jason, don't do that
to your brother.
Want me to do that to you?
We're supposed to meet
at the house at 6:30.
- I thought we were meeting here.
- Mnh-mnh.
All right.
You're welcome to stay
and have some food.
My dad's cooking.
( Sportscaster
talking on radio )
Matt?
Should we do something?
No.
It's okay.
I'll, uh
I'll see you later, then.
Okay.
A little while.
Oh.
Ruth: She's not
divorced yet, you know.
Matt: It's the same thing.
Maine has crazy laws,
that's all.
Anyway, he loves her boys.
Oh, God, you don't think
he wants to...
No, he's not going to marry her.
Well, then what's he
doing with her?
She probably loves him.
Girls always have.
Let's just leave it at that.
( Sighs )
Well, he won't listen to me.
I've asked him three times
to dismantle that swing set.
Oh, leave it up.
Looks like a young
couple lives here.
( laughs )
Well, he needs his head
in school not in her.
So to speak.
- ( Shocked gasp )
- Ow.
It would help if you
were on my side.
Oh, I can be on your side.
( Chuckling )
- I've got a needle.
- Here I come, ready or not.
- You don't need those.
( Tone beeps )
Mr. And Mrs. Adams on?
Okay, you can put your shirt
back on now.
Yesterday, he was up
and around all afternoon,
but today he tumbled.
He's fallen twice.
I have all I can do
to get him up.
He's weak.
Said when he couldn't
work no more,
he didn't want to live.
For a while, he sat
and just mended our nets
but he can't do that no more.
How's your dad, Matt?
Oh, I'm sorry, doctor.
Now, Elwyn, you remember,
Jesse Fowler passed away
a while ago.
We were at his funeral,
remember?
( Fax machine dialing )
Back in an hour, Janelle.
Uh, forgot my lunch.
Starting to become a habit.
You just missed him, Matt.
He went home for lunch today.
Oh, right.
I forgot, he's got an interview.
( Door closes )
Frank?
Hello?
Hey, Frank!
Yeah, dad?
What are you doing here?
I thought you were driving
to Boston for the interview.
Yeah. No, it was rescheduled.
- Uh-huh.
- ( footsteps approaching )
Hi, Dr. Fowler.
Oh, hi.
Uh, where are the boys?
Um, they're with my mom.
Um.
Do you like coleslaw?
Mm-mmm.
Have some more.
Sure?
I got 'em.
Put your clothes on.
Hands up. Chin up.
- Mom, I want to play.
- All right, all right.
- Hey, mom, there's Frank.
- Here's your hat.
Wave, you guys.
Mom, hurry up. I'm late.
I'm hurrying.
I'm hurrying. I'm hurrying.
You'll play too,
but first, we'll watch him.
Hey, Frank.
Did you tell your mom
how good it was?
How good what was?
Aw, Frank had quite a time
this afternoon.
Loved your coleslaw.
Ate enough for two.
Well, that's what it's for.
- Hot dogs?
- Yeah, I'll take one.
No.
So, how are the kids?
Things okay?
Yeah, they're fine.
Good. That's good.
Oh, how was your interview?
It was... it was... it was great.
Good.
Jason!
( Singsongy ) Jason.
She's such a brave girl.
That's it.
You're driving me nuts, ma.
I've had lots of girlfriends
and I don't understand
why this one is any different.
I know you don't.
We're not serious, ma.
No?
No.
It's a summer thing.
Mmm, I see.
How'd you get in this time?
Chimney.
Thank you.
What can I help you with?
I was just dropping
that off for Jason.
What?
That.
I didn't know where
you'd want to put it.
It's about time he got it.
What am I going to do with it?
It is really going to mean
a lot to him, rich.
He's really been
improving lately.
Yeah, so I heard.
Would have been nice
if you'd come to his game.
I just got your message.
Where are they, with him?
That's none of your business.
I see, they're my boys, but
they're none of my business.
You know what I mean.
Yeah.
( Clears throat )
I was thinking
about moving back,
here with you and the boys.
What are you talking about?
What am I talking about?
I'm talking about moving back
is what I'm talking about.
I know what you're thinking.
It's different now.
Yeah?
Yeah.
How's the job?
Your father take you
back on at the cannery?
That's funny.
Still getting checks,
aren't you?
Or do I have to call
my father's accountant?
Hey, did you see my
new rig out there?
It's really nice.
It's not exactly new.
I traded David the truck for it.
It's got room for all of us.
Good grocery-getting car.
You want to take a ride?
Rich, you don't change.
You don't change, do you?
Change? No.
No, I don't change.
Everything around me changes.
You change.
You take my house
and you take my kids
and you fuck this other guy
but me, I don't change at all.
It's not your house.
Oh, really?
No, as far as
( whispers ) fucking goes
who was it that answered
the phone the other morning?
She just...
It doesn't matter. I don't care.
It's not working.
Nat
I just want a chance.
For what?
So you can pretend
they have a real father
- for a few days, and then...
- I am their real father!
I am their father.
No, Richard.
You know what defines a father?
It's what he does.
Not what he promises.
It's being a positive,
consistent presence.
( Chuckling )
A positive, consistent presence.
Wow.
What does that mean?
I just don't get it.
But then I'm not fucking
a college boy, am I?
Look, uh...
Can you just go now?
I don't want you here
when they get back.
Oh, you wouldn't want that?
- No.
No, you have to leave now.
Okay.
I'll see you later, Richard.
Yeah. Good-bye, Nat.
Hey.
You know, I've been ignoring
our difference in age
but you keep playing
with those blocks,
I'm going to start to worry.
You're not looking at the house.
Look.
It's not all mine.
It's part Mack.
See, the whole idea
of what Mack was trying
to achieve was a common area
in the center of the house.
I mean, large open spaces,
they weren't unique to Mack,
but the idea of separating
the family
so that the parents
were on one side
and the kids are on the other,
so they'll all spill
into the center.
It's brilliant. It's
I'm boring you, aren't I?
No. Mnh-mnh.
I was just thinking.
About what?
About you.
School.
What if I wait a year?
Frank...
- A year is not going to make...
- No, you can't do that, Frank.
Why not?
I've thought a lot about this.
I have, and...
No, y...
You told me it takes forever
just to establish yourself.
Exactly. So what's a year
in forever?
That's twisted logic.
Do you know what Duncan
said to me today?
Oh, you wouldn't be changing
the subject, would you?
He said,
"Frank, I don't think Jason
really understands girls."
Oh, he didn't.
He did.
( Both laughing )
"Understands girls."
Well, what'd you say?
I didn't know what
to say to that.
I said, "Give him time, Duncan.
He'll come around."
If this is how he is now,
then we're in trouble.
What is this, Action Man?
Yeah. Richard gave it
to Dunc for his birthday.
( Women singing
Balkan folk song )
Very good.
Okay, it's 7:30.
We should stop now.
Now remember when
you sing these words
the way we feel about the harbor
is how the Balkans felt
about the River Sava.
And listen to your tapes!
"Mmollih ta"
is still very rough,
and we've got
a 40-minute program
to have ready by Labor Day.
Labor Day.
Oh, and Anna?
Yeah, Ms. Fowler?
Next time, duck.
Yoo-hoo.
Yeah. Great.
( Groaning )
Dad... is that acid?
What are you putting in there?
Oh, my God. What happened?
Come on, Frank. Hold still.
All right, dad.
This was her husband, wasn't it?
Ex. He dropped in.
You going to press charges?
No.
Well, what's to stop him
from doing it again?
Did you hit him at all?
Come on, tell me tell me
you hit him.
- Matt.
- Just so he doesn't do it again.
I don't think I touched him.
Aah! Jesus, Dad.
So what are you going to do?
Take karate?
Oh, that is not the problem.
Mom, you know you like her.
I like a lot of people, Frank.
What about the boys,
did they see it?
No, they were asleep.
Did you leave
her alone with him?
He left first.
She was yelling at him.
I believe she had
a skillet in her hand.
Oh, for God sakes.
Did you call the police?
Not yet.
- You didn't call them?
- Well, I just got in.
When did I have chance
to call the police?
- Where's the phone book?
- No, mom, no, don't call them.
If you call the police,
they'll come over
- and scare the kids.
- Matt?
- We got to call them.
- No, we're not calling them.
It was a scuffle.
That's it. It wasn't serious.
Oh, right, just like the
relationship isn't serious.
Oh, Ruth. Now is not the time.
Well, when is the time, after
he knocks him into a coma?
This is stopping now.
Oh, really?
Come fall, you're on a plane.
Are you taking them with you?
What are the boys going to think
when you just disappear?
Hey, easy, mom.
Frank, this is not some
sweetie from Vassar
that you can visit on holidays.
You're not in this alone.
And the sooner you end it,
the better.
( Quietly ) Oh, God.
What are we going to do?
I don't know.
Well, you've got
to talk to him, Matt.
( Sighs )
I don't know.
Maybe he's right about
scaring the kids.
Why don't we just sleep on it,
deal with it tomorrow?
Are you going to call
the police, or do I have to?
I just told you what I think.
If you want to call them,
call them.
It's not the first time
she's played around, you know.
She's not with the guy anymore.
No, I mean from before.
What are you talking about?
Oh, come on, you've heard
the same things I have.
You seem to forget.
I don't take my lunches
in the teachers' lounge.
Maybe he still loves her.
Best part of the cod.
The outsiders,
they won't touch it.
Summer fishermen...
Well, the part-timers
like Frank here...
Get in your hair.
As many as 80 of them
now with licenses.
Hmm. Should've put up a sign.
"Stay in your own backyard,
or lose your traps."
See, Henry here is just sore
'cause I catch about
twice as much as he does
with an old second-hand
Boudreau.
Don't you listen to him, son.
That boat is fine.
She was my first.
I kind of miss her, sometimes.
And that truck you're driving.
When are you headed back
to school, Frank?
Hmm?
( laughing )
Hi, Dr. Fowler.
How you doing, Jason?
Good.
What'd you pull?
Not too bad.
About 40 pounds.
I haven't caught sight
of you in days.
You know where to find me.
When are you coming home?
Has it come to this?
Come to what?
You having to run errands
for mom.
I'm thinking of building
a couple hundred more traps,
see if I can do better
than break even.
Take you more than two years
to get a license
to fish off-season.
Right. Unless Henry takes me
on as his stern man.
You think he'd do that?
Maybe.
It's as good a life as any.
It was good enough
for your father
and sometimes things
just skip a generation.
You don't think...
You don't think you
might need something more?
Why?
So I can have an Ivy League
education like you, and
Christ, if it's so great,
how come you sneak
out of the office
every day to come down here?
I like spending time
with my son.
Uh-huh.
I don't know, dad.
It's just... I don't know.
She's a wonderful girl.
And that's what I see.
Hey, Frank!
How long you gonna
be parked there?
I'd like to unload!
Give me a hand?
Yeah, sure.
You can't hypnotize the cards
into changing, Matt.
For Christ sake, bet,
or you know Carl's gonna start.
The begger's dog
and the widow's cat.
Feed them
and thou wilt grow fat.
The gnat sings
his summer's song.
Poison gets
from slander's tongue.
The poison of the snake and newt
is the sweat of envy's foot.
The poison of the honeybee
is the artist's jealousy.
All right, Carl. Two bucks.
I'll tell you, man, you got
to get out of this Blake thing.
You're in a rut.
Don't get him started, Matt.
Whenever I do my own stuff,
you guys bitch and moan.
- That's not true!
- We love your stuff.
- It's great stuff, right?
- ( laughter )
Carl?
I'm in.
Everybody in? Frankie, you in?
( All groaning )
Guess I'm the winner.
Always the quiet ones.
Deal.
Come on. Come on.
Don't mind me.
Your father's snoring.
( Sniffs ) Ugh...
Eat.
You must be hungry.
I'm not hungry.
Coffee?
So you talked to her?
Yeah.
And how is she?
She's great.
Frank, I just I just
wanted to tell you that we...
That I liked her.
Do like her.
She's a wonderful girl.
Ma, you're not really
going to have this conversation
with me right now, are you?
- Good night.
Okay. All right.
No, that's fine, sir.
I'll send it to you right away.
Okay.
Oh, yes, I'm very excited.
I'm, uh...
It's a beautiful campus, and I'm
I'm, uh, preparing already.
Yes. Oh, thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Yes, well,
compared to your models...
It doesn't compare to your
models, but
I am.
I'm aware of the Lautner House.
Yeah.
Excuse me, sir,
can you hold on one second?
( Beep )
Hello?
Jase?
Jase, what is it?
Okay, Jason, stay put.
I'll be right there. Stay put.
Natalie: He just, um
he just pushed me,
he didn't hit me.
He didn't hit you. That's great.
We should throw a party for him.
He didn't hit you.
Frank.
That's enough of this.
We're calling the police.
No, w-w-w-w-w-wait,
wait... uh-uh.
Natalie,
we're calling the police.
No, no, I don't...
I don't know what I want to do.
I don't... I hate this.
I hate the kids seeing this.
I... I don't know what to do.
( Sobbing )
Hey, it's okay. It's okay.
I'm here now. I'm here now.
It's all right.
I'm not going anywhere.
Okay.
It's all right.
Okay, okay.
Mom!
Oh!
( Pounding on door )
Go upstairs with the kids.
No. I'm afraid.
Natalie, go upstairs!
I'm not letting him in
the house! Go upstairs!
No. Uh-uh.
It's better if
he doesn't see you.
Go upstairs.
Don't let him in.
- Go.
- Frank, don't let him in.
Richard: Open the door!
Frank? Frank, buddy,
you in there?
Frank, I'm really sorry about
what happened, all right?
I apologize.
I'm sorry about what happened.
Now open the door.
Richard, leave. Leave now!
I'm not letting you
in this door.
She left. Natalie is gone.
She's not here,
and I'm calling the police
if you don't leave.
Just go.
All right. All right.
( Rattling )
Motherfucker!
Read him a story.
I'll be right back, okay?
I don't want to stay here!
You have to.
You have to stay here.
Look at me.
You're staying here, okay?
Read him a story.
Jason: Clock, clock, tick-tock.
Where's the clock?
What time is it?
You're fucking lying!
Where is she? Natalie!
Put that away! Put that away!
( Gunshot )
( Screams )
No!
( Sobbing ) No!
( Running footsteps )
Mommy!
( Intercom beeps )
Woman: Matt, there's a
Mrs. Strout on line two.
She says it's very important.
Hello?
Hello, Natalie?
( Choir singing haunting
Balkan folk song )
( Singing continues )
Great.
Priest: Your fear of death
is but the trembling
of the shepherd
when he stands before the king
whose hand is to be
laid upon him in honor.
Is the shepherd not joyful
beneath his trembling
that he should wear
the mark of the king?
Yet is he not more mindful
of his trembling?
For what is it to die
but to stand naked in the wind
and to melt into the sun?
And what is it
to cease breathing
but to free the breath
from its restless tides
that it may rise and expand
and see god unencumbered?
Only when you drink
from the river of silence
shall you indeed sing.
And when you have reached
the mountaintop
then you shall begin to climb.
And when the earth
shall claim your limbs
then shall you truly dance.
( Subdued indistinct
conversation )
( laughing )
Can I get you anything?
Uh... where's Ruth?
She went to lie down, Matt.
Excuse me.
( Applause on television )
Man: My next guest is
a very talented funnyman
who will be performing live
at the end of the month
at the Montreal Comedy Festival
"Just for Laughs."
Please welcome Anthony Clark!
( Cheers and applause )
Clark: Wow.
Host: How we doing?
They're so nice. Wow.
- They're good people.
- They really are.
Some of them were packing,
but we've cleared that up.
- That's good.
- So what's been going on?
Well, you know, I've actually
been out with Ricky Martin,
livin' the vida loca.
( laughter )
You know Ricky?
Actually, when you hang out
with Ricky,
a lot of people want
to speak Spanish to you.
And I think that's cool.
I took three years
of Spanish in high school...
( lawnmower in distance )
( Knock on door )
Yeah?
Matt, I'm going to go to lunch.
Okay.
Can I get you anything?
No, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm... I'm okay.
Okay.
( Dinnerware clattering )
Don't worry, I didn't make them.
I wanted the cheese.
What? Oh. That's mine.
( Chuckles ) Sorry.
You got back to work
so quick, Matt.
It's not too soon?
I can't stay home.
So, how's business?
Oh, you know, same old crap.
Got held up again.
Well, you knew that.
- No, I didn't.
- Yeah.
They got 75 bucks.
Were you on the till?
They'd have gotten something
else if I'd been on the till.
( Both chuckle )
So, how you doing, Matt?
You don't write, you don't call.
Where'd the love go?
Nag, nag, nag.
( Chuckling )
They set the bail hearing yet?
Uh, sometime in
the next few days, yeah.
Are you going?
I don't know.
Davis says it's
a formality, really.
I haven't talked with Ruth
about whether or not
she thinks we ought to go.
If it's too much for Ruth,
I'll come with you.
Thanks.
Uh, it'll be all right.
Davis says it's
a formality, really.
The criminal trial set yet?
Uh, October.
October?
That's what they tell me.
Christ, they take their time.
Well, he's in there now.
They're keeping him busy,
I'm sure.
You know where they'll
move him, once he's sentenced?
Got any, uh, Tabasco?
Hey, Anita! Tabasco!
Hey!
Aw, shit.
Next weekend, Matt,
we really want you to
come up to the camp.
Katie's insisting.
Not to pressure you or anything,
but if you don't come
she's going to invite her
sister and that idiot
and I'm going to wind up
insulting him again.
The future of my family
is in your hands.
Uh... let me ask Ruth.
Woman on television:
So the combination of spices
is very Southern,
and I'll tell you
what makes it Southern.
There are coriander seeds,
which I'm going to put...
- Hi!
- How was your day?
Fine.
I had lunch with Willis.
It was really great to see him.
My day was fine, too, thanks.
Sorry, did you say something?
No.
Katie and Willis invited us
up to the camp for the weekend.
I said I'd check with you
in case we were doing
something else.
That sounds fine.
We, uh, we don't have to go.
You don't want to?
Yeah, I want to.
Then tell them yes.
Well, I thought you might be
busy getting the girls ready.
No.
Okay.
All right,
the next matter is the matter
of State of Maine
v. Richard Strout.
The record should reflect
that the defendant
has been incarcerated
in the Knox County Jail
without bail
since the 17th of July.
We're here for a bail hearing.
Mr. Davis, given the fact
that we have a very
crowded trial calendar
I'm going to suggest that we do
both the bail hearing
and the probable cause hearing
today at 2:00.
So unless I hear any
objection to the contrary.
I'd like to set it for 2:00,
and we will take testimony
of your witnesses at that time.
Natalie: I
I closed the door.
I
I walked t-through my room.
( Voice breaking)
I heard some yelling.
I heard yelling. Heard yelling.
I got to the stairs
( sighs )
And then I heard
I heard the shot.
Richard...
- Lawyer: I-I'm sorry.
- ( sobs ) Richard...
Could we go back just a minute?
Mrs. Strout, you said
you heard the shot.
Yes.
You heard the shot?
Did you actually witness
the accident?
Objection, your honor,
there are no grounds
to indicate this
was an accident.
Sustained.
Strike the word "accident"
from the record.
Rephrase your question,
Ms. Keyes.
Mrs. Strout, in the
police report you stated
that you had witnessed
the firearm discharge.
Did you witness
the firearm discharge?
I thought you said there
would be a jury trial
some time in October.
If he was incarcerated
the judge would have set
an October court date
basically to save the county
the cost of housing
and feeding him as an inmate.
But, with bail, unfortunately,
the court date is always later.
You mean there's nothing
we can do about this?
You let that bastard
just walk out,
and we're supposed
to just sit here?
We can't appeal bail.
It's just not set up that way.
The state's ball code is to
ensure future court appearances.
Now, in this case,
Strout's family was prepared
to put up a substantial
amount of property as bail.
That, along with his ties
to the community
made it very hard for us
to convince a judge
that there was a serious
risk of flight.
Now, you can file a civil suit.
I recommend it. But not now.
Wait until after
the criminal trial.
Ruth: And when will that be?
Well, honestly could be anywhere
from 12 to 18 months.
Oh, my God.
You're confident you can put him
away for good then, right?
The things she said in there,
what's the damage?
The way this is going,
potentially manslaughter.
Jesus Christ.
He killed our son!
He... it was no accident.
Ruth, Ruth, Ruth, Ruth.
Uh. How long will
he be sent away for?
Well, that's hard
to say, really.
Anywhere from five to 15 years.
But we're confident that
we'll get the maximum.
- So even with good behavior...
- Five years?
- He'll do ten full years.
- Ten years?
Are you out of your mind?!
Dr. Fowler, Mrs. Fowler,
I'm sorry.
I understand.
No, you don't.
( Whispering ) No, you don't.
Reporter: Dr. Fowler,
what will your next step be?
Matt: Uh, I don't know.
Reporter: Dr. Fowler,
how do you feel
about the result today?
Matt: Well, that's...
That's something
Dr. Fowler, have you had
any contact with Mrs. Strout?
Matt: No.
How's Mrs. Fowler handling this?
Do you feel that justice
has been served today?
I think our legal system
will determine that.
( Camera shutter clicking )
( Reporters clamoring )
- ( Door closes )
- Can you believe this?
I ask those idiots to leave,
and no one budges, not one.
What are we supposed to do,
make them sandwiches?
What are you asking for?
What?
If you want them to leave,
tell them to leave.
Okay, I'll tell them to leave.
Good.
Woman on television:
And they never come up
to the standard.
And so they're always and
forever disappointed.
Always.
They're never doing enough.
They're never
working hard enough.
They never behaved right enough.
They were never
a good enough father
never a good enough husband.
And not only can they not
please themselves sad to say,
most of the time nobody else
can please them either.
You slept late for you.
Yeah, I took one of your pills.
You never do that.
Mmm.
Well, there it is
in black and white.
You should read some
of the things he says.
It's unbelievable.
Yeah.
Well, I, uh, I better be going.
Where? It's Saturday.
Oh, there's some stuff I have
to catch up on at the office.
I won't be long.
( Door opens and closes )
( Cash register keys beeping,
receipt printing )
Thank you.
Do you want your receipt?
Matt: Natalie.
Hi.
I, uh, hope I'm not
disturbing you.
Unh-unh.
Not at all.
Could you break a 50, please?
Excuse me.
( Register beeps, whirs )
Thank you, dear.
Could I possibly have
another bag?
Oh, sure.
( Door bell tinkles )
Yeah, well, I was just, uh...
just wondering how you're doing.
I tried to reach you.
Oh.
Um.
We're at my mom's now.
I wanted to call you.
That's... that's okay.
Dr. Fowler, I
can't
yeah, I-I know.
I didn't lie.
I didn't lie the first time.
It was...
It's how it came out.
( Door bell tinkles )
Mrs. Fowler?
No, uh...
Man: Can I get a pack
of Marlboro Reds?
( Register beeping )
( Bangs register )
( Receipt printing )
( Door bell tinkles )
( Door closes )
How are the boys?
They all right?
Yeah.
Uh, I got to go.
I'll see you.
So how much of this is yours?
( Chuckles )
You ask me that every time.
You know the cove,
the other side of the cabin?
Yeah.
All the way to
the other shoreline.
Almost 350 acres.
Know what it went for
when I bought it?
No.
You don't want to know.
( Both chuckle )
Oh, and that's little Charles
down at the pool.
He figured out how to
get down to the pool
on the elevator by himself.
Oh, he must've been very proud.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, and that's Shannon
waiting in line for...
Oh, my God, that roller coaster.
You know the one? Oh, my God.
Were the lines very long?
Uh, yeah, yeah, sometimes.
60 minutes and upwards.
Unless, of course,
you got the, um, Fast pass.
What's the Fast pass?
Uh, well, you know,
you got all these different
kingdoms there and, uh,
so you take this Fast pass.
It's kind of a laminated card.
You just put into a machine
and it tells you
when to come back
so, you know, you don't
have to wait in line.
You just go right in and...
You guys ever go to Florida?
No.
How many grandchildren
do you have now?
Um...
( laughs )
Uh, well, all right, there's
little Charles and Shannon
um, the three older ones
and the babies.
( Quietly )
Joe, Jay, Mary, George
Wendy, Lee... so that's 11.
Must be wonderful.
Willis always says
"I guess there's no danger
of us dying off."
( Voice breaking )
I'm so sorry, Ruth.
I just wasn't thinking.
I wanted to have more, uh,
but we had Frank,
and... Matt was just
starting his practice.
So I guess it made sense.
Little Charles.
Willis: Only got half
a cord of oak left at home.
And you know how much that
bastard Daniels charges.
At least I can stack this
up to the cabin
have something
to burn this fall.
Katie: You know,
it's a wonderful product
and they treat you pretty good.
On account of selling Mary Kay,
we got the new Subaru.
Well, the ride up
was very comfortable.
It's a very nice car.
Well, it's not really a car.
It's got four-wheel drive.
It's a little SUV.
What the hell is
all that "SUV" crap?
Willis:
"Sports utility vehicle."
It's a little Jeep.
SUV?
( laughing ) ATV and KFC.
What's with all these...
Uh, these, uh...
- Acronyms.
- Yeah.
I guess it's just
too much trouble
to say what something
is anymore.
What does PMS stand for?
All right, I was an Army brat.
I grew up with Jeeps.
Willy, he's uncomfortable
that I know more about one
masculine thing than he does.
Only one?
( laughter )
Thanks, buddy.
I like this guy.
You've done a nice job
up here, Katie.
Don't tell me you made
these curtains.
Is that antique linen?
Well, sort of.
They're pillowcases
from our first house.
I've saved every knickknack
and whim-wham we ever had,
you included.
Willis: Well, our timing is off.
( Matt chuckles )
Of course, he don't like working
in recruitment, anyhows.
Christ, they got them boys
coming down
to the office in the mall.
He gets them half-processed
and they decide
they want to take
that "delayed entry" thing.
Christ, I couldn't do it.
Katie: Or they decide
not to join up at all.
Willis: Like that one kid.
He had him all the way
through the works and, Christ.
Yeah the boy's folks
called, uh, called David
and said that the boy was...
He wanted out so bad
that he... well,
he'd taken his own life.
Something like that gets to you.
Christ, I couldn't do it.
I'm going now.
Okay.
Are you looking forward
to going back?
Mm-hmm.
You look nice.
( Chuckles )
( laughing )
( Woman singing )
( Choir singing
Balkan folk song )
( Singing stops )
That was very good.
I goofed up a little bit, but...
- Ruth.
- ( gasps )
It comes in waves.
And then nothing
like a rest in music.
No sound, but so loud.
I don't know what to do.
I... I feel so angry.
Louise McVey
lost a child a few years back.
Maybe you remember.
She had four.
It was the youngest, wasn't it?
Yes.
She told me about
a vision she had
when she found out
her daughter had died.
She saw herself at a great
distance from the Earth
and encircling it,
an endless line.
As she got closer
she saw that it was made up
of mothers
traveling forward.
She fell into line
and began walking with them.
When they reached
a certain point
the line divided,
and she said she knew
that all the millions
of women on her side
were the mothers
who had lost children.
She seemed to find
great comfort in that.
How did the little girl die?
A drowning, some kind
of swimming accident.
Oh.
The name of the game
is Texas chase 'em.
Henry: Oh, geez.
Is there a problem?
Why do you always delude
yourself with that crap?
- What are you talking about?
- Look, we're not in Vegas.
It's five-card draw
or seven-card stud.
That's what I said...
Five-card draw, jacks to open.
- Carl?
- Asshole.
I'll bet a buck.
Raise a buck.
( Sighs )
Say something, for Christ sake.
Quit pussyfooting around me.
You want me to stare
at these cards all night?
There are things
of which I may not speak.
There are dreams
that cannot die.
There are thoughts
that make the strong heart weak
and bring a pallor
into the cheek
and a mist before the eye.
And the words of that fatal song
come over me like a chill
"a boy's will
is the wind's will.
And the thoughts of youth.
Are long, long thoughts."
Okay, you got the two.
Willis: I'm in there.
I'll take one.
Willis: Okay, you got it.
I'm going to need...
Oh, I need them all... three.
Make them good.
( Couple talking indistinctly )
( Car door shuts )
( Metal clinks )
Matt?
Ah!
Sportscaster on radio:
Atlanta 1, Red Sox nothing.
From the stretch, Martinez.
Still one and two on Jordan.
He's hit 13 home runs.
He's got a teammate at third
with two down.
Ramon Martinez gets the sign,
checks the runner at third.
Comes to the belt
and to the plate.
A swing and a bouncer
up the middle.
Nomar fields it,
gloves it, throws to first.
Inning over.
They leave a man
in scoring position.
Jordan's out... six to three.
Good effort in that inning
by Ramon Martinez
against a tough hitter.
After two and a half innings,
Atlanta one, Red Sox nothing
on the WEEI
Red Sox radio network.
No. I'm sorry,
that's totally unacceptable.
Yeah, so what did he say?
He... no, we can't allow that.
Hold it a sec.
Excuse me, Matt.
Ryan Collit's out there.
His mother just brought him in.
I'll, uh, I'll call
you back later, okay?
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
I'll be back at 4:00, Janelle.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Dr. Fowler,
but you just missed him.
Thank you.
No, I really need to see him.
He go to lunch?
That's right.
He's across the street.
Thank you.
That's what they do, you know?
Oh, hey, Matt.
Hi.
Have a seat.
Thank you. Thank you.
- This is my assistant, Jack.
- Oh, hi, Jack.
- Don.
- Hi, Don.
This is Ed. That's Matt Fowler.
So how's everything going?
Oh, uh, it's...
It's okay, you know.
I just wanted to go over
a couple of things, and,
you know, when... when
you've had your lunch.
Sure.
We really are doing
everything we can, Matt.
- I promise you that.
- Yeah. What can I do, Bill?
There's nothing, really.
Look, it can't be manslaughter.
There's got to be something.
Can't you find something,
you know,
like... like some piece
of evidence?
I mean, that happens.
Doesn't that happen?
We really are doing
everything we can.
I'm not going to lie to you...
All we've got is Strout.
He claims that
there was a struggle.
Forensics can't determine if
there was a struggle because
of the condition of the house
when Frank got there.
The best thing for you to do
is just sit tight.
Now, we haven't thrown
in the towel yet
and you shouldn't either.
We've still got two
investigators
working on this case.
( Voice fading ) It's still
a priority case for us.
We've got leads we're
following up on...
( coins jingling loudly )
Before we wrap this up,
but we're doing the best we can
with the resources that we have.
You've just got to hang
in there with us.
You have to have
some confidence.
( Jingling continues )
( Alarm blares )
( Engine starts )
Man: He takes these bats and
nails them right on the wall
above the scale because he
knows big mouth's gonna come
in there and weigh his catch
eventually, you know?
He's putting the bats up,
one of the old-timers says.
"Hey, Ivan, what
the hell are you doing?"
The old man says,
"Sending a message,"
and turns around
and walks out the door, right?
Now, I walk in,
there's these damn baseball bats
up on the wall, right,
with a big, huge note written
right across the front of
them. ( Laughs ) - What'd it say?
"Here's the bats,
if you got the balls."
( Both laughing )
He never messed
with our traps again.
Hey, Dr. Fowler.
Oh, hi, Tim.
Did he ever, uh
did he ever talk to you
about what happened on that day?
No. No.
I don't even see
Richard anymore.
And he'd never tell me
anything anyway.
Believe me.
Oh, sure, sure. Of course not.
I was just wondering if...
If, uh, you know
maybe you heard something
through the grapevine.
Maybe, uh, maybe one
of his buddies said something?
No.
I was thinking...
His brothers still work
with you, right?
They must talk.
What I'm saying is,
if we could find something...
Just something concrete.
If you could...
It could be just, you know,
a slip of the tongue.
I'll keep my ears open.
Thank you.
It's funny running into
you here, Dr. Fowler.
Yeah, well...
( music playing indistinctly
through headphones )
( Click, music stops )
Oh, I was hoping we could talk.
I
I wanted to tell you
how truly sorry I am.
And
if there's anything
that I can ever
do to... to
talk with you...
Oh!
( Music playing indistinctly
through headphones )
( Men laugh )
Man, better get back
to the grind
and don't steal anything.
Hello, Mrs. Fowler.
Will there be anything else?
I want a pack
of Marlboro Lights.
Sure.
That will be, uh, $14.95
with the cigarettes.
Thank you.
Matt: How did it go today?
Something wrong?
Wrong?
What could be wrong, Matt?
What do you want?
I want to know what's going on.
Oh, right.
You're obviously upset.
Is there something
we can talk about?
Talk? Who, us?
What if somebody walked in?
They wouldn't recognize us.
They'd think they were
in the wrong house.
Do you want to talk or not?
Oh, you mean about
our dead son? No.
We haven't before.
Why should we bother now?
What can I do, Ruth?
Forget it, Matt.
Why don't you just go?
What do you want from me?
I want you to stop acting
like nothing's happened.
That's what I want.
Why, because I'm not
bouncing off the walls?
No, Matt,
that would require feelings.
We don't want you
to hurt yourself.
Do me a favor, Ruth.
You want a grieving contest,
go find someone else.
Oh, I know how you grieve.
Go have another beer.
What the hell is
that supposed to mean?
What do you know?
You know nothing.
You don't you don't know
what I go through.
No, I don't know
what you go through, Matt
or if you go through anything.
But that's your choice,
dear, not mine.
You're goddamn right it is.
My choice is not to
scream at the world.
Maybe one of us has to be
reasonable around here.
- You ever think of that?
- Reasonable?
Gee, Matt
I don't know about you,
but I miss my son.
I'm glad you have time
for reason.
That's what you imparted
to Frank, that sense of reason.
( Dish clatters )
Oh, he thought you were
very reasonable.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Are you... are you saying that...
That I'm the one responsible?
Is that it?
Well, uh
well, let me tell you something.
Let me tell you something.
- You got it backwards.
- ( water stops running )
I know what you think...
That... that I was too lenient.
That I let him get away with...
Everything! Everything!
Yes, yes, yes, and why?
Why did he ever come to you?
- He wouldn't listen to me!
- No, he wouldn't listen to you...
He wouldn't listen to you
because you never listened to him.
No, but you did.
You were winking at him
the whole time.
You encouraged him.
You wanted what he had... her.
Oh, my God,
you've got to be kidding!
Come on, you know it!
You wanted it
and you couldn't get it.
That's why you didn't stop him...
So you could get
your kicks through your son.
You can't admit the truth
to me or to yourself
that Frank died for your
fantasy piece of ass!
Oh, you know
y-you want to know
why our son is dead?
You really want to know?
He was with her not
because of me.
He went there because of you.
Yes, he did because
you are so controlling,
so overbearing,
so angry that he was it.
That he was our only one.
That is not true.
Oh, yes, it is. Yes, it is.
Even when he was a kid
you were telling him how...
How he was always wrong.
Oh, I remember
one time you yanked him
out of a Little League game
and sent him home
for throwing his...
His glove in the dirt.
He was what? Nine years old?
Everything he did was wrong.
Well, what was wrong
with him, Ruth?
You're... you're so unforgiving.
You are.
That's what he said.
And you're pulling
the same shit with me
and that's a horrible way to be.
It's horrible.
You're bitter, Ruth.
And you can point your finger
at me all you like
but you better take
a damn good look at yourself.
I just wanted to talk
about what happened, Matt.
( Chuckles )
You want me to be open with you,
embrace you?
You scare me.
How can I talk to you?
Sometimes I...
Sometimes I can't
even look at you.
( Tapping on door )
Oh, God.
( Tapping continues )
( Sighs )
That's probably the police.
Hi, there, I'm Kristen Gellar
from the Rockland
Gymnastics Association
and today we're selling
brand-name candy.
Each purchase is matched
by the Tandy Corporation
to help us meet our goal
of traveling to Oahu
to compete in the east/west
conference.
Uh, okay, I'll,
uh I'll take some.
Oh, and today we have a special.
Six bars for $10.
Okay, I'll, uh... I'll do that.
- Should I hold something?
- Yeah. Could you hold this?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Okay, there's... there's the 10.
Thank you.
Here.
You can pick anything you want.
Any six is... okay.
Ruth.
What I said just now...
I, uh
I had no right.
No one
no one should ever have
to hear stuff like that.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
No. You're right, Matt.
I am horrible.
Please, please, please don't.
I don't blame you.
It's just
that girl came by the school.
And I couldn't forgive her.
And I was
I was so.
I'm sorry.
I've been so
I've been so angry.
That's okay.
It's just.
I've seen him,
and I keep seeing him.
I know. I... I know.
In his room, you know,
sometimes I can swear
he's there.
And, uh, today, at a stoplight,
I could've sworn Frank...
Not Frank.
Richard.
( Sobbing )
And I don't know what to do.
Ruth, Ruth, Ruth.
Uh.
Where... where did you see him?
Everywhere. Downtown.
At the market.
I saw him...
I saw him at South End.
He smiled at me, Matt.
I keep running into him.
He smiled.
( Crying )
Oh, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
Katie: Honey,
are you coming to bed now?
Soon, baby. Matt's still here.
Oh. Well well, hi, Matt.
Uh, honey, when you come to bed,
would you bring me my pills?
Um, they're on the, um,
top shelf
from when the kids were here.
- All right.
- All right, thanks, dear.
Matt: I never thought
about bail.
I thought I wouldn't have
to worry about him for years.
You know what I heard?
He's tending bar up
to Old Orchard Beach
for a friend.
You ever notice even the
worst bastards have friends?
Well, nobody knows
him over there.
If they do, they don't care.
They drink what he mixes.
I hate him, Matt.
My boys went to school with him.
He was the same then.
You know what he'll do?
Five years at the most.
Yeah, I know.
Remember that woman
about seven years ago?
Shot her husband and dropped him
off the bridge in the St. George
with a 100-pound sack of cement
and said the whole way
through it, nobody helped her.
- You know where she is now?
- Where?
She's up to Sears port
now, a secretary,
and whoever helped her,
where the hell is he?
It'd break my heart,
Matt, it would.
But you ever think about just
moving away?
Yeah, we have.
It wouldn't matter.
Yeah.
( Woman singing slow
Balkan folk song )
( Women join in singing )
Let me lock the place up.
I'll walk you to your car.
Good night, Richard.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Wait up. Come on, you want
to come over for a drink?
No, thanks.
- Come on!
- Maybe some other night.
Just one drink?
( Engine starts )
Come on!
All right.
Fucking bitch.
What are you doing here?
Anything I can... help you with?
Don't talk.
Oh, God.
Unlock the door and get in.
Wait just a minute.
Let's calm down.
Let's calm...
All right, all right, all right.
All right.
( Whispering )
All right, all right.
All right.
Unlock it.
( Exhales deeply )
Is there anyone at your place?
Not tonight.
Good.
Drive there.
Drive slowly.
Don't try to get stopped.
All right.
He was making it with
my wife, Dr. Fowler.
Don't talk.
Let's go to the back door.
Keep your mouth shut.
Turn the light on.
Where's your suitcase?
My suitcase?
Yeah. Where is it?
Uh, in the bedroom closet.
Okay, that's where we're going.
When you come to a door,
stop and turn the light on.
Let's go.
There's no wall switch.
Where's the light?
By the bed.
Go ahead.
Sit down on the bed.
Which closet is it?
Where are the suitcases?
I wanted to work things out
with Natalie,
try to get back together again
but I couldn't...
I couldn't even talk to her.
He was always with her.
Dr. Fowler, it was an accident.
I'm going to jail to pay for it.
If I ever get out,
I'll be an old man.
Isn't that enough?
You're not going to jail.
Pack clothes for warm weather.
Y-you're going to let me go?
You're going to jump bail.
What?
Go ahead.
All right, all right.
See, it's, uh it's the trial.
We can't go through that,
my wife and I.
That's why you're leaving.
I've got you a ticket.
My wife keeps seeing you.
I can't have that anymore.
Thank you, Dr. Fowler.
I'd go pick up my boys,
and he'd be there.
Sometimes he spent the night.
Duncan told me.
I'm sorry, doctor.
All right, that's enough.
I, uh
I need some things
from the bathroom.
Keep walking.
I got to pee.
Go ahead.
( Foot kicks door)
( Zipper unzips )
( Urinating )
Wait.
Let's go.
You know they'll catch me.
They're going to check
passenger lists.
I didn't use your name.
They'll figure that out, too.
You think I wouldn't have done
it myself if it was that easy?
You were alone.
We got it worked out.
Who's we?
Start the engine. Let's go.
There's no planes
this time of night, Dr. Fowler.
Go north on 73.
The airport's south.
Someone's going
to keep you a while.
They'll take you to the airport.
Turn the radio on.
Find the game.
I-it's after 1:00.
They run it again.
No more talking.
( Rock music playing )
( Dialing stations )
( Crowd cheering )
Sportscaster: Let's see,
the last Red Sox player
to have a three-home-run game
would have been Trot Nixon
last year at Detroit.
Nomar had one previous to that.
Off with a fast ball. Ball one.
Galarraga holds
against Daubach at first.
The outfield swung
around to their left.
And a ground-ball roller
to shortstop.
Flip to second,
they force Daubach.
6-4 on the force, Garciaparra.
Actually hit into a force play
to end the inning.
6-4 to get Daubach at second.
The inning is over.
Red Sox have left seven.
After six, the Red Sox 7,
the Braves 2.
On the WEEI
Red Sox radio network.
Hit the scoring run,
there, one for two.
Six for ten with a home run,
three RBIs in the series.
Hits one into the air.
Turn around.
Why?
- We missed it! Turn around!
- Okay.
That's like using a
rolled-up newspaper
for that hit.
Sanders is up.
Homered his first time.
One for two.
His fourth of the year.
( Sportscaster continues
indistinctly )
There's nothing back here,
Dr. Fowler.
I don't understand why we don't
just drive to the airport.
You don't think
we'd leave your car
at the airport, do you?
Knuckleball over the
inside corner for strike two.
I'll get 20 years, Dr. Fowler.
I'll be 53 years old.
That's a year younger
than I am now.
Here's the pitch.
Inside. Just missed.
The crowd groans.
Where are we?
Almost there.
Turn it off.
Leave the lights on.
Is this your cabin, Dr. Fowler?
No, it isn't.
Let's get the bags.
( Vehicle door opens )
Mr. Grinnel.
I'll get them, son.
Wait.
You can take this.
( Running footsteps )
Matt!
What did you do?
This isn't what we talked about.
He, um...
He tried to run.
We were going to wait
and take him out in the woods.
I couldn't wait.
I better get the ATV.
( Thunder rumbling )
( Rain falling )
Wait.
( Twig snaps )
Come on. We got to go.
( Boat approaching )
( Metallic clanking )
Come on. Go.
( Train whistle blows
in distance )
What time is it?
It's ten to 4:00.
We lost an hour.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
High tide.
Can't stop people
from fishing, Matt.
Fucking bridge.
I'm sorry, Willis.
Stopped into his
little shed there once.
Place reeked.
The guy spilled more whiskey
than we've ever drunk.
We'll just pray he's already
three sheets to the wind.
Katie's pill will
be wearing off soon.
( Quietly ) Okay.
Okay. Okay.
All right.
Did you do it?
( Whispering )
Are you all right, Matt?
There was a picture of him
and Natalie on the wall.
What is it, Matt?
The way she was smiling.
What?
I don't know.
Matt.
What am I thinking?
You must be hungry.
( Ruth descending stairs )
Ruth: Matt?
Matt?
Do you want coffee?
( long sigh )
( Dog barking in distance )