(arrows whooshing)
(gentle inspiring music)
(air whooshing)
(metal scraping)
(air whooshes)
(simple bright music)
(graceful piano music)
(ethereal music)
(upbeat music)
♪ It's too late ♪
♪ For tears ♪
♪ Honey it's too late ♪
♪ Too late to cry ♪
♪ Oh but it's too late ♪
♪ Oh for begging me baby ♪
♪ Honey it's too late ♪
♪ Too late to cry ♪
♪ Now that you need me darling ♪
♪ I'm cruel to walk out
oh, oh ♪
♪ I provide, sacrifice for you ♪
♪ And I need, I'm
here without, oh, oh ♪
♪ But it's too late, oh ♪
♪ Oh for loving me baby ♪
♪ Honey it's too late ♪
♪ Too late to cry ♪
(gentle mysterious music)
(gentle mysterious
music continues)
(bell dings)
- Hello?
(TV chatters faintly)
Hello?
(ominous ambient music)
(ominous music)
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music continues)
(door creaking)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(door creaking)
- Oh, shit!
- Oh!
- Scared the, scared
the shit out of me.
I wasn't expecting
you till seven.
- Yeah. Sorry, I
didn't wanna be late.
- It's Gwen, right?
- Yeah. Gwen Taylor.
- Right. Teddy.
Teddy Miles. This is my place.
I appreciate you saving my
ass on such short notice.
- Yeah, of course.
- Yeah.
(TV chatters faintly)
- I noticed the window in
one of the rooms was open.
Cabin 18, the wind was
blowing at the door.
- Maybe you think you should
get a new quarterback. Geez.
So you just moved
to the area, or?
- Mm-hmm. From Ashford.
It's not too far.
- By yourself, or you
got family around here?
- No, I'm on my own.
- Oh.
- You said on the phone
that this was a cash job?
- Yes. Straight in your pocket.
Yeah, I mean, hell, if
you take to the job,
then maybe we could make it
a regular thing, you know?
- Really?
Wow, that'd be great.
- Carmen usually works nights,
but her kid's been
getting pretty sick.
- Oh. Yeah, that's terrible.
- Yeah.
I would normally
work the double,
but I just have this
thing that I can't miss.
It is with a girl, so.
(head thumps)
(Gwen gasps)
- Fucking Yogi, don't
do this to me.
Sorry, that's Yogi.
Yogi, come on.
Why would you do this today?
- [Gwen] Oh, here.
- Oh. Hey, thank you.
(both grunting)
Really gotta get this
thing fixed. Oh my.
Oh, heavy. Oh, let's see.
Look, I know it looks as
if the damn Addams family
used to live here,
but trust me, they,
they did not.
They never lived here.
This place is harmless.
It actually belonged to my
grandfolks way back when,
but we haven't quite
updated it since, so.
You know, I got, like,
crazy, crazy plans
for this place.
I'm talking some big-ass
plans for this place.
I'm just waiting on a
loan approval. Right?
And then as soon as that
comes in, I'm going to,
I'm gonna remodel
Miles Ahead Motel.
What you think?
(playful music)
- Looks good.
- Yeah, it could
be pretty sweet.
It's already got
five stars built in,
so that's covered. (laughs)
And hell, who knows?
You know, if business booms,
then maybe get a
franchise out of it.
Like, that'll be, yeah. Yeah.
Let me give you the tour.
(ominous music)
And we don't get that many
guests this time of year,
truth be told.
Mostly folks just passing
through to Denning.
(swings creaking)
Now, we got 20 cabins.
All are basically identical.
Okay, so queen bed,
mini fridge, phone.
You know, it's not much,
but it's a place
to rest your head.
And standard-definition
television.
Okay. Let's see.
Shower, toilet, all
pretty much standard.
(ominous music)
(Gwen scoffs)
So, already cleaned cabin 12,
but eight still
needs some doing.
- Okay, cabin eight. Got it.
- Right. You need me to
show you the ropes, or?
- I think I can handle it.
I did notice, however, that
you don't do a French fold.
- A French what? (laughs)
(gentle whimsical music)
- If we drape the banding back,
the finished side
will be exposed.
Not only will the bed
look more comfortable,
but the guests will feel the
softness when they climb in.
- Well, shit, now I want
to jump in that thing.
I wanna take a nap right now.
- Yeah. My mom used
to work in motels.
I used to help her out
after school sometimes.
- Okay, here we have
the supply room.
Oh, don't forget
to use this brick.
Now, the door only
opens from the outside,
and this brick will keep
you from getting locked in.
It is very, very important.
(Teddy groans)
Okay. So linens are kept
up here, towels down below.
More cleaning supplies above
the washer-dryer combo.
Fuse box right over
here. What else?
Just give me a second, okay?
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
Sinkhole last summer.
Been on the phone
with the county
for months trying to
get them to close it.
Assholes are finally
coming this weekend.
- I've never seen one before.
- Yeah. Sucked all the
water in the damn ground.
Luckily, nobody
was swimming in it.
(ominous music)
- Teddy, how come
cabin 13 is only 45.50?
That's half the price
of the other rooms.
- Oh, superstition.
- You can't be serious.
- It's the same reason
why flights are cheaper
on Friday the 13th,
or animal shelters are
overrun with black cats.
People are fucking stupid.
They will believe anything.
Have you eaten?
- Not yet.
- Well, Postmates don't
come out this far,
and the wifi is a little janky,
but if you're in the
mood for some killer pho.
- It's pho-king delicious.
- Yeah, it's the best
Vietnamese in town.
It's the only Vietnamese
in town. Yeah.
So, I do believe that is,
that's everything.
- I have to ask.
What kind of security
do you have here?
(ominous music)
- Security?
Oh, we have, I mean,
we have a monitor on the desk.
- Oh. I mean, protection.
This hotel is a ways out, and
I'm a woman alone at night.
What if I get some
asshole guest?
- Oh, just call the police.
- Yeah and wait, what, 30
minutes if they even show?
- Well, if you want,
there's a fire ax next
to the vending machine.
Nobody's gonna mess with you
if you swinging that
thing around,
you know what I'm saying?
They might call the
police on you, so.
Okay, Gwen.
Relax, okay?
I know it seems a little
spooky, but trust me,
I haven't had any trouble here,
and neither has Carmen.
But I tell you what,
if you feel unsafe or
threatened in any way,
there's a deadbolt
in the parlor.
Just lock yourself
in there and then,
you know, just call me, okay?
(Gwen sighs)
Trust me, Gwen,
you're gonna be fine.
(rats scuttering)
- Is that rats?
- Hmm.
Tell me that's not rats.
- Oh, no, that's not rats.
(rats scuttering)
Okay, that's rats. That is rats.
Okay, I'll tell you what.
Pho is on me, okay?
(gentle whimsical music)
You ain't gonna eat that much
pho, so I'll just take this.
Whew, it's chilly tonight.
Okay, Gwen, I will see
you in the morning.
7:00 A.M. okay?
And Gwen, welcome
to the night shift.
(car door closes)
(engine roaring)
(engine roaring continues)
(ominous music)
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music continues)
(knocks on door)
- Ms. Marsh.
Ms. Marsh?
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
My name is Gwen. I just
started the night shift.
I'm taking over for
Mr. Miles, the manager.
You're just staying the
one night, is that correct?
(door opening)
Hi. I just wanted to make
sure you were all right.
Do you need anything?
Fresh towels, perhaps?
- No.
- Okay.
Well, if you change your
mind, just give me a call.
I'll be in the office
most of the night.
(ominous music)
(door slams)
(lock clicks)
(ominous music continues)
(crickets chirping)
(door creaking)
(crickets chirping continues)
(windows slams)
(engine roaring)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(gentle whimsical music)
(Gwen yelps)
Oh my God.
Gross.
(Gwen scoffs)
(gentle whimsical music)
Ew. Ew, ew, ew, ew, ew.
Ew.
(toilet flushing)
(lights clicking and creaking)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(door slams)
(door opens)
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hello?
- [TV Reporter] Labored
by these lawsuits
and with their stocks
continuing to crash,
the company has now been
forced to file for bankruptcy.
In other news,
authorities have yet
to apprehend a
convicted murderer
who escaped a facility
Wednesday evening.
Police are asking
residents in the area.
- [Gwen] Yeah, can I get the...
Pho Thit, the Pho Thit Lon?
I don't think I'm
saying that correctly.
The one with the pork.
Yeah. And not too spicy, please.
Great, thanks.
(gentle hopeful music)
(Gwen sighs)
(gentle hopeful music continues)
Oh, fuck. I need coffee.
(phone ringing)
This is The All Tucked
Inn, how may I help you?
Hello?
(phone dial toning)
(phone ringing)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(phone ringing continues)
(female caller laughs)
(tense sinister music)
(tense sinister music continues)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(door opening and creaking)
(crickets chirping)
(light switch clicking)
(crickets chirping continues)
Shit.
(Gwen breathing heavily)
(noise groaning)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(door creaking)
(light switch clicks)
(noise groaning)
(ominous music)
(plumbing groaning)
(door creaking)
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music)
(phone dial toning)
(ominous music continues)
(creaking)
(phone ringing)
(ominous music)
(phone ringing continues)
(ominous music continues)
- It's for you.
(Gwen screams)
(phone ringing)
(Gwen panting)
- Excuse me.
This is broken. Are you okay?
(Gwen pants)
Are you okay?
(ominous music)
- There's gotta be
one in here somewhere.
You have to excuse me. It's
my first night working here.
- Oh, no, that's fine.
You said your name
was Gwen, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, I'm Alice.
What did you see in there?
- What?
- In the cabin. Number 13.
- Oh. Yeah, I've barely
slept in nearly 20 hours.
I literally just moved
here and started this job,
and my mind is pretty
scattered right now.
And with this place
looking the way it does,
the taxidermy and the old pipes,
I, um...
I thought I was hearing
things, seeing things.
- That's a shame. I do
love a good ghost story.
Listen, I hope I didn't
come off as rude earlier
when you knocked.
I was a little upset.
- Yes!
Found one.
- Oh, great. Thanks.
- No, no, no!
Oh, shit. It's locked.
- Wait, what? Don't you
have a key or something?
- No.
It can only open up
from the outside.
We're stuck.
- Hey! Help us!
Someone help us!
We're locked in here!
Let us out!
- No one else is staying
at the motel, no
one can hear us.
- Fuck.
- Wait, do you have
your phone on you?
- No. That's why I
needed the dryer.
It fell in the fucking sink
when I was dyeing my hair.
What time does your
manager come back?
- 7:00 A.M.
(ominous music)
- [Alice] Oh, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
- [Gwen] Hey, hey,
hey! It's okay.
- No, I'm claustrophobic.
- Okay. Just, just calm down.
Just breathe.
- [Alice] No. Ah, what is that?
There's somebody else in here.
- [Gwen] There's nobody in here.
- [Alice] No, no, no. There's
somebody else in here.
I felt something thing.
(ominous music)
(tense music)
(Alice yelping)
- Okay, stay behind me.
(Alice screams)
- You all order the pho?
- Hey, let us out of here!
- What?
- [Gwen] Open the fucking door.
(Alice and Gwen panting)
- Ah, shit.
- What?
- I got you the wrong order.
- Mm. What was this one?
Pork?
- I don't know what it
is, but it's delicious.
- Thank you, for the food.
- Are you kidding?
Mr. Miles paid, and he owes us
after the shit we just
went through.
(Alice laughs)
How he has managed to
keep this place open,
I will never know.
- Hmm.
(Gwen chuckles)
- So why red?
- Uh...
It's my mom. She never
lets me do anything.
Dye my hair, go to parties,
watch horror movies.
We got in this big
argument. I left.
Doesn't really know where I am.
- You ran away from home.
- Well, I'm not going back.
- Where's home, your mom?
- Umm...
Denning.
Yeah. No, it's a shithole.
Yeah, it's so boring.
- Alice, I know you
don't want to hear this,
but your mom is just
trying to look out for you.
- Oh.
- She must be worried sick.
- No, no, no, no.
You don't know her.
She's a bitch.
One time, Hobie Kittredge
gave me a hickey,
and she like, grounded
me for a month.
(Gwen scoffs)
- Yeah, my mom was the same way.
She was tough as hell
on me, super strict.
My younger sisters, they got
away with it, but not me.
But family matters.
Listen, Alice,
(ominous music)
it's dangerous to be
on the road by yourself.
The world can be a scary place.
There are bad people out
there doing bad things.
Anyway, I just think
you should reconsider
what you're doing.
That's all.
My mom, she passed
away a while ago,
but I still miss her.
- Yeah, think, she's probably
trying to reach me now.
- Do you want a Coke?
(Alice chuckles)
- Fuck yeah.
(engine roaring)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(door slams)
- Oh, shit.
- Jesus.
- Sorry, I didn't
mean to scare you.
- No, it's okay.
Sorry, I'm just a little
spooked from the rats.
- Oh, yeah. Here, no,
let me help you out.
- It's okay. Don't worry.
- No, it's okay.
It's really no bother.
- It's okay. It's fine.
I said I got it.
I don't want you
to cut yourself.
- Well, thank you
for dinner again.
I'm gonna go and try
this out on my phone.
See if I can get it to work.
- Yeah, good idea.
(door creaking)
Alice.
Don't forget to lock
your door, okay?
- Yeah, always.
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(bell dings)
(door thuds)
(ominous music)
(head thuds)
- Fuck.
Goddammit, Yogi.
(gentle whimsical music)
(Gwen groaning)
What the fuck.
(gentle whimsical music)
(Gwen groaning)
(Gwen breathing heavily)
(engine roaring)
(ominous music)
(door creaking and closing)
(ominous music continues)
- [Birdie] Jesus Christ. Warn,
look at this dump! (laughs)
- Welcome to The All Tucked
Inn, how may I help you?
- Dead birds. Dead
fucking birds.
I told you, didn't I say so?
- You totally did.
(gasps) Oh my God.
- Ma'am. Ma'am, please
don't touch that.
- She can touch
whatever she wants.
Hi. Now, we would like
your very best room.
(bell dinging)
We just escaped
a gallery showing
that was absolutely
fucking rudimentary,
and we want to still
enjoy ourselves
so this night is
not a total waste.
- My idea, of course.
Let's stop in a seedy
motel just like they do
in the movies!
(Warner and Birdie laugh)
- Sure. How long would
you like to stay?
- I guess, I don't know.
We'll stay for the full hour.
- You'll only need 10 minutes.
- Birdie, play nice.
(Birdie growls)
(Warner scowls)
- Sir, this isn't that
kind of establishment.
We don't rent rooms by the hour.
But if you'd like,
I could book you into
a cabin for the night.
- Oh my God. Wait, are
you fucking kidding me?
Don't...
Don't tell me people actually
sleep in this shithole.
- It's a nightly charge,
sir. 91 even per room.
- Oh my God, we have
the cash, Warn.
Just pay the girl.
- It's not about
the money, Birdie.
So are you really telling me
that you will not rent
us a room for an hour?
- I can't. It's against policy.
- My God. Shit.
How does this fucking
dump even stay open? God.
What kind of salary do they
even have you on here, huh?
- Easy, Warn. Come on.
- Look at her. Hey,
mm-mm, look at her.
Look at my wife.
She is a fucking goddess.
Do you think I would
ever let her sleep
in this disease-ridden pigsty?
Hmm? This shit
stain for a motel?
I mean, people have
probably died here, right?
Been murdered.
- Like I said, it's
91 even per room.
- Fine, just say what you
want. What do you want?
Do you want 100? There's 100.
Fine. You know what, why
don't you just take 200.
- Like I said, it's just $91.
- [Warner] Why don't
you take 300, right?
350, 4, huh? 400.
- Sir, please stop.
- Jesus Christ! Just give
me my fucking room key.
(ominous music)
- Room two.
Would you like me to
show you where it is?
(Warner groans)
- Let me guess, it's
between one and three.
Then I think we'll
manage, won't we?
- [Birdie] Warn.
- [Warner] What, baby?
- I got glass in my Prada.
- Oh.
- Fuck. There's shards of
glass all over the floor.
- All right, come on, come
on, come on. Let's go, baby.
Here we go. Let's go,
let's go, let's go.
(Birdie laughs)
- Sorry, I just, I need you
to sign the registration book.
- Yeah, well, fuck you
and your stupid book.
(Warner and Birdie laugh)
(ominous music)
(swings creaking)
♪ Dreaming, dreaming ♪
♪ Dreaming you look my way ♪
♪ Hoping that you'll
be my something ♪
♪ Dreaming, dreaming ♪
(crickets chirping)
(whip cracking)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(whip cracking)
- [Warner] Ow!
Oh. Ow!
Ow.
(whip cracking)
Shit.
(sinister music)
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music)
- Gross.
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(liquid bubbles)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(liquid bubbles)
(stairs creaking and rattling)
(ominous music)
(Gwen gasps)
(stairs clank)
(Gwen groaning)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(tense sinister music)
(Gwen screaming)
(Gwen continues screaming)
Help, help me! Help me!
- [Alice] Here! Gwen, here!
(sinister music)
- Gwen? What is it?
What's wrong?
(Gwen gasping)
Gwen.
Okay. What'll it be?
Russia, Ireland, or Jamaica?
- Whatever's strongest.
Thanks.
- Nostrovia.
Oh.
You saw something
again, didn't you?
In the pool. What'd you see?
What'd you see?
- I...
I--
- You know this place
is haunted, right?
- What?
- Yeah, it's like,
one of the most haunted
locations in the state.
It's actually like, part of
the reason why I came here.
It's notorious, really.
I heard like, a
shit ton of stories.
I just wanted see if they
were true, you know.
(Alice chuckles)
(Gwen sighs)
Shit.
- Jesus Christ.
(Birdie and Warner laughing)
- [Birdie] Stop!
- [Warner] All right,
hold on. (laughs)
Oh.
- Alice.
- Yeah?
- Have you seen a
strange car lurking
around the motel tonight?
- Lurking. What do you mean?
(somber music)
Gwen, are you okay?
- When I was your age,
a man named Walton
Grey, a loner,
broke into our house.
He killed my mom and my sisters,
and he tried to kill me.
I was the only
one that survived.
- Jesus.
- They caught him,
and they locked him
away in an institute,
but two days ago, he escaped.
- Are you serious?
- I found this in my mailbox.
It's a necklace my mom gave me.
It went missing the night
Walton Grey killed my family.
I always believed
that he took it.
- Holy shit.
- I was so scared, Alice.
I just, I left. I ran.
But he's followed me.
I saw him.
- What you've seen him? Tonight?
- Twice, outside.
- Gwen, are you sure it was him?
Because you said you haven't
been sleeping a lot lately.
- I don't know. I think so.
I don't know what
I'm seeing here.
This place is just
so fucking strange.
- Yeah, yeah. No shit.
Look, I think you
should call the police.
You know, for your
own safety at least.
- Yeah. Yeah, you're right.
Alice, I need you to
do something for me.
I want you to keep this
door locked, just in case,
and I want you to stay
inside, all right?
- Yeah, of course. You got it.
Gwen?
I, um...
I thought about what you said,
and I'm going home
in the morning,
back to my mom's.
Family matters, right?
(door closes)
(lock clicks)
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(door creaks and closes)
- Hello?
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
What the fuck.
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(Gwen breathing heavily)
(Gwen screams)
(tense sinister music)
(Gwen breathing heavily)
(tense sinister music continues)
(Gwen screaming)
(upbeat music)
♪ I know what's in my heart ♪
(phone ringing)
(upbeat music continues)
- Just met this bitch.
Gwen, slow down.
Okay. What happened?
- You never told me this place
was fucking haunted, Teddy.
- [Teddy] What? Haunted?
- Don't play dumb
with me, asshole.
I'm...
I'm seeing things.
Ghosts, Teddy.
- Oh God, Gwen.
Okay. Is the place a
little fucking old?
I'll give you that. Is
the place a little spooky?
Sure.
- A little?
- Look Gwen, what I'm
trying to say is,
Gwen, it's not haunted, okay?
It's just not.
- You're telling
me, swear to God,
that you've never seen
anything at this motel.
- No. Uh-uh.
- Swear to God, Teddy,
you've never seen anything?
- Nothing, Gwen.
Nothing, I run a clean
ghost-free establishment.
If there were ghosts,
I would know about it.
Don't be ridiculous.
- You're lying to me.
- I'm not lying. I swear.
- You know what,
this place is a fucking
horror show, Teddy.
I should sue your ass.
I got...
I got fucking
ghosts, I got rats,
I got a weird sex couple
wearing bird masks.
- Okay, I don't know
nothing about no bird masks.
- I'm not coming back.
Teddy, you hear me?
This is my last goddamn shift.
- Gwen, Gwen, Gwen, come on now.
- I am done.
- Don't do that.
Don't do that, Gwen.
- See your ass at seven.
- Gwen, don't. Gwen, don't do--
(Gwen sighs)
(bell dings)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
- [Visitor] Hello?
(Gwen breathes deeply)
(door creaks and closes)
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
I was--
(ominous music)
- I'd like a room.
- How long would
you like to stay?
- One night. Been a long drive.
(ominous music)
Don't I recognize
you from someplace?
- I don't think so.
- Hmm. You must have
one of those faces.
- That's what people
keep telling me.
It'll be 91 for the night.
- Cheap.
Really cheap.
(visitor humming)
(ominous music)
Here.
91.
(ominous music)
- Why don't I put you in...
(key rattles)
Cabin 12?
(ominous music)
- Are you gonna
show me to my room?
- Yes, certainly.
Actually, why don't I put you
in cabin eight?
It's just been freshly turned.
- Sure. Sounds good.
(ominous music)
(door creaks open)
(ominous music continues)
(door closes)
(key rattles)
- Here we are. Queen bed.
There's a mini fridge.
There's a phone
on the desk there.
(door slams)
- I didn't catch your name.
What did you say it was?
- The towels.
I just need to make sure
you have clean towels.
(ominous music)
(sinister music)
(tense sinister music)
(visitor groaning)
- Oh, fuck.
Gwen, don't you know who I am?
- You're Walton Grey.
- My name is Raymond Bailey.
I'm your doctor.
- What?
- You've been under my care
at Ashford Psychiatric
Facility for 12 years.
Two nights ago, you escaped.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, you're lying.
You are Walton Grey, and
you killed my family.
- No, Gwen.
You, killed your family.
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
Do you remember
what you told me?
Huh? How they mistreated you?
How they hated you?
You were the family stain.
What did you do to your family?
Gwen, do you remember?
(deafening sinister music)
- No.
No, no, no, no.
No.
Walton Grey killed my family.
- There is no Walton Grey.
You made him up.
His name, it's an
anagram of your name,
Gwen Taylor.
He's a figment of
your imagination.
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
You need your medication, Gwen.
You're not well.
I uh,
I called the hospital,
once I knew I'd found you.
See, the necklace. The necklace.
Remember?
You told me that you
wore it the night
that you killed your family.
You told me it was the only gift
that your mother ever gave you.
Remember you telling me that?
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
Gwen, Gwen, Gwen, Gwen, Gwen,
Gwen, Gwen, Gwen, Gwen, Gwen.
Gwen, listen to me.
Listen to me, Gwen.
I need you to hand
me those scissors.
Please, hand me the scissors.
Hand me the scissors.
Gwen, put--
(ominous music)
- Open your fucking mouth.
- You sure this is the place?
- The All Tucked Inn.
That's what the doc said.
- Well, maybe you
give them a call.
This my motel is shit.
(ominous music)
- That's her. What
the hell is she doing?
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
- Come on, let's go.
(tense ominous music)
(tense ominous music continues)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(tense sinister music)
(man groaning)
(Alice panting)
(ominous music)
(phone rattles)
- Shit.
(Alice panting)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(door knob rattling)
(sinister music)
(keys rattling)
(tense sinister music)
Come on. Please, please.
(door slams)
(door knob rattling)
- [Gwen] Alice.
Alice?
(unsettling piano music)
(tense sinister music)
(Alice grunting)
(tense sinister music continues)
(ominous music)
(Alice panting)
(ominous music continues)
- Oh, shit.
(tense music)
(tense music continues)
(car alarm beeps)
(engine roars)
(tires squeal)
(engine roaring)
(tense music)
(Alice panting)
(Gwen groans)
(tense music continues)
(ominous music)
(door closes)
(Alice panting)
Shit.
(ominous music continues)
(Alice panting)
(door opens and closes)
(ominous music continues)
(shoe squishes)
(thudding, squishing)
(ominous music continues)
(ax squishing)
(blood splashing)
(Alice panting)
(ominous music continues)
- You gotta admit, you
brought this on yourself.
(Alice panting)
(ax squishes)
(crickets chirping)
(engine roaring)
(engine roaring continues)
(crickets chirping)
(crickets chirping continues)
- Hey, Gwen, can we
talk about all this?
Gwen?
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
Hello?
Gwen?
(ominous music)
Gwen, what the hell.
I've been looking all
over the place for you.
What were you um...
Wh, what, what were you doing
down in the pool?
- Come over here. I'll show you.
(upbeat music)
♪ Let's go sunning,
it's so good for you ♪
♪ Let's go sunning
'neath a sky of blue ♪
♪ Breathe the sun,
everyone ♪
- [Mom] Where are
you now, sweetie?
- I just passed through Denning,
but I'm thinking I
should probably stop soon
because I think I'm on
seven hours straight now.
There's a motel up ahead.
It's a popular spot.
- [Mom] Okay.
But I want you to call me
as soon as you check in.
Oh, I miss my baby already.
- (chuckles) Mom, I
literally saw you yesterday.
(mysterious music)
(mysterious music continues)
(birds chirping)
- [Gwen] Hi there.
- [Cole] Hi.
- Admiring our pool I see.
- [Cole] Yeah.
- Certainly is one of our
most impressive features.
The guests just love it.
- I bet. It's a... it's dope.
- You won't believe this,
but last year we had a giant
sinkhole at the bottom.
- For real?
- Sucked the water right out.
I mean, the hole was so big,
you could fit five people
down there. (laughs)
- No way.
(Gwen continues laughing)
(birds chirping)
- Come on, let me check you in.
- Yeah.
(keyboard clicking)
- Sign here.
Have you traveled far?
- No, just out of state.
Yeah, heading down to Ashford
for college, actually.
You ever been to Ashford?
- Can't say that I have.
Now,
let me...
put you in...
...cabin eight.
Oh, it's my favorite.
- Sounds great.
(Cole snorts)
(ominous music)
Are you okay?
- Never better.
Let me show you to your room.
(door opening)
(bells jingling)
(door closing)
(head thumps)
(upbeat music)
♪ It's too late ♪
♪ For tears ♪
♪ Honey it's too late ♪
♪ Too late to cry ♪
♪ Oh but it's too late ♪
♪ Oh for begging me baby ♪
♪ Honey it's too late ♪
♪ Too late to cry ♪
♪ Now that you need me darling ♪
♪ I'm cruel to walk out,
oh, oh ♪
♪ I provide, sacrifice for you ♪
♪ And I need, I'm
here without, oh ♪
♪ But it's too late, oh ♪
♪ Oh for loving me baby ♪
♪ Honey it's too late ♪
♪ Too late to cry ♪
♪ But I know you know that I
know that I know that it's ♪
♪ Too late for wanting me baby ♪
♪ Honey it's too late ♪
♪ Too late for tears ♪
♪ Honey I know that
it's too late ♪
♪ Too late for tears ♪
♪ Honey I know you know
that I know that it is ♪
♪ Too late for tears ♪
♪ And I've gotta say for me
that it's too late darling ♪
♪ Too late for tears ♪
♪ Honey I know that it is ♪
(gentle unsettling music)
(gentle unsettling
music continues)