[man] Not tomorrow,
the day after, right.
[indistinct chatter over phone]
You, me, Gary, Brad.
We'll be teeing off at...
- Well, I like Gary.
- Dr. Dandewarr, I'm in a hurry...
We'll be teeing off at 7:30.
If you're not there
because of Gary, come on.
I gotta go.
Am I missing something?
Why did Dr. Cho order
a head X-ray
when the man
was bitten on the hand?
Uh, the patient was
in a bar fight.
He was communicative when he was
admitted at 6:00. That's 6:00am.
This morning,
that's when I started my shift.
Where is the patient now?
I'd like to see him.
They moved him. One of
the night nurses can...
- Page me when you find him.
- Sure.
I'll do that.
[woman speaking
over loudspeaker]
Cora, can you do me a favor
- and locate a patient for me?
- Hey, Ana. Sure.
- Edward Solomon?
- Yep.
[tapping keys]
- Aren't you off?
- An hour ago.
- [both chuckle]
Here he is.
They had him backwards.
Solomon Edward.
He's upstairs in ICU.
- From a bite?
- I don't know what from.
Toxicology's gonna
work him up in the morning.
I'm gonna get out of here.
Can you page Dr. Dandewarr
and let him know?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Did you talk to
Luis about Sunday?
- I will. Night, Cora.
- Night.
[woman speaking
over loudspeaker]
- Hey.
- [man 1] Hey, Ana.
[woman speaking
over loudspeaker]
[man 2] Let's go.
It's starting early.
[man 1] Great. Later.
[man 2] Let's go, let's go!
[horn and sirens blare]
[woman over radio]
...an unconfirmed...
[man over radio]...confirm
it is not an isolated...
["Have A Nice Day"
by Stereophonics playing]
[Ana] Hey, Vivian.
Ana, look,
I can go backwards.
Let me see.
[Ana] Hey, that's amazing.
Maybe tomorrow after work,
I'll do a few backward laps
around the block with you, okay?
- Okay.
- All right.
[Ana] Careful, now,
I gotta pull in.
Say hey to your mom for me,
okay?
Okay.
[people talking on TV]
- Hey.
- [Luis] Hey, you.
You're late, you missed it.
They just cut the mailman loose.
- No, Richie? The chubby one?
- [Luis] Mm.
[Ana] Oh my God,
he had such a sweet voice.
I can't believe that.
There you go.
Hey, you.
How'd it go today?
Not bad. You?
Good. I'm trading shifts
with Cora
so if I take Sunday,
I can have a three-day weekend
at the end of the month.
- Sunday? Yeah.
- Is that okay? Yeah.
I think Cora's got this new guy
she doesn't want me
to know about.
Really? Wow. Lucky her.
I thought maybe you'd gone out
with the girls or something.
What, and miss date night?
[man 1 on TV] 27 horsepower,
turbocharged...
[man 2 on TV] Please stay tuned
to this special news bulletin.
We will return to our regular
scheduled programming
immediately following
this report.
[click]
[mumbles]
[Luis] Vivian's here.
Vivian, honey, sweetie,
are you okay?
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
- Call an ambulance!
- [growls]
[Luis screams]
[Ana] Vivian!
[hissing]
[shrieks]
Luis! Luis! Luis!
Let go! Let go!
- Let go! Let go! Let go!
- [thudding]
I can't get it!
Hold it! Hold it! Hold it!
Let go. Let go! Let go!
I'm going to call for help.
[tone over telephone]
[recording]
All circuits are busy.
God, no. No no!
- [Ana panting]
- [banging on the door]
- All circuits are busy...
- Don't do this to me, please!
Don't do this to me!
[recording]
All circuits are busy...
Luis? What are you doing?
- [growling]
- [Ana screams]
[groaning]
Luis?
- [gasps]
- [screaming]
[distant siren blares]
- Help!
Get back, Ana.
[man] Get back!
Just tell me what's going on!
I told you to get back.
[horn honks]
[people screaming]
[Luis growls]
[woman screams]
[man 1 over radio]
...emergency broadcast
here in the Milwaukee area.
[man 2 over radio]
The following is information
for local evacuation centers.
If you live in
Waukesha County...
Help! Can you help? Please!
- ...22 Robin Lane.
- [approaching police siren]
If you live in
southern Milwaukee County...
[tires screeching]
...1353 Henderson Road.
If there is no activity
where you live,
- stay inside and lock all doors.
- [people screaming]
If you live in
Jefferson County...
This is the
Emergency Broadcast System
for the greater Milwaukee area.
If you live in Racine County,
there is no information
available at this time.
Please stay inside
and lock all doors and windows.
Miller Park is no longer
considered a safe haven.
Please avoid the stadium
and proceed to other locations.
Meanwhile, civil unrest
is still being reported
in the area of the RiverWalk.
Please avoid traveling...
There are unconfirmed reports
that several
military personnel...
The following locations
are still listed...
[woman screaming]
- [screams]
- [shouting]
[Ana screams]
[birds chirping]
[chanting]
[man 1]
I'll take your questions.
[man 2] Is it a virus?
[man 1] We don't know.
[woman] How does it spread?
Is it airborne?
[man 1]
Airborne is a possibility.
We don't know.
[man 3] Is this an international
health hazard
or a military concern?
[man 1] Both.
[woman 2]
Are these people alive or dead?
[man] Hold him down!
We don't know.
[woman] Is that true?
["The Man Comes Around"
by Johnny Cash playing]
...the following shelters
have been compromised.
Listen,
I've lost the teleprompter.
[sirens and gunfire]
...shifted from
containment to...
[people screaming]
[woman] I've just spoken
with the President.
'He's in constant contact
with CDC as well as FEMA.
No more questions.
- [screaming]
- [gunfire]
- [man 1] Stay back! Right there!
- [man 2] A US off...
[man 3] God, they're here!
- [growling]
- [man]...the four beasts.
And I looked and behold,
a pale horse
And his name that sat
on it was Death.
And hell followed with him.
[birds chirping]
[gun cocks]
Say something.
Please.
[distant siren]
[distant noise]
[gunfire]
[Michael] All right, okay.
Put the guns down!
What are you doing? He's a cop!
Come on, put the gun down.
I thought you were one of them.
You do not want to go that way.
What's that way?
Officer, sir?
You do not want to go that way.
What's that way?
It's pretty bad.
What about Fort Pastor?
Maybe if you had wings.
The road's thick
with those motherfuckers.
How do you know?
We just tried. Come on.
Back when there was eight of us.
We're going to the mall.
Shit.
Damn.
- [woman screams]
- Hurry up!
[gunfire]
Back up!
[growling]
Open the door!
[pounding]
[metal creaking]
[Michael] Lights.
[Ana] Here.
[distant screaming]
- No?
- No.
[Muzak playing]
[Andre] Come on.
Sit right there.
We need to make sure
this place is safe.
I'm gonna see if the doors
over this way are locked.
I'll check down there.
Maybe, Officer, you could
go down that direction,
check for...
All right. Okay.
Maybe it's better
you stay here with the gun.
Andre and I will check around.
Baby, I'll be right back
No, just stay right here.
Stay right here.
[Muzak continues playing]
[growling]
[breathing fast]
Shatterproof, asshole.
Shit.
[muffled noises]
[echoing thud]
[growling noise]
[growling]
[roaring]
[distant screaming]
- [growling]
- [Luda screaming]
[growling]
[growling and hissing]
[howling]
- What happened?
- Come on, move.
Move!
Which way?
Here. Elevators.
[Andre] Let's go! Let's go!
[elevator bell dings]
Can I see that arm?
- I need to suture that.
- Yeah.
- Are you okay?
- [elevator bell dings]
[Kenneth] Yeah.
Find someplace else.
- Look, we just need a place...
- [cocks gun]
Maybe you didn't hear me.
There is no place else.
Well, it's tough shit,
'cause this is our place
and you can't stay here.
Yeah. And you
already trashed Metropolis.
Look, dumbass,
my wife is pregnant.
- [elevator bell dings]
- We can't run anymore.
- His arm...
- Those things are down there.
Well, these are
all your problems, not mine.
If I put my foot up your ass,
would that be your problem?
Hey, asshole, I'm the one
pointing the gun at you.
He is a cop, CJ.
- [elevator bell dings]
- So what?
[elevator buzzer rings]
[Ana] We're not gonna cause
any trouble.
Just let us stay here
for a little while. Please.
Okay.
Come out of there slowly
and give your weapons
- to Bart and Terry.
- Don't do it.
You must be
out of your fucking mind.
You can take your ass on
over to Quality Inn,
if it's still there, Shaq.
Huh? You want to do that?
Let's go.
Hey, don't give him that gun.
[Andre] Fuck.
Fuck.
Smart move.
[man speaking over TV]
...everywhere.
Nobody knows what's going on.
There's a lot of blood
and there are bodies.
There's a slew of fires.
We're back
to a live picture now.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
Give me one second here.
Ma'am, are you American?
All right. Let's go, guys.
Come on. Get your own little TV.
Come on. Let's go.
Excuse me.
Please. Is there a restroom?
No. You're staying here.
Then why don't you tell us
which spot in here
you'd like us to take a piss.
All right. It's around
the corner, that way.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
where do you think you're going?
She's not going anywhere alone.
"She's not going anywhere..."
This is a fucking
nursery school!
Terry, go with them.
Hi, I'm Bill Vibert
with 23V Cable News.
I'm at one
of the collection depots
waiting to interview
Sheriff Cahill.
I understand you're having
a difficult time
killing these things...
Just shoot 'em in the head.
They seem to go down permanently
when you shoot 'em in the head.
Then you gotta burn them.
You gotta burn...
Danny! Danny! Put another round
in that woman over there!
Look! She's a twitcher!
- [dog barking on TV]
- Twitcher.
Now, that is one cool
motherfucker.
Bleeding's not gonna stop
on its own.
I need to stitch his arm.
You a fucking doctor?
No, I'm a fucking nurse.
I know some of these people
that we're putting down.
First aid kit's
in the security office.
What are you gonna do?
It's gotta be done.
Huh? What did I tell you boys?
[sheriff] Get those bodies
off the truck!
We haven't got all day here.
America always
sorts its shit out.
You know, you're lucky.
He could have bitten it off.
Yes, I believe you're referring
to a report
that came in this morning.
That report was completely...
[reporter] What can we tell
the people out there
that don't know what to do?
[man] What I would suggest
is that you come to Fort Pastor.
If you can't make it here,
we have
multiple search-and-rescue teams
out there
and they will find you.
My brother's there.
He's waiting for me.
[crying]
- [door bangs open]
- What's the holdup, darling?
Hm?
[Michael] So what's the plan?
The plan is you drink
a tall glass
of shut-the-fuck-up.
- [Kenneth groans]
- [Michael] OK. That's one idea.
What about
locking this place down?
Sooner or later,
they're gonna get in here.
Mm.
That's good.
Like I hadn't thought of that.
Okay, no doubt. You probably
already thought about
putting a sign up on the roof.
'Cause, you know,
there's still planes in the air.
Might be good
to let them know we're alive.
We can get some paint
from Case Hardware.
Use some office doors
to board up the weak spots.
That's a solid plan.
CJ, is it?
- Yeah.
- All right, CJ.
[clears throat]
All right, everybody listen up.
I'm gonna give everybody
a job to do
and I expect you
to do all of it.
I don't want to see
any half-assin'.
Why don't you can start
by cleaning up that mess
you made in Metropolis.
Hey, CJ, look!
Terry.
Take a look at Ben Cozine.
Hey, Ben.
Ben!
Christ.
Look at him.
[Ben screeching]
[Bart] Look, he's a twitcher.
TV says you gotta shoot 'em
in the head.
TV said a lot of things
that aren't true.
Well, fuck the fucker.
I told him not to go downstairs.
[Ben screeches]
Let's go.
Let's get to work.
[whispering] Holy shit.
[growling]
[screeches]
[echoing gunfire]
[man 1] Let's do it.
[man 2] All right,
let's pick him up, then.
All right.
Ready? One, two, three. [groans]
[man 1] One two, all right?
[both] One, two.
- [thud]
- [distant growling]
What are they?
I don't know.
Why are they coming here?
[Kenneth]
Memory, maybe. Instinct.
Maybe they're coming for us.
[echoing gunfire]
- [distant growling]
- [gunfire]
[Ana] Look over there.
There's someone on the roof.
[CJ] Yeah, his name's Andy.
He's alone.
He may as well be on the moon.
[Ana] Poor guy.
What's he pointing at?
[helicopter approaching]
- Helicopter.
- Hey, it's coming.
- [man] Fuckin' A, man!
- [all shouting]
[all] Hey!
[man] Where's he...?
[Ana] Please... What's he doing?
What's he...?
No.
No, I mean, they saw us, so...
They're gonna be
coming back, baby. Don't worry.
They're gonna send somebody,
something.
[Ana] It's safe here.
We'll just wait for them
to come back.
I don't want anybody
sneaking around
and stealing shit.
Comprende?
[lock clicks]
Sweet dreams.
[chuckling]
Those assholes
are gonna get us killed.
[Michael sighs]
We have to do something.
I'm not doing anything to create
problems for Luda and me.
The helicopter's
coming back soon.
I hope so.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means it might come
and it might not. We don't know.
[speaking in Russian accent]
What do you mean, not come back?
You said it was coming back!
We have to get to hospital.
Hey, baby, listen, listen.
Don't worry, okay?
This guy, he...
he doesn't know shit.
All right? It's coming back.
Hey, my man, you know,
I hear you talking a lot.
You know,
you're always saying something.
Who the fuck are you
that we should listen, huh?
Were you like Special Ops?
Were you in the Marines?
What the fuck do you do?
I sell televisions at Best Buy.
[chuckling]
[Andre] Wow.
Hey, Officer,
how do you like following a guy
that sells TVs?
About as much as I like
following a guy who steals them.
I'm not following anyone.
I'm going to Fort Pastor
to get my brother.
They seem to need
to feed on warm flesh.
Some basic skills remain.
They don't seem to have much,
if any, reasoning power.
And how does this spread?
[CJ] These guys
are so full of shit.
They're saying
the same damn thing all day.
Tell me something
I don't know, asshole!
I've just been informed
that we're going off the air...
[Bart] Wanna hear something
that really sucks?
...and switching over
to the Emergency
Broadcasting System.
You know that chick
at Dairy Queen?
[reporter] I don't know
when we'll be back on the air.
- The fat one?
- Yeah.
[reporter]
Until then...
[Bart]
She was coming over tonight.
I would have
tapped that shit for sure.
Bart, dude,
everybody's dead, okay?
Your mom's dead.
Your brother's dead.
That fat chick at Dairy Queen...
[reporter]...to say a pleasure
it's been...
Dead.
[reporter]...report the news
these past 26 years.
- God bless you.
- Yeah.
- [reporter] God bless America.
- That sucks too.
Hell is overflowing
and Satan
is sending his dead to us.
Why?
Because...
you have sex out of wedlock,
you kill unborn children,
you have man-on-man relations,
same-sex marriage.
How do you think
your God will judge you?
Well, friends...
now we know.
When there is no more room
in hell...
the dead...
will walk the earth.
- [distant pounding]
- [distant growling]
- [static noise on TV]
- What the hell?
[Muzak playing]
[gasping]
- Hey, dumb-ass.
- Hm?
It's the timers.
It's eight o'clock.
- [sighs]
- Terry.
Go shut 'em off.
It's Bart's turn.
You're the trainee, man.
Shit rolls downhill.
I wish somebody
was working at Hallowed Grounds.
How hard is it to make
a cup of coffee?
I wanted a soy mocha latte
with foam.
Faggot.
What are you doing?
What's the news?
Bad.
Hey. Hey!
Hey.
What?
The bathroom in here is fake,
it doesn't work.
I'll tell CJ.
I'm telling you.
You're the type of cat
that goes to church
and all that kind of shit,
right?
Yeah,
I do all that kind of shit.
So what do you think?
Hm?
What is this?
Is this the end of times?
'Cause if it is,
I'm telling you, I'm fucked.
I'm serious. I've done
some bad things in my life.
Oh, I get it.
You saw hell yesterday,
now you're scared
of going to hell
for all the bad things
you've done.
I'll tell you what,
go in the stall,
say five Hail Marys,
wipe your ass, and you
and God can call it even.
You think I feel
like I deserve to be here?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, well, I don't.
And I'm cool with that.
But, you see, that's not it,
'cause I feel like I'm here
for another reason.
I feel like I'm here
to bring that baby on this earth
and give it everything
that I never had.
I just want the opportunity
to change things.
[Muzak continues playing]
[Muzak stops]
Shit!
[gunshot]
CJ!
How did you get out?
Who gave you permission
to loot the goddamn stores?
What are we gonna do
about that truck?
We're not gonna do anything
about that truck.
There's people in it.
Yeah? And how do you know
they're not fucked up
like everybody else out there?
Well, for one thing,
they're driving a truck.
- [gunfire]
- Oh, and shooting guns.
If we start letting people
in here,
we're gonna
let the wrong ones in
and then I'm dead,
and I don't want to die.
- Who are the wrong ones?
- Nobody here is sick.
I intend on keeping it that way.
I just think...
I did not ask
for your opinion, lady!
If you want to argue,
argue with this.
- [Michael] Hey, take it easy.
- Shut your fucking mouth.
Get the gun out of my face.
You can't turn them away, CJ.
You'll kill them.
Tough shit. Self-defense.
- I'm not killing anybody.
- Know what? I'll kill you.
No, no, Stop it, CJ.
Don't do this.
Shut up!
I'll kill each
and every one of you
to stay alive,
you hear me?
Get the fucking gun
out of my face!
Oh. You got quite
a mouth on you.
Somebody should show her
how to use it.
Is there a holding cell
in there?
Yeah. Back of the security room.
That's real good, man.
You're gonna get us all killed,
dumb-ass!
Fucking traitor.
- Get off me.
- [Andre] Hey.
I hope you got a good plan.
Come on.
[distant growling]
- Hey! Hurry!
- Through here. Down here.
[Michael] I can't see
a damn thing.
[Andre] Me, either.
[truck back up alert beeping]
Why is he backing up the truck?
[crash]
- Through here!
- Hey!
Shit.
What the fuck?
We gotta go out there.
You better throw that bullshit
right out of your head.
I'm not going back out there.
That's not part of the plan.
Change of plan.
I'm gonna open the door.
- No.
- Okay.
One, two...
- Don't do it, man.
- ...three.
Come on, man.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
[growling]
- [Andre] Shoot 'em in the head!
- [gunshot]
I don't see anybody.
- Get back inside. They're fine!
- Get back inside!
Here you go.
There are six more people
inside the truck!
- Andre, look!
- [growling]
[gun clicks]
[moaning]
[woman] Thank God.
I couldn't stay
in that fucking truck anymore.
[Ana] All right, anybody
who's injured,
let's get you into Metropolis,
right away,
I'll take a look at you.
Let me take a look at her.
Can you help me...
What's your name? Sorry.
Uh, Glen. Yeah, sure.
Just give me a second
to collect myself, okay?
- Thanks.
- [Ana] Okay.
If you want to wait for me
in there,
I'll take a look at your leg.
Can you hold this?
Yeah. We're just going
right there.
Oh, my arm.
It's okay, ma'am. We'll make you
nice and comfortable.
The rest of you, we've got
plenty of food and water.
- Help should be along soon.
- [chuckles]
Help? Did you hear that
from the same jackass
who told us
to go to St. Verbena?
- The church downtown?
- Yeah.
It's the first place I went.
Some dipshit on the radio
said it was safe there.
He was wrong.
Is that where
you picked them up?
Well, I got this call on the CB
from that guy Glen,
saying all these folks
were in the chapel.
He's a priest?
No, he plays the organ.
I was in the neighborhood
so I picked them up.
Well done.
Thanks.
Hey, I'm sorry, excuse me,
when you two fellows
are done blowing each other,
maybe Davy Crockett
can tell us the deal here.
Well, we haven't heard much
since the TVs went down...
- Excuse me. Whose rig is that?
- It's mine.
- You mind if I borrow it?
- I'm not using it, officer.
- Keys?
- They're in the cab.
The truck's not gonna make it
to Fort Pastor.
No, forget the truck.
That place is fucked, man.
Bloodbath city.
How do you know?
We just came from there.
Is everyone there dead?
Dead-ish.
Yeah. In the sense
that they all...
sort of fell down and then...
- I'll look for myself.
- You're not gonna make it.
- ...got up and...
- I'll get as far as I can.
Right now it's about one foot...
...started eating each other.
- I'll take my chances.
- Don't be an idiot.
Please. There's people here
right now could use your help.
Fuck y'all.
It's nice to see that you've all
bonded through this disaster.
[distant growling]
[chuckles]
Hey. You, uh, need anything?
No, we're fine.
Don't worry about us.
He's got a bite on his hand.
Yeah.
- She's cold.
- [labored breathing]
That's good, right?
- [moaning]
- I don't know. It's weird.
I've never seen an infection
this bad
that didn't come with a fever.
That guy's arm looks
pretty bad over there.
You should probably
check it out.
All right.
Stay with her for a minute.
Here, let me take
a look at that.
I'm fine, really.
They don't hurt much at all.
Tucker could use you
more than I could.
His ankle's cut pretty bad.
I'm just gonna
clean it up a bit.
[Terry] You okay?
Ma'am, can I get you something?
Like a glass of water?
[deep gasps]
Ana! Ana, come here!
Anyone know her name?
Died without a name?
Damn.
Guys, do you wanna move
into the other room?
Holy shit!
[screams]
[thud]
[gasping]
Holy shit.
I think it's the bites.
Frank said she was
walking on her own
when she got in the truck
five hours ago.
The bites killed her.
The bites brought her back.
How do you know?
I watched it happen.
I felt her pulse, she was gone.
Then...
Yesterday I saw
the same thing to somebody else.
I think that's why
it spread so fast.
All right.
So who else
in the group is bitten?
Frank for sure.
What about the one
with the foot?
Tucker? He says no, he fell.
So it's Frank. Tall guy, right?
Right. So we have to
quarantine him
right away.
Where exactly do we do that?
I don't know. There must be
some place to keep him in here.
Then what?
I don't know. But...
It's too dangerous
to keep him around here.
I'm sorry,
what are we talking about here?
Are we talking about
killing him?
Would you rather we waited
for him to die
and then he tries to kill us?
Yes. No. You can't kill him.
- Ana...
- He's got a daughter!
I'm sorry.
I don't think there's
any other choice.
He's right.
You can't do this.
What if I'm wrong?
You've seen it happen before.
Frank?
Michael's coming to shoot you.
What are you talking about?
You're infected.
You're going to become
one of them.
[Frank] Is this true?
Are you here to kill me?
You've been bitten.
It's only a matter of time.
No. No. No.
Leave my dad alone. Go away.
You can't do this.
You have to understand
that she's lost everyone.
Her mother,
her two brothers.
[sobbing]
I'm all she's got.
Well, Michael,
what are you waiting for?
[Frank's daughter sobbing]
Go ahead. Kill him.
Hey, kill Tucker, too.
Wait a minute. I was never bit.
We can't be sure.
Do it, Michael.
Are you sure it's the bite?
No.
She's sure.
I'm sorry.
[clicks teeth]
- Hey.
- Hi.
Are you okay?
Mm.
Let me see your arm.
It hurts.
It's already starting to heal.
Andre, I can't have baby here.
Why not?
People have been having babies
for millions of years,
all on their own, no hospitals.
Wait.
- Oh, yeah. [chuckles]
- It's moving.
I felt it.
We gotta come up with a name
for this baby.
I want Russian name.
Don't start that again.
African name.
- Please?
- Come here and give me a hug.
[Frank] Sweetie.
I'm so proud of you.
I couldn't ask for anything more
in a daughter.
I love you.
[daughter] I love you too.
Time to go, honey.
No.
Terry, come on, man,
open the door.
Shut up.
[CJ] Come on, man,
don't tell me to shut up.
Just come open the door.
I got you this job. Come on.
You want...
every...
single second.
[sighs] Ana.
I'm glad you didn't do it.
- [howling]
- [gun blast]
["Down With the Sickness"
by Richard Cheese plays]
[zombies shouting]
- [gun blast]
- [horse howls]
- [spanking]
- [woman moans]
Fuck me harder!
[bell jingles]
[chuckles]
[CJ] Okay, here's a good one.
Top ten ingredients
to a successful relationship.
[mumbling]
All right, I'm gonna skip
to the top three.
Number three,
"He listens to me."
Number two,
"He tells me he loves me."
And number one.
Well, it's trust.
Number one is trust.
[zombies growling]
[gun blast]
[chuckling] Holy shit.
He got him.
So, who do we have next?
[man] Uh...
Yeah. Burt Reynolds.
Tell him, uh...
tell him to get Burt Reynolds.
[chuckles]
[man] My goodness.
Man, he's good.
It barely even looked like him.
Oh, oh... um...
Rosie O'Donnell.
Tell him to get Rosie.
Yeah, Rosie.
Nah, too easy.
Give him something hard.
You guys had really
rough childhoods, didn't you?
A little bit rocky?
Hey, sweetheart,
let me tell you something.
You, uh, you have my permission,
if I ever turn into
one of those things,
do me a favor,
blow my fucking head off.
Oh, yeah, you can count on that.
I guess the first time
I knew I was gay...
I was 13.
This guy...
Todd,
he was building a deck
in our backyard...
Uh, uh, Okay.
Just, please, stop.
[chuckles] I remember he had
the most astonishing blue eyes.
Oh, my God! I'm in hell.
[mock cry and scream]
- [Muzak playing]
- [laughter]
Hey, Andre, how's Luda doing?
She's fine.
Hey, where's that lemon stuff?
It's all gone.
Steve likes to put
it in his booze.
Try the vanilla stuff.
All right.
I'd like to drop by
and check on her,
and just see how she's doing.
No, thanks. She's fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
It's okay, hon. We understand.
[meows]
- Thanks.
- [giggles]
[distant growling]
And before that,
I worked in a stationery store.
And I drove a snowplow.
Fixed copiers.
God, it's such a shame
that this whole end-of-the-world
thing's holding you back.
[all laugh]
- Okay, worst job.
- Oh.
I know which job
I was the worst at.
It was being a husband.
That's not a job.
- [Michael] It sure is.
- [all chuckle]
You guys just haven't met
the right girl.
Yeah, I tried it
three times and...
I got pink slips every time.
What were you best at?
Being a dad.
I think I was best at that.
- [gasps and screams]
- [gun cocks]
- [man] Everybody calm down.
- [woman] Are they inside?
[Michael] No. Does this place
have generators?
[screaming]
Shh. Okay, shh.
Shhh. It's all right, baby.
- [screaming]
- Shh.
Baby, please.
You got to be quiet, okay?
It's gonna be all right.
Our baby is on the way.
It's coming.
That's it.
It's in employee parking
level three.
They keep them in a pen
near the parking shuttles.
Have fun.
Hey, wait a minute.
You're coming too.
No, I'm not.
I said I'd tell you
where the generators are.
I never said I'd show you.
Did you think I'd just leave you
two up here?
You come with me
or you go back in that cell.
All right.
I ain't going anywhere
without a gun.
You're not getting a gun.
Trust.
The primary ingredient
in any relationship.
Have at 'em, cowboy.
[whispering] Asshole.
Bart, get the chains.
[loud noise]
You ready to roll?
You're coming with us?
No, you're coming with me.
I've done this before.
Know how to use that?
This one's the dangerous end,
right?
Now it is.
[chuckles]
[door closes]
This is level one.
We gotta walk down to three.
[distant noise]
[distant thud]
[distant growl]
What the fuck was that?
I just saw something.
You didn't see shit, Bart.
Shut the fuck up.
[loud noise]
[distant noise]
Oh, shit. Here it comes.
[panting sound]
[panting]
Jesus Christ.
It's a fucking dog.
Come here, boy.
[whimpers]
At least we know nothing's
down here
or it would've eaten him.
See? I told you I saw something.
[dog barking]
[Michael] What's wrong, boy?
There's nothing wrong.
That dog's just fucked up.
[screaming]
[growling]
[louder growling]
Run!
Wait, CJ! Wait up! Wait!
It's locked!
It's fucking locked!
[screaming]
[Kenneth] Come on, let's go!
CJ!
I'm out!
CJ! Matches!
[howling]
[howling stops]
Breathe.
You're doing good. Breathe.
- [deep guttural breathing]
- You're doing good, baby.
I'm sorry.
[gasps]
[howling]
[baby music playing]
- Thanks.
- Okay. That's the last.
I'm gonna go check on Luda.
I haven't seen her in a while.
- I'll go.
- You sure?
Yeah. I'll take them
some candles.
Okay.
Let me know
if they need anything.
Okay. I'll have a smoke
on the way.
- See you.
- Bye.
[Luda groans]
It's coming.
I see it.
[ripping sound]
[sizzling]
[flies buzzing]
Guys?
Oh, my God.
It's a girl.
- [growling]
- [gasps]
[gasping]
You want to kill Luda?
You want to kill my family?
[Luda continues growling]
[Andre screams]
[groaning]
[groans]
Norma! Come on, Norma.
What happened?
The son of a bitch shot me.
Get away from her.
Wait. Just wait.
She died of the gunshot.
She wasn't bitten.
She's gonna wake up though,
right?
[Ana] No.
No, if she was one of them,
she'd be up by now.
[exhales deeply]
- Terry?
- [Terry] Yeah.
Hold this.
[squealing]
Oh, God.
[echoing gun blast]
Somebody should say something.
Yeah.
Glen?
No.
You worked in the church.
I played the organ.
Come on,
you must have heard the priest
say something
about life and death.
It was a job.
I don't believe in God.
I don't see how anyone could.
Somebody should say something.
There's nothing to say.
I've been to a lot of funerals.
I've folded the flag
and given it to a lot of
wives and fathers and kids,
and I told them how sorry I was.
But that's not what
I was really feeling.
In the back of my mind,
I was always saying,
"Better them than me."
But I don't believe that now.
Because now I realize
that there are some things
worse than death
and one of them is sitting here
waiting to die.
I don't want to die here.
I saw a couple of buses
in the garage.
We could fix them up,
we could reinforce them,
then get as far from here
as possible.
And then what?
Oh, I have an idea. Um...
While we're at it,
why don't we swing by the marina
and hop in my boat
and take it
for a pleasure cruise,
you jackasses.
Wait a minute.
That's a good idea.
There's islands in the lakes,
there's not a lot of people
on them.
I was kidding.
How far is the marina?
[chuckling] Oh, my God.
You're serious?
I think it's a damn good idea.
How about the rest of you?
Kenneth?
Yeah, it's a good idea.
We have to pick up Andy.
He's part of the group.
[chuckling] Excuse me.
Not to shit
on anyone's riff here
but let me see
if I grasp this concept, okay?
You're suggesting that we take
some fucking parking shuttles,
and reinforce them
with some aluminum siding
and then head over
to the gun store
where we watch
our good friend Andy
play some cowboy-movie,
jump-on-the-wagon bullshit.
Then we're gonna drive
across a ruined city
through a welcome committee
of a few hundred thousand
dead cannibals,
all so we can sail off
into the sunset
on this fucking asshole's boat?
And head for some island
that for all we know
which may not even exist?
Yeah.
Pretty much, yeah.
Okay.
I'm in.
["Hangman's Song"
by Tyler Bates playing]
We have 12 of these
shotgun shells,
twenty-six of those
pussy.9-Mils,
and 16 of those.357 Magnums.
Yeah, well,
that's still not very much,
so hopefully we'll get
to the dock
and there won't be
too many of them.
Hm.
Nice to see you busting
your ass today.
[chuckling] Oh, that's sarcasm.
That is awesome.
Yeah, you know,
I would love to help
but, uh...
a captain never works
alongside his men.
[mimics whip sound]
You guys have a good one.
What a total dick.
Guys, where did Chips go?
Chips?
Where'd you go, Chips?
I can't find him. Chips?
Come here. Come on, Chips!
- [mockingly] "Come on, Chips!"
- [woman] Where'd you go, honey?
- Come on, boy.
- [whistles]
- [barks]
- [gasps]
Oh, there you are. Come on.
There's my boy. Don't you
ever leave me again, okay?
Ever, ever.
Hey. Kenneth wants everyone
upstairs for a meeting.
Come in here first.
I want you to see this.
When those things
are on the side of the bus,
this'll get them off.
Cool, huh?
Wow.
That might be
the most romantic thing
anyone's ever shown me.
[Michael chuckles]
I'm trying here.
Yeah, I know.
It's not just about
him starving, Steve.
If we go to pick him up and
he doesn't have his strength,
then we're gonna be
carrying him. It's...
She's right.
[man] He's a hell of a shot too.
We're gonna need him.
I'm not saying
we don't need him.
There's no point
in arguing about this.
We need a solution.
We need to get some food
over there.
I have an idea.
We draw straws and the loser
runs across with a ham sandwich.
[mock laughter]
[Ana] Could you be
a bigger prick?
I think so
but that's irrelevant.
My question to you is
what's your plan?
Come on!
- [whistles]
- [overlapping chatter]
I got it.
We've got to get over there
anyway...
- Shut up!
- ...more ammunition, all right?
I have an idea.
Stop, it's hurting him!
No! He's not safe!
Nicole, they're not interested
in him, I promise.
Okay, they want us, okay?
Chips is gonna be fine.
- [barking]
- [zombies growling]
[whistling]
See? Look, he's walking
right by them.
They're not even
paying attention to him.
[Kenneth] The walkie's
in the bag?
[man] Yeah.
Let me see. Let me see!
[Andy blows whistle]
- [Chips barks]
- [Nicole] There he is.
Good boy. Good boy, Chips.
- Okay, he's there, he's in.
- Give me those.
Oh, man.
- What? What?
- No.
No. Oh, man. They got him.
They got him!
[gunfire]
I'll try him on the radio.
Andy. Andy, do you copy?
Andy, can you hear me?
Andy?
[Andy] Can you hear me? Hello?
This thing working?
I'm dinged up pretty bad
but I think I'm gonna be okay.
Where are you hurt, Andy?
Goddamn,
those bastards bite hard.
I just have to stop
the bleeding.
- It's really going.
- [Chips barks]
Easy, boy. Easy. Is this Ken?
Is that you, man?
Yeah, it's me, brother.
Hey, man,
good to hear your voice.
I guess we're gonna meet
up-close pretty soon, huh?
Oh, shit, hang on.
Ah, Jesus. He got me good.
You just hang in there.
- You got the food, right?
- [Andy] Yeah.
- Do we tell him?
- [Chips barks]
[Andy] Hey, this dog got a name?
- See, Nicole, Chips... Nicole?
- [tires screeching]
What the hell's that?
Oh, my God, it's Nicole!
[tires screeching]
Shit.
That idiot's going after
the fucking dog.
She made it! She's in!
[Nicole] Guys, I found Chips!
I got him. He's okay!
Nicole, how's Andy looking?
[Nicole] I don't know.
There's a lot of blood in here.
It's everywhere!
There's blood everywhere!
Wait a minute, I see him.
He's on the roof.
He's writing something.
What's it say?
[Nicole] Guys?
Tell her to get out!
- [Nicole] Guys?
- What's wrong?
Nicole, baby, how's the truck?
[Nicole] I'm not going back
out there.
- [Chips barks]
- [Nicole] Chips, be quiet!
Tell her to get
the hell out now!
Honey, listen to me.
You need to find
a place to hide.
Can you do that?
[Nicole] What do you mean?
What's going on?
- Nicole?
- [Nicole] Here's Andy.
- [growling]
- [Nicole] Oh, my God!
No! Tell her to get out!
Nicole, listen to me.
[Nicole sobbing] I'm in a closet
but he's outside,
he's trying to get...
[Michael] Nicole? Nicole?
[Nicole] Help me.
Please, you have to help me!
I'm gonna die!
[static noise]
We need to do something. Now.
Tucker, listen, when we
come back through here
we may have company.
You need to stay here
and make sure
that fire door stays open.
Wait, wait. I'm sorry. Uh...
Why does he stay here
while I go
on the suicide mission
to rescue Terry's already
dead girlfriend?
Fuck you, man.
We don't know that.
Either way,
we've gotta get over there
and get the guns
to get out of this parking lot.
Michael, it's okay.
- Let him stay.
- Yeah.
Steve, don't fuck this up.
Yeah. Totally.
[rats squeaking]
[CJ] All right.
That's it.
[Michael] Are you sure?
I ain't a plumber but I'd say
we're at the end of the line.
[zombies moaning]
[distant growling]
[pounding]
[growling]
Go! Go!
Through here!
Hurry up!
[Ana] Hurry up! Hurry!
.357,.357. What do you need?
.38,.38. Here.
- [Ana] Damn it.
- [Michael] Hurry up.
All right.
Oh, shit.
- Nicole?
- [pounding]
[growling]
- Andy.
- [growls]
- I'm sorry, brother.
[Andy stops growling]
[thud]
[Michael]
Nicole, are you in there?
[Nicole] I'm here! I'm here!
[Chips whimpers]
[Kenneth]
Get as much ammo as you can.
You got a plan?
Uh-uh. You?
How about a barbecue?
[zombies growling]
[pounding]
How do we know if he hits it?
[loud blast]
[man] CJ! Over here, hurry up!
Over here!
Go! Get down! Look out!
Come on, Tucker! Come on!
- Shit!
- [screams]
- Ah, my leg!
- I got you, Tucker.
Go! Go!
[zombie growls]
Shit!
Go!
[screams]
Shoot me! Shoot me!
- [Nicole] Hurry! Come on!
- [Chips barks]
Hurry, hurry!
Goddamn Steve Markus!
- [Nicole] Steve, come on!
- Open up!
[Nicole] Open the door!
Open the door!
- [Michael] Steve!
- I'll fucking kill him!
[growling]
[Michael] Steve!
Let's go!
[screeching]
God damn it!
[Kenneth] Move!
- Go!
- Move it, guys, move it!
[woman]
Where are you guys going?
- Just go right now! We're going!
- Go! Go!
They're right behind us! Go! Go!
Go!
[growling]
Come on, move!
They're right behind us!
Get in!
[man] Close the door!
[Muzak plays]
I like this song.
[Chips barks]
Everybody in!
Hey, there you are.
What the hell
happened to you guys?
Prick.
I'll deal with you later,
motherfucker!
Wait a minute! Nicole!
Get in!
I'll take the gun.
Okay.
Okay, let's get out of here!
Hold on!
Oh, Christ!
CJ, now! Go!
[growling]
They're trying to turn us over!
Hit 'em with the saw!
- [chainsaw buzzes]
- [shrieking]
[screams]
[CJ] Give me a shotgun!
Holy shit.
There's still one hanging on.
Which fucking side?
Right side!
- I got him.
- [chainsaw buzzes]
- You gotta drive faster, man.
- [growling]
Hard left! Hard left here!
[screaming]
Whoa, stop! Stop, guys!
- What?
- We lost them.
Back it up! Back it up! Back up!
Kenneth, are you there? Kenneth?
[coughing]
[Ana] Kenneth, are you there?
Kenneth, are you okay?
What the fuck?
- [growling]
- [screaming]
What are you doing?
Fucking nursery school.
CJ!
Ana, no! Everyone's dead.
Steve took off.
What?
[CJ] Let's go! Come on!
Steve!
- [howling]
- I got him.
Damn.
[growling]
Look out!
Come on, come on!
Go, go, go!
- [gun blast]
- Open the door!
- Hurry up!
- Come on!
Guys, get in!
Let's go.
Where's Ana? Ana!
Ana!
- Get in! Get in!
- [Ana screams]
- What the hell were you doing?
- [truck engine starts]
[engine revs]
[Chips barks]
Hold on!
- Come on, boy.
- Go.
Kenneth! Here.
Get out on the end of the dock.
- [Kenneth] CJ, come on.
- Do it! I'll catch up!
There it is!
Terry, get the bowline!
- [cocks gun]
- Shit.
CJ!
Damn! Fuck!
Come on!
Bitch! Shit.
Come on.
I'll blow every
fucking thing up.
[approaching growls]
Okay, let's go, let's go.
- I can't go.
- What?
Downtown when they jumped
on us.
Oh, no, Michael. No.
I have to stay here.
You can't. No, you...
I'm sorry, Ana.
- I can help you.
- No, you can't.
You can help them.
Stay on the boat.
I can help you.
It's okay.
It's gonna be all right.
No.
It won't.
Hey.
It will.
You sure you wanna do this?
Yeah.
I think I'll just stay here
a while.
Enjoy the sunrise.
[boat engine starts]
[gun blast]
["People Who Died" by
The Jim Carroll Band playing]
I run a tight ship.
- Where did you get that thing?
- [Terry] I found Steve's camera.
[chuckling]
Put that down and help us.
- [Terry screams]
- [growling]
[Terry]
Kenneth, fucking shoot it!
[Terry] Christ!
[Terry] Oh, shit!
Get your damn camera
out my face.
...like there's anyone there.
Terry, put the camera down
and help us off the boat.
- [Chips whimpers]
- [Terry] Nicole, what is it?
[Nicole] Chips, no!
[Chips barks]
[approaching growls]
[Terry] Oh, shit!
[Kenneth] Stay behind me!
- [growling]
- [gunfire]
["Down with the Sickness"
by Disturbed playing]