Okay. So,
Mr. "Hey, sweetie pie,"
is from Denver.
Some kind of salesman.
His name's
on his shirt.
Is Tamara here?
Please.
I have a family.
No. I beg you, please.
Help me, please.
No.
Maya?
You're at Venus
County Hospital.
I'm Nurse Danica.
I'm Dr. Tate.
Ryan? Ryan? Where's Ryan?
I'm so sorry.
He didn't make it.
Unfortunately,
he'd lost too much blood.
Ryan.
There were
three of them.
Two were like, um...
doll masks?
Did you
and your boyfriend see...
Fiance.
Did you or your fiance
see anything else?
You almost died.
Maybe your memory's
just a little bit fogged up.
They had a truck.
A red truck.
I felt like they liked it.
Like they enjoyed it.
It was some kind of ritual.
Has this happened before?
Well, there's been...
Tommy.
Is there anything else
you can remember?
Tamara.
They were asking
about a girl named Tamara.
Who's Tamara?
Dr. Tate says time
to wrap it up, Sheriff.
Doc knows best, huh?
Don't worry.
We'll find these killers.
You boys are awful quiet.
I'm not getting into it,
Carol.
Come on, Sheriff.
We all want to hear
what you know
about who killed
that young couple.
The girl didn't die.
Oh, I heard they both died,
that they left
this world together.
Nope.
She's gonna be okay.
You want to hear my theory?
She did it.
The girl.
Probably for some
big insurance money.
Gorgeous hair,
but a dark heart.
Well...
sounds like you done cracked
the case, Jazz.
I'm just saying.
You never know
what a killer looks like.
Is Sally there?
Can I come in?
Got your ball.
Go fetch.
Come on.
Do you want
to play cards?
I have an idea.
Why don't I play you
your favorite song?
Maya?
It's me, Nurse Danica.
I have your pain meds.
Thanks.
Here you go.
That's it.
How you feeling?
I'm okay.
Who's Tamara?
I didn't really know her.
Just the story.
It's just an old ghost story
that people tell here.
Try not to think
about that, okay?
Get some rest.
Hi, Maya.
I knew you wouldn't leave me.
Never.
Hey, I'm so sorry
we're stuck here.
I want to get you
out of there.
We are working
on a private EMT,
hopefully today,
which will pick you up
and take you
to Portland Hospital.
Howard and I
will meet you there.
I love you so much.
We'll be there soon.
It's gonna be okay. Okay. Bye.
Debbie?
Hello?
Is Tamara here?
Who the fuck are you?
Shit!
Help!
Fuck you!
Get off!
Shit.
Fuck.
No.
Shit!
Fuck!
Please. Please...
Freeze.
Please.
Please, I just need
to use your phone
to call the police. Please.
-There are people trying to...
-Sheriff ain't gonna help ya.
Why?
Because he...
Shit!
Oh, shit!
Open the...
Maya?
Here. Put this on.
That's Chris' jacket.
It's warm.
She's ex-military.
Three years in the service.
Look, Maya. I'm really worried
about your stitches.
If your wound opens up,
you could lose
a lot of blood and die.
Please.
Please. Just drive.
Please, just drive. Please.
What are you doing?
Open the door! Open it.
Let me out!
Let me out of here!
-Maya?
-Let me out of here!
-Maya!
You said you would help me!
-I am helping you.
-Let me out!
-Open it!
-Maya. Maya. Maya.
Let's take her
back to the house.
-Let me out!
-Maya!
Let me the fuck out!
Open the fucking door!
-Calm down.
-Let me out!
-Okay, calm down!
-Hey!
Let me
the fuck out of here!
Hey. Hey! Hey, hey!
Relax! Relax! Calm down.
Relax.
I'll take you back
to our house. Okay?
It's safe. I promise.
Look. I'll clean your wound
and we'll figure out
the rest tomorrow. Okay?
Okay. Your house.
Now,
look to the Lord and unto me.
We will serve the Lord.
Depart from Satan.
Refuse to give in to him
by standing strong
in thy faith.
The scripture says
when we see evil...
Oh, gosh,
she's fucked up.
Is that...
What the fuck
are they doing here?
...for human nature.
Because human nature
is wicked.
Human nature is evil.
There's a reason
it needs rebirth,
it needs redemption.
The devil came to Eve
in the Garden of Eden.
He came and whispered
in her ear
through the serpent and said,
"Come with me.
I will show you the way."
That's the way to Hell.
Jesus told her of the danger
of the hellfire.
Maya, meet
our idiot roommates.
-Gregory.
-Wayne.
Why are you two walking
down in the middle of the road
in a rainstorm?
Where's your truck?
Perry's bar.
Dickstain here
forgot the keys,
and by the time
he realized it,
Perry locked
the fuckin' place up.
So you're the one
everybody's talking about?
He says,
"Depart from me, you cursed,
"into everlasting fire
prepared for the devil,
"and his angels."
So there,
in the great book of Matthew,
Jesus' words call out
about the end, about evil.
His eyes watch in secret
for his victims.
He lies in wait
to catch the innocent.
He catches them
and drags them off in his net.
Turn away from this Satan!
Repent for your sins.
I'm searching
for the way of life
and the way of death.
The way of Heaven
or the way of Hell.
The way of light...
...or eternal fire.
Which way are you on?
What the fuck
are you looking at?
Jesus said,
"I am the way.
I am the only way."
Behold, open your soul
and receive Christ.
Don't come to this place.
Break thou the arm
of the wicked
and the evil man.
Jesus said, "I call Heaven
and Earth to record..."
"I've set before thee
life and death."
"Blessing and cursing."
Telling us there shall be
great tribulations
such as was not since
the beginning of the world
to this time
nor will ever be again.
Except those days
should be shortened.
There should be no man saved
but for the sake of the world,
of all mankind.
Those days will be shortened.
All you have to do
is pick up the phone,
and call the number
you see on your TV.
And talk with you
about this wonderful decision.
The decision to take the Lord
into your heart today.
-What the...
-Maya!
Maya!
Come back!
Maya,
what are you doing?
What the hell's
wrong with you?
Come back in the car.
If we don't
find anything here,
let's go back to the station.
Yeah, sounds good.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Fuck! Please.
Oh, my God. Fuck!
Hey, no, wait. No, wait.
I taught them to come to me.
Gotta put it
right up to his nose.
Yeah, like that.
I'm gonna teach the boars
to do lots of things.
Yeah, I think you will.
Ow. Ow. My ankle.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Just a little dust.
It doesn't look too bad.
See?
Here. Let me help you up.
Thanks, Jimbo.
Crew finished
searching the woods.
Jesus, Tommy,
keep your voice down.
Maya ain't in the woods.
-She's a missing person.
-Correction.
Her whereabouts are unknown.
She's not an MP
for another 24 hours.
Look, maybe...
maybe we should
call in the State, the FBI.
Calling in the cavalry
doesn't end well
for guys like you and me.
They'll second-guess
everything.
Open up our files.
You want the Feds looking
into why you didn't
press charges
against the widow
Saunders now?
Man, me and her
didn't start up.
Mmm.
What the fuck!
Jesus.
I'm not gonna hurt ya.
I'm here because
of the lack of response
by the sheriff's department
to all the murders
in the area.
You must be Maya.
Are you okay?
Do I look okay?
No.
Maya, I'm here to help.
Billy Buford, Oregon State
Police Internal Affairs.
-Do you have a car?
-Yeah, it's outside.
Get me the fuck out of here.
Okay.
Nice and easy.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. Thank you.
Fuck! Fuck!
What the fuck?
Fuck!
Fuck. Okay.
Help. Is anybody home?
Please, help me.
Help me, please.
God.
We are evil.
It warns us that
you shall be driven mad
by the sight of what you see.
The most evil of this world.
"The sins of my mother
conceived me,"
David said.
We are all sinners
and we were born in sin.
And then when we grow up,
we make the choice to sin.
The Bible tells us that
there's a burning Hell
in the human heart.
And that people who seem to be
good and wholesome in time
may be changed
into vicious killers,
into murderous maniacs
just like that.
We all know
the story of a woman.
A good woman.
A beautiful woman
whose husband was...
You're out of the woods.
Congratulations.
...hardly
any reason at all,
while he was asleep,
she shot him, killed him dead.
How do you like my tattoo?
Um... I...
You don't like it?
I knew you were gonna have
a tough time making friends
around here.
A lot of us have the same one.
Got it on a teen church trip
a few years back.
You know how teens are...
the sex and the...
the booze.
Cheap tattoos.
That's cool.
Excuse me.
Stuff didn't
line up earlier, but...
No, I don't know.
You're up.
Leave her alone,
Gregory.
I'm not doing nothing,
I'm just...
welcoming our guest.
She's all yours.
Fuck!
Look, don't take it
personally, okay?
-He's like that to everyone.
-Arrogant prick.
Grandparents left him money
and an old sailboat.
Still has the sailboat.
And he still acts
like he owns the town.
He's harmless, though.
Girl, I have done
some crazy shit in my life,
but jumping out
a moving car...
It's suicidal.
Look, you're lucky
to still be in one piece.
Let's get you back to bed.
So you can rest.
It's your phone.
I rescued it from
the hospital's lost and found.
Hello?
Excuse me?
I need to get some gas.
Shit!
You scared me.
I'll turn on the pump.
Hey, Gander Street
is which way from here?
You going to the lake house?
Uh-huh.
What for?
Picking someone up.
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah...
Just the gas, then.
You were, uh...
you were stabbed in the...
stomach, right?
Did you think
you were gonna die?
What were you thinking about?
Time.
How slowly it was moving.
How fast it all felt.
How little I had left.
What'd you want
to do about it?
In that moment,
I would have done anything...
to kill him.
Pretty lucky.
Am I?
Yeah.
This shit's been, uh...
it's been going on for years.
You're the only one
that survived.
How many others?
Ten? Fifteen?
Does it matter?
Why?
Does there have to be a why?
Gregory? Gregory?
Damn. Bitch.
Fuck.
-Gregory.
-God, leave me alone.
Don't just
walk away from me.
I'm trying to talk to you.
Why are you harassing her?
Go back in the house
and yell at me,
-I'll let you...
-You're hammered.
You're drunk.
Good observation.
Where are you going?
You can't drive.
Just listen to me.
I told you to leave her alone,
why don't you
just leave her alone?
Get out
of my fucking face.
Calm down.
Get the fuck
out of the way!
Fuck.
♪ Rock-a-bye baby
♪ On the treetop
♪ When the wind blows
The cradle will rock
♪ When the bough breaks
The cradle will fall ♪
Jesus Christ.
Drive. Drive, drive. Drive.
'Cause you're here.
Come get me.
Is Tamara here?
Wait. Do it again.
I'm waiting.
Is Tamara here?
Look like
you've been through hell.
I know where they are.
Where are they?
No, no! No! Stop!
Stop! No! No! No!
See you soon.